Jack, this is hard for me.
The Chinese have proof
that you led the assault on their consul.
- And now the Chinese want me?
- That's right.
The man they sent to take you
into custody has orders to kill you.
- Orders from who?
- Someone in Logan's camp.
Dale Spaulding, Secret Service.
I've orders to take Jack Bauer into custody.
I intend to execute those orders.
Jack.
He's dead.
I'm sorry.
Oh, God, Jack.
Give me the epinephrine.
I hope it's not too late.
Come on, Jack.
Come on, Jack. Dammit!
Hey.
Chloe, run interference with the local coroner.
Sync up their database
with Jack's information.
- That won't cover the autopsy.
- There won't be one.
They wanted Jack dead. Now he's dead.
Mr. President, you saved my life.
I'm only sorry it came to this.
- I just wanted to let you know that I was out.
- I'm glad.
Jack, you do understand, when you hang up,
for all intents and purposes,
Jack Bauer is dead.
I understand that, sir.
Mr. President, it's been an honour.
Jim Nichols. You're on pump number one.
Sterling Rush, Patrick Priest,
you're on pump number four.
Phil Stone, Greg Nelson, you're on pump five.
Sorry, guys. That's all I got today.
Frank. I know I promised you work today,
but pump seven went off line last night.
- I'll try again tomorrow.
- Tomorrow'll be much better.
See you tomorrow.
The sun is shining, but the air is cool
at President Logan's retreat,
where Russian president Yuri Suvarov
is expected later this morning.
Everything worked for me
up until the chapter on your first campaign.
It's a little long-winded,
and I think that we can cut that down by half.
Why don't we start with the paragraph...
You didn't hear a word I just said, did you?
- Yeah. I was listening.
- No, you weren't.
You're right.
- I'm sorry.
- Are you OK?
I can use a break.
- What's going on?
- What do you mean?
I mean you've been distracted
ever since you got to Los Angeles.
I don't know - it's like you're somewhere else.
Writing my memoirs,
maybe it's put me in a melancholy mood.
Is that all it is?
Yeah.
David, I'm your brother.
Whatever it is, you can tell me.
It's all right. Really.
OK.
Well, then, let's get back to work.
One more chapter and we'll take a break.
Why don't we jump down to, um, chapter six?
There'll be questions
about your relationship with Sherry.
David.
Get help!
Stay with me. Stay with me. Get help!
Walt. My chair?
- Mr. President. I had it adjusted.
- Good.
- Adjusted? What are we talking about?
Suvarov is over six feet.
He can't be looking down
at the president of the US.
That's a risky proposition.
If the press finds out...
- They won't.
- Don't underestimate the power of image.
Stalin and Churchill,
they both sat for FDR at Yalta.
This will define my administration. We have
to make sure that the media presents it right.
I'll get it.
- Yeah?
- Greg Porter for you.
Put him through.
- Have you checked on my wife?
- She's still getting ready.
She'll be fine, sir. I'm in contact with Dr Hill.
I'd feel better
if you would check on her yourself.
She cannot have one of her meltdowns today.
You're the only one she listens to, Walt.
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
Mike?
Mike, what is it?
David Palmer has been assassinated.
- What?
- It just happened.
Oh, my God.
- Where?
- In LA.
I don't believe this.
Mr. President,
CTU is standing by to brief you directly.
Whenever you're ready.
- Tell LAPD to set up a perimeter.
- They're sending everyone.
- Witnesses?
- Not yet.
- Who's running search and sweep?
- Secret Service.
Narrow the area. Make sure
Ballistics runs a line-of-fire trajectory.
- Sir, President Logan's ready.
- I'll call Ballistics.
- Put the president through.
- Yes, sir. Go ahead.
- Mr. President.
- Bill.
Not to diminish the loss we're all feeling, but
I am expecting the Russian president soon,
so let's say what needs to be said.
- Of course.
- Have you arrested the person who did this?
- Not yet, sir.
- Then what do you have?
The damage inflicted
by the single shot indicates
that Palmer was hit by a. 308-calibre bullet
fired from an adjacent building.
We've initiated an interagency protocol...
Don't... don't give me protocols, Bill.
Give me results.
Whoever did this, I want them dead
or in custody when the Russians get here.
Until we know more, I would ask that you
consider postponing the signing of the treaty.
No. Absolutely not.
We can't discount the possibility that this
attack is connected to the arms agreement.
A former president was assassinated
15 miles from where you are,
and I'm sure I don't need to explain
the significance of this day.
Do you realise the political capital I've spent
just to get the Russians to the table?
If we call this off, they won't come back.
Spenser.
- Spenser!
- What?
- Get out of my bed.
- Yeah.
I had a good time last night, too.
This was a mistake. Get outta here.
What do you mean, "a mistake"?
We had a great time.
I don't get involved
with people who work for me.
- It's too late for that.
- Don't tell everybody at work about this.
I don't want everyone thinking I'm a slut.
Believe me - no one's ever gonna think that.
What's that supposed to mean?
You should lighten up, you know?
You'll live longer.
- What are you doing?
- When you quit overanalysing it,
I think you're gonna find out
that you and I are pretty good together.
So I'm telling you in advance - yes.
Yes what?
I'll let you buy me dinner,
get me drunk, have your way with me.
Any time you want.
You know, um, arrogance doesn't turn me on.
I've read that some women respond to it,
but I'm just letting you know I don't.
- What is it?
- President Palmer's been shot.
He's dead.
...first comment since the death
of the former president.
Security is at the highest level
at President Logan's retreat.
To repeat what we know up to this point-
President David Palmer
was assassinated in Los Angeles.
The former president was in the penthouse
apartment of his brother, Wayne Palmer,
when a single bullet was fired from
another high-rise building across the street.
- President Palmer was...
- Who is it?
It's me, Frank.
Hey.
I saw your truck. I thought you were on today.
Ned didn't need me this morning.
It's so terrible what happened.
Are you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine.
- Come on. I'm making breakfast.
- OK.
- Frank's gonna join us.
- Great.
Derek, stop it.
Morning.
Use a glass, please.
Here.
Excuse me.
- Can I ask you something, Frank?
- Yeah, sure.
That rig in Alaska you worked on.
What was that called again?
The Albatross.
And you were there last year?
- Yeah. Why?
- That's funny.
My friend's brother has worked on that rig for
five years. He's never heard of Frank Flynn.
- It's a big platform.
- He says everyone knows everyone.
- What is this? An interrogation?
- I just don't like being lied to.
- Derek.
- It's all right.
- No one's lying to you, Derek.
- Really?
- A lot of the guys just use nicknames.
- Yeah.
What's your friend's brother's name?
- Eat your breakfast.
- I'm not hungry.
Sorry. He's just kind of protective of me.
It's the best thing in the world for him
to have a man around here.
- What he said about me and Alaska...
- You don't owe me an explanation.
I figure if you had wanted to tell me about
your past you would have told me already.
I trust my instincts.
And I trust you.
Former president David Palmer
was killed just a short while ago.
No information has been released,
but an independent source has verified
that Palmer was in Los Angeles
visiting his brother...
- Bill will call if he needs us, you know that.
- No, he won't.
Come on. It's not our job.
- Not any more.
- This is different.
Come on, Michelle.
I'm just as upset as you are.
But there are other people at CTU
can handle this.
No one who was active
during the other attempts on his life.
Tony, you and I worked up suspect profiles.
We ran scenarios.
- And they have our records on file.
- They don't have our experience.
I never once regretted our decision
to leave CTU.
But I don't want to look back on today
and realise I could have helped.
We're running a business here. Rick Rosen's
expecting our presentation in an hour.
You can handle the meeting on your own.
Michelle.
Don't do this.
- It's Rick. Leave me a message.
- Rick, it's Tony Almeida.
I wanted to let you know
that Michelle can't make our meeting.
She had to go someplace.
On second thought, I'm going with her.
Michelle!
- Did Jepson brief you?
- A car bombing. Two former agents were hit.
Their names were Michelle Dessler
and Tony Almeida.
- You knew them?
- Yeah.
We're looking for a connection
between them and Palmer.
- I sent the parameters to your screen.
- I'll get on it.
- Yeah?
- Are you coming in?
I just got paged on a level-five protocol.
Of course I'm coming in.
- I wanted to give you a heads-up.
- "Heads-up"?
- It's bad, Chloe.
- President Palmer was gunned down.
- It's not just him.
- What are you talking about?
Someone planted a bomb
in Michelle Dessler's car.
- What?
- Michelle's dead.
Tony's not doing too good.
Doesn't make any sense. They were retired.
Buchanan thinks it's linked to Palmer.
We're cross-referencing Palmer with Tony
and Michelle, see if we can find a connection.
Anything they may have had in common.
Chloe.
Go.
- Chloe.
- I'll call you back.
- Why?
- Call you back!
Chloe.
Hey!
Since I don't have work,
I can take care of the fence.
That'd be great. I can't thank you enough
for all the work you've done around here.
Least I could do.
Excuse me. Yeah.
Jack, I know this isn't protocol.
Please don't hang up on me. I need your help.
Hold on. I can barely hear you.
I don't have a very good signal. Excuse me.
- What?
- They got Tony and Michelle. She's dead.
Tony's critical. They're gonna kill me.
- What?
- There's four people know you're alive.
Three are down. I'm the only one left. This has
to be about you. It's all we have in common.
- What happened to Tony and Michelle?
- There was a car bomb.
There was a guy outside my apartment.
He was chasing me.
Oh, my God. Where is he now?
I think I lost him. I'm at a payphone, I dumped
my cellphone. I don't know what to do.
Chloe, you need to go dark.
That means zero contact with anyone.
- Even CTU?
- Especially CTU.
Whoever's behind this
is probably monitoring them.
Someone knows I'm still alive.
- Who?
- That's what we need to find out.
Head north out of Los Angeles.
There's an abandoned oil refinery
at Variel and Topanga.
Wait for me there. Take cover by the large
storage tanks at the north end of the field.
- You're coming to LA?
- Half an hour.
OK. Thanks.
Tony Almeida is being medevacked in. I have
a trauma team standing by to receive him.
- You're bringing him to CTU?
- We can't protect him in a hospital.
Michelle and Tony have been inactive
for over a year. Who would want them dead?
- Whoever wanted Palmer dead.
- We're assuming they're connected.
The timing was too close
to write it off as a coincidence.
There is a connection. Let's find it.
Sir. The DOD liaison is here. I need to
set her up with the protocols for the summit.
I'll take care of it. You have your assignments.
Send updates directly to my screen.
- Where is she?
- She just cleared security.
- Audrey.
- Bill.
- It must be hard for you to be back here.
- Thank you, Bill. I'm fine.
I'm sorry about Michelle.
Cummings briefed me. He said you wanted
to postpone the signing of the treaty.
President Logan is making a mistake.
- I don't disagree.
- Have you let him know that?
- He's the president, Bill. It's his call.
- That's what I'm afraid of.
He wants me to make sure that your
top priority is still security for the summit.
Station five is set up for you.
We'll go over the revised security protocol.
Great. Thank you, Bill.
David Palmer was a man of truth,
and of honour.
And his influence will be felt
for generations to come.
Our nation grieves for its loss.
Martha and I offer our deepest sympathy.
You look beautiful, Mrs. Logan.
I look like a wedding cake.
Let's start over.
Oh, you can get that.
- Is Mrs. Logan ready?
- Not quite.
- You didn't tell her about David Palmer?
- No.
Thank you. She'll take it hard when she finds
out. They've been friends for a long time.
You don't have to talk about me
like I'm not here.
Excuse us, Evelyn.
- Martha.
- Oh.
Walt, I'm sorry. I know I'm late.
I'm sorry. I'm just having a bad hair day.
Martha. I've got some very bad news.
It...
- It's not Charles, is it?
- No. No, he's fine.
He wanted to tell you himself.
Wh... what?
Walt. Walt.
What... what is it?
David Palmer was assassinated.
No.
I'm sorry.
- I know how close you were.
- When did this happen?
- Less than an hour ago.
- This morning?
- Yes.
- I...
I... I have to talk to Charles.
He's doing damage control.
Keeping this off the front page.
- No. I have to talk to him now. No!
- He's doing a press conference. Martha!
Martha!
Agent North. Call John. Tell him
not to let Mrs. Logan anywhere near the stage.
Yeah.
As I look back
upon the deeds of David Palmer -
not only one of this country's great leaders,
but one of this world's great men...
- Mrs. Logan.
- Let go of me. Let go of me. Let go!
...President Palmer's entire family.
To them, I also pledge
the full resources of this great nation
to find and to punish those responsible.
- I can't let you go out there.
- Don't touch me.
Get away from me, or I will have your family
eating dog food out of a can.
- Martha, stop.
- Mike, dammit, I am the first lady.
Tell your stormtrooper to stay away from me.
- I need to talk to my husband.
- He's in the middle of a press conference.
Hundreds of millions of people
are watching him, live.
What is it, Martha? What is so urgent?
I mean, maybe I can help.
Yuri Suvarov and I will sign a treaty
that promises a new level of cooperation
between us and our Russian friends.
Tell Charles I want to see him
when he's done.
All right.
- Don't shoot me.
- What are you doing here?
I'm sorry I followed you.
I'm just... I'm just worried about my mother.
Get up. Get up. Get up!
Dammit! Come here. You're going with me.
This is none of my business.
I won't tell anyone.
Just let me go, OK?
I really wish I could, kid, but I can't.
You're going with me. Get in the helicopter.
Frank. Frank. Come on, please.
- Please.
- Move.
Prep a sterile cranial field.
I need access to the right hemisphere.
Right away.
- I'll prep the area.
All right.
- I need to talk to Tony.
- He's nonresponsive.
According to the paramedic on the chopper,
a head trauma has affected his speech.
- They're trying to relieve the pressure.
- Will he be able to talk then?
The doctor doesn't know.
I want real-time updates on his progress.
- We need Tony to explain this.
- What is it?
- A connection between Tony and Palmer.
- Tony's phone records?
The last time Tony spoke to President Palmer
was the day that Jack Bauer was killed.
- Did you pull the transcripts?
- I tried, but the files were corrupted.
- What's he hiding?
- Something about Jack's death.
- Are you kidnapping me?
- No.
- Then where are you taking me?
- Los Angeles.
Why?
I couldn't leave you back there.
You'd have gone to the police.
What is this about? Who are you?
Someone who's not supposed to still be alive.
- Like some kind of witness relocation thing?
- Yeah, something like that.
- So you were a criminal?
- No.
Listen, Derek.
The less you know about me, the better.
So what are you gonna do with me?
- Hello.
- Diane, it's me.
I can barely hear you. What's that noise?
- I'm in a helicopter with Derek.
- Derek?
He's fine. Listen, I need you
to pick him up in Los Angeles for me.
- Why is he with you?
- I'll explain when I see you.
Frank, what are you doing with Derek?
Please do this. I need you to get in the car
and start driving now.
- You're scaring me.
- Do you remember you said you trusted me?
Right now I need you to trust me.
Derek's gonna be fine. Just do what I say.
I need you to start driving
towards Los Angeles.
Don't talk to anybody about this.
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
Frank!
I don't understand. I thought you
were worried about me going to the police.
I have something to do in Los Angeles.
Once it's done, it doesn't matter.
- How are you doing?
- I'm sorry. I didn't mean to make a scene.
I know that.
Dr Hill says
you haven't been taking your medication.
I don't like the way the pills make me feel.
Marty.
- We just need to get through today.
- Charles,
the reason that I needed to...
needed to talk to you...
What is it, honey? Go ahead.
I think that David was killed because of
something he was about to tell me.
Come over here.
- What are you talking about?
- He called me yesterday.
- He said he wanted to meet with me.
- Meet with you about what?
He said that it concerned national security
and that it involved you.
- Me?
- Yes.
- What else did he say?
- Just that he would explain when he saw me.
If this was so important,
why wouldn't he have called me himself?
Charles, you shut him out of this White
House about 18 months ago, you know that.
He had no real access.
Except through you.
- You don't believe me.
- I didn't say that.
You didn't need to.
Martha.
I am not making this up.
- I am not crazy. I am not a fool, Charles.
- Martha, it's gonna be all right.
I am not making this up.
- All right. I'll have Walt look into it.
- You will?
- Yes.
- Thank you.
But right now,
President Suvarov and his wife are arriving
in one hour. I need you to be there.
I need you by my side.
Yes.
- Come here.
- I'm sorry.
- Is she all right?
- No, she's not all right.
She's having another one of her delusions.
She thinks David Palmer
was about to tell her something.
She's imagining she's in the middle
of one of her own conspiracy theories.
What should we do?
Nothing.
- Have you talked to Chloe this morning?
- No. Why?
She left her apartment about a half-hour ago.
- She should have been here.
- Probably traffic.
She commutes against traffic.
She's not answering her cellphone.
- I wouldn't worry about it.
- She sounded strange when I talked to her.
She always sounds strange.
I'll call Adamson, have him locate her cell.
- Don't waste his time. She's fine. I'm sure.
- What makes you so sure?
- It doesn't matter.
- It does to me.
I saw her. OK? Uh, about half an hour ago.
- I thought you said...
- Forget what I said.
- Where did you see her?
- Man. Do you really need me to spell it out?
Don't worry about Chloe. She's fine. All right?
Can you just let me out here?
- There's nothing here.
- Just pull over, please.
Why won't you talk to me, Frank?
Can you please tell me what's going on?
Please?
A friend of mine's in trouble.
I needed to pick her up in a hurry.
This is the only way
I could get to her quick enough.
- Chloe.
- Jack.
- Are you OK?
- I'm fine. What's happening?
- Why would anyone want to kill us?
- I don't know, but we're gonna find out.
I need to get access to CTU's archives from
a secure location. Can you help me do that?
I can't do it from my laptop. There's
a research loft at Caltech. I can get us in.
Who's that?
- I'll explain as soon as we're in the car.
- I don't have a car. I took a cab.
Come on. Get in the helicopter. We gotta go.
Derek, get back in.
- Jack.
- What?
It's them. How did they find me?
I don't think they ever lost you.
- Come on.
- What's going on, Frank? Who are they?
- What are we waiting for? Take off!
- We're not at speed.
We're not gonna make it. Get out. Get out
now, and stay by the side of the helicopter!
Here! Take him and go into the refinery.
Find somewhere to hide. Move!
I can't see a thing.
Double back. Cut him off. Go through
the smoke and get him. I'm going around.
Go over here.
Hold your fire, Chloe!
- What are you doing? Let's get outta here.
- Take Derek and walk away.
Walk away now!
You're not gonna make it
unless you get medical attention.
You tell me what I want to know, and I'll
get you to a hospital. You understand me?
- Do you understand me?
- Yeah.
Four people knew I was alive.
This morning you tried to take 'em out. Why?
Palmer was the primary... primary target.
They only cared about Palmer.
The others were just a diversion
to set you up.
- Make it look like you did it.
- Why did they want to kill Palmer?
To keep him from talking.
They had to shut him up.
- What did he know?
- I wasn't given that information.
I was only hired to take out the principal.
You're the one that killed Palmer.
Yeah. Oh, God.
Who's behind this?
I got my orders through a closed site.
We never use names, you know that.
That's all I know. Take me to a hospital.
Yeah.