I don't want to see either
one of you ever again.
Do we have a deal or not?
Yeah, we got a deal.
I'm going after him.
We're done.
We're just getting started.
(grunts in pain)
Jenny!
(gunshots)
(groans)
We need to talk about
you having Tarin arrested.
I know you consider
Tarin a friend.
We are more than friends.
We're in love.
You've been carrying
on with this man...
behind my back?
Who are these men, Samir?
These are men I
have recruited.
We can't get the rods
out of the country,
so let's use them as
a radiological bomb.
Then we'll show the
Americans how strong we are.
(grunts)
(groans)
Samir!
Over here!
There are people chasing me.
They have the rods
you are looking for.
I thought you had the rods.
They turned against me.
Just get me out of here.
We'll get you out, Mr. Hassan.
MAN: When things get
this colossally screwed up
people look for
someone to blame.
HASTINGS: So what
have you got in mind?
Renee Walker- she killed
one of our main leads.
You're talking about a
woman who put her life
on the line when
she didn't have to.
Well, someone has to
pay for this, Brian.
I'm sending someone over
from Justice- Kristin Smith.
She'll take care
of everything.
They're setting you up-
don't say another word.
It's too late.
This is over.
We're leaving now.
Hands in the air.
Do it now!
HASTINGS: You offering
to bring in Farhad? Yes.
If you drop the criminal
investigation against Renee Walker.
If we do this, Jack, it's
not for one rescue operation,
it's till this whole thing
is over and done.
Deal.
We're about to transport
him to the embassy.
You have two minutes.
Thank you.
Bashir, clear the room.
Tarin, did they hurt you?
Not yet.
They won't until they
get me to our embassy.
I tried to reason
with my father,
but he wouldn't listen.
He thinks you're involved in
the conspiracy with his brother.
Even after I told him about
us, he doesn't trust you.
You told him about us?
I hoped it would
change his mind.
But if anything, it's made
things worse between us.
(whispers): Come closer.
Listen to me, Kayla,
there is a way out of this.
There are a few men still loyal
to me- Bashir is one of them.
He's agreed to help me escape.
As soon as he's able, Bashir
will slip me a handcuff key,
and he's placed a gun in
the car for me to find.
You won't hurt anyone?
The gun is so I won't have to.
Once I'm free, I
have a place to stay
until the Americans
grant me asylum.
Kayla... I want
you to come with me.
Meet me at the Teodore Hotel.
Promise me you'll come.
(door opens)
Tarin, we need to go.
(handcuffs rattling)
(crickets chirping)
(grunting)
Cole, he's dead!
Just go.
(panting): What?
Nobody knows you had
anything to do with this.
It's my fault.
I lied about everything.
Who I am, what I've done.
I'll call the police.
I deserve to take
the blame for this.
(panting)
What's done is done.
We're cleaning this up,
and no one's ever gonna
know what happened.
I don't want you involved.
I'm already involved.
We're gonna strip down his
van so it can't be I.D.'d.
We'll dump the
bodies in the swamp.
Hey. Hey!
They're scum, Dana, and
no one's gonna miss 'em.
You want to go to prison for
the rest of your life? For them?!
Get started on the van.
I'll go get the other one.
(sniffling)
PATTY (over intercom): Mr. Hastings,
the president's on the line.
Thank you. This is Hastings.
Mr. Hastings, I'm
here with Rob Weiss.
I was told you
have urgent news.
Yes, ma'am.
We received a call
from Farhad Hassan.
Farhad?
Yes. As we suspected,
he was trying
to smuggle the nuclear
rods out of the country.
The people he's working
with have turned against him.
What do we know?
Well, Farhad believes
they want to use the rods
to construct a dirty bomb
and set it off somewhere
here in New York City.
Why would they do this?
Between Hassan's
crackdowns and CTU,
we've backed them
into a corner.
This is their response.
Do you believe him?
Yes, I do.
Farhad is turning himself in.
He's agreed to help
us prevent this attack.
Where is Farhad now?
He's in a warehouse
just outside the city
near Forest Hills.
I've enlisted Jack
Bauer to lock him down.
Now, Madam President,
the men who turned
against Farhad
are covert assets
for the I.R.K.
Now, if we can get access
to the I.R.K.
intelligence files,
Farhad may be able to
help us I.D. these men.
It will put us
that much closer
to tracking them down. Those
files are the lifeblood of Hassan's
intelligence operation-
he'll never hand them over.
Especially in his
current frame of mind.
Hell, the man's gone
off the deep end.
Well, maybe this will
pull him out of it.
Tell Hassan we have
found his brother and
I need to speak to him
immediately.
And contact
Tim Woods at Homeland.
Have him put
together a briefing.
I need to know exactly
what we're facing
if, God forbid,
this attack happens.
Thank you, Mr. Hastings.
I'll be in the
counsel chamber.
Yes, Madam President.
HASTINGS (over
intercom): Mr. Weiss.
Yeah?
Are we alone?
Yeah. What is it?
I want to let you
know that I've decided
not to pursue charges
against Renee Walker.
What?
Why not? I told you...
We have a lot
more to worry about
right now than blaming Walker.
Walker murdered
a valuable lead
that might have gotten
us to those nuclear rods.
You're not hearing me.
We have a new lead
now- Farhad Hassan-
and that is what
I am pursuing.
You want to replace me as
head of CTU, be my guest.
But until you do,
stay the hell out of my way.
- Hastings, you're making...
- I'll let you know
when Bauer reaches Farhad.
(sighs)
Okay, Farhad Hassan is located on
the northeast corner of the warehouse.
We're gonna have to move
fast, because he's injured.
King, Lynch, you're gonna
go in from the south.
Owen and I will
cover your flank.
- Understood.
- As soon as we've
got him locked down, we're
gonna initiate our interrogation.
CTU's gonna upload files on
probable suspects-
I need that
available and on a computer
- as soon as possible.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Bauer, we're getting
a call routed through CTU.
It's Farhad Hassan.
Put it on speaker.
This is Jack Bauer. Go ahead.
(quietly): How close are you?
Ten minutes out. Are you okay?
There's someone here.
(crickets chirping)
They're close.
They're looking for me.
Please... hurry.
Madam President.
I'm told you have my brother.
What happened?
Please.
He called CTU
and surrendered himself.
I don't understand.
The men that Farhad
was working with
turned against him,
and they have taken
the nuclear rods.
Now, he believes that
they intend to construct
a dirty bomb to
attack this city.
Now, apparently,
these men are members
of your covert
intelligence operations
here in the United States.
I find that hard to believe.
Well, your brother
has no reason to lie.
By turning himself in, he's
facing the death penalty.
We have to assume
he's telling the truth.
I need for you to give
us intelligence files
for every asset you
have in this country
so Farhad can identify
these terrorists.
Mr. President,
I have given you
a great deal of latitude
to sort out your
domestic situation,
and now there is a
threat to my homeland,
and I need your cooperation.
I suggest you turn
Farhad over to me
and let my people
question him.
We'll get the
answers you need.
There's no time for that.
There's a CTU team
moving on Farhad as we speak.
They need to
question him on site.
I need the files.
What you're asking is a
serious breach of our security.
I understand that.
But you need to understand
that if this radiological
attack takes place,
I will be forced to retaliate.
You would attack...
my country?
I will have no choice.
I need those files...
and I need them now.
I'll call my acting
head of security.
You'll get the files
in a few minutes.
Thank you.
I want you to know,
Tarin, that I don't believe
you are guilty of treason.
But I have no choice
but to follow orders.
You don't have to
explain yourself, Nabeel.
I would do the same
thing in your position.
I don't hold any
of this against you.
Whatever happens to me,
you must not blame yourself.
Never forget that.
I appreciate that.
- Don't move.
- What are you doing?
Nabeel, give me
your weapon now.
Slowly, two fingers.
Come on.
Driver, pull over here.
Remove your seat belts.
Put your hands on
your head, both of you.
Get out of the car now.
Don't move.
Give me the keys.
Put your hands down.
Tarin, don't do this.
You'll only make things
worse for yourself.
You know what they'll
do to me at our embassy.
It can't be any worse.
(phone ringing)
It's President Hassan.
Give it to me.
Come on!
Let's go. In the back.
(ringing continues)
Open it up.
Take out your cuffs.
Lock yourselves down.
(ringing continues)
Nabeel isn't answering.
Where is he?
Transporting Tarin
to the embassy.
Keep trying to reach
him on his mobile.
If he doesn't answer,
send a security
team to track him.
Yes, sir.
And contact Colonel Al Jhanis.
Tell him on my authority
to give CTU access to
the files they requested.
Yes, sir.
(phone ringing)
Hello.
It's me. Where are you?
I'm leaving the
U.N. right now.
Is everything all right?
Yes, it worked.
Meet me at the hotel.
I'll be there in ten minutes.
I love you, Kayla.
I'll see you soon.
(over headset): Go ahead, Mr. Hastings.
Farhad, are you there?
Yes, yes, I'm here.
Our field team is approaching
the south entrance.
Stay where you are until
they secure the site.
He's almost on me.
I can't stay here.
Do not move until they
lock down that shooter.
Do you understand me?
Farhad?
Farhad?!
Farhad, talk to me.
(rapid gunshots)
(tires squealing)
Over here!
Medic! Come on! Medic!
JACK: That's him,
that's Farhad.
Owen, take your team
and sweep the area.
Chloe, we've got Farhad,
but he's been hit.
I need those
files immediately.
I.R.K. intelligence
just sent them over.
Good.
(phone ringing)
Yes?
It's done.
Farhad is no longer a problem.
Are you sure?
I shot him twice, but
the police arrived,
and I had to get out of there.
You know where to find us.
Yes.
Mr. Bauer.
Speak to me. We have two large
caliber slugs to the abdomen.
He's bleeding out. I don't think
he's going to make it to the hospital.
Do whatever you have
to do to stabilize him.
We need to talk
to him now. Go!
This is B team.
We found their truck, but
there's no sign of the rods.
Let me know as soon as
these files are uploaded.
Mr. Hassan, in a few seconds,
I'm going to show you
photographs of covert operatives
working for your country
within the United States.
I need you to identify the
men who stole the nuclear rods
from you. Can you
do that for us?
Yes.
Are those files uploaded yet?!
Almost. Come on!
Blood pressure's dropping.
We've got a rapid heartbeat.
What the hell's happening?
He's going into shock.
Give me 30 cc's epinephrine.
You keep that man alive,
do you understand me?
Keep him alive!
Let me do my job!
The telepresence conference
- is ready, Madam President.
- Thank you.
Good to see you, gentlemen.
Madam President,
Brian Hastings at CTU
has brought us up to speed,
and we're ready to review
some specifics with you.
Good. I'm listening.
If you would refer
to your monitor...
and the diagram of
Midtown Manhattan.
According to CTU,
the stolen nuclear rods have
a maximum explosive yield
of 300 pounds.
That's enough
radiological material
to contaminate approximately
one square mile.
If the device were detonated
in a more densely
populated area of Manhattan,
we could be looking
at casualties
in the tens of thousands.
Dr. Landry?
Most of the deaths would be
from severe radiation poisoning.
The remainder of the
victims would expire
from radiation
induced illnesses.
Primarily leukemia
and other cancers.
We also have to consider
that the affected area
would be rendered
uninhabitable
for approximately 40 years.
Obviously a citywide evacuation
is out of the question.
That's right. There are
millions of people on this island
with few points of egress.
It would take days
to get them out.
Not to mention that going
public with this information
would cause mass panic.
I agree. We need to keep this
threat from the public for now.
Focus our efforts on making sure
that this attack never happens.
CTU believes the nuclear rods
are still outside the city,
so they're fortifying
radiation detection efforts
at the bridges and tunnels.
We are also hardening
high value targets
such as the financial
district, landmarks, subways.
But we can't ignore that the
U.N. may also be a target.
Give the danger, I think we should
evacuate the entire building.
We can resume the conference
from a safe location.
All right, inform the
delegates of the situation.
- Thank you, gentlemen.
- Madam President.
CTU has your
brother in custody.
He's been shot.
They're trying
to stabilize him.
(two beeps)
Yes?
MAN: Sir, Agent Rahim
is calling for you.
He says he's located Nabeel.
- Put him through.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. President, we found
Nabeel and his driver
locked down in the
back of their vehicle.
- Tarin has escaped.
- What?!
Nabeel wishes to
speak to you, sir.
Yes, okay, put him on.
I'm sorry, Mr. President.
Tarin had a gun with him.
I don't understand how.
Are you saying somebody
helped him escape?
It would seem so.
But Mr. President,
there's something
else you need to know.
Right after he escaped, I
overheard Tarin on the phone.
(whispering): I believe he
was speaking to your daughter.
Kayla? Are you
sure about this?
Yes, sir.
It sounded like he
was going to meet her
somewhere in the city.
(phone ringing)
(phone beeps)
Kayla, call me back.
Call me back, Kayla.
(sighs)
Come inside.
Oh, thank God,
you're all right.
Oh!
I contacted an
American lawyer I know
who's an expert at
international law.
He's agreed to meet
us in two hours.
This is such a
terrible situation.
Yet I've never felt so happy.
I feel the same.
Mm!
Mr. Bauer, we did our best.
He didn't make it.
I know you did. Thanks.
We swept the area,
sir. It's clear.
No hostiles. No trace
of the nuclear rods.
Copy that.
CTU, this is Bauer.
We lost him. Farhad's dead.
Damn it.
I still think we've
got another play.
Whoever shot Farhad couldn't
confirm that he was killed.
We came up on him too fast.
They don't know how
badly he was wounded.
So what are you
proposing, Jack?
I'm saying that we use
Farhad as dead bait.
Leak it to the press that
we've got him in custody,
and he survived.
We're transporting
him to a local hospital
where authorities are
going to question him.
They'll have to
make a move on him.
- He knows too much.
- Sounds like a Hail Mary.
Right now it's the
only play we've got.
But if they make a move on
Farhad, which I think they will,
we'll be waiting for them.
Mr. Hastings, you
said you wanted me in
till this was
resolved. This is it.
We have Hassan's
intelligence files.
We can scan and
cross-reference
with facial
recognition software.
Maybe spot the terrorists
before they attack.
All right, Jack.
It's not exactly
standard procedure
ferrying a dead man's
body across the city,
but I'm willing
to give it a shot.
We'll figure out
a hospital route
and put a press
statement together.
You get ready on your end.
Okay, thank you.
Get that body
ready for transport.
Owen, assemble your men.
Briefing in less than five.
Aerial one is in position
over the route, sir.
Sniper teams have checked
in. They're all in place.
Come on, hurry up.
(zipping bag)
Let's go.
(both grunting)
(panting)
(water gurgling)
(water burbling)
It's over, Dana.
Let's get the other body
and get cleaned up
before we head back to CTU.
Cole, what about us?
I don't know.
(grunting)
We have just received word
from New York
Counterterrorist Headquarters
that Farhad
Hassan- brother of
Islamic Republic of Kamistan
President Omar Hassan-
has been found alive.
We're told that Farhad
Hassan contacted CTU
a short while ago and agreed
to turn him over to authorities.
Farhad is alive.
What?
CTU responded immediately,
but when they arrived,
they found him shot.
No word yet on how
Farhad Hassan sustained
these gunshot injuries,
but we do know that he
is expected to survive,
and he's being transported
to St. Julian's Hospital
under heightened security
where he will be
questioned by authorities.
This is impossible.
Farhad Hassan has been on the
run since early this evening...
I shot him twice.
But you didn't make
sure he was dead.
I told you I didn't have time!
I'll make this
right. I'll go back.
You're too conspicuous.
Farhad will be
heavily protected.
But if Farhad talks,
the authorities could find us
before we can build the weapon.
You think we don't
know the implications?
We're sending Marcos.
His mother's American.
They won't suspect him.
He's in the truck
with the rods.
The peace treaty
may now be halted
due to a series of
alleged terrorist attacks.
(phone flips open)
(speed-dial tone)
ELAINE (over phone): Hello?
Mom, it's me.
Marcos?
Yes. Listen, I
can't talk for long.
What is it? Are you okay?
I'm fine, Mom.
I need you to do
something for me.
It's very important.
Okay.
Okay. What is it?
I need you to get up right
now and leave the city.
Go to Aunt Shelley's.
Aunt Shelley's?!
Just do it for me, okay?
Don't ask me why.
Leave right now.
Marcos,
this is crazy...
I'm not gonna
leave the apartment
in the middle of the
night for no reason.
There's a reason; I just can't
tell you what it is right now.
Please, Mom, do this for me.
Where are you?
Don't worry about me.
Well, I'm not going
anywhere unless I know
you're all right.
I'll meet you at
Aunt Shelley's,
and I'll explain everything.
Go, Mom, now.
Okay, I'm leaving.
(door latch clanks)
I have to go. I love you.
Are you ready, my friend?
Yes.
Good.
It's time.
You need to keep him
looking alive the entire way.
You're all clear on
what you need to do?
Yes, sir.
Jack, it's Hastings. Go ahead.
We've coordinated
with news outlets.
They put out the false
report of Farhad's arrest
and transport to the hospital
for questioning.
The hook has been baited.
Okay. The most
logical place for them
to attack is when
we're en route.
That's where we're gonna
be our most vulnerable.
Well, NYPD and SWAT
are mobilizing now.
They're going to be embedded
at strategic points
along the way.
They're also securing
St. Julian's Hospital.
Copy that. Tell
the support teams
it is imperative that we
take these terrorists alive.
They've been briefed, Jack.
Okay, we're moving out.
You two take the follow van.
Owen, you're with
me in the ambulance.
Copy that.
Hey, are you all right?
Yes, sir.
(whispering): Look, I
know you and your men
have not had a lot
of field experience,
and we have put you in
an extreme situation.
But I promise you,
if we're attacked,
every part of this
route is covered.
We've got a lot of
support out there.
I'm fine, Mr. Bauer.
Let's do this.
Yeah.
Our delegation is
preparing to head
to McGuire Air force Base.
We'll be setting up a
temporary ops center there,
where we'll be able to
monitor the situation.
And the other delegates?
U.N. Security will
coordinate the evacuation.
Everything should go smoothly.
Can I get you anything,
Madam President?
No, thank you, Rob.
You have done
more than enough.
I'm just sorry that
your first few months
on the job have
been so challenging.
I wouldn't have had
it any other way.
I'll see you in a moment.
I spoke to one of my aides.
He told me my
brother is... dead.
I'm afraid so.
When CTU is finished
with their operation,
I would like Farhad's remains
to be returned to my country.
Personally, I don't
care where his body rots,
but my mother will
want a proper burial.
I'll see that it's done.
But right now, Mr. President,
we must all evacuate the U.N.
I'm not leaving,
Madame President.
I'm staying here.
I don't understand.
My daughter Kayla is missing.
Missing?
Kayla is romantically involved
with my former head of security.
She's run off with him.
Tell me what we
can do to help.
I appreciate that,
but my security teams
are searching for her now.
I understand how
worried you must be,
but there is nothing
that you can do
to help her by staying here.
Please come where
you'll be safe.
I can't, Madam President.
She's somewhere in the city,
with no idea that a
nuclear threat exists.
I won't go anywhere
until she's been found.
All right.
I understand.
I will talk to you very soon.
Thank you.
They're turning
west Sixth Street.
Pulling into the hospital.
Chloe, bring up the
hospital security feed.
Get facial recognition
up and running.
CTU, this is Bauer. We're
moving into position.
Farhad's body's been
taken to his room.
Let's go!
Secure these doors!
HASTINGS: Bring up
the exterior cameras.
♪ ♪
(phone rings)
This is Bauer.
Jack, it's me.
Hey.
I've been released.
I'm free to go.
Good.
Chloe told me what you did.
You leveraged Hastings.
Said that you would
head up field ops
until this crisis was over
in exchange for CTU dropping
any possible charges against me.
I didn't ask you
to do that, Jack.
I know you didn't.
Look, someone in the White
House is trying to set you up
to take responsibility for
the failure of our mission,
and I couldn't let that happen
because you did nothing wrong.
You understand me?
Renee, you need
to let this go.
You're not responsible
for what's happening
Yeah, okay.
Hey, I meant what
I said earlier.
When this is over, I want
to be there for you...
with you.
I'd like that.
I'll have a CTU agent
take you to my apartment.
I'll meet you there
when this is over.
All right, Jack.
Look, I'm getting chatter
over the comm. I gotta go.
Okay, bye.
This is Bauer. Go ahead.
HASTINGS: Jack,
facial recognition
just picked up a match
with the I.R.K.
intelligence files.
His name's Marcos Al-Zacar.
American-born.
Working undercover
with the I.R.K.
for the last three years.
Where is he?
Approaching the side entrance.
Brown hair, blue scrubs,
wearing aé dark-blue jacket.
Copy that.
Hold on, Jack. he's got
something in his hand.
It looks like a
remote detonator.
I think he's wearing a vest.
Chloe, can you
disarm it from there?
Possibly, if I can pin
down the detonator model,
I may be able to
scramble the arming code
using the transmitter
in the mobile comm.
Get on it. Owen,
you've got a man
approaching your position.
He's got brown hair.
He's wearing green
scrubs and a blue jacket.
Yeah. I see him.
He's our hitter. We believe
he's wearing an explosive vest
with a remote detonator.
Okay. What should I do?
Stay calm and do
whatever he asks.
CTU techs are going to try and
disarm the vest from offsite.
Okay.
Owen?
Owen.
You can do this.
Just try and slow him
down as much as possible.
We've got you covered
every inch of the way.
Yes, sir.
(exhaling)
Excuse me. This
is a secure area.
I'm going to need
to see some I.D.
Listen to me very carefully.
I have a bomb.
Give me your weapon right
now, or I'll kill us both.
Your weapon now.
Okay. Okay.
Just take it easy.
Slowly.
Yeah.
Where is Farhad Hassan?
Third floor.
Take me to him.
Anyone asks who I am,
you say I'm a doctor,
and I'm cleared.
Come on, son.
Okay.
Move.
Okay. Go.
Hello?
Dalia, it's me.
We need to talk.
Don't try to change
my mind, Omar.
I told you, I'm leaving.
I haven't called
to change your mind.
I called because
Kayla may be in danger.
What do you mean?
She's run away with Tarin.
They've been
seeing each other.
I know.
How long have you known?
What difference
does it make, Omar?
What kind of danger is she in?
Farhad is dead.
The nuclear material
he tried to acquire
is in the hands
of the terrorists.
They're going to use
it here in Manhattan.
No.
How did this happen?
I'll explain later.
But right now you
need to call Kayla.
I've left messages, but
she won't return my calls.
But she might talk to you.
Please, Dalia.
She's angry at me.
I had Tarin arrested.
I thought he was part
of the conspiracy.
All right.
But Omar, what about you?
Don't worry about me.
Just help me
find our daughter.
I- I'll try.
Sabira, I need the captain.
(elevator bell dings)
Chloe, it's Jack. We're
moving to the third floor.
Where are we at with the vest?
I've identified
the detonator, Jack.
It's German-made, K7 variant,
but that model is used in
a lot of configurations.
I'm going to need a
visual on the vest.
Copy that.
Owen, it's Jack.
CTU cannot disarm the
vest unless they see it.
I need you to get the hostile
underneath one of the
surveillance cameras
and make him show it to you.
I repeat, CTU cannot
disarm the vest
unless they see it.
You ready?
(over comm): Team three, they're
approaching your position.
What are you doing?
I want to see proof.
Proof of what?
A bomb.
I don't believe you have one.
You don't keep moving,
you're gonna find out.
Right now.
You want Farhad, you show me.
I said, "Move."
No.
Owen did it, Jack.
I've got a visual on the vest.
Now, move.
Okay.
We're set in position
near Farhad's room.
Now, what's the status?
It's a DDR configuration.
I just need to pull up the
frequency of the receiver.
Chloe, you've got
about 30 seconds
before they reach that room.
Got it.
3.15 gigahertz, standard GSM.
Running it through
the mobile comm now.
This'll take a few seconds.
Stand by for assault.
On the floor, face down!
Do it now!
Don't move!
Come on, Arlo. Hurry up.
(timer beeping)
That's it. It's done.
Jack, the vest is disarmed.
Move in. Go, go, go!
(timer beeping)
(grunts)
(monitor beeping rhythmically)
(door slams open)
(gun clicks empty)
It's all right.
Lower your weapons.
I'm going to put my gun away.
We're not here to hurt you.
We just want to talk.
Stay calm.
It's all right.
I just want to talk to you.
No. No!
(grunts)
He's still moving.
Notify the perimeter.
Do not fire! He's unarmed!
(slams shut)
(grunting and panting)
(straining)
This is Bauer.
I'm in the east wing.
Suspect has barricaded himself
in some kind of
pressure chamber.
I need a team down here now
to help me open the door.
(cell phone ringing)
Yes?
MARCOS (on phone):
It was a trap.
Farhad was already dead.
What? The police were waiting.
They tried to ambush
me, but I got away.
Where are you?
I locked myself inside
some kind of oxygen chamber.
They can't get in here.
At least not yet.
You know what you must do.
I can't.
I- I think they-they
scrambled the arming code.
You need to set
it off manually.
I don't know how to do that.
I'll talk you through it.
Can you open the
detonator control?
Yeah. I-I think so.
Um, it's going
to take a minute.
Work quickly.
You cannot let
them take you alive.
Can you hear me?
JACK (over comm):
I just want to talk.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com