Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net
Shared by http://DJJ.HOME.SAPO.PT/
I'm aware that your generals
are pushing you toward a military response.
Until you have the component
I have no choice
but to continue on our present path.
The man with the component
no longer works with the Chinese.
He's offered to trade it back to us and...
I've authorised the exchange.
Phillip Bauer is a sociopath.
We can't trust he'll give us the component,
whether we give him the boy or not.
- What are you asking me to do, Karen?
- Whatever it takes to stop the exchange.
It won't be long before
they figure out how I located Jack.
They already have.
They're probably on their way to arrest me.
They're here.
Send the kid down now.
Show the sub-circuit board first.
I need to verify it.
There they are. They've got Josh.
I don't have a clear shot
without putting Josh at risk!
Get down!
Get me the names and locations
of every offshore oil platform
within a ten-mile radius.
My father didn't pick this location at random.
Morris, no luck tracing the oil leases
through the CNC servers.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Chloe. Chloe.
Can someone please help me?
Darling? Darling? Can you hear me?
Can someone please help me?!
Joshua.
- I don't wanna be here with you.
- We're not staying here.
- I don't wanna go anywhere with you!
- Look, Josh...
I don't expect you to understand everything,
not now anyway.
Someday you will, and you'll thank me for it.
In the meantime, you'll do as you're told.
Is that clear?
- Good.
- (Cheng speaks Chinese)
- The submarine is on schedule.
- How soon before they pick us up?
30 minutes.
Her vitals are strong.
She's in no immediate danger.
- Why did she collapse?
- Dehydration, exhaustion.
She hasn't slept in 36 hours.
He said I'm fine, Morris. It's not a big deal.
You should be at your work station.
No, I should be right here with you.
You should be checking the EPA database
to see what oil platforms Phillip Bauer owns.
Other people can do that.
If you really wanna make me feel better,
then go find Phillip Bauer.
Are you sure you're all right?
OK, then.
- Morris, is Chloe all right?
- The doctor says she's gonna be fine.
Jack was right about his father.
One of his companies owns a lease
on an oil platform six miles offshore.
- He has the boy?
- That platform's been decommissioned.
OK, give me the wheel, Nadia.
Let's try a thermal scan,
see if we can pick up any signs of life.
That's crowded
for a decommissioned platform.
Can you back-time the satellite imagery
a few minutes?
There, that must be Josh Bauer arriving.
That would be 20 minutes after he was taken.
Timing works. Send a copy of this to my
screen and forward it to the White House.
- Get me Tom Lennox, please.
- (woman) Right away.
(phone rings)
- Dr Hastings here.
- This is Morris O'Brian.
Have Chloe O'Brian's test results
come in yet?
You just left here a few minutes ago.
We're still running those tests.
Well, when do you expect the results?
Soon.
Can you call me when you get them?
I'm afraid I can't,
not without Ms O'Brian's permission.
- I'm her husband.
- Ex-husband.
I'm sorry, but I can only share information
with Ms O'Brian's family.
Fine.
Reports indicate the Russians
are setting up an offensive position.
- They could attack at a moment's notice.
- That's correct.
Sir, CTU have just located Phillip Bauer
and a dozen or so confederates
on an oil-drilling platform
six miles off the coast of Los Angeles.
- And he has the sub-circuit board?
- We're assuming so, sir.
Pass this on to Suvarov.
It'll buy us more time. Meanwhile...
I want an assault team
despatched to that oil rig.
- Mr Vice President, if I may?
- Go ahead, Ethan.
If the platform is well-defended,
an assault team might run into trouble.
I recommend an air attack.
Two navy F-18s could obliterate
that platform and everyone on it.
- What about the sub-circuit board?
- If it's not destroyed, it'll sink.
The saltwater
will render it useless in minutes.
Tom?
We think Phillip Bauer's grandson
is on that same platform.
Now, he might well survive
a surgical strike by an assault team,
but there's no way he'd live
through this proposed aerial attack.
We are talking about
an innocent 16-year-old boy here.
None of us like this,
but if the Russians attack our base,
a lot of innocent young men are gonna die.
And an air strike would be the most effective
from a political point of view.
It'll show the Russians that we're sparing
no effort to destroy the sub-circuit board.
- Send the F-18s immediately.
- Yes, sir, Mr Vice President.
- You'll be all right. You'll make it.
- Jack, I'm sorry.
- You were following your orders.
- Get the kid. Get the kid, Jack.
- I will.
- (phone rings)
- Did you find my father?
- Yes, on an oil platform six miles offshore.
Is Josh with him?
Thermal scan shows three people arriving
20 minutes after Josh was taken,
- so it's highly likely he was one of them.
- Nadia, I wanna lead the assault team.
- There's not gonna be an assault team.
- What?
I just got notification that the White House
has ordered air strike by navy F-18s.
The vice president thinks
an assault team will take too long.
- When will it happen?
- Less than 30 minutes.
Look, I need you and Bill to come back to
CTU on Aerial One for an immediate debrief.
Jack?
Fine.
- What's wrong?
- CTU located my father and Josh
on one of the offshore oil platforms.
There's no assault. They've launched an air
strike. No one on that platform will survive.
I'm sorry, Jack.
Jack, don't even think about it. You wanna
get yourself killed? You won't save Josh.
- I realise he's your nephew.
- I'm not gonna do it because of that.
I'm gonna do it cos he's an innocent kid
being written off as an acceptable loss.
It's wrong.
Nadia's ordered us back to CTU
on Chopper One. I'm gonna take it.
I'll fly. You prep the weapons.
It's been a while, but I can get us to
the platform. With luck, I might get us back.
- You don't need to do this, Bill.
- Yes, I do.
I don't wanna live with this one, either.
Let's get ready.
You're gonna need that.
We're commandeering your helicopter.
Get out. Now!
Matching target coordinates.
We'll be in range in 22 minutes.
Sir, significant numbers of Russian troops
have assumed a flanking position
along the eastern rim of our military base.
What am I to take from that?
A tactical advancement like that
indicates imminent attack.
(Lennox) All right, put him through.
Sir.
- You got Suvarov?
- Yes, sir.
Mr President, this is Vice President Daniels.
Mr Vice President, the last time we spoke,
you said an opportunity had presented itself.
Unfortunately, that didn't work out. But there
has been a significant new development,
and I'm asking you to hold off
on any military assault on our base.
For what reason, sir?
The Chinese agents
who are in possession of the component
are on an oil platform off our West Coast.
We assume they are there
waiting transport to China.
I've ordered an air strike to destroy the
platform before that rendezvous can happen.
I realise that you have no reason
to accept what I'm telling you...
not without proof, but I implore you...
Mr Vice President, I believe you.
Moments ago, one of our listening posts
intercepted a transmission
to a Chinese submarine operating
in the western Pacific.
The point of origin is ten miles off your coast.
And the contents suggest the submarine
is en route to pick up the component.
- Then you know that I'm telling you the truth.
- You say you've launched an air strike?
Yes, that's the only way we can make certain
that the component's been destroyed.
Sir, we're prepared to give you a real-time
uplink to our satellite feed of the assault.
One moment, please, sir.
How long until your fighters reach the target?
Less then 20 minutes, sir.
20 minutes, Mr President.
Very well. But be advised, nothing less than
the complete destruction of this oil platform
will give us the assurance we require.
Understood.
Stand by, the satellite feed
will be there momentarily.
I wish you luck, Mr Vice President.
The coastguard and the navy are patrolling
a five-mile perimeter around the target.
- (man) I want real-time updates.
- Yes, sir. I'll keep you in the loop.
- What is it?
- Jack commandeered the chopper.
- He requested an uplink to our satellite feed.
- What?
He's on the way to the oil platform.
He's with Bill Buchanan.
- (Nadia) Aerial One, confirm. Come in.
- This is Bauer. We copy.
Jack, I know you wanna save your nephew,
but I can't authorise a suicide mission.
We don't need authorisation, we need help.
Those F-18s will be in striking range
in 18 minutes.
- What if we find the component first?
- The strike team's orders are noncontingent.
- All you'll do is get yourselves killed.
- It's Bill.
I understand the pressure you're under,
but believe me, this is the right call to make.
You need a visual on the oil platform?
Yes. We need to know how many hostiles
and where they are.
- Uploading the latest satellite capture.
- You'll have it.
- Copy that. Send it to my PDA.
- PDA, got it.
Thank you, Nadia. You did the right thing.
Bill, I need you to put your comm unit in.
- How should I make our approach, Jack?
- Wind's heavy out of the west.
If we fly into it and stay low,
we should be able to catch them off-guard.
- It won't buy us much time.
- Engage them from the air.
I'll hold them off so you can land,
then we'll move in.
The target is locked and acquired.
Josh, we leave in 15 minutes.
Please, just let me go.
- I can't do that.
- Why not?
Because I can't!
You have a lot to learn.
Now it's my responsibility to teach you.
First lesson is, pay attention.
(Cheng speaks Chinese)
What is it?
There's a helicopter approaching.
We need to get to the boat and head west.
There's a locator beacon on board.
The submarine will pick us up.
Here, take the component.
I'll see about the helicopter.
I'll join you shortly.
Let's go, Josh.
Once we hit the deck,
we're gonna have to move hard.
- You ready to move up?
- Ready!
Take it up!
You're clear to land!
(shouts in Chinese)
Don't move!
Where's the boy? Where's the boy?!
- You're too late. You're too late.
- Take this. Get him up to the chopper.
- What are you doing?
- Making sure Josh isn't here.
We only have ten minutes.
Get up! Get up!
Go! Go!
- Come on, Josh, stop it!
- I can't.
Of course you can.
All it takes is a little self-control.
You're behaving like a child.
You have to learn to control your emotions.
You must never let them control you,
you understand?
Good. Come on.
Target will be in range
in four minutes, 30 seconds.
I'm not going with you.
You're not gonna shoot me.
Give me the gun.
- Now.
- No!
As long as you're alive,
me and my mom will never be safe.
Josh, listen to me.
- I've always cared about you.
- No! You only care about yourself.
That's not true.
You're the reason I'm doing all this.
- Shut up!
- I love you, Josh.
Argh!
Josh!
It's all right. I've got him.
You can lower that weapon.
Josh.
Lower your gun.
I know how scared and angry
you must feel right now.
I know. I've been exactly where you are.
I know exactly how you feel.
But trust me, you do not wanna live
with the pain of taking another person's life,
even if you think they deserve it.
In a few minutes, there's gonna be
an F-18 air strike here.
We need to get out of here.
We need to get out of here now.
Please.
It's all right. Just give me the gun.
It's all right. It's all right.
It's over. It's over.
I need you to get up to the top of the platform
and get in the chopper now. Go. Move!
- What about you?
- I'll be right behind you. Keep going.
Get up.
Get up! It's over.
- Then finish it.
- No.
You are gonna be held accountable
for what you have done today.
I don't think so.
You don't have time to carry me. Not if
what you said about the air strike is true.
And you don't wanna die, not here.
Not with me.
You're gonna get off easy.
CTU, this is Aerial One.
My count shows the strike in two minutes.
Negative, you have 90 seconds before
those F-18s are within striking range.
You need to get off that platform now.
- Bill, confirm.
- Copy that. Stand by.
- Where's Jack?
- He's with my grandpa.
Get in.
Mr Vice President, target is in range.
Strike team reports...
missile lock.
Take it out.
Echo 64 is clear to engage.
(man) Echo 64, you are clear to engage.
- Wait! We can't leave without my uncle.
- We're not leaving. Hang on.
- Jack, I'm coming to the south, level three.
- Copy that, Bill. I'm on it.
Bill, I see you. I'm on the southwest corner.
Fox one. Fox two.
(Nadia) Aerial One, please confirm.
Bill, please confirm.
Bill, this is Nadia. Do you copy?
(Bill) CTU, this is Aerial One. We copy.
I've got Jack and his nephew, and Cheng
in custody. We're heading back to CTU.
We'll have a landing crew standing by, sir.
The strike team reports multiple direct hits.
Satellite recon is reporting...
target is completely destroyed.
Good work.
Mr President, you're seeing what we see?
Yes, we are.
(speaks in Russian)
We concur that the target
has been eliminated.
Then I trust you're satisfied that
the component's been destroyed as well?
I am.
I'm ordering the full withdrawal of our troops
from the eastern rim of your military base.
Good, Mr President. You will excuse me
if I wait until your troops are withdrawn
before I order our squadrons in the air
to stand down?
Yes, of course.
And Mr Vice President,
I regret that the events of this day
have brought us to such a dangerous
and unfortunate situation,
but when my country's security
is threatened...
I understand, Mr President, all too well.
Yes, I'm sure you do.
My best wishes
for the recovery of President Palmer.
Thank you.
Goodbye, Mr Vice President.
- What the hell happened?
- He fell. Uncle Jack fell!
All right, I'm going back.
He's all right.
- Where are we going?
- Back to CTU.
No, we can't. We have to go back for him.
Jack's not ready to go back yet.
Sir.
You should know, sir,
we've received confirmation
that the Chinese have recalled
their sub to its base at Ningpo.
Tell Admiral Smith to shadow them. I want
them to know we're aware of their activities.
Yes, sir.
And thank you, Ethan, for everything.
Extend my gratitude to the Joint Chiefs.
Congratulations, Mr Vice President.
Sir, not to quash your flush of victory here,
the actions of the Chinese
cannot go unaddressed.
We'll leave that for another day, Tom.
Right now, I don't know about you,
but I could use some sleep.
There's just one other outstanding issue
I would like to discuss with you, sir.
Karen Hayes?
She's about to be transferred
into FBI custody.
Now, in light of the recent terrorist attacks,
the nuke in California,
the plot against the president,
I just think we need to preserve
whatever fragile faith
the American people might still have
in this administration.
Just let Karen and Bill resign
with their reputations intact.
All right, Tom.
Take care of that for me.
All right. Thank you, sir.
Here's that tape recording you asked for.
- Hey.
- Hi.
- How you feeling?
- Good.
- Jack got the boy out. They're both safe.
- What about the Russians?
They backed off. They were satisfied
the component was destroyed.
- Jack's father?
- He was killed in the air strike.
And Cheng is in custody.
- Good.
- Look...
I was talking to Dr Hastings.
He says the test results are in, but he's not
telling me anything. He insists I talk to you.
Is it... serious?
Yeah.
Bloody hell, Chloe. Whatever it is,
I'll help you get through it.
- No, you won't. We're not together.
- Oh, sod that.
Really, come on, when you collapsed,
I thought something might really be wrong.
I can't lose you, darling.
- Really?
- Yeah, really. I love you.
OK. That's good, cos I'm pregnant.
You mean... what? With child?
That's usually how it works.
- Chloe...
- You know, this is a nice moment.
Let's not ruin it by saying something stupid.
Let's just go back to work.
OK.
- Tom?
- Karen.
- You've come to say goodbye?
- Well, in a manner of speaking.
You're free to go. The vice president
is dropping all charges against you.
- What about Bill?
- He's being pardoned as well.
The vice president
still expects your resignations,
but you're free to go live your lives
without fear of prosecution.
Is that suitable?
Yes, yes, yes, it is.
All right. Well, good luck.
I know you had a hand in this, Tom.
Thank you.
You know, Karen,
I actually think I'm gonna miss you.
Really?
I can answer that better after you've gone.
There's your mother.
You'll be debriefed
at a federal detention facility.
My people will not abandon me
like you abandoned Jack Bauer.
Get him out of here.
- It's good to see you again, sir.
- Good work today. You should be proud.
Thank you.
That means a lot coming from you.
Where's Jack?
He fell from the chopper into the ocean
during the extraction.
He made it to shore. He's fine.
- Why didn't you pick him up?
- He didn't want me to.
- I don't understand. We need to find him.
- We'll never find him.
Not if he doesn't want us to.
Let him go.
Somehow itjust doesn't feel real.
But I am grateful that she's alive.
- (woman) Let me know if I can do anything.
- Of course.
Anything at all.
I'll let you know. Thanks.
(door clicks open)
Put it down.
Now.
- Are you here to kill me?
- Depends.
Where is Audrey?
I told you, you're not
getting anywhere near her.
You do not tell me what to do any more!
Do you understand me?
You do not tell me what to do.
I just watched my father die,
and I felt nothing.
You know why?
Yeah, you know why.
Because that man was dead to me years ago.
I admired you.
I looked up to you like a father.
You were the kind of man I wanted to be,
and you took advantage of it!
- Jack, listen to me.
- No! You are gonna listen to me.
Earlier today, you said that I was cursed,
that anyone I touched
ended up dead or ruined.
How dare you? How dare you?
The only thing I did,
the only thing I have ever done,
is what you and people like you
have asked of me.
- Why didn't you try to get me out of China?
- I did try.
Not hard enough!
You had the political power.
Was the timing not right?
Was it a little too complicated?
- Or was I just an acceptable loss?
- Jack, I understand your anger.
Shut up!
You don't understand a thing about me.
But I know you.
I know why you're angry at me, and it wasn't
because Audrey went to China to save me.
It was because when you told her not to,
she did it anyway.
You'll never understand
that kind of commitment, that kind of loyalty.
You're right, Jack.
It wasn't fair of me to put all this on you,
to blame you for what happened to Audrey.
I know the sacrifices you've made.
I know this country owes you
more than it'll ever repay.
I'm not interested in what you think
this country owes me.
I want my life back, and I want it now.
Audrey's all I've got, and you can't stop me.
In case you've forgotten,
I'm very good at disappearing.
And if you try sending someone after us,
I'll kill 'em.
Pretty good at that too.
Simply getting your life back, Jack,
isn't gonna change who you are.
And you can't walk away from it.
You know that. You've tried it.
Sooner or later,
you're gonna get back in the game,
and my daughter's gonna pay the price,
like your wife did.
- You son of a bitch.
- Jack.
I beg you, just stop for a moment and think.
Think, Jack.
You won't be able to take care of her
the way you want to.
Where is she?
Take me to her now.
Hey.
It's me. I'm here.
I know that I promised...
to take care of you,
and protect you,
but I'm at a crossroads.
Right now, the best way...
the only way...
to do that is to let you go.
I hope one day you can understand that.
I hope one day you can forgive me.
I love you with all my heart.
I always will.
Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net