Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net
- Marilyn.
- Jack. What happened?
My father escaped. I don't know where he is.
I want you both to go back to CTU.
Josh, I know there's a lot to explain,
and when this is over
you and I are gonna sit down
and I will talk you through what happened.
Thank you for saving my son.
He reminds me of you.
I told you I was sorry.
(Morris) You said I should
stop helping terrorists arm nuclear bombs.
We're done.
(Cheng) I've interfaced the component.
There's a problem.
The circuit board is damaged.
- Can you fix it?
- No, not unless I have the security override.
We don't have access to that information.
You will have to find someone
who has the necessary expertise.
An FB-sub-circuit board
from one of the weapons
is now in the possession
of an agent of the Chinese government.
If you do not intercept this component,
my generals have instructions
to initiate an appropriate response.
How did the Russians find out?
Only select people at the White House
even knew about this.
You're saying there's a spy?
Which staffer are we talking about here, Tom?
(Lennox) Lisa Miller, sir.
Bishop's been passing intelligence
to the Russians that he got from you.
I swear to you, I didn't know.
It's still treason.
You're gonna go back to your boyfriend,
and you're gonna make him believe
that we have the component back.
White House is pressuring us to find Cheng.
We have to hope we can
get some information out of her.
It'll be impossible to communicate in the near
term unless we shock her out of this state.
Mike. Will they let me speak to Audrey?
(Doyle) The shrink doesn't think
it's a good idea.
He's about to try protocol of his own
using big doses of drugs.
- It could kill her, Jack.
- Why did you uncuff me?
Cos I think you need
to do something about it.
Is there anything you can tell me to help us
find Cheng, or where they were holding you?
Please.
Jack, put your gun down.
Not until I get a guarantee from you
that Audrey is safe.
(Audrey) Bloomfield.
- (Jack) What'd you say?
- Bloomfield.
Morris, did you get that? Have Chloe
track it down. Keep Doyle in the loop.
Earlier I got through to Audrey.
I can do the same thing again.
I just need some time. Please.
Stay away from my daughter.
Everything you touch,
one way or another, ends up dead.
Jack.
I thought you should know
James Hellerjust left with his daughter.
He also reiterated to me
his demand that you stay away from her.
He'll be filing a restraining order to that effect.
I'm sorry, Jack.
The name that Audrey gave us when I was
talking to her - Bloomfield. Did it pan out?
It did. It's an old copper refining facility
in Jefferson Heights.
We found copper particles
on Audrey's clothing
so we think
that's where Cheng was holding her.
If that's his base he should have the Russian
component there so we're locking it down
- and dispatching teams now.
- Let me go with them.
- You're still under arrest, Jack.
- For 20 months Cheng tried to break me.
I know him. I know how he thinks.
I am your best chance at stopping him.
You wilfully disobeyed an order. Your actions
resulted in Cheng getting that component.
That's why I'm begging you to let me go.
I caused this mess. Let me clean it up.
Please. Dammit, Nadia,
you have the authority to let me do this.
This isn't about finding that component
but revenge against Cheng.
Cheng is responsible for Audrey's condition.
You're damn right.
I want Cheng more than anything
in the world.
But I gave President Palmer my word
that I would destroy that component
before I let it fall into enemy hands.
Please,
give me a chance to keep my word.
I'm sorry, Jack. I can't.
Don't even think about it, Jack. If you make
a move I will have you put in restraints.
Maybe I could help from here.
I- I could run tactical.
Division are sending over
a ranking section chief to replace me.
I promise you I will take it up with him
when he gets here.
OK, thanks.
I've a land-sat image of Bloomfield.
It's a big place.
There's Cheng's Hummer at the rear entrance.
- Put it over to tactical.
- It's already happening.
- Status update on LAPD?
- Reserve units are on their way.
They should have a perimeter in 20 minutes.
- Are you OK?
- Fine.
- You don't look fine.
- Chloe and I have split up.
- Shut up, Morris.
- Well, it's pointless being coy about it, right?
We're still doing ourjobs. We're all
professionals. If I were you, I'd stay out of it.
I will.
These are the transcripts
from Marilyn's statement.
- (Milo) All right, thanks.
- I'll take care of it.
Wheels are rolling in five minutes.
Listen up. Your objective is the Bloomfield
copper facility in Jefferson Heights.
We believe this is Cheng's safe house
and he has the component in his possession.
LAPD is setting up a five-block perimeter.
Yourjob is to penetrate the facility,
apprehend Cheng
and secure the component.
If Cheng gets out of the country
with that component
Russia will hold us responsible for providing
the Chinese access to their defence codes
and they'll strike back at us.
We need to recover that component.
There is no room for error.
Real-time tactical feeds and satellite recon
will be uplinked to your PDAs.
Any questions?
Good luck.
You're doing a good job.
- Just trying to keep the roof from caving in.
- We're putting every available agent out.
If Cheng is in that facility,
we're going to get him and the component.
Be careful.
(speaks Chinese)
Zhou.
Do you have the data?
- It's about time.
- We have to finalise our attack plan.
I want to attack the target in 15 minutes.
We'll be ready.
(speaks Chinese)
(TV)... authorities throughout Los Angeles
are scrambling to deal with the devastation
caused by the nuclear detonation
and its aftermath.
- Local hospitals report being overwhelmed...
- Josh.
You gotta stop watching this
and try and get some sleep.
They're saying that 12,000 people are dead,
all because of what Dad did.
Honey, it's not that simple.
- The terrorists were responsible...
- But he was involved.
He let it happen.
- I wish I was never even born.
- Don't say that.
Why? That's how I feel.
I wish I was never part of this sick family.
You listen to me. Listen to me.
You are not your father.
You are not responsible for anything he did.
Come here.
I love you. I do.
We're gonna be OK.
I promise you we'll get through this.
- We've been here for hours. I wanna go home.
- We'll go home in the morning.
Right now, I want you to close your eyes
and get some sleep.
OK? Come on. Lie down.
- Sorry to interrupt.
- That's OK.
This is a transcript of your statement.
I need you to review it.
All right.
- Mrs Bauer?
- Please, call me Marilyn.
I know you and Jack are close.
There's something you need to know.
- What is it?
- It's about Audrey Raines.
She's still alive.
What?
(phone rings)
- Hello.
- It's me.
Hey, you. I thought I wouldn't
hear from you again till morning.
Sorry I left so suddenly.
We had a crisis with the Russians.
What kind of crisis?
It doesn't matter any more. It's been averted.
Well, that's good.
Anyway, I was thinking maybe we could
pick up where we left off, if you want.
(sighs)
Well, I do, sweetheart, but isn't Daniels
gonna want you to stick around
so he can paw you every chance he gets?
I'm the last thing on his mind right now.
Well, his loss. How soon can you get here?
I'm on my way.
I love you.
I love you, too. I'll see you soon.
All right. That sounded, uh... genuine enough.
Now, when you go back to Mr Bishop you will
find a way to excuse yourself from the room
to allow him time to access your PDA.
We've uploaded memos
stating that a Chinese agent tried to smuggle
Russian technology out of the country
and was taken out in a military strike.
Do you understand?
You want the Russians to think
the component was destroyed.
That's correct. It's up to you now.
If you can feed all this convincingly to Bishop
he will relay it to his Russian contact
and with any luck at all,
President Suvarov will call off
his threat of military action against us,
at least for the time being.
I'm sorry. I just don't know
if I can go through with this,
if I can be with him again
and act like nothing's wrong.
(snorts)
Well, I'm sure you'll manage.
For the last year
you've had no problem lying to me.
Agent Hollister and I will be in a van
parked across the street from Bishop's.
We'll be monitoring everything. You do
as you're told and it should all go smoothly.
Marilyn, what are you doing here?
You should be with Josh.
I had to see if you were all right.
I'm fine. I don't think the charges will stand up
given the extenuating circumstances.
I meant... I meant about Audrey.
I'm so sorry, Jack.
I feel awful telling you she was dead.
- You didn't know. No one knew.
- But still...
I heard the Chinese caused her to have
some kind of psychological breakdown.
- Is she going to be all right?
- I don't know.
- What do her doctors say?
- It's out of my hands.
What do you mean, it's out of your hands?
Her father Secretary Heller
has already taken her away from here.
I've been ordered to stay away from her.
- How could he do that? You saved her life.
- Marilyn, please.
I don't wanna talk about this.
Ms Yassir told us that Josh and I don't need
to be in CTU custody any more.
- They'll process us out in the morning.
- Good.
I'd like to bring Josh by to see you
before we go.
That'll be fine.
Jack.
Whatever happens, when all this is over
I want you to know...
I'll be there for you.
Thank you.
Mrs Bauer.
Marilyn, you really should go.
Chloe.
Any word on Cheng?
Doyle's leading a team
to Bloomfield right now.
- Please keep me informed.
- Jack, we'll get Cheng and the component.
There's only one entrance point.
Yes, but that will put you
in an optimal position for a quick strike.
Ryan, take your team around back.
The rest of you, follow me.
This isn't going to be bloodless, Cheng.
People are going to die.
You do what you need to do.
Doyle's team is moving into Bloomfield now.
Your objective isn't to cause casualties.
Your objective is to obtain the package.
Nothing else takes precedence.
I understand.
Let's move.
We'll access the sewer lines from here.
Once below ground
it's roughly 180m to the target.
All right?
Let's move.
Don't let me down.
- Clear.
- Anything?
- No, there's nobody here.
But you have to see this.
We have empty rifle magazines,
stun grenades, C4.
Look. This is an arsenal.
- See if you can find anything else.
- Yes, sir.
- (phone rings)
- O'Brian.
- (Doyle) Chloe, put Nadia on.
- Nadia, it's Doyle.
- Go ahead, Mike.
- Cheng's not here.
Bloomfield's been evacuated. I guess they got
out before we could lock down the perimeter.
Check satellite feed.
Try to back-time the frames.
And we found a whole bunch
of empty weapon crates.
- What kind?
- Large-calibre rifles.
Military-grade C4, grenades...
Enough of an arsenal for a small army.
It looks like the Chinese were planning
to launch a major assault.
Assault on what?
(beeping)
- We're at the junction.
- Good. Head east 153m.
That will put you directly beneath
CTU and the entrance point.
Scanning these satellite images, I'm getting
a lot of dropped data fields in sector eight.
Chloe.
- I heard you.
- Do you know what might be causing it?
I'm practically blind here.
You know that patch we downloaded
from the USGS subnet?
It conflicts with the imaging software.
Deactivate it.
Thank you. That's all I needed.
Morris.
I know you're trying
to be professional about everything.
I'm sorry. I'm really having a hard time
with what happened between us.
You've nothing to apologise for, darling.
You broke up with me because
I said something stupid I didn't mean.
About me arming nukes and being a coward?
That wasn't stupid.
- It was the truth.
- I don't believe that.
- You were right whether you admit it or not.
- You're saying what I think doesn't matter?
No. I'm saying that I didn't break up with you
because of what you said.
I broke up with you because of what I did.
No matter how much you think you love me,
I know there'll always be that knowledge
and you won't be able to get past it.
- You're wrong.
- You know me better than anyone, right?
Yeah.
When am I ever wrong?
As soon as you're in you will create an
opportunity for Bishop to access your PDA.
Is something wrong?
- I'm frightened.
- You should be.
If this doesn't work
you will be facing treason charges.
- I've cooperated fully.
- Great. You can testify to that at your trial.
So, get a grip here.
You will do whatever is necessary to assure
Bishop nothing has changed between you.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
- Let's get the car up here.
- The surveillance camera's all set in the bag.
It's all yours.
All right. Let's button things up here.
- (phone rings)
- Yes.
She's on her way inside, sir.
- Are you sure she can pull this off?
- Let's hope so, sir.
I appreciate what you're doing. I know this
doesn't... fall under yourjob description.
We're all doing some improvising today,
aren't we, sir?
We both agreed it is in our interest
to keep this circle small.
(sighs)
Hey.
Hi.
You OK?
- Of course. Why?
- (Bishop) You seem... I don't know... tense.
Oh, Mark, come on.
After everything that's happened, who isn't?
All right.
Well, maybe I can loosen you up.
(laughs)
How's that? Better?
Yeah.
You know, I'm...
I'm gonna freshen up first.
Relax.
We already had a shower, remember?
I'm really happy you came back.
The more time I spend away from you,
the harder it is to let you walk out the door.
I may have to strap you to the bed...
permanently.
Go on, just get out of the room.
Leave him alone with the PDA.
- I bet you'd like that.
- Mm.
You know, I'm sorry.
I'm just feeling really grungy.
The situation at the White House
has me stressed. I'll be right back.
I thought you said that crisis was averted.
It was.
Then you should feel relieved.
Well, you know me.
I'm always worried the next crisis
is around the corner.
I think I know how to take your mind off of it.
Come on.
Hold on.
We're here. Set the charges.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah. Charges have been set.
Stand by. Input the code.
It worked. We're in.
Tying us into their security system.
Overriding their comm.
We'll go in sectors.
Two minutes until everything is shut down.
Escape factors from Bloomfield. We analysed
every route from the facility - over 20.
So they could be anywhere in the city.
Morris and Chloe are back-timing
the satellite. Hopefully they'll get a fix.
- All right. Keep me posted.
- Have we heard anything from Doyle?
His team's halfway through the forensic
sweep but they haven't found anything so far.
- What?
- Never mind.
I saw the look that you gave me
when I was talking to Doyle.
(sighs)
I understand if your feelings
for me have changed.
- Milo...
- Yes, I... I was hurt, but...
If there's something going on
between you and Doyle, I just...
I want you to know that it's, uh...
it's OK.
Milo, to be completely honest
I don't know what I feel.
So much has happened today,
I haven't had a chance to...
I haven't had a chance
to think through anything.
- I just need some time to sort it all out.
- Nadia...
- Nadia, I've got something.
- What is it?
This is from about 50 minutes ago.
I've checked the frames before and after.
(Milo) So they got out
before Doyle's team arrived.
Give LAPD a description of the vehicles.
Chloe, see if we can figure out
where those vehicles were headed.
- Charge is set.
- All right. Clear out.
- Doyle.
- (static)
Doyle.
CTU to field unit Bravo. Come in.
- I can't get an outside line.
- Yeah, I can't reach Doyle. Comm's down too.
- Could be a hiccup in the server.
- Check it.
- (phone rings)
- Pressman.
I don't know what the hell is happening.
I can't access any of the servers.
The permissions have all been reset.
(speaks Chinese)
I've got a visual on the SUV and the van.
Cheng was heading south on the 110.
They exit at Florence, heading east.
That's six blocks from here.
That was security.
They just lost visual surveillance.
- What are you talking about?
- Every one of our security cameras.
They all just went out at once.
Chloe, Code Red emergency lockdown.
(alarm)
This is Nadia. Code Red is confirmed.
Lock this place down.
- Right away.
- (door opens)
- (banging)
- (gunfire)
Everyone, get to your assigned
safe rooms now! Go! Get moving!
(gunfire)
(man speaks Chinese)
- Flood the outer sectors with tear gas.
- I can't get into the system. We're paralysed.
(gunfire)
(man) Move it!
Base one, come in.
Listen. CTU is under attack.
You need to open the door now.
Base one, come in. Base one, come in.
Everyone on the floor!
I can hear them. They're in sector three.
They're coming this way. Let me out!
- No one's responding.
- We need to get up to the lounge.
There are civilians there. I need a weapon.
Cellphones! Throw them in front of you!
Head count. Check the roster.
Set up the comm unit. Filter all
communication and turn off the alarm.
Who's in command?
Who is in command?
I am.
Milo Pressman.
I'm acting director of CTU.
Come here.
- You! Come on!
- Face forward.
In line. Keep going.
Get down. Get down.
(speaks Chinese)
- Hello?
- (static)
- Phones are dead.
- What's going on?
I don't know.
Josh, look out! Help me push this
against the door. Hurry, Josh!
Open the door!
On the floor! Now!
We found Bauer. The boy's with his mother.
- (Zhou) Good. Bring them here.
- On our way. All right, get up!
Leave my son alone.
Where are you taking us?
(screams)
- Are you all right?
- Yes. Jack, what do they want with Josh?
- What do you mean?
- They came here to get him.
- Are you sure they came for Josh?
- That's what they said. Yes.
We gotta get outta here. Come on.
Stay close. Come on.
Shut the door.
Come here. Josh, I want you to climb up here
and crawl through the air duct.
- Go!
- I'm not leaving you!
Josh, you're not leaving anyone behind. We'll
be following you. We'll be right behind you.
He's out of ammo. Let's go!
Put your weapon down on the ground now!
I'm putting the weapon down.
I'm putting it down.
Both of you, get on your knees!
- We have a problem.
- What is it?
The boy got away.
He's inside one of the ventilation ducts.
We have the boy's mother and Jack Bauer.
- Send the woman and Bauer to me. You wait.
- (speaks Chinese)
Get up! Let's go, let's go!
Cut power to the ventilation system. Tie me
into the PA system. I wanna talk to the boy.
Cheng, the boy's escaped.
We've captured his mother and Jack Bauer.
Get the boy back.
I don't care what you have to do!
Zhou.
We're getting another call from Agent Doyle.
I think we need to respond.
Nadia Yassir.
Nadia Yassir, stand up!
Come here.
According to that roster,
you were the ranking officer here.
Are you?
Are you the ranking officer?
Yes.
One of your men has been calling.
Answer him. Tell him you had a problem
with your communication system.
If you try to warn him,
I will kill everyone here,
starting with you.
Do you understand me?
Come on.
Answer it.
Nadia.
- It's Mike. I've been trying to get hold of you.
- We've had a problem with comm.
- What kind of problem?
- It's sorted out now.
My team hasn't picked up any leads
on Cheng. Were you able to get a visual?
- Not yet.
- What is taking so long?
All you had to do was reposition
satellite surveillance.
Mike, we're working as fast as we can, OK?
What else do you want me to do?
When we get a visual on Cheng's vehicles
I'll let you know.
All right. Thanks.
Now go sit back down.
(man) Move. Quick.
Bring her over here.
What do you want with him? Who sent you?
You don't ask the questions.
If he makes another move, shoot him.
Activate the PA.
Josh, I want you to listen to me very carefully.
I know you're scared and I don't blame you,
but you really don't have to be.
The truth is we're not going to hurt you.
We're going to take you to a safe place.
- That's all I can tell you right now.
- Leave him alone! Josh!
I know you heard that, Josh.
Your mother's here with us.
She's OK - for now.
I don't wanna hurt her, Josh.
There's been enough bloodshed today.
Show yourself to one of my men.
If you do, nothing will happen to your mother.
If you don't, I'll shoot her.
She'll die for nothing, because one way
or another we're going to find you,
even if we have to tear this building apart.
So I'm asking you to save your mother's life.
I'm going to give you ten seconds.
If you don't show yourself by the time
I've finished counting, she dies.
One.
Two.
Three.
Four.
Five.
Six.
Seven.
Eight. Nine.
- (Josh) Please, wait! Wait!
- (man) I can hear him. He's coming right now.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on, let's go.
I got him. We're coming to you.
Cheng.
- We have the boy.
- Good work.
Bring him to me right away.
- Put her with the others.
- (whimpers)
- Take him with the others.
- Mom!
- Josh!
- Sit down!
The operation was successful.
My men have your grandson.
- How is he?
- Under stress.
A little emotional but physically unharmed.
- Is his mother alive?
- Yes. So is your son Jack.
- You have any trouble?
- None to speak of.
Your codes gave us full access to CTU. Have
you finished repairing the sub-circuit board?
Almost. I'll return it
when you bring me my grandson.
We will meet at the rendezvous point
in 20 minutes.
It'll be waiting.
- Call me when I can talk to the boy.
- Will do.
Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net