- What's going on?
- What do you mean?
I'm your brother.
Whatever it is, you can tell me.
- It's all right. Really.
- OK.
One more chapter
and we'll take a break.
David.
Get help!
Whoever did this, I want them dead
or in custody when the Russians get here.
I would ask that you consider postponing
the signing of the treaty.
No. Absolutely not.
I think that David was killed because of
something he was about to tell me.
He said that it concerned national security
and that it involved you.
Is she all right?
No, she's not all right.
She's having another one of her delusions.
- What is this? An interrogation?
- I just don't like being lied to.
No one's lying to you, Derek.
I'm not hungry.
Sorry.
You don't owe me an explanation.
If you had wanted to tell me
about your past, you would have.
Yeah?
Jack, I know this isn't protocol.
Please don't hang up on me. I need your help.
They got Tony and Michelle. She's dead.
Tony's critical. They're gonna kill me.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry I followed you.
I'm just... I'm just worried about my mother.
You're going with me.
Hold your fire, Chloe!
Palmer was the primary target.
To set you up.
Make it look like you did it.
- You're the one that killed Palmer.
- Yeah.
The president's retreat is vulnerable. You
need to post two more people here at Delta.
- It's a likely point of infiltration.
- I'll pull assets from somewhere else.
- Marcy, hi. Can you give me the figures?
- 167...
- Excuse me. Sorry to interrupt.
- What is it, Edgar?
We have a visual on the suspect.
He may be the Palmer shooter.
- Were you able to make an ID?
- I think you should see for yourself.
About an hour before
President Palmer was shot,
someone broke into the building
the sniper used.
We have a frame grab from a security video.
I ran it through a high-res filter,
so it may take a few seconds to render.
Audrey.
What is going on here, Jack?
They're setting me up
for Palmer's assassination.
- Palmer's not even president. Why kill him?
- I don't know.
You need to get
as far away from here as you can.
No, I need to find out
who really killed President Palmer.
How are you gonna do that?
Start at the beginning,
investigate the original crime scene.
David Palmer was visiting his brother. Maybe
he left something there that can help me.
Palmer was killed an hour ago.
The place will be crawling with
Secret Service, FBI, police.
I need schematics
and an interagency deployment grid.
Can you get that for me or not?
Yeah. I should be able
to log on remotely from the site.
OK. Come on. Let's go.
How could you kill that guy?
I'm sorry you had to see that, Derek.
Get in the van.
I'm not going anywhere with you.
You're gonna do exactly what I tell you.
Let go of me!
Let's get something straight, kid.
The only reason you're still conscious
is because I don't wanna carry you. Get in.
Analysis indicates
the video hasn't been doctored.
Jack was in the building the sniper fired
from at the time Palmer was assassinated.
That's impossible.
This whole thing is impossible.
Bill, you were there when Jack was shot.
He had no pulse, no vitals.
And I have no idea how Jack staged
his own death. But I understand his reasons.
He was to be handed to the Chinese
to spend his life in prison.
Yeah, but none of that explains
why Jack would want to kill David Palmer.
I had Curtis pull the phone logs.
Palmer, Tony and Michelle were all talking
to Jack right before he was supposedly killed.
Our working theory is that they conspired
to help Jack fake his own death.
Now you're saying that Jack was behind
the attack on Tony and Michelle too?
Why would Jack want to kill
the people who helped him?
He may have stopped trusting them
to keep his secret.
Jack would never murder his friends.
Audrey.
I don't wanna believe Jack did this either.
But right now it's the best explanation
for the evidence we have.
I'm sorry.
- The White House needs to know.
- I'll call the president.
Thanks.
Bill.
What is it, Curtis?
I had Adamson run data recovery
on Tony's phone records.
Chloe was on those calls
with President Palmer and Tony.
Chloe knew Jack was alive?
Apparently.
I called her in an hour ago.
She should be here.
I've been calling her,
but she's not answering.
I wanted to run a locate,
but Spenser talked me out of it.
- If anything happens to her, it's your fault.
- Stop.
Have Adamson track her cell.
We need to get to her before Jack does.
Put out an interagency alert.
Bauer's now the prime suspect
in Palmer's assassination.
Emphasise that he's a former agent and
should be considered extremely dangerous.
Excuse me, sir.
What is it, Walt?
Mrs Logan called again.
I can't keep stalling her about this Palmer call.
Why would he call my wife
about a national security threat?
That's what she says he wanted to talk to her
about - "a matter of national security. "
- Maybe if I investigated the phone call.
- Stay focused on the summit.
I am, sir. Which is why we can't risk having
Mrs Logan obsess about this phone call.
Showing her the truth might help her
get on with her responsibilities.
So what are you suggesting?
If Palmer called her yesterday, our office
will have a recording of their conversation.
- Get that for me.
- Yes, sir.
And Walt?
Thank you for doing this.
Mr President,
Audrey Raines is holding on line three.
Ms Raines, President Logan.
You're also on with Walt Cummings.
Sir, CTU has a suspect
in the assassination of President Palmer.
Good.
Who is it?
Ms Raines?
It's Jack Bauer, sir.
- Bauer is dead.
- We've all been living under that assumption.
I don't understand.
What makes you think it's Bauer?
CTU has verified surveillance video
placing Jack Bauer
at the same time in the same building
as the sniper who killed President Palmer.
Audrey, this is Walt Cummings.
Let me get clear on this. Are you saying
that Bauer shot David Palmer?
We're proceeding under that assumption.
Why? For what possible reason?
David Palmer might have known
Bauer was alive,
knowledge he shared with three CTU agents,
all of whom were targeted in the last hour.
He does have a history of insubordination,
irrational behaviour, addiction.
Jack Bauer has a history of
great service to this country.
How does this affect the summit?
We're recommending that you delay
or reschedule until Jack is apprehended.
Ms Raines, you have a suspect. Find him.
Yes, sir.
Sir. President Suvarov
arrives within the hour.
Should we inform his security chief
that he's a potential target?
No.
I want this information limited to those who
are involved in the manhunt for Jack Bauer.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir.
I found Haas.
- He and his men are all dead.
- How did this happen?
I'm not sure. The last time I spoke to Haas,
he was about to move on Bauer.
Any sign of Bauer now?
No. I'll dispatch a team and track him.
We'll have him in 24 hours.
No. Let CTU find Bauer. Once they have him
in custody, we'll take him out.
Bauer won't impede the operation?
He won't have a chance.
We launch in less than an hour.
Their hardware's military spec. Fragmentation
grenades, percussion grenades.
There's a comm unit we can use.
Who are these people?
- Yeah?
- Frank. Please tell me what's going on.
Diane, I know it's hard, but please try not
to worry. Derek is fine. Where are you now?
Um... I'm about a half-hour outside of LA.
- Just tell me where to meet you.
- I don't know yet.
Head towards the city.
I'll get back to you when I can.
- Can I talk to him?
- Of course. Hold on.
It's your mother. Talk to her.
- Mom?
- Derek?
Are you OK?
- I'm all right.
- Are you sure?
- We're about a block away.
- Who was that?
- Say goodbye to your mother.
- I have to hang up now, Mom.
- Don't worry. I'm fine.
- Derek, I love you.
Yeah, me too.
Give me the phone. Get to the back of the van.
Go!
While security agencies are remaining
hushed, speculation begins to grow.
We're told that that speculation
will not be addressed
because the government says
security is of utmost importance.
Behind me is the Los Angeles
apartment building
where President Palmer was
assassinated a little more than an hour ago.
- You can also see Americans of all ages...
- Pull up, please.
Credentials?
All right. Go on through.
Let her through.
We're clear.
Come on up front.
Hold the light on the bag.
Can you get a wireless access point?
I'm reading the agents' transponders. I can
track their locations to within three feet.
Jack, there are 167 agents
in and around the location,
25 of them
in Wayne Palmer's apartment alone.
I know. That's why we'd better hope that this
is the last place they're gonna look for me.
Testing, one, two.
Testing, one, two, three. OK.
This is a field ops communication unit.
Just put it in your ear and we're set to go.
Derek, put out the light.
Officer. I live here. I was told that I needed to
check with one of the agents to get clearance.
- Can you help with that?
- All right, let me check.
- What...?
- Relax. He's really good at this.
Are you sure he's OK?
Yeah.
I think.
- Chloe, do you copy?
- Yeah.
Wayne Palmer's apartment is the penthouse.
I'm going up now.
There are four agents waiting at the lobby.
Hold off on going up if you can.
Too late.
at the time of the assassination
and assemble at a secure location.
They need to be confiscated
for frame-by-frame analysis downtown.
I'm entering the apartment.
Most of the agents are in the living
room. That must be where Palmer was shot.
There are two rooms to the north, 15 feet,
probably bedrooms. They're clear. No agents.
This first room is a study.
- Let me know if anyone comes this way.
- Will do, Jack.
You keep calling him Jack.
He told my mother and I his name's Frank.
Who is he really?
Jack Bauer. Until a year and a half ago
he worked for the government.
Is that why we're
where the president was killed?
Please don't ask me any more questions.
Can't you at least tell me why
he had to pretend he was someone else?
Certain people thought the best way to
cover up their mistakes was to get rid of Jack.
You mean kill him?
Yes.
Jack gave up everything and everyone
in his life, including his daughter.
He has a daughter?
- I've already told you more than I should've.
- I have a computer in the study booted up.
President Palmer had a user account.
- Is it password secured?
- No.
Only one of the files is encrypted.
That's where we'll look.
Give me the computer's IP address.
I'll upload a decryption program to it.
Hold on.
292.162.12.2.
- Someone's at the door.
- Not according to the deployment grid.
- Do not raise your voice.
- You son of a bitch. You killed my brother.
Mr Palmer, you know I didn't do that.
Any evidence they showed you
against me has been fabricated.
I served your brother for years.
I would have gladly given my life for his.
He was my friend.
The only reason that I am here is to try and
figure out why and how he was assassinated.
- I was hoping to find clues on that computer.
- Why don't you ask Secret Service to help?
I'm being set up. Whoever's behind this
has planted evidence making me the shooter.
It's useless to try to convince the authorities.
And you think you'll convince me?
If I killed your brother, why didn't I kill you
when you walked through the door?
Think about this, Wayne.
Why would I be here?
Please. I need your help.
Jack, how do you expect me to believe you
under these circumstances?
- Take the gun.
- Jack, what are you doing?
Take the gun.
... after two terms in the house
and one in the senate,
David Palmer was elected president
with a 60% plurality.
Here you are, Mrs Logan.
David and I first got to know each other
when he was elected to Congress.
He and Charles
never saw eye to eye politically.
David never let that
get in the way of our friendship.
Oh... That picture's
from his inauguration.
At the ball, I was one of the first people
David asked to dance.
- We need a few more minutes with your hair.
- I know. I can do it myself.
- I'm just trying to help.
- Oh, I'm sorry, Evelyn. I know. I'm sorry.
Mrs Logan. May I... have a word?
Of course.
The president asked me
to look into the call from David Palmer.
I was beginning to think
you were ignoring me.
- So when did this call take place?
- Last night.
It woke me up. I had fallen asleep watching
the news, so somewhere between 10 and 11.
I'll have someone pull up the call
from the audio archives.
Walt.
He doesn't believe me, does he? Charles.
He thinks I'm making the whole thing up.
- I wouldn't say that, Mrs Logan.
- Well, of course you wouldn't say it.
- Mrs Logan...
- Walt, you can go now.
Did your brother say or do anything
out of the ordinary before he was shot?
He'd been distracted
ever since he came to Los Angeles.
I finally called him on it this morning.
What'd he say?
He never had the chance
to say anything, Jack.
The decryption's done. You can open the file.
OK, I'm going into it now.
That's the first chapter of his memoir. It
makes no sense. Why would he encrypt that?
- There are print-outs of it all over the place.
- Maybe he hid some information in it.
We'll compare this to the print-out,
see if he added or changed anything.
I've got one right here.
No...
- You haven't sent the file allocations. Why?
- I need a higher-level access code.
- If you're upset about me and Chloe...
- I don't care.
If you hadn't left her on her own,
maybe she'd be OK now.
Don't you think I know that?
Look, you're just making it harder
for me to do my job.
Use Chloe's access code. JJ72.
You won't get firewalled with it.
Thank you.
SYSTEM ERROR
- Edgar.
- What?
This is weird. I tried logging in
under Chloe's access code.
The system says I'm already signed in.
Let me see.
- Chloe's logged in remotely.
- Are you sure it's her?
Yes. See the way the traffic's
redirected to an external socket?
Even I don't know how to do that.
Then she's alive.
Buchanan.
- Sir, it's Edgar. I think we can find Chloe.
- How?
She's accessing our system to a laptop.
I'm running a locate now.
- What's she using the system to do?
- All I can see from here
is she's tracking Secret Service
and FBI deployments.
The locate came back.
She's at Wayne Palmer's building.
Signal's faint.
She could be in a garage under the building.
Let me know if she changes location.
Why would Chloe be at the scene
of Palmer's murder tracking agents?
She wouldn't be.
Unless someone was forcing her.
What do you mean?
Maybe Jack left evidence he needs to erase.
Surrounded by all those agents?
Jack can explain when we apprehend him.
Bill Buchanan at CTU. I need to speak to
the Secret Service field director immediately.
- Yes?
- Have you left yet?
We were delayed.
We're still loading the truck.
- You should be on your way.
- We'll be there in 20 minutes, as planned.
Call me when you're approaching.
Wait. Stop, stop. Right there. He added
something in the middle of a sentence.
A... a name and an address. There.
Chevensky - 16 Transport Way.
Did you get that? It looks like an address.
Yes. Transport Way is a street
at the Ontario airport.
Check all flights into Ontario.
Look for a passenger Chevensky.
Try and make the connection.
Jack, Secret Service
is changing its deployment.
How?
A lot of agents are moving into the building.
I'm on my way down.
They know that I'm here.
- Let me help you get out of here, Jack.
- No. You can't risk being connected to me.
And until we know who to trust, you can't tell
anybody what we found. Do you understand?
I'm gonna do everything I can
to find out who did this to your brother.
I'll be in touch.
Chloe, I need another way out of here.
Checking.
Across the hall, through the kitchen.
One agent at the door.
Copy that.
I'm in the elevator. Where are they
concentrating their agents?
They cut off access to my grid. I don't know
where the agents are. They were in the lobby.
I'm getting out on the second floor.
Come on, Jack.
- What'd you get for me on Chevensky?
- He's a baggage supervisor at the airport.
Jack Bauer!
Agent O'Brian!
The perimeter is sealed. There is no way out.
Step into view with your hands in the air.
We know you're down here.
We got a visual!
Do not shoot! We need them alive!
No one fire!
Don't fire!
- Do not fire!
- Get out of the vehicle.
Step out of the vehicle.
Check the back. Get the side.
Step to your left. Get down on your knees.
Cuff her.
Open the back.
Bauer's not here. Secure the area.
Get in. Give me my bag.
Come on.
Got it.
Frank?
Yeah, it's me. Listen, Derek is all right.
I just need to know where you are.
I'm, uh, on the 210 at the 10.
OK, I want you to take the 10 east
to the Ontario airport.
Go to the parking lot in front of the terminal.
I'll meet you on the west side of it.
Understand?
Yeah. Yeah.
Diane, listen to me.
I am so sorry that I got you involved in this.
But it's gonna be all right.
I'll be there in a few minutes.
OK.
OK, thanks.
This is Agent Jennings.
There's no sign of Jack Bauer yet, but we've
apprehended your agent Chloe O'Brian.
She tried to escape our agents
and leave the building.
- You're telling me she wasn't under duress?
- Not as far as I can tell.
Put her on the phone.
Uncuff her.
Bill Buchanan wants to talk to you.
- Hi.
- Chloe, what the hell's going on?
Jack's being framed to cover up
the real reason Palmer was assassinated.
- Says Jack?
- Says the man who killed Palmer.
I heard his dying confession.
You'll find his body
at the refinery at Variel and Topanga.
Do you have evidence
that Palmer's death is to do with the summit?
- No. Jack's trying to figure that out.
- How? Where is he?
- I can't tell you.
- Why not?
I don't think you believe him.
You're trying to arrest him.
Chloe, I'm not gonna ask you again.
I'm ordering you to tell me where Jack is.
I'm sorry. I'd like to tell you but I can't.
Chloe!
- Sir.
- Bring her back to CTU.
Curtis, take a team to the refinery.
Edgar, make sure Chloe goes into
a holding cell when she gets back.
That woman, Chloe...
she told me some stuff
about what you used to do.
Yeah, well, she shouldn't have.
Why did you have to lie?
Couldn't you have just told us the truth?
First of all, you have to understand I never
thought anything like this could ever happen.
After your mother rented me that room,
I started to remember what it was like
to have a family.
How nice it was.
I started to believe that a guy like me
could actually get a second chance.
I know you don't believe this now...
but I really do care about you.
And I care about your mother.
I hope one day you can understand that.
Charles.
- Evelyn said you wanted to talk to me.
- I do.
Did Walt find the tape of the phone call?
I told him approximately when it took place.
- Why don't we sit down?
- I don't want to sit down.
All right.
Don't be concerned
that there's any connection
between David's death
and the phone call he made to you.
He said it was a matter of national security.
Those were his exact words.
- There's got to be a connection, of course.
- There isn't.
David was killed by
an unstable ex-CTU agent.
This was not a conspiracy, this was
one man acting out some kind of grudge.
Did you hear the call?
Can we just drop this?
Did you or didn't you hear it?
- Hello?
- Martha, it's David Palmer. Did I wake you?
No, no, David. Not at all. What's going on?
I need to talk to you.
It's hardly a matter of national security,
but I'm hosting a charity dinner next month
for the Art In Action programme.
- No. That's not what he said. No, that's not it.
- I would like you to be there.
No, that is not it. That is not it.
Charles, that's not it. Let me...
Martha, listen!
- We'll talk more in the morning, then.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
- Send the president my best.
- No. That's not what he said.
- Yes, it is.
No, that is a trick.
- I am not crazy.
- Listen to me.
- I know what I heard!
- Martha! Martha! Listen to me.
I spoke to Dr Hill.
He said if you are not consistent with your
medication you can become disoriented.
Your memory can be affected.
- He said that?
- Yes.
That's why you remember
something different.
I know you don't like
how these pills make you feel,
but you need to take them.
If Jack was responsible for Palmer's death,
why would Chloe cover him?
It doesn't make sense. There's something else
going on here and we're missing it.
NSA intercepted some chatter
identifying the summit as a target.
We're sourcing it now,
but the reliability's approaching 95%.
- Time frame?
- Within the next 15 minutes.
That's when Suvarov's scheduled to land.
Logan said he won't postpone this summit.
In light of this, he may not have a choice.
- Operations.
- Put me through to Mike Novick.
Suvarov's helicopter
is leaving the air base.
- His arrival at the retreat is on schedule.
- As are we.
We'll go dark now.
No communication until after your strike.
- I will monitor your progress from here.
- Understood.
Udachi.
- Mr President?
- Yeah, Mike, what is it?
CTU has confirmed intelligence
suggesting President Suvarov's helicopter
will be targeted.
- How good is this intelligence?
- Very good. They want you to reschedule.
No. I've told them, I'm telling you.
I will not postpone this summit.
Then at least have Suvarov
alter his arrival plan.
His chopper can land at a different site.
He can come by motorcade.
The risk would be reduced.
And the impact of his arrival
would also be reduced.
The media is waiting
for a landing in five minutes.
- Mr President...
- I don't wanna hear it, Walt.
It's up to Secret Service and the air force
to protect our airspace. Make sure they do it.
There's your mom.
Hey.
I'm sorry about the way I treated you earlier.
You're a good kid.
Go get your mom.
- Mom?
- My God.
Oh!
Oh, are you OK? I was so worried.
- Things are fine.
- Are you sure?
I'm fine.
You gotta tell me right now
what the hell is going on here, Frank.
My name's not Frank. It's Jack Bauer.
I lied to you. I lied to you about a lot of things.
And I'll explain as soon as I can, but right now
you and Derek need to go to this address.
- CTU?
- Counter Terrorist Unit. I used to work there.
You need to ask for a man named
Bill Buchanan. Tell him I sent you.
I'm sorry.
I have to go.
When we get there, what do we tell him?
Tell him the truth.
- Where is the baggage claim supervisor?
- Down that hall, to the left.
DOD is giving us the all clear
on the airspace on the retreat.
... unprecedented levels of security.
The president admits Suvarov was given
an air escort of F-16 fighter jets...
- Any word from our agents on the ground?
- OK. I'm all quiet so far.
If they're going to attack the helicopter,
it's going to be now.
The helicopter touching down now.
It will be only moments
before Presidents Logan and Suvarov
will meet face to face for the first time.
There was speculation
the summit might be postponed
following the death of President Palmer,
but President Logan said the late president
would not have wanted a vital step
towards international cooperation...
Mr President. A pleasure to see you.
President Logan, smiling broadly,
extends a greeting to his Russian counterpart.
Our intel must've been wrong.
... relief that Suvarov
arrived without incident.
The ceremony will be carried live
throughout the world...
- Mom, do you see those men?
- Yeah.
That's where Jack went.
Something's wrong. I have to warn Jack.
Derek, where are you going?
Come back here. Derek, come back here!
Derek!
- Get back in your...
- Come back! I gotta get my son.
Derek! Come back here!
- Please go to your car. Get back in.
- I've gotta get my son! Derek!
Chevensky.
- Why was President Palmer killed?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
You will tell me.
It's just a question of how much it hurts.
No!
Get on the floor! Go!
Quiet!
You will not be harmed as long as
your president complies with our wishes.
Derek!
- Derek!
- Ma'am, stop.
I'm trying to find my son in there!
My son...! I have to get my son!
I have dealt with the Martha Logan situation.
- She's not going to be a problem?
- No.
I altered the tape of the phone call
before the president heard it.
There's no evidence on my end that Palmer
was trying to warn her about the attack.
Good.
The terminal and the hostages are secure.
It'll only be a matter of time
till the president is notified of the demands.