Transcript by Addic7ed.com
Sync: Brownie
This is Meredith Reed.
Ms. Reed, the people that you think are responsible
for killing President Hassan were not working alone.
They were being funded and managed by people working
inside the Russian government.
How do you know this?
I'm being set up, just like you were yesterday.
I need to get this evidence to you.
Arlo got a cell phone intercept report off NSA's Echelon.
Keywords: "Jack Bauer."
PILLAR:
We confirmed the voiceprint.
Reed's connection to Hassan means
she'd be highly motivated to help him.
Take it to the press. That's his next move.
This is a major opportunity
to make everything go away, sir:
Bauer and the evidence.
I need to find Jack...
or else they're gonna kill him.
If we can get to him, we can expose the cover-up.
- Jack's gotta be working with someone.
- Who?
I don't know. I never saw 'em, but Jack showed up with
state-of-the-art weapons and comms.
Pavel, do you see Bauer?
If you have a shot, take it.
I've got him.
Put it down.
Everything's all clear up on top, Jack.
Come with me. Do exactly what I say.
(shouting and screaming)
Move!
PILLAR:
He knew it was a trap.
The evidence is on this memory card.
Take it.
When you see it, you'll know it's real.
DANA:
The hit on Hassan is all arranged.
Bazhaev and his people are taking care of everything.
I already know that you killed Renee Walker.
What I want to know is the name of the Russian pig
inside your government that gave the order.
Where's the SIM card for your phone?
You dumb bastard, you swallowed it.
This is
for my friend.
(grunts, crunching)
MAN: You've reached the mobile number
of President Charles Logan.
ANGELA:
As a principal player in this
unprecedented and historic peace initiative,
Secretary of State Kanin's untimely decision
to withdraw for health reasons was a difficult one.
However, the president wishes it to be known
that in Secretary Kanin's absence and per his own
recommendation, she has sought and gained the counsel
of former President Charles Logan.
Now, the President
is acutely aware that this decision bears some controversy.
But President Logan's experience with foreign policy
and his skills in negotiation
have already proven to be a great asset
in these final hours before
the signing of the peace agreement
with the Islamic Republic.
Once Mrs. Hassan...
Excuse me, Mr. President.
...and the IRK delegation...
Your car to the heliport is ready and waiting downstairs.
Has, uh, President Suvarov's plane arrived yet?
It should be
touching down at JFK within the next 20
to 30 minutes, and then he'll be choppered in
to the 93rd Street Heliport.
Thank you, Ellen.
Tell them I'll be down in a moment.
Yes, sir.
ANGELA (on TV):
Once Mrs. Hassan
and the IRK delegation have hashed out a few remaining
points of protocol with President Taylor...
(phone ringing)
...the signing will commence as scheduled.
Tell me you have a lead on Bauer.
PILLAR:
I'm sorry, sir.
We tracked him to an adjacent building,
but Bauer managed to get out of the cordon,
along with the reporter Meredith Reed.
Also, he's killed Pavel.
I've taken jurisdictional control
over the scene from NYPD.
We should be able to keep this contained, but...
it's not gonna matter
if Bauer's already passed along the evidence
he got from Dana Walsh to the press.
The story's going to come out.
No, not necessarily.
We still might be able to manage this.
Look, sir, I... I know you've told me
that you're committed to seeing this through,
but you can still extricate yourself from this mess.
There's no evidence of your involvement yet.
You can still delay the press announcement.
It's too late for that, Jason.
The White House Press Secretary just announced
my role in the peace process.
There is no turning back.
And there's something else you should know.
Bauer didn't just kill Pavel.
He butchered him.
He beat him savagely, and then he eviscerated him.
I don't think Bauer's just looking
to expose the Russians' involvement
in the plot against Hassan.
This guy's out for blood.
Then you better find him and stop him, hadn't you?
Yes, sir.
Keep me posted.
I'm not going any further
till you tell me what happened back there.
You killed that man, didn't you?
Ms. Reed, your life is in danger.
You want to get through this thing alive,
you're gonna do exactly what I say.
Do you understand?
Jack, I can't get a locate
on the number you called from this cell phone.
It's restricted.
I'm gonna have to route a back trace.
Can you do it here?
No, I need the equipment at my place.
Get back to me as soon as you got a location.
- All right.
- Let's go.
Who is it you're looking for?
Someone who can give me
the names of everyone else involved.
And what are you gonna do when you find them?
- It doesn't concern you.
- How can I trust you
if you don't tell me what you're doing?
Because I'm not the person who's trying to kill you.
The video file that I gave you
is the only proof of the Russians' complicity in
President Hassan's assassination.
But the conspiracy doesn't end with the Russians.
There are people within our own government
that are trying cover this up, including President Taylor.
Why would the President want this covered up?
Because she's trying to keep
the peace accord alive with the IRK.
And she knows if Dalia Hassan finds out
that the Russians had a hand in the death of her husband,
she'll never sign the agreement.
What do you want from me?
I need you to break the story in case I don't make it.
I think President Hassan deserves that, don't you?
Lemme see your cell phone.
Okay.
Wait. What are you doing? I...
They've seen you with me.
The authorities are going to start monitoring
your usual forms of communication.
You can't go home, you can't go back to your office.
Is there anyone that you work with that you trust?
Uh, my editor Gary Klausner.
You need to try and get him the evidence.
I can get you as far as a pay phone.
After that, you're on your own.
I'm glad we were able to come to terms.
So am I.
Thank you, Madam President, for your patience with me.
I am still new to this.
You are a natural leader, Dalia,
and you have a superb advisor in Minister Jamot.
I appreciate the endorsement, Madam President.
Pardon me...
for interrupting.
We were just finishing up.
Dalia Hassan.
Charles Logan.
I'm honored to finally meet you, Mrs. Hassan.
I was a great admirer of your husband.
I'm so sorry for you loss.
Thank you.
President Taylor tells me
you were instrumental
in convincing the Russian delegates to stay
- at the negotiating table.
- I'm honored to play
even a small part in such an historic event.
Madam President, may I have a few moments with you?
I'll see you at the signing.
You still haven't found out
how Logan convinced the Russians to stay?
I've investigated it,
but I learned nothing from the delegates.
I can have our intelligence service look into it.
No. Thank you, Jamot.
I trust President Taylor.
We have to assume that if she involved Logan,
it was for a good reason.
The operation to capture Jack Bauer was unsuccessful.
He got away, along with the evidence
that he took from Dana Walsh.
You said you had the situation under control.
Clearly, I was overly optimistic.
And in my optimism,
I neglected to tell you
that Bauer made contact with a journalist.
Meredith Reed.
My God...
You need to call her publisher right away.
Deny any foreknowledge of whatever evidence she has,
and demand that they do not run the story.
You're suggesting muzzling the press?
Have you forgotten that freedom of the press is
Constitutionally protected?
You are the president, for God's sake.
Invoke national security.
You tell them this story will start a war.
Innocent lives will be lost.
New lies to cover old ones.
The time has passed for hand wringing, Madam President.
If you don't use the power of your office
to shut this story down,
your peace agreement won't be the only casualty.
You don't need me to tell you the damage
that your criminal prosecution will do
to this country.
This country survived your presidency.
But it won't survive yours.
Me... I inherited my presidency.
I was never
nearly as popular as you are.
And most of my alleged misdeeds never made the press.
But if you were to bare your sins
to the people who put you in office...?
You are a beacon of righteousness,
not only for Americans, but for the rest of the world.
You are the President
who had her own daughter arrested
rather than see justice go unserved.
You're a poison.
I never should have let you to do this.
With due respect, Madam President,
I... I gave recommendations,
I made whatever arrangements needed to be made.
But every decision was yours.
Let's not pretend otherwise.
I've... I've studied you
for a number of years, Allison.
I pride myself on being a good judge of character.
You're a smart woman.
You've always known what needed to be done
and were willing to do it.
Which is why I know
you will call Meredith Reed's publisher
and make sure he kills the story.
I would suggest you do it now.
You, uh...
You have a signing ceremony to prepare for.
And I need to go meet President Suvarov.
Chloe,
you need to see this.
- What is it?
- I just
tapped into a live feed from Pillar's team.
This guy was found strung up
and sliced open in an abandoned building
across from the department store. He's got Russian papers
on him, but I can't make 'em out, the rez is too low.
Looks like someone left a sniper rifle at the scene.
What's the caliber? Bring it up.
They tagged it as a .308 Springfield.
That's the gun that killed Renee.
That's got to be the shooter.
Jack did this, and you still think
you're gonna be able
- to talk him down?
- I gotta try.
Pillar and his people are just gonna kill him,
and I can't let that happen.
(beep)
Got a match from the department store security feed... 82%.
That's the guy helping Jack?
Yeah, James Ricker... Ex-Green Beret, Special Ops.
He served with Jack in the Gulf
before Jack was enlisted by CTU.
Just one problem.
He's dead.
It says he was killed in
a chemical plant explosion in Basra seven years ago.
Yeah, well, then he must have a twin who was there
when Jack reversed the ambush.
You better go back to your station.
Pillar's watchdog is getting suspicious.
Arlo,
cross-reference Ricker's photo
with State DMV database.
He must be living under an alias in the city.
We find Ricker, we find Jack.
Okay.
(phone ringing)
JACK:
Yeah?
You get the location?
RICKER:
You didn't tell me that was
- Logan's phone that I was tracing, Jack.
- Does it matter?
Yeah, it kind of does.
I think you know it, too,
or else you would've been straight with me.
Listen, taking out a bunch of Russian spooks is one thing,
moving on an ex-president, that's quite another.
That's a seriously line you're crossing there, pal.
I know exactly what I'm doing.
Are you gonna give me his location or not?
Logan's in a vehicle.
He's moving west from the U.N.
I'm syncing up with the Secret Service deployment grid.
I'll upload his route to your tablet.
Hold on.
Okay, I've got it.
Listen, Jack, I sure hope you know what you're doing,
because this path you're on,
there ain't no coming back from it.
I wasn't planning on coming back.
Look, you're right, you've already done
more than I had a right to ask for.
I want you to start erasing all your connections to me.
Jim...
thanks for everything. Good-bye.
Oh. Thank you.
Are you sure that's all you need? Should I call the doctor?
It's just a headache.
I'm fine. Thank you.
- You wanted to see me, Madam President?
- Yes, Tim.
Please sit down.
You remember the reporter CTU arrested last night?
Yes, uh, Meredith Reed.
It has been brought to my attention
that she intends to publish an unfounded story
regarding Omar Hassan's murder.
What is she gonna be writing?
I need you to contact the FBI,
have them search the Sunday Magazine offices,
locate Reed,
and seize whatever evidence she purports to have.
Um, I... I... I don't understand.
Her allegations are false, but the allegations alone
could derail the peace process.
Well, even so, Madam President, you have to be aware,
they'll accuse you of censoring the press.
Tim, I did not ask for your counsel.
I know exactly what I'm ordering you to do,
so please just do it.
Yes, ma'am.
(grunts)
Hey, drop-off and receiving?
Uh, yeah, straight ahead.
- Right there.
- Thanks.
Just make sure Duggan knows
he's covering the Logan profile.
Tell him we'll work out the byline later.
(phone rings)
Editor's desk. This is Klausner.
REED:
Gary, it's me.
Look, a... are you alone?
Can you speak freely?
Yeah.
Yeah, wh... what's going on?
I don't have a lot of time. I have a lead on a story.
- I'm listening.
- I have a digital video recording
indicating that the IRK terrorists who killed Hassan
were being funded and run by Russian operatives.
(scoffs)
Uh, y... you sure it's legit?
Where did you get it?
From Jack Bauer.
Bauer?!
The man's a fugitive.
Look, Gary, it's really not safe for me to talk.
I'll explain more when I see you.
Can you meet me?
Sure, of course.
All right, that diner with the coffee you hate.
I can be there in, uh, 15 minutes.
Okay. And, Gary, don't tell anyone.
All right?
I got it.
Meredith... be safe.
Yeah. You, too.
There's no need to panic.
NOVAKOVICH:
Do you know what he did to Pavel?
He was beaten savagely, gutted like a pig.
His men shot dead.
I'm... I'm sorry to hear that,
but we both knew that, uh...
Bauer would be a difficult problem to solve.
You know what he's doing, don't you?
He's eliminating everyone involved,
working his way up... how long before he gets to me?
That's not going to happen.
How can you be so sure?
Because you told me yourself
your man would never talk,
and if that's true, then...
nobody outside of your inner circle
is able to point the finger at you.
I promise you...
Bauer's never going to know.
And on the upside, his recent activities
have given us a bit of an advantage.
What advantage?
CTU orders concerning him have been upgraded
to "shoot on sight."
First you have to find him.
They're going to find him, don't worry.
He can't... he can't stay under the radar forever.
I'll keep you posted.
(tires screeching)
(horns honking)
(gunfire)
DRIVER: Come in! Come in!
We're under assault! We are trapped
in the 4th Street underpass.
DRIVER:
This is Unit LEZ-1, requesting immediate backup.
Both entrances are blocked. We are boxed in.
Oh, that's... that's Jack Bauer.
That's got to be.
Did you hear what I said?!
That's Jack Bauer!
Don't just sit there!
He's coming for me!
Sir, stay in the vehicle.
We're armored and the glass is bulletproof.
(gunfire)
LOGAN:
Close the door!
The assailant is masked.
It may be Jack Bauer.
- Close the door! Secure the vehicle!
- Close the door!
Stay down, Mr. President.
Kill him!
(Logan gasps)
(gas hissing)
(coughing)
(continues coughing)
(coughing, hacking)
(gagging)
JACK:
Mr. President, get up, or I will kill you right here.
Move!
(gunshot)
I just got your flash.
What'd you find out about Ricker?
You were right.
DMV records show Ricker living in Suffolk County
under the name Simon Strocker.
I tried to confirm, found out he moved from there
18 months ago, but he left
a forwarding address with the postal service...
it's right here in SoHo.
Hey, Devon, what's going on?
Pillar's people are requesting backup for the team
- in the field.
- Why?
You didn't hear?
Jack Bauer just kidnapped Charles Logan.
How the hell did he pull that off?
Charles Logan?
I need to hear what's going on in that room. Follow me.
How far out are you?
We're approaching the tunnel now.
How the hell did Secret Service let this happen?
Bauer hit the town car with tear gas.
The agents were too incapacitated to pursue.
PD's got the tunnel locked down.
I'm working on getting you schematics.
Hurry up.
(tires squealing)
CTU! Make a hole!
(man coughing)
Where did Bauer take President Logan?
I don't know.
(coughing continues)
You must have seen something.
(coughing)
Come on... tell me you saw something.
- Sorry, sir.
- Nothing?
No one saw anything.
Eden, they went through an underground service gate.
I need those schematics.
Sending them to you now.
Go.
All right, Kirsch, take the corridor.
Brown, you're down there.
Ames, you're with me.
Remember, unless it poses an immediate threat
to President Logan, you shoot Bauer on sight,
and you shoot to kill.
Let's go.
(Logan panting)
Through here.
(grunts)
Look at me.
I said look at me!
(whimpers)
You're going to tell me everything I want to know.
Jack, you're making a mistake.
Don't you even try and pretend you're not a part of this.
I found the man who killed Renee Walker:
the Russian operative Pavel Tokarev.
I got his cell phone.
The last call he got was from you.
I know how it looks.
- You got to let me explain.
- Explain what?
That you sent for him to kill me?
You sent him to kill me, right?
Yes! Damn it, yes!
Why did you take out a hit on Renee Walker?
I had nothing to do with that.
I was brought in after that happened.
Who brought you in?
President Taylor needed my help
to bring the Russians back to the table.
I... I called my sources in Moscow.
They told me that people in their government
were behind Hassan's assassination.
I... I told the Russian delegation I had evidence of that fact
and the names of everybody involved.
It was just to keep them at the conference.
What evidence? What evidence?!
It doesn't exist.
I was playing poker.
It was a bluff. It worked.
It kept Taylor's peace agreement on the table, but you...
You were determined to screw things up.
And to... Oh! Oh!
Ow! Easy. Jack! Jack! Jack! I admit.
I admit, I was part of the cover-up,
but I'm not part of the Russian conspiracy.
I had nothing to do with the terrorist attack
or your friend's death.
I... I... I'm... I'm not the bad guy here.
Okay, but you know who is.
You know the name of the person
inside the Russian government
who's giving the orders. I want that name.
- Jack...
- Give me the name!
- You got five seconds before I put a bullet
- through your head.
- No! No! You don't have to do that.
- Five...
- I'll tell you.
- four... three...
- Mikhail Novakovich.
He's the head of the Russian delegation.
He's been trying
to kill the peace treaty from the start.
(panting)
You're lying.
No! No! No! I'm not lying to you! No! No! No! No!
You got my call from Pavel's phone.
You check the previous calls.
There's a dozen more from Novakovich.
I'm telling you.
He's the one you want.
(door thuds open)
Shut up!
(muffled groan)
Say another word,
and I'll drop you right here.
(Logan gasping anxiously)
Get on your knees.
Oh, no. Please.
Don't shoot me, Jack.
If I was gonna kill you, you'd already be dead.
(choking)
(gags)
PILLAR:
Bauer was just here... find him!
Mr. President?
Are you okay? Can you hear me?
Eden, I need a med unit at the 49th junction.
On its way.
Is it Bauer?
PILLAR:
No. It's the president.
He's unconscious.
Bauer escaped. I'm gonna need you to redirect the pursuit.
I'll stay with the President.
Understood.
They still might catch up to him.
They haven't yet. Do you have Ricker's file?
Yeah, including his current address.
I'm sending it to you now.
How are you planning to handle this?
We can't send any tactical units to pick this guy up
without Pillar finding out about it.
I'm not using any of them.
Then who are you going to get?
All of our agents are fully deployed in the field.
There's nobody to send.
There's one.
(sighs)
Ms. O'Brian?
Ms. O'Brian?!
I just saw the flash from Division.
They approved your request
to release Agent Ortiz into your custody?
Yeah, I'm in a hurry, so...
What do you think you're doing?
He's a non-cooperative witness
who is facing federal charges.
In case you haven't noticed,
I'm still in charge of U.N. security,
and you've taken away all my resources.
And not that it's any of your business,
but Agent Ortiz designed the entire U.N. operation.
The signing is in less than two hours.
His assistance in the field is vital.
I'm going to have to clear this with Pillar.
Do what you want, but to me, you have bigger problems,
like not finding Jack Bauer.
(sighs)
Are you Meredith?
Yes.
There's a Gary Klausner on the phone for you.
It's up by the cashier.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Where are you?
Meredith, the FBI is here.
They showed up before I could leave.
They're looking for you, questioning everyone,
including me.
You didn't tell them anything, did you?
Of course not.
But they've got an executive order
from the President.
They say you're in possession of materials that pose
a national security risk.
It's a cover-up, Gary.
The White House is trying to suppress the story.
You can't let them.
Look, until we clear this up,
you have to protect that evidence.
I told them I haven't had any contact with you,
but for all I know, they're tracing this call.
You better get the hell out of there.
And go where?
Mr. Klausner.
We said no communication outside of our presence.
I... I... I'm canceling an appointment.
Gary, they're going to bury the truth.
Not if I can help it.
I'll try to put a call in to Ed Sampson
at the Justice Department,
but until then, lay low.
Now go.
Okay.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
I have to go to the U.N., and
division has given you
a temporary furlough into my custody.
Since you had earlier command of UN security,
I'm gonna need your help coordinating protocols
and deployment for the signing ceremony.
And Pillar's okay with this?
I'm still provisional Director of Operations.
I don't need his consent.
So, are you coming, or would you rather
wait here for your federal prosecution?
(scoffs)
Let's go.
I'll take him from here.
You want to tell me what's really going on?
Yeah.
You were right about Jack.
He is working with somebody.
It's James Ricker,
ex-CIA Op.
We found him living at a place on Mercer Street
under the alias Simon Strocker.
Maybe he's still with the company.
No. I checked with Langley. He was listed as deceased.
More than likely, he's gone into business for himself,
dealing arms or intel. In any case,
he's not going to be happy we tracked him down.
Wait a second.
Why are you telling me this?
I need you to talk to him.
Get him to tell us where Jack is.
Are you good with that, or have you still not taken sides?
I want to expose this cover-up as much as you. I'm in.
Good. Log sheets
will show you accompanying me to the U.N.
I've secured you a separate vehicle waiting at the gate.
Is there any more intel on Jack?
Has he resurfaced yet?
Yeah, you could say that.
Sir, I just received word.
President Suvarov's plane has
touched down at Kennedy Airport.
Tell Ivan to bring the car around.
I want to be at the U.N. when the President arrives.
(phone ringing)
Where's Novakovich?
- I'm not going to ask you again.
- 11th.
11th floor, suite 1170.
How do I get up there?
Secure elevator inside of garage.
- Where's your keycard?
- I don't have one.
(grunting)
Where is your keycard?
I don't have one, I swear.
His personal guards have them at elevator.
- How many?
- Two.
And upstairs?
One outside the suite, two inside.
Another by elevator.
Where else?
Where else?!
That's all. That's all I know.
(grunting)
(bell chimes)
(blade slashing)
(bell dings)
(groans quietly)
Do you really need an arsenal?
Better to have it than to not.
Besides, Ricker's a trained killer.
He's gone to a lot of trouble
- to stay off the grid.
- Fair enough.
I also have to consider the possibility
that Jack's with him.
Listen, Chloe,
I can't be worried about Jack anymore,
not after what you told me he did to Logan.
Obviously, Logan's part of the conspiracy.
He terrorized a tunnel full of commuters
with automatic weapon fire.
He shot Secret Service agents.
He shot to wound.
He's careless, and he only cares about revenge.
Does that sound like the man you know?
Like the man you're trying to save?
This is about exposing the Russians' cover-up.
It's not about Jack.
Are you sure about that?
Because if Jack's there,
and he makes any move other than complete surrender...
I'm putting him down.
You still want me to go?
I don't really have a choice.
Whatever happens, call me at the U.N.
You got it.
(engine starts)
You'll approach the rostrum
immediately prior to the signing ceremony,
and take a seat here
in position three, next to your mother.
I'm honored.
But is that appropriate?
I may be her daughter,
but I don't have any official role in government.
(knocking on door)
Excuse me.
Ms. Hassan, there's a call on your father's secure line...
a woman demanding to speak with your mother.
She's in a meeting.
That's what I said, but this woman
- is quite insistent.
- Who is she?
She won't say.
We're done, Ms. Hassan.
I'll see you in the staging area.
Thank you.
Line two.
Hello. Who is this?
Ah. Is this Kayla?
Who are you?
Sorry, um...
my name is Meredith Reed.
I need to speak to your mother.
I know who you are.
What do you think you're doing calling here?
I... I know I'm the last person that
either of you wants to talk to right now...
You're right. I'm hanging up now.
No, please, please, your mother needs
to hear what I have to say
before she signs the agreement with President Taylor.
What is it that is so important?
I... I'm sorry, I need to speak to your mother directly.
Haven't you caused my mother enough pain?
Leave us alone!
It's about the people who really murdered your father.
What are you talking about?
We know who was responsible.
What you don't know is, those people were working
under the orders of Russian agents.
What?!
- Hello?
- When your mother gets back
from her meetings, have her call me
at this number... can you take this down?
(panting)
Go ahead.
It's 212-555-0121.
I'll explain everything to her then.
Wait...!
Meredith Reed?
FBI. Get your hands where
- we can see 'em.
- Wait, wait, what... what is this?
What is this?
Wait. Wait.
You have no right to take that.
I... I haven't done anything wrong.
What is this?
You're under arrest.
- I... I've done nothing wrong.
- Let's go.
I've done nothing wrong!
(knocking on door)
Yes?
Mr. Woods, ma'am.
I've just received word from the FBI.
Reed is in custody,
and they've secured a data card they found on her.
(sighs)
No one sees what's on it but me.
Understood.
MAN:
Sir, we'll take it from here.
No, you won't... I'm riding with him to the hospital.
(clears throat)
Give him some space.
(weakly):
Nova... Novakov...
Nova...
Novakovich.
Warn...
Bauer knows.
Warn Novakovich Bauer's coming after him.
PARAMEDIC: Sir, we gotta get going.
- Not yet. Just do
- what you can for him here.
- Understood.
(phone ringing)
(ringing continues)
Yes?
Mr. Novakovich?
Hello? Hello?
It's Berkov.
We've been attacked.
It was Bauer.
Where's Novakovich?
He's dead.
Everyone is dead.
Berkov, did Novakovich say anything to Bauer?
I need an ambulance.
Just answer my question.
What did Novakovich say to Bauer?
Nothing. Bauer just came in shooting.
But he was bleeding.
I think he was wounded by one of the guards.
All right, sit tight. An ambulance is on the way.
Go.
(quietly):
Novakovich is dead.
Bauer killed him, killed all of his men...
I don't know if Novakovich said anything to Bauer.
(phone ringing)
Yes?
LOGAN (clears throat):
Yuri.
Charles Logan.
I was under the impression you were going to be
at the heliport for my arrival.
Yes, well...
(raspy chuckle)
...I ran into some trouble.
I'm afraid I have bad news.
It appears that Mikhail Novakovich
was just murdered by Jack Bauer.
- What?!
- Yeah, and, uh, Bauer learned
that, uh, Novakovich was responsible
for ordering and...
coordinating Omar Hassan's assassination, as well as
the rest of Samir's activities.
Where would he get that idea?
From me.
The lunatic was gonna kill me, Yuri.
What can I say?
Think of it as, uh,
sacrificing a rook for a king.
Then Bauer has no idea
that Novakovich was operating under my orders?
None.
Uh, according to a witness,
Mikhail didn't have a chance to give you up,
even he wanted to.
As far as, uh, Bauer is concerned...
the trail ended with Novakovich.
And he's being hunted
by every law enforcement agency in the city.
And I've... I've heard that, uh... (chuckles)
he's been wounded.
Wounded... there is nothing
more dangerous than a wounded animal.
Look, if you're so worried about Bauer,
you never should have given the order
to kill Renee Walker.
That's what stirred up the hornet's nest.
If I had known that you were going to find out
about our activities and use that information
to blackmail me
into signing Taylor's peace agreement,
I wouldn't have bothered with the woman.
Water under the bridge, Yuri.
I needed an opportunity to put myself back in the game.
I'm sorry that it has come at your expense.
You wouldn't begrudge an old friend
his second chance in the sun.
LOGAN (over radio):
All right, then, I will, uh,
I will meet you at the United Nations...
(clears throat)
as soon as I can.
(Jack groans, pants)
www.addic7ed.com