Mr President?
We need medical assistance! Help!
This is security. I need help at the ramp.
Clear, sir.
Clear.
Step over there, please.
Give 'em ID.
There you go.
Open one.
You OK, Jack?
I won't be OK until we get this thing signed.
That's not what I meant.
OK. We're all here.
- What kind of changes are we talking about?
- They're not deal breakers.
He's still gonna give up the terrorist cells.
He just wants to go to a class 2 detention.
Not maximum security.
- You're giving him it?
- Yeah.
My client's not happy that
you won't hold him in Florida.
- He's getting Minnesota.
- Give him Florida. There's no difference.
I let you do your jobs.
Why don't you let me do mine?
We don't want this thing
going south over some detail.
Salazar is unstable. We can't predict what'll
push his buttons. There's too much at stake.
I know you two spent the last year
getting Salazar and I respect that.
- But there's a protocol that I have to follow...
- Luis, come here for a second.
Putting him away is not the point. If he
doesn't talk, we've accomplished nothing.
I didn't lose a year of my life
to arrest some drug dealer.
Salazar deals with terrorist cells around the
world. Bringing them down is our objective.
I understand. But if you give Salazar
everything he asks for, he's gonna want more.
This is the deal. And he's going to take it.
Here.
You better be right.
Douglas. Is that my life
you're holding in your hand?
It's ready to be signed.
Are you in there, Jack?
Forget about Bauer.
How can I forget about
the man who put me here?
Pretended to be my friend.
I'm concerned about you, Jack.
The things you did to get me here,
I wouldn't wish on anyone.
Let's face it, you'll never be the same.
Hey. Neither will I.
So I guess we are in the same boat.
I'm about to name names, Jack.
This is a big moment for both of us.
That makes me happy.
Because, you see, we are connected now.
I don't know. Maybe we always have been.
I marked the changes.
I don't need to see the changes.
But I do need the pen.
Unless you want me
to sign it with my own blood.
That's kind of funny - "my own blood".
Where do I sign this, Douglas?
Right here.
You have done a good job as my counsel.
Been a go-to guy, as they like to say here
in the States. But I think they're on to you.
And I don't think you have
what it takes to keep your mouth shut.
What do you mean?
Son of a bitch.
Open the door. Open the door!
Do it now!
- Get a medic in here. Now!
- This is your fault, Jack.
- And what happens next is on you, too.
- What does that mean, huh? Is that a threat?
- Chase!
- Son of a bitch.
- Back off!
- Take a walk!
Did you hear me?
What happens next is on you, Jack.
It's on you!
- Dr Macer. We isolated the body.
- You said my name was on it?
Yes. It's on his chest.
Run a full panel of tests to be sure, but I think
we're dealing with a pneumonic virus, type III.
Type III? Isn't that the virus group
your team's been doing simulations on?
I think that's why this was addressed to me.
- Has CTU been contacted yet?
- No. We've been waiting for you.
Go ahead and start the pulmonary tests.
I'll call Director Almeida.
Hey. The President arrive at SC yet?
Just about. We're swapping our people
now Secret Service is in place.
They're waiting for
your resource assessment.
All right, I'll call 'em.
- I've had it, Tony, I swear to God.
- What's the problem, Adam?
Chloe O'Brian does not touch my data.
If Field Ops wants something, she asks Jack
or talks to you, then you tell me.
- Did she damage anything?
- That's not the point.
My department has zero downtime
because of the procedures I put in place.
- Did she damage anything? Then let it go.
- No...
Jack's got his department and I got mine. But
we're all under the same roof, understood?
Good. Now, lighten up. You're gonna
drive yourself and the rest of us crazy.
All right. Hold on.
Sunny Macer from Health Services
is on the line.
- By the way, have you heard from Hertzog?
- No, not yet.
- Relax, Michelle, you're gonna get the job.
- You're not going to Langley without me.
Hey. What's up?
- This is one I'm sorry to be right about.
- What are you talking about?
Cordilla virus.
It's a type III pneumonic virus.
Remember I raised the possibility
a strain could be out there?
- Yeah.
- It is.
Someone just dropped off a dead body
infected with the virus.
These guys are serious. They blew up the
door to get our attention. This is a message.
That somebody's got the virus
and they're willing to release it?
Yeah, exactly.
Do we need to issue a quarantine advisory?
No. Once the host is dead it's not contagious.
Call the other county facilities,
see if there are any more cases.
- What about the ID on the John Doe?
- Send everything over. We'll work it up.
- It's on its way.
- All right. Thanks, Sunny.
What is it?
Initiate a level one setting protocol.
And I don't think you have
what it takes to keep your mouth shut.
What do you mean?
Salazar could have killed Shaye any time
over the last three months. Why today?
- He was cutting his deal.
- Maybe, but I don't think so.
This is your fault, Jack.
And what happens next is on you, too.
"What happens next."
- CTU.
- This is Bauer. Patch me through to Almeida.
Hold on.
-  Hey.
- Is anything going on there?
We just had a major protocol come in.
Possible biothreat to the city.
Tell me about it.
A dead body infected with the Cordilla virus
was left at Health Services.
We figure it's the first shoe dropping. We're
waiting for somebody to take responsibility.
- Jack?
- Yeah.
You thinking this is connected to Salazar?
I don't know. I don't know, maybe.
- I'll get back to you.
- All right.
- I need copies of all four images.
- Right away.
- Mr President.
- Wayne. Are we ready for the run-through?
Almost. The advance team dropped a ball
so we can't get in there for a few minutes.
- That's fine.
- No, it's not fine. I fired Judy. It was her fault.
She's done some good work for us,
hasn't she?
Tonight's debate is critical. She should have
had every single base covered but she didn't.
Mr President. How do you feel about
the debate with Senator Keeler?
Confident. Ready to go.
Sir, this is your first time back to LA
since the attempt on your life.
- Were you uneasy about coming back?
- Not at all.
Los Angeles is a great city. Would've been
back here sooner if events had allowed it.
What is important is that we're here now,
looking to the future.
Thank you. That's all for now. We'll have a
formal Q&A this afternoon. You'll be briefed.
David, we gotta talk about those GAO
members. Keeler's gonna bring it up tonight...
David? David, are you all right?
I'm fine.
- Let me call one of the resident doctors.
- No, it's all right. I'll wait for Anne.
- Where you going, Jack? We have to talk.
- Not now.
- Then when?
- Call me. Right now we gotta get to CTU.
Why?
Salazar killed Shaye for a reason. He picked
today to do it. We gotta find out why.
Fine. Let's go back in there
and put the screws on Salazar.
You think he's gonna talk to us after
what we just watched him do? Not a chance.
Come on. Let's go.
Jack.
Just call me.
All right, so what else did Almeida say
about this dead body?
- Jack.
- What?
I asked you about Tony.
What else did he say?
He said the body was dumped
at Health Services. They're trying to ID it.
You know, you never answered me before.
About how you're doing.
- What are you talking about?
- You know what.
- This is Bauer.
- Jack, it's Chloe.
I have Kate Warner for you.
Should I put her through?
Uh...
Yeah. Put her through.
- Jack?
- Hi, Kate.
I just wanted to let you know I found
that leather jacket you thought you'd lost.
Oh. Uh...
- OK. Great.
- So, uh, what do you want to do?
I could bring it over. Or send it.
You don't have to do that.
I'll just send someone over to pick it up.
- You sure?
- Yeah.
- OK, then.
- Kate. How are you?
You know, it's hard.
I miss you.
I'm really, really sorry.
Don't be.
- Take care of yourself, Kate.
- Bye.
- How's Kate?
- She's all right.
- So you guys are still talking?
- No, not really.
All right. None of my business. Sorry.
I didn't mean it like that. She's just trying
to return a couple of things of mine, that's all.
Got any water?
Talk to Sunny. She was checking with
the other facilities for any more cases.
If there are, find out where.
Take all the regional cells
that have bioterrorist capabilities
and put 'em in a high-speed cache.
OK.
Tony, it's Larry Hertzog from Langley
on line two.
Hey, Larry.
Yeah, we are.
Uh-huh.
Yeah, I will. Thanks.
- Was that about me?
- Yeah.
He doesn't have a job for you right now.
There's no new funding till after the election.
I see.
Also, Larry told me that he needs
an answer from me by the end of the day.
They're in a hurry to fill the post.
We both know you can't pass this up.
It's a major career move.
Call him and tell him it's yes.
And you'll come along as the wife?
Without a job?
I'll go anywhere with you.
As long as I don't have to cook.
Sweetheart, if you promise not to cook,
I will take you with me anywhere.
But if they don't have a job for you,
I'm not interested.
Tony. Homeland Security on line one.
We'll talk about it later.
Almeida.
Pretty much. Just have to refresh
the data on my panel. Thanks.
- Hey, Kim.
- Yes, Michelle?
- You ever done a capability search?
- Couple of weeks ago, for Tony.
- The East European cells?
- Yes.
Good. This one's different.
It's gonna be global.
- Here's my access code.
- I'll get right on it.
Thanks.
Hey, Adam.
Does the link file have DES encryptions?
No, it's two key.
- What volume is the filter on?
- Étude seven.
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Are you saying you had to break me?
No, mi ángel.
It was you who break me.
¿ Qué más?
¿ Seguro?
Sí, señor.
OK, it's coming up now.
Thanks, Chris.
- Adam, I'm piping this over to your system.
- What is it?
Frags on the body that was dropped off at
Health Services. We're doing an ID analysis.
- Where are you in the capability search?
- It's gonna be another 15 minutes.
- So you're open?
- What do you need?
Adam'll break off part of an ID.
We need a name. Give her the file.
- I don't need her help.
- Yes, you do.
This is urgent.
I'm ready, Adam. Send the file.
- I'm open, Adam. Send me the file.
- No.
- Michelle told you...
- I don't need anyone doing my work for me.
- What is your problem?
- Everyone in this place earned their job.
You got it cos of your dad.
What the hell is this?
- Tracy, is your system locked?
- No.
OK, thanks.
It could be you forgot
to set the group permission.
Someone who knows
the tree structure changed the ownership.
That wouldn't be me because I'm incompetent
and only got this job because of my dad.
- Change the ownership back, Kim.
- Send the data fork.
It's your ass. Michelle's waiting.
Fine. I'll send it. Just unlock my system.
No problem.
- Hey, Jack, I'll be up in a minute.
- OK.
Chloe. Give me what you got.
Are we in sync with the systems?
Everything Health Services sent
is in volume one.
- I've reprised all the Salazar information.
- Where are the date keys?
- I couldn't get those for you.
- Why not?
You'll have to talk to Tony, so he can tell
Adam and Adam can give them to me.
- You're kidding me, right?
- No. Adam's anal and he hates women.
Chloe.
Just get it for me, OK, please?
Close my door.
- Yeah?
- It's Michelle.
The teleconference with Health Services
is about to start. Come down.
No, I'm gonna stay up here.
Patch them through.
- OK.
- Thanks.
You scared me.
- What are you doing in here?
- I am refreshing a drive.
What's going on with Salazar?
Were you there when it happened?
Yeah.
Yeah, it was pretty crazy.
How's my dad taking it?
- He's OK.
- Good.
I was thinking about talking to him today.
Uh-huh.
- Today might not be the best day.
- Chase, no day is a good day.
We said that we would tell him if we were still
together after two months. It's almost three.
Why don't we just tell him
and get it over with?
All right.
But I'll do it. OK?
- Are you sure?
- Yes, I'm sure.
- Really?
- Really.
You can't put the drives there.
What I need you to do is look under...
- F6, right?
- Yeah. OK, thanks.
We received results of more tests.
The news isn't good.
This is a weaponized strain.
It has been engineered to kill more rapidly.
How rapidly?
It's a bit of a guess but, based on the autopsy,
if infection starts at T equals zero hours,
there's a noncontagious latency period
of 14 hours.
After 14 it presents. After 20 the host
is incapacitated. By 24 the host is dead.
What are the epidemiological consequences?
If the virus initiates at a single location,
there will be a couple hundred cases
by the end of day one.
By the end of day two
it could be in the thousands,
but from there it's easier to talk about
in percentage of population.
By the end of the first week, nine per cent
of Los Angeles county will be infected.
Nine per cent?
That's over a million people.
And those people will die
within 24 hours of infection.
So tell me, if someone were gonna try to
release this virus into the general population,
how would they do it?
That's the million-dollar question.
It could come from anywhere.
We don't know who has it.
We don't know where they plan to release it.
We don't even know what form it's in.
Kyle?
What, Ma?
- Tim wants you to know he's at the pool.
- Thanks, Ma.
Can you take me to the doctor
later on this afternoon?
- What's Dad doing?
- On a job interview. Fingers crossed.
Fingers crossed.
Can Aunt Norma take you?
Why? What's so important
that you can't take me?
I mean...
It's just I got a bunch of stuff
to do today, Ma. I'm sorry.
- Fine. I'll call Norma.
- Thanks.
Love you, Ma.
Mr President. The country was in shock
after the attempt on your life.
But its prayers were answered
when you survived.
That said, many Americans have expressed
concern that you are not fully recovered,
and are not strong enough
to serve for four more years.
How would you respond
to those who make such claims?
I wake up every morning at 5am.
I spend the first hour in the weight room.
While I'm exercising,
I'm prepping for my meetings.
- And then I put in a 16-hour day...
- Hold on!
Could we pause the video, please?
Get ready to play it back.
Sorry, Chuck. Hold on. Don't dignify
that question with a defensive response.
I didn't realize that stating
the facts was being defensive.
They bring up the assassination attempt, fine.
You remind them it was your administration
that arrested the man
behind the attempt on your life
and exposed his organization
and put his top-tier people away.
All this while you were in
this so-called "weakened state".
Keeler would be lucky to have a fraction
of your energy. That's what you tell 'em.
Mr President. Go ahead, Chuck.
And Mom called him the timid brother.
Ah, there's my doctor. How are you?
- Mr President.
-  All right. Let's break for a minute.
I'm fine. How's he been?
- Seems a little tired.
- I am not tired. I'm just a little jet-lagged.
How's this going?
I'm definitely winning the run-through.
- 130 over 80.
- Good. This is Wayne Palmer.
- How tired?
- I'm fine.
- We haven't done a workup in a while...
- No. No, no, no. No tests.
You start looking for something
and you don't stop until you find it.
I'm fine, Anne.
OK.
But when you get back to DC, I want you to
have a complete physical. Doctor's orders.
Yes, ma'am.
Anne. I need him alone for a minute.
- He's all yours.
- What is it?
I just received a disturbing call
from Health Services.
They found a body in Los Angeles that's been
infected with a contagious and deadly virus.
There's concerns
it's not just a random occurrence.
- Meaning what?
- CTU is looking to the possibility
that this could be a criminal action.
Criminal action? Based on this one death?
I don't know the details,
but it has to do with the circumstances
under which the body was found.
- Keep your eye on this one.
- OK.
Chuck, can we go down to question seven,
about homeland security?
- Chloe.
- Yes?
- Where are the transcripts of Salazar?
- I sent them to your system, in your directory.
Dammit, I wanted it stored
with the rest of the files from Salazar.
OK. I'll do it.
Chloe, if you can't get things right
the first time, I can get someone who can.
If you wanted it with the other files
you should have said so.
- That isn't standard, so I wouldn't do it.
- Do it that way from now on, OK?
I can't read minds. You'll just
have to spell it out for me, otherwise...
Dammit, Chloe! Just do it now!
Fine.
Hey, Jack.
What?
- What was that all about?
- I need you to replace Chloe for me.
Replace her? She's the best analyst we got.
- She's not. She's slow.
- She's not slow.
She may be a little weird
but she knows her stuff.
You look like hell.
What did you just say to me?
We're on an active protocol, OK?
I need to know if you're up for it or not.
I like working with you, Chase.
You're a nice kid.
But don't you ever come into my office
and talk to me like that again. Understand?
I'm just saying you're on edge. OK?
I mean, come on, man,
you're about to fire Chloe for no reason.
- Chloe.
- Yes?
I'm sorry I took your head off.
We're just having a bad morning, OK?
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
You're happy?
Look, Jack. There's one more thing
I gotta talk to you about.
- This is Bauer.
-  We've got something new on Salazar.
OK, we'll be right down.
They got something on Salazar.
What do you wanna tell me?
Nothing. It'll hold.
Good.
In order to plug any possible security
breaches, we'll do date checks from now on.
Break your logs into eight-hour intervals.
Put different encryptions on each interval. If
one is breached, one won't bleed to the other.
- Did you tell him?
- No. There's a lot going on. It'll happen.
An anonymous call came in to the FBI ten
minutes ago. They're gonna stream it to us.
- Did you hear it?
- Yeah.
- OK. It's ready.
- Bring it up.
You've received our package
and realized we're in possession of a type III
pulmonary immuno virus.
Listen very carefully to these instructions.
Our demand is very simple.
We want the release
of Ramón Salazar in the next six hours.
If you refuse to comply, the virus
will be unleashed to the general population.
As your experts will tell you,
you will not have time to stop its spread.
Details of how Ramón
is to be delivered will follow.
- That's it.
- Do we know where the call originated?
It came out of a scrambled satellite signal.
We're trying to narrow it down.
You know Salazar better than anybody else
here. Who are we dealing with?
His brother. Hector was next in command.
He went underground
when Ramón was taken into custody.
Look. I know that the Salazars own multiple
properties in South America and Mexico,
registered under dummy corporations.
Unfortunately, the Mexican government
is saying they can't locate them.
We're gonna have to throw out a pretty large
net to trace the origin of that call.
- We'll work on it.
- How are we doing with the ID on the body?
- Michelle's running the DNA.
- What about prints and dental?
- No teeth, no fingertips.
- We need this ID. It's the only hook we've got.
What about questioning Salazar?
Complete waste of time.
This is a man without vulnerability.
He doesn't respond to interrogation or care
about a living soul, including his children.
Tony! We've a match on John Doe.
- Show us what you got.
- The dead body is a David Goss.
He's a street dealer in East LA,
also an informant.
He flipped sides so many times
DEA stopped working with him.
- Last known address?
- We're working on it.
We need to know who infected Goss. Work up
a list of people involved in his life this week.
- We'll pull together everything we can.
- Work it from the other side too.
Go through Salazar's network.
Find the supplier who sold to Goss.
Good work. Chase, come with me.
Let's see if anything's come in on Hector.
Entonces, asegúrate. Que no se note nada.
Sí, señor.
Ponle el petrol. Ponle fuego.
Sigue, ponle el petrol.
Why do you have my father
doing this kind of work for you?
It's not his job.
It is today.
Why did you kill Shaye?
Take a look around. You're in a US prison
where your ass will rot until you're executed.
You want to improve your conditions here,
you better start talking to me.
- What do you want to talk about?
- Why did you kill your attorney?
- I didn't want him talking to you.
- About what?
About anything.
It's eating at you, isn't it?
What am I up to? Come on, Luis.
You have me in chains. Two tough guys
waiting for a chance to beat me to a pulp.
Do it, Luis!
See if you can beat it out of me.
You are no fun.
Where are you going?
Claudia.
Claudia!
What's wrong?
My father is the ranch foreman.
You promised he wouldn't be involved
in your other activities.
I pay him three times over.
He can perform an extra task or two.
No, no, no. No.
I told you when we came to live here
that I didn't want him or my little brother
to be exposed to your illegal business.
You broke your word, Hector.
And that hurts me.
It hurts.
I'm sorry, Claudia.
- Please, I make it up to you.
- How?
I give your father some time off.
An extra month's pay.
That's your solution
to every problem, isn't it?
Money.
Claudia.
Claudia!
- Yeah?
- Have you made the call to the FBI?
Yes, I did.
- What about our boy?
- I'm watching him now.
- Keep him close.
- I will.
So what was it like to get knee-deep
in some fine Tijuana dell?
Huh?
- I didn't do that.
- What do you mean?
I mean I didn't go down there to get laid.
- But you said...
- No, I know. I know what I said.
I just didn't wanna tell you
in case something happened.
So, what's the big secret?
Remember Zach Parker from high school?
Sure. Didn't he get busted last year
for dealing coke?
Yeah, yeah.
Whatever. He set me up
with this guy down there.
- "Set you up"? How do you even know him?
- I know him, OK?
What are you into here, man?
Are you selling dope?
No.
- I'm not exactly selling anything...
- Then exactly what are you doing?
This guy... he paid me five grand
to bring some coke over the border.
I did that last night.
Today I drop it off, I get another five.
- You're outta your mind.
- It's just one time.
Getting over the border's the hard part.
That's already done.
Why are you doing this?
Cos my mom's on dialysis.
My dad's out of a job.
We're about to get evicted from this crappy
apartment. Is that good enough for you?
Dude, you are seriously insane.
Look, Tim.
I'm about to make this drop later today.
I was thinking, maybe we could go together.
- Forget it!
- You just wait in the car.
I go in, I make the drop, I come back out.
That's it. There's no big deal.
I'm not interested.
Think about it.
- Mr President, sir.
Carry on.
- When did FBI get this call?
- About 20 minutes ago.
- We don't know who we're dealing with?
- It was a scrambled voice on an open line.
All we know is what he said. They want
Salazar or they're gonna release the virus.
What's your take on this, Wayne?
Do we cancel the debate?
So far, DOD, the Pentagon and CTU
haven't recommended raising the alert level,
but they are discussing whether or not
we should stay in Los Angeles.
- Sir.
- Yes, Aaron?
Dr Packard's here. She's asked to see you.
- Tell her I'm busy, please.
- Yes, Mr President.
Aaron, wait.
- Tell her I'll speak with her.
- Yes, sir.
You really wanna do that right now?
Yes, Wayne, I do.
- Yes, Anne?
- I want you to start taking these.
One in the morning and one before
you go to bed. It'll help your energy.
- I told you I was fine.
- I know what you told me.
Are you gonna trust your doctor or not?
Course I am.
So, what's going on? You seem upset.
Nothing.
It's just gonna be another one of those days.
What does that mean?
I've got to get back.
OK.
We'll talk later.
- What is wrong with this system?
- What?
The grid won't come up.
That's because you need
to "control S" out of it.
You're still in Navigation.
Thank you.
Look, can you just patch it
through to my office?
- What's his problem today?
- Nothing.
This time line goes straight
from December to February.
- What are you trying to do, Jack?
- Same as you. Solve this problem.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Listen, Jack.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
I look up to you.
I'd take a bullet for you if I had to,
but right now I'm gonna hold the mirror up.
You were under with Salazar for six months.
I know what they did to you.
And I know what you did to yourself.
You can't make that go away overnight.
You think I didn't know?
You should mind your own business, Chase.
All I'm trying to say
is that I'm here for you.
But today is not the day to try
to prove to everybody that you're all better.
It's about to hit the fan.
You know that and I know that.
So do what you gotta do, man.
Get your head straight so we can do our work.
Dad, you up there?
Dad?
Yeah.
Can I come up?
I need to talk to you about something.
Uh...
Not right now, sweetheart.
I'm in the middle of something.
OK. Call me when you have a few minutes.
OK.