- =http://sfile. ydy. com=-
proudly presents
Previously on 24
Tanner. Emerson spoke to
his man inside the bureau.
- He says you're clear.
- Good.
Look, I need to prep my men on the next
job, so why don't you tell me what we need.
I'll give you the specs when I get there.
I'll engage him. Cover my flank.
I can handle it.
I don't understand. Almeida
was orchestrating these attacks.
If he doesn't have the cip device, who does?
Almeida's working for the juma regime.
This is colonel ike dubaku.
We demand an immediate withdraw of the
U. S. Naval strike force by this time tomorrow...
the american troops are still
in position near our country.
President taylor just received your demands.
The perhaps it is time for a
more forceful demonstration.
I know about samantha roth.
She's hiding something about my son's murder.
Roger wasn't murdered.
I wasn't completely honest with you.
What do you mean?
Roger didn't commit suicide, mr. Taylor.
He was murdered.
Jack, tony is not a terrort.
He's working with me.
We're working outside the government.
That's why we have to get tony back undercover.
Bauer, you're going to make it out of here.
Shut up.
Get down!
we got to get you out of here and back undercover.
Go!
tony, let's go!
- =http://sfile. ydy. com=-
sync: ﬂ«»‚»‚ ∞Óµ¬÷Ì ≈›≈›∑…
24 Season07 Episode04
The following takes place between 11am and 12pm
renee...
security saw bauer and almeida
getting into a dark-colored panel van.
- What direction were they heading?
- West.
What's happening with td. O. T. Cameras?
I've been trying. Traffic images aren't loading.
What do you mean not loading?
Just what I said. The server's not responding.
The hacker must be jamming the transmission.
How the hell can they do that?
Well, if I knew, I'd be able to get around it.
Continue checking ancillary security cams, atms,
parking garages-- there has to be something.
Well, keep canvassing the area.
Someone else may have seen the vehicle. That...
fine. Let me know.
No luck on municipal cameras.
Looks like they have someone
running interference for them.
Damn it.
Bauer must have worked out this
escape with almeida's people.
I'm so sorry, larry.
That son of a bitch played me. Had me
believing the bureau was compromised--
someone on the inside working against us.
I realize now it was him all along.
Don't put this on yourself. He played us both.
No, I should have seen it.
This is fine, take it downstairs.
Bailer's facing a federal
indictment-- years in prison.
Almeida must have offered him a way out.
Agent moss... the white house is on line one.
I'll, uh, take it in the
conference room. Thanks, erica.
I'm going to make this rig, larry.
Whatever it takes, I will find bauer and almeida.
Well, throw in a cip device,
and maybe we'll be off the hook.
Janis, what's the status of that shooter?
He hasn't regained consciousness yet.
But a print match is just coming up now.
His name is alan tanner.
He was former special forces,
discharged after desert storm.
Discharged why?
Medical reasons.
He made claims to having gulf war syndrome.
Tried to sue the government, case was dismissed.
I want to be informed the minute he's awake.
I'm connecting you now.
Agent moss, this is ethan kanin.
I'm here with the president.
What are you and your folks
doing about the situation?
We put out an all-agency alert.
Everyone understands apprehending
almeida is our top priority.
How did he escape?
He had the help of a former ctu
agent that we mistakenly trusted.
A man by the name of jack bauer.
Bauer?
I thought he was in the middle
of a senate investigative hearing.
Yes, sir, that is correct.
We issued a subpoena a few hours
ago, excusing him from the hearings
in order to enlist his help
in apprehending almeida.
Now you're saying that these two men are allied?
It would appear so.
My god...
you and your people have
royally screwed up, agent moss!
Without almeida, we have no way of finding
dubaku and no chance of recovering the cip device.
Ethan, let's stay on point.
Agent moss, are you working any other leads?
Yes, madame president.
A confederate of almeida's
who was wounded earlier today.
He's just out of surgery.
We're waiting for him to regain consciousness.
Do we have a time frame from the
hospital on when that might happen?
No, ma'am. Not really.
Let me be clear, Recapturing almeida
and bauer isn't just your top iority,
it's your only priority.
Yes, ma'am.
Keep us posted, agent.
Bottom line: The bureau is not going
to be the answer to our prayers here.
I'm afraid not.
How much time does that leave us?
Less than two hours.
Dubaku's demand is that our forces retreat
behind the 23rd meridian within 24 hours.
Now, in order to meet that timetable,
the fleet and carrier air wing must
start withdrawing by 1:00, at the latest.
Which would effectively end our mission in africa
and condemn another 100,000 sangalans
to a certain and brutal death.
On the other hand, if you authorize the invasion,
dubaku will undoubtedly engage the cip device.
How far has the faa gotten
with grounding aircraft?
Still over a thousand planes in the air across
the country waiting for clearance to land.
Dubaku could bring down any
one of them at any moment.
Or... use the device for something far worse.
I ran for office on the principle
of non-negotiation with terrorists.
How can I abandon that now,
the very first time I'm tested?
And, if I do so, won't I be telling
dubaku, and the rest of the world,
that blackmailing america works?
Madame president, those are
questions for the future.
We have a decision to make now.
What do you call this place?
We like to think of it as ctu.
What's left of it, anyway.
Jack...
chloe.
It's good to see you.
It's good to see you, too.
I'm glad you're with us.
I'm not with anyone until someone
starts answering some questions.
Might as well start with you.
Why the hell are you not dead?
I was dead, jack.
For almost ten minutes.
Or so I was told.
- By who?
- By him.
His name's david emerson.
I don't know who he paid off at ctu,
but it was his people who injected
my body with a hypothermic compound,
and was able to revive me.
Who is he and what does he want?
Independent contractor.
Enlists ex-military and intelligence
operatives, jobs them out to clients.
Apparently, I fit the profile.
What profile?
Former employees with grievances
against the federal government.
Emerson had been keeping tabs
on me ever since I left ctu.
After michelle was killed...
he figured I'd make a good recruit.
And everyone else thinking
you're dead, so much the better.
Yeah.
And since then, you've been working
undercover to expose his operation?
- No, jack.
- What?
I was really working for him.
I was angry.
I hated the federal government
for what it took from me.
I ran emerson's crew for more than three years.
And I did some pretty bad things.
What made you turn against him?
The cip device.
Emerson had my crew stealing
components to breach the firewall.
I knew what that meant:
Innocent americans would die.
And I didn't signed up for that.
Damn it, tony! Why didn't
you call the authorities?
- He couldn't, jack.
- Why not?
He found out emerson's client was dubaku.
That's who you believe has
agents inside the government.
The juma regime controls
sangala's vast diamond wealth.
Dubaku hasn't been shy about throwing it around.
How widespread is the corruption?
Pervasive. That's why tony came to me.
He didn't know how far or high up this thing went.
Dubaku is the key to this thing, jack.
If we're going to uncover the conspiracy,
we have to get to him before he leaves the U. S.
That's why I have to get
back under soon as possible.
There's a new job in the
pipeline for me and my crew--
I don't have all the details,
but I do know that it'll get me
in the sa room with dubkau himself.
The challenge is going to be
reinstalling tony with emerson.
We have to assume emerson knew tony was in
fbi custody and somehow managed to escape.
Emerson's going to think tony
made a deal with the U. S. Attorney.
That's right.
I can help you with this.
Yes, you can.
Outside of the three of you, who
else is involved in this operatn?
It's just us. This is it.
Please, at least tell me that you've got
some proof that this conspiracy exists.
Yes, we do. But only at the lowest level.
At this point, we've just
begun to scratch the surface.
Okay.
I'll work with you.
But only because, right w, you
are the only people that I trust.
You give me one reason to question
that, and I swear I will turn you in.
You understand?
All right. Chloe, set up the call with emerson.
I found two freelancers who might work. Angers.
- You trust them?
- Yeah. I've worked with them before. They're close.
- Litvak knows them, too.
- Okay.
They may want to know more about
the job before they sign on.
Only thing they need to know is what it pays.
all right.
- Yeah?
- It's me.
Tony.
Where are you?
I'm at a parking garage, getting a car.
I got away from the fbi.
Yeah, I heard.
I also heard it was jack bauer who broke you out.
That's right.
That doesn't make any sense, tony.
Uer's working for them. He helped capture you.
It's only because he didn't have a choice.
He's on board now.
What do you mean "on board"?
You heard about the senate hearings this morning?
They're going to file
criminal charges against him.
I told bauer that if he
helped us out with the mission,
you could get him out of the country.
Look, david, if it weren't for
jack, I'd still be in custody.
We can use him, I'm telling you.
I don't know, tony.
Morgan's hiring new men now.
Morgan's a thug.
He can't run point on something this important.
Let me do it like we planned.
Bauer can take tanner's
place and we're good to go.
All right, bring bauer.
We're at 2211 chesterfield.
- Right off nolan.
- Got it.
He buy it?
We'll see.
mr. Taylor, I understand you were looking for me.
Yes, agent gedge, I have to go out and
I'm going to need some transpoation.
Certainly. Where will we be going?
I'll direct you on the way.
I need a destination for the manifest, sir.
As before, I'd like you to
keep this off the manifest.
And no driver this time, just you and me.
I thought we were through with
all the subterfuge, mr. Taylor.
Please just do as I ask.
I'm sorry, sir, not without an explanation.
It's samantha roth.
She says she has new information
regarding my son's death.
Mr. Taylor...
I thought I was done with this, too, believe me.
I didn't initiate this. She called me.
Brian...
I know you felt obligated to report
my prior activities-- and rightly so--
but i would still like to think that I can
count on your loyalty when I ask for it.
I could lose my job, sir.
This will be the last time. I promise.
Henry?
Please.
- I'll call you as soon as I secure a vehicle.
- Thank you.
Who was that?
Staff, nothing.
- Here, can you help me with this?
- Sure.
It was a gift from my father. You remember?
On the day I won back his seat in the nate.
Prime minister matobo has asked to see me.
He's going to want to know why I
haven't authorized the invasion yet.
What are you going to tell him?
I don't know.
The american people elected you because
they trust your judgment, allison,
and they're going to trust you to
make the right call on this, too.
I don't know what the right call is.
The right call...
is whatever you decide it is.
How many units in the field?
17-- all availab
agents are deployed.
Widen the grid-- we have to assume bauer and
almeida have gotten outside of our perimeter by now.
On it.
sean hillinger.
Sean, its me.
Christina. Where are you?
I'm calling from the plane.
You haven't landed yet?
No, th-the pilot says we're
in a holding pattern...
but we just keep circling and circling, and
I can see other planes out the window, too--
eight or nine, at least.
Christina, sweetheart, relax.
But the woman sitting next to me says
she heard something about a near miss
and a problem with the air traffic control system.
Sean, do you know anything about this?
Yeah, it's true.
The faa has grounded some planes,
but it's only a precaution.
- Really?
- Yeah, it was an isolated incident. You're going to be fine.
Okay. I just...
I got worried there for a
minute. You know how I am.
I do. Now, listen, I want you
to call me as soon as you land.
I will.
I love you.
I love you, too.
Was that your wife?
Janis told me her plane's still in the air.
You okay?
Okay, there's a maniac out there with the
capability of bringing down planes at will,
so, no, erika, I'm not okay.
Her flight is number 18 in the
queue, so it'll be another two hours,
at least, before hers gets clearan.
I'm sorry.
Is there anything I can do?
No.
No, there's nothing anybody
can do; that's the problem.
Yeah, she's right here. I'll
let her know. Thank you, bye-bye.
Renee.
I just got off the phone with the hospital.
Tanner's regained consciousness.
Is he well enough to talk?
He's well enough to ask the doctor
to make a phone call for him.
- Who did he call?
- Gage whitney pace, which is a law firm, I think.
The second largest in dc.
Go grab your laptop, janis. You're coming with me.
I am?
Why?
Because we have to get to
tanner before his lawyers do
and because if I can get
almeida's location out of him,
I want you on-site to vet the
intelligence to our field teams.
- Go.
- Okay.
Tell me about emerson.
He's british, former sas.
Urban warfare, sniping, close-quarter combat.
Saw action in beirut and mogadishu.
So he's good.
Extremely.
But he's not some wack job or ideologue.
He's about two things--
money and personal loyalty.
Sounds like you still admire him.
Listen, jack, he treated me like a
brother when I thought I had nobody else.
Is this going to be a problem?
No.
I know he's on the wrong side of this.
I'll do what has to be done.
We're here.
- Where's emerson?
- Inside. Come in.
David.
Good to see you.
Take mr. Bauer downstairs. I need to talk to tony.
What's going on?
Bringing in bauer is not worth the risk.
What are you talking about?
Have a seat.
Emerson will be right with you.
I'd still be in fbi custody if it wasn't for him.
Tony, you already made your case.
We can use him.
I considered it...
but I'm going a different way.
I owe him, david. You understand that?
Yeah, and I appreciate your sense of loyalty.
I always have, but this is business, tony.
You can't have A...
an unknown factor like jack bauer
coming in and messing things up.
so, what, you're going to kill him?
No, you are.
They're going to kill him.
- He'll get out of it.
- What if he can't?
Then jack's death solidifies
tony's position in the crew.
Tony was in fbi custody.
If he'd gone back in there by himself, the
suspicion would have rested on him alone.
So by deflecting it onto jack...
we keep tony's cover viable.
you knew this might happen the whole time.
Yes.
So did jack.
put your weapon down!
Put your weapon down or I will kill him!
I came here to do a job, not
be double-crossed by you.
U're already shorthanded. You need good
men, not like these two traffic cops.
Look what I've done to them.
I am here because I've got nowhere else to go.
Tony said if I helped you, you
could get me out of the country.
Look, if you don't believe me, pull the trigger.
what, are you crazy?
Kill him!
No.
kill him or I'm out of here.
Fine.
keep it.
*****
So you're requesting a priority
landing for flight 112 out of las vegas?
This is not a request. I'm forwarding
an urgent protocol from the white house.
And your name was...
larry moss, special agent in charge.
This is a matter of national security.
Agent moss, may I have your
level five access number?
6223-510.
Thank you, sir.
Flight 112 is moved to the head of the
queue and should be on the ground shortly.
Thank you.
President taylor, this is colonel ike dubaku.
As you have no doubt confirmed, the near-collision
at jfk international was no accident.
We have the cip device.
We have the capability to kill
tens of thousands of american
and we are prepared to do so.
I wanted you to hear it for yourself, prime
minister, so that you would understand my dilemma.
I see.
You are recalling the invasion force.
Well, that determination has yet to be made.
And this device over which dubaku has control, it
poses a significant risk to your people?
Yes.
It's a technology that has the
potential for mass civilian casualties.
And it puts the infrastructure
of my country in grave jeopardy.
What of sangala?
Believe me, no one is more
aware of what's at stake than I.
So you've been informed of the
situation in kasga province?
Juma's troops are advancing on a refugee camp.
Over 2,000 lives are threatened.
Mostly women and children.
There is also the matter of those soldiers
who have, on the promise of american support,
deserted the regime and joined
my freedom fighters on the ground.
At least...
provide us the weapons we need
in order to defend ourselves.
You've been patient with us before, mr. Matobo.
I can only ask that you be patient again.
No please, if you'll excuse me.
Madame president, I implore
you, do not abandon my country.
Mr. Matobo, I will do everything that I can.
I count on you.
Thank you.
You didn't think that I would want
to know about the refugees in kasanga?
Madame president, you have enough to think
about without being burdened with details.
Especially details that might push me
toward proceeding with the invasion.
Ma'am, you have to start focusing
on alternates to the invasion.
Give me a good alternative and I'll consider it.
I'm not saying it's a good
alternative, but it's the only one.
Comply with dubaku's demands.
Stand down the task force.
That's your recommendation?
- Back down?
- It is.
Damn it, ethan, you heard matobo.
He's has fighters on the ground counting on us.
Do you want me to be responsible
for another bay of pigs?
Kennedy survived the bay of
pigs, and you'll survive this.
A superpower has to act first and
foremost in its own best interests.
- Always?
- Always.
No apologies.
What about allowing a third party
to dictate its foreign policy--
- does a superpower do that?
- Yes,
if there's no other option.
And right now, there's not.
What have we heard from the fbi about
the search for almeida and bauer?
Nothing, ma'am.
Check with them anyway.
No hard feelings, jack?
Forget it.
Have to be careful in our
profession. I'm sure you understand.
- Yeah.
- We all know the drill.
Disagreements are fine, but when a
decision's made, fall in or you're gone.
I've heard a lot of guys say that.
Good to know you mean it.
Before you were subpoenaed, you traveled
the world, place to place, more than a year.
Why?
What were you looking for?
It doesn't really matter.
Whatever it was, I didn't find it.
You must have known what was waiting.
Why'd you come back?
Wanted to know what it was
like to walk into a propeller.
That's funny.
But no, really.
Why?
This is my home.
That doesn't expelf in to the justice department.
Tony said you were in beirut and mogadishu.
And afghanistan.
Two tours. Went back a third
time as a private contractor.
Be polite, professional, and have a
plan to kill everyone you meet, right?
Pretty much.
That's the question, isn't it?
Where do the rules of engagement
end and the crimes begin?
You want to know why I came back?
That's why.
I'm not sure I follow.
I just got tired of talking to myself.
You see, I actually believe
everything I did was right.
So I wanted to start a dialogue.
Come clean, set the record straight.
First mistake.
So I found out.
No one who hasn't been to the edge
and looked over can ever understand.
Yeah.
it's good to have you on board, jack.
yeah?
What was that about?
He's just trying to get a handle on me.
Watch yourself around him, jack.
And do not underestimate him.
I won'T.
All right, listen up.
I just got the call. We're a go.
A go for what? We don't even
know what the hell the job is.
Picking up a package, delivering it to our client.
Here's the location.
A residence at 167 foxhall road.
It belongs to the state
department. Memorize the layout.
We don't know the exact spot of the
pickup yet, but probably the master suite.
The package is a person.
Ye, it is.
Former prime minister matobo of sangala.
The assignment is to grab him
and deliver him to colonel dubaku.
The colonel wants to ask him some questions,
and as you can imagine, the
colonel can be quite persuasive.
Now, matobo hatight security, so finish
arming up, be prepared to engage.
We roll in two minutes.
They're going to kidnap matobo. We
have to alert somebody and stop this.
No, we do nothing.
But you heard them-- they're going
to torture him and probably kill him.
Unfortunately, yes.
Matobo single-handedly led the fight
against genocide in his country.
- He doesn't deserve this.
- I understand that, chloe.
But if we don't go along with the grab, jack
and tony will not find colonel dubaku,
and we will not get to the
bottom of this conspiracy.
Agreed?
agreed.
I don't want you to wait for me.
Sir?
Just drive away. I'll call you when I need you.
You know I can't do that, Mr Taylor.
We're already off the manifest, Brian.
She won't talk to me unless I'm alone.
All right, I'll take up a position on the bridge.
She'll never know I'm there.
All right.
Mr. Taylor.
Sam.
I can't stay long.
What you told me on the phone, is it true?
Yes, they killed roger and
made it look like a suicide.
Who? Who did this?
The same people who provided false documents to the
sec to show he'd been trading on inside information.
Who arthey?
I don't know who they are.
They just said that they would
kill me if I said anything.
Easy, easy, sam.
Easy.
I loved him.
I know you did, sam.
But right now, I really need to know what happened.
Roger was tasked with auditing
the brokers in his department.
That's how it started.
When was this?
January.
Uh, early january.
The compliance officer at his firm asked him to flag
any undisclosed ownership in securities positions.
I don't understand.
Basically, kickbacks.
But what he found was something else.
Two of his portfolio managers
had taken on a new client.
The bahamas branch of switzerland's
oldest bank: Bank lausanne international.
What was wrong with that?
Bank lausanne's records revealed that it was
actively trading with firms doing business in sangala.
Sangala?
It jumped out at roger, too, for
obvious reasons, and digging deeper,
he uncovered other blind accounts
that were copying the bank's trades.
Which accounts?
Accounts that were traced to a senior
member of your wife's administration.
Who?
I don't know.
But whoever it was had a vested
interest in the proposed military action.
Somebody who was betting against her,
who didn't think she'd be able
to pull it off politically?
Betting heavily in 10,000-share blocks.
Roger was a day or two away from
presenting her with the evidence.
It's all here.
Account numbers, trading
records, everything that he knew.
I'm sorry that I can't help you out more.
Samantha...
I've given you all I can.
Do what you have to do, but leave me out of it.
Please?
Okay.
Thank you.
Is tanner in there?
His condition is still listed as critical.
Are his lawyers here yet?
No.
But they will be any minute.
Okay, get wn to the lobby
and keep an eye out for them.
Call me as soon as they enter the hospital.
Got it.
Come on.
hello, mr. Tanner.
I'm agent walker. This is agent gold.
We're with the fbi.
I think you remember me.
I know you're in pain, so I'll make this brief.
Tell me where tony almeida is.
Does almeida have another base of operations?
Is that where the cip device is?
My lawyers...
cannot help you, mr. Tanner.
You're going to spend the rest of your
life in prison if you don't cooperate.
But if you do, I give you my word, I
will personally vouch for you.
Helping me find the device can go a
long way towards reducing your sentence.
I'm sorry. Is something funny?
They'd never let that happen.
Who is they?
Colonel dubaku? Is that who tony
almeida takes his orders from?
Do you work for him too?
Go away.
Open your eyes, mr. Tanner.
I said open your eyes.
Look at me!
Is dubaku here in this country?
Does he have the device?
Renee...
renee, renee...please.
I don't know what you're doing.
What are you doing?
- walker.
- Tanner's lawyers just arrived.
All right, thanks.
His legal team is here.
I need you to stall them.
Me? How am I supposed to do at?
I don't care. Make something up.
Just keep them out of this
room as long as you can.
I'not coortable with this.
Comfortable with what?
We are breaking about 50 federal
guidelines just by being here.
Listen to me, janis.
This man is our only lead.
That man asked for legal counsel.
I heard him.
Thousands of lives are at stake here.
We either bend the rules a little bit
right now or we lose this chance forever.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I just...I can'T.
Look, tony almeida and jack bauer
escaped custody on my watch.
I have to make this right.
You either help me or you don'T.
Okay.
*********
You're out of time, mr. Tanner.
Tell me what you know.
You can do what you want to me.
I'm not going to tell you a damn thing.
who do you work for?
You can't do this...
where is almeida?
How do I find the cip device? Tell me now.
My lawyers...
you can't do this.
You're fbi.
This is illegal.
I have rights.
I suggest you use your last breath wisely.
Go to hell.
I assure you, I'm taking this very seriously.
Then tell us where our client is.
As I said, he was moved for security reasons.
Into the annex?
Yes, sir.
Then why isn't he there?
Listen, if I can just get on
the phone, I'll call my office.
We'll get to the bottom of this...
we've had enough of your help, agent gold.
I...
I'm genuinely confused too.
Excuse me.
We're trying to find our client, mr. Alan tanner.
Just a minute.
I've got a ventilator malfunction.
Damn it! He's coding!
Get a team and a crash cart over here, stat!
Code blue: Room 421, tanner.
It's blocked or something.
- We have to get in there!
- I'm trying to!
- It won't push.
- Open this door!
This is an emergency!
I can't get the door open.
It's jammed!
Is somebody in there with him?
He's all yours, counselor.
Wait a minute.
We need to talk to you!
Renee...
you don't want to know, janis.
Don't ask.
Have agent alves drive you back to the office.
- Hillinger.
- Let me speak to larry.
Sir, I've got walker on the line.
Did you get anything?
I may have a lead on aeida.
Apparently, there's a plot in place
against the former prime minister sangala.
Matobo?
Tanner says almeida's crew
has a plan to abduct him.
- When?
- Pretty much now.
Listen, larry, if almeida's still a part of this
and we can get there before him, we can set a trap.
All right.
I'll alert the prime minister's
security detail and scramble a tac team.
Matobo's housed in a state department residence:
167 foxhall road.
I'm on my way.
Renee, do not go in alone.
Wait for backup.
Right.
Is this major etolo?
It is.
This is special agent larry moss, fbi.
This is not a drill.
Code: Alpha alpha delta.
Lock the prime minister down.
I repeat, lock him down.
Yes, sir.
we're clear. Go.
Where's matobo?
I don't know...
where is he?
Where is he?
I got him!
drop the weapon! Now!
Put the gun down!
On your knees!
Where is matobo?
You will not be able to get to him now.
What is happening, ule?
Who is doing this to us?
Stay calm.
It's going to be all right.
It's dead.
- What you got?
- It's a safe room; reinforced concrete.
Why the hell didn't we know about this?
You have three seconds to open the door.
- One... I can'T.
Two...
it can't be unlocked from the outside.
It can only be opened from the inside.
Jack, if we leave here without matobo,
we lose our only chance of getting at dubaku.
- =www. ydy. com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-»‚
÷Ì ≈› -=www. ydy. com/bbs=-
24 Season 07 Episode 04