I can't reach her!
Please help me.
I can't move.
There's two more
trapped inside that one.
Help me. I... I can't move. Oh, my God.
Sarah, save what you're doing. I need you.
- What is it?
- I just heard from one of our sources.
There's a probability that someone from our
FBI watch list was spotted in LA yesterday.
- Tomas Sherek. Who is he?
- He's worked with terror cells near Istanbul.
He's suspected of coordinating
suicide bombings last summer.
Istanbul?
There was some chatter this morning about
a possible attack by a group out of Turkey.
Here it is. From Ankara.
- What was the target?
- East Coast. New York or DC.
- But the time window passed.
- Passed?
The targeted time is for 8am.
It's already past ten on the East Coast.
What if they got the target wrong
and it's West Coast time?
Then it's gonna go down within the hour.
- Tell Curtis. I'll take this to Driscoll.
- I can take it.
- Why?
- I thought you wanted to keep working it up.
You're really transparent. Stop trying
to be Driscoll's pet. She doesn't like it.
Any voice confirmation
from anyone on the train?
No. The signals just confirmed a bomb.
We're trying to get in contact. It's in a remote
area, but local police are heading there.
All right.
We have discretionary authority
out of Point Mugu.
Have them direct a patrol aircraft over the
area. Put the pilot in contact with our people.
- Should we monitor emergency services?
- No. County will cover that.
A truck full of C-4
derailed a train in Santa Clarita.
Free up some people.
Division's gonna send data.
- That could be related to what we found.
- What did you find?
Two things. First, intelligence indicated the
possibility of an attack at eight this morning.
Bombing was at seven. That's within an hour.
What's the second thing?
A Turkish national on the FBI watch list,
Tomas Sherek, was last seen in the city.
- He could be related to the bombing.
- OK. Open up channels with Division.
Start investigating this bombing.
Work up what you have on Sherek.
We'll brief in a few minutes.
What about the Defense Department meeting?
It's in a half hour.
Who's Secretary Heller sending?
Jack Bauer.
Jack? Are you sure?
Yeah. He hasn't been back...
well, since you fired him.
- Is it gonna be uncomfortable?
- What?
Going back to CTU. Seeing Driscoll again.
I don't blame her for her decision.
How can that be? She forced you out of CTU.
She didn't want an ex-junkie.
That's not unreasonable.
You weren't a junkie.
You were doing your job.
I was addicted to heroin.
It didn't matter why.
Do you miss your old job?
I could have joined other agencies
if I still wanted to do field work.
But I didn't.
I wanted something different from my life.
It might not seem like a lot to you.
But for me...
To be able to have this
kind of a connection with someone...
I couldn't do that before.
I'm glad you can now.
- We'd better go.
- Yeah.
Secretary Heller's gonna be
in the lobby in five minutes.
- Secretary Heller?
- Yeah.
I called him Dad once in a press conference
so I decided then to use his title all the time.
Audrey...
Your father's a very perceptive man.
I would like to tell him about us
before he finds out on his own.
Look...
My dad is kind of old-fashioned.
Even though Paul and I are separated,
he still considers us married.
I understand that. And I don't want
your father to draw the wrong conclusion
and think that I had
anything to do with the break-up.
Yeah, but you didn't.
Please, Jack.
Let's just give it a little more time.
I'm gonna tell you something
and I don't want you to panic.
I'm falling in love with you.
Look, I don't want you to say anything.
And I don't need you to feel the same way.
I just wanted you to know.
- I will see you downstairs.
- Yeah.
All right. This is what we have.
A known terrorist named Tomas Sherek
managed to enter the country undetected.
There's a likelihood Sherek
helped organise the train attack.
If he did, he's gonna get
out of the country as fast as he can.
Which means we have
a small window of opportunity here.
Who's covering airports and customs?
I am. I've issued a mandate
to LAX, Long Beach and Ontario.
As usual, Edgar, we can't hear you.
Where's your laptop if you need to pull data?
Sorry, I'll speak up. And I don't need
my laptop. I have everything memorised.
What I was saying is that I've asked
all the airports to add a layer of security.
- Any local contacts for Sherek?
- I'm looking into those now.
All right. Promote everything
we receive up to Division.
Let's find Sherek
before he leaves the city. Let's go.
Excuse me. Do you think it's a mistake
to assume Sherek is on his way out of LA?
- No.
- But the timing on the intel doesn't match.
It said 8am and the train bombing
happened around seven.
Just focus on finding Sherek.
-  Yes.
- It's Tomas.
- Did Dar get the briefcase?
- Yes. He's on his way to you now.
Good. You did well, Tomas.
- What about Maurice?
- He's waiting for you.
He has everything you need.
- Behrooz, are you eating with us?
- I'll be right down, Mom.
- I'm concerned about him.
- Concerned? Why?
- I think he's still seeing this American girl.
- You said you'd talk to him.
I did. I told him he was no longer
allowed to have contact with her.
And he agreed, right?
Yes.
But I think he's still seeing her
behind our backs.
- I'll speak to him.
- No.
I'll take care of it.
Behrooz, we're sitting down to eat.
- Behrooz.
- I'm on the phone.
Get off and come down now.
- Who is he talking to?
- I don't know.
Sorry.
- Who were you on the phone with?
- My friend Scott.
- You were talking to that American girl.
- No, I told you, I don't see her any more.
Don't lie to me, Behrooz!
I hear your phone calls at night.
I read your emails.
- You read my emails? That's my business!
- Don't you raise your voice to your father.
While you live under my roof,
there is no such thing as your business.
No more communications with that girl.
Do you understand me?
Don't look at her. You're talking to me.
Yes, sir.
... where a horrible tragedy
struck a short time ago.
An early morning commuter train collided with
a truck that was apparently crossing the track.
Reports are coming in that most
of the passengers were severely injured.
Casualty estimates as high as 30.
NTSB agents have arrived on the scene
and are investigating the cause.
At this time, the authorities
are not saying if this was an accident
or a targeted attack,
but, as you can see, there has been...
So far, everything is on schedule.
- Have you spoken to Tomas?
- Yes.
The briefcase is on its way to us now. When it
gets here, you'll take it to the warehouse.
Why doesn't Dar take it there directly?
He doesn't need to know where our people
are working. That's the safest way.
Behrooz...
If your father seems severe,
it's because our job here is a difficult one.
If we are to succeed,
it's important that we are of a single mind.
I understand.
What we will accomplish today
will change the world.
We're fortunate that our family
has been chosen to do this.
We cannot fail.
Yes, Father.
Morning, Jennifer.
- What are you doing here so early?
- I'm not here early.
- You've been here all night?
- Yeah.
- What are you working on?
- Nothing right now.
I'm just stealing some software
from Adobe and Microsoft.
You're gonna get caught one of these days.
Hey, Melanie.
Don't tell anybody or I'll have to kill you.
What the hell is this?
Whoa.
Melanie, come look at this.
Looks like someone's
trying to corrupt the Internet.
Yeah, but it hasn't started propagating yet.
They're just placing the nodes.
Look at this.
- This could tank every system in the world.
- You've gotta tell somebody.
If I call the feds from here, they'll trace
the call. They'll know I was stealing code.
Then do it from a payphone.
Yeah.
I'm up to speed on the train bombing.
How many confirmed dead?
32.
- I didn't know that.
- Call Carl.
- I will. Thanks, Al.
- 32 dead.
- What's the initial assessment?
An act of terrorism.
When you get to CTU, I want you
to find out all the details and call me.
And listen... I don't want anyone, except you
two, to know about this meeting with Richard.
Of course.
I tried to get ahold of you last night.
Where were you?
- I had dinner with a friend.
- Anyone I know?
No.
- Jack.
- Sir.
I'll call you when I get to CTU.
Yeah, I'll get her. Hold on.
- O'Brian.
- Chloe, it's Edgar Stiles.
You don't need to use your last name.
You've been here over a month. What is it?
I got a friend of yours.
He says he needs to talk to you.
- Who, Edgar?
- His name is Andrew Paige.
Fine. Put him through.
-  Hello?
- I can't take personal calls here.
It's not personal. I found something
on the Net I think you should know about.
There's a fake NAT table
and several large corporate routers.
- It was loaded this morning.
- How would you know?
I was trying to download some software
and I noticed it.
By download, I assume you mean steal,
or you wouldn't have seen a NAT table.
OK, fine.
But I hacked deeper
and I found all kinds of stuff.
What kind of stuff?
I think someone's positioning code
for a major Internet attack.
The thing is, not all
the code remarks are in English.
- What language were they in?
- I don't know.
It looked Middle Eastern.
Like Arabic or Turkish, maybe.
- You find something?
- Sarah was working on Sherek's contacts.
The system flagged Maurice Landstrass.
He owns a dry-cleaners in Studio City.
We found his business is owned by a holding
company based out of Ankara, Turkey.
All right. Give this to Ronnie, tell him
to get over there and see what he can find.
- Excuse me, Miss Driscoll.
- What is it, Chloe?
I just got a call from an old classmate.
He noticed some high-profile
Internet nodes have been compromised.
- This could be related to our present threat.
- Why?
A computer network virus was launched
this morning from a server in Turkey.
That's where Sherek is from.
Should I start working it up?
No.
The bombing and Sherek are all we should
be dealing with now. But pass it to the FBI.
- Excuse me, sir. Can I help you?
- Yes, I have a meeting with Erin Driscoll.
Jack. It's OK, Sarah. This is Jack Bauer.
Oh. Mr Bauer. I'm sorry.
No, it's fine.
Chloe, how have you been?
Not perfect, but OK.
How are Kim and Chase?
Good. They just got a house in Valencia.
Kim's taking care of Angela.
Chase works for a private security company.
That's interesting... I mean, I'm interested,
I just have to set up a protocol.
Yeah.
- Jack.
- Curtis. Is Erin ready for our meeting?
Almost, but I should tell you,
you'll probably get cut short.
- The train bombing in Santa Clarita.
- Among other things.
- What other things?
- I won't bore you with it.
- We're out.
- OK, we'll have you on voice three, data four.
- Ronnie, Jack Bauer. Jack, Ronnie Lobell.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hey, Jack.
- Ronnie's got your old job, head of field ops.
- Yeah, I know. How's it going?
- It's busy. It was nice meeting you.
Would you rather reschedule this?
That won't be necessary.
Erin will be free soon.
Tell you what, why don't you
use this station to make any calls.
- It won't be long.
- OK, thank you.
I don't know, Max. Let me find out.
It's a Vandenberg representative.
How long will they be pushed back?
Don't change anything with Vandenberg.
We'll stick to the original schedule.
OK, Max. Yep. We'll see you then.
- Have you spoken with your brother?
- No.
I don't think he knows I'm coming with you.
It's probably best that he doesn't.
All right. I'll stay in the car.
Dad, if Richard goes to this protest
in Lockheed, it's not the end of the world.
- It's not a page-one story.
- That's not the point.
It's an embarrassment to me
and to the president.
- What are you gonna say to him?
- I have no idea.
What gets to me is he doesn't know
the first thing about the politics of this.
- He's doing it to rebel against you.
- Since when am I the enemy? What did I do?
Nothing. Richard's acting like a spoilt child.
He's gonna have to grow up someday.
- Audrey Raines.
-  It's the president calling.
It's the president's office.
- Heller here.
- Please hold for the president.
-  James.
- Yes, Mr President.
I'm thinking of raising the terror alert level.
Because of the train bombing?
No, not just that.
Langley's picked up some chatter.
We have intel on watch-listed individuals
who've gotten into the country.
My instinct is to wait
until the NTSB weighs in on the bombing.
In the meantime,
we can increase our state of readiness.
All right. I'll take that into consideration.
I'm meeting with the secretary of state
and Director Shaye in a few minutes.
- I'll see if they feel the same about it.
- Yes, Mr President.
Thank you.
- Hello, Erin.
- Hello, Jack.
- I'm sorry Secretary Heller couldn't be here.
- It's just as well.
I'm sure you were told
we have a protocol in progress.
So why don't we just go down the items
and get it over with?
That's fine with me.
I'll be direct with you, Jack.
- I didn't like the budget your boss proposed.
- What's the problem?
Well, this Department of Defense is asking
for 85 per cent of all interagency monies,
which leaves very little for CTU.
If you want a bigger piece,
you're gonna have to justify it.
I have a proposal for you.
Satellite surveillance for harbour traffic?
- Yes. Problem?
- Yes. It's insufficient.
- You need to maintain bodies on the ground.
- Too expensive.
Not if you utilise intelligence
from other agencies.
I am not gonna have Secretary Heller sign off
on a budget that doesn't make sense.
- I'll talk to Heller about it myself.
- No, you'll talk to me.
We're not doing this twice.
-  Erin, Ronnie's arrived at Landstrass'.
- Where's the feed?
On channel one,
as soon as he sets the hidden camera.
Excuse me, Jack.
OK, here we go.
Stand down until I give the order.
Aaron, go around the back.
Sean, you're gonna take the side.
Hello?
- Can I help you?
- Are you Mr Landstrass?
- Do I know you?
- Ronnie Lobell. I'm with Los Angeles CTU.
I need to ask you a few questions. What do
you know about a man named Tomas Sherek?
I don't know this name.
We have records of you
contacting him in the last two days.
- Wasn't me. I run a legitimate business here.
- I never said your business wasn't legitimate.
Look, you just can't
walk in here and harass me.
- He's hiding something.
- It's being handled, Jack.
Listen to me. His store's open, but the blinds
are closed. There's no other employees.
This guy is way too nervous.
Trust me, he's hiding something.
Ronnie, turn your back
on Landstrass for a moment, please.
It says you open at 6am.
Have you been here the entire time?
Yes. What's this about?
Right there.
Do you see that?
Tell him to look for something on his right.
Ronnie, on Landstrass' right,
see if there's any place Sherek can be hiding.
- Do you mind if I look behind that counter?
- Yes, I do.
Look, this is my store
and I want you to walk out now.
I'm not walking out until I look around.
- Back door!
- On the ground!
He's headed back to you!
It's Sherek. We've got him.
Great job.
Remember, Dad,
we're on a tight schedule today.
Richard.
Dad.
- Hello.
Hey, it's me.
- Aren't you supposed to be with Driscoll?
- Yeah, she had to step away.
CTU has just picked up a prime suspect in the
train bombing. They're bringing him in now.
- My father's still in with Richard.
- I'll brief him later. I wanted to let you know.
- All right. That's good news.
- Yeah. I think so.
All right.
- I'll talk to you later.
- Wait, wait.
- What is it?
- Look...
About earlier... I don't want you
to think that that made me uncomfortable.
- It's just, since Teri died, I never thought I'd...
- Jack, it's all right.
- I understand.
- No. No, you don't.
I just want you to know that...
I'm falling in love with you, too.
Wow.
- You caught me off guard.
- Yeah, I'm sorry about that.
- Driscoll's coming back. I gotta go.
- Then go.
- OK. I'll talk to you when I get a break.
- All right.
- What's happening with the suspect?
- Ronnie's bringing him in.
- Who is he?
- Fortunately for you, Jack,
it's our problem, not yours.
Right.
I'm going, Dad.
And there's nothing you can do to stop me.
How many cars do you need to get places?
I didn't come here
to argue about the environment.
I didn't ask you to come at all.
I do not want you to attend or to speak
at that rally at Lockheed this afternoon.
You don't have leverage over what I do.
Not since I stopped taking your money.
Can't you think of anything besides yourself?
If you do this, it will humiliate the president,
and it will be dangerous to national security.
What could be more dangerous
than 2500 missile delivery systems?
Spare me your sixth-grade
Michael Moore logic.
The world is a little bit more complicated
than that, Richard. We do not live in a utopia.
America has enemies.
Enemies who were our friends a year ago,
and in another year, it'll change again,
unless people stop supporting your
psychotic need to control the world.
Psychotic need? We serve our country!
We serve the cause of freedom.
What do you do?
Why don't you just go back
to your little motorcade and drive somewhere
where people actually buy
the lies you're selling.
OK, look. We don't have to do this, OK?
We do not have to.
Fine, Dad. What do you wanna do?
Do not disrespect me. I am your father!
Nothing. It was my friend, not me.
What's his name?
- Andrew.
- Andrew what?
- Andrew Paige.
- Who did you tell?
- I swear, we didn't tell anyone. I don't know.
- Don't lie to me.
- He just stumbled on the site and logged out.
Don't lie to me!
Where is Andrew Paige now?
I was just doing my work. I don't...
Use station five. Chloe's opened up a socket.
You can access the records volumes
- to look at those budget numbers.
- OK, fine.
- I know this guy.
- Sherek?
When I was here, we knew him as Jann Bolek.
We linked him to over a dozen bombings
in Europe in the late '90s.
We weren't able to stop him
from today's attack, but we did catch him.
Jack, I'm sorry I was abrupt before.
You helped us with the takedown. Thank you.
Erin, listen to me.
This doesn't make sense.
I know this guy's file, he's a major handler.
He wouldn't risk exposing himself here in the
US for a train bombing. It's not big enough.
We'll consider that when we interrogate him.
Give my best to Secretary Heller.
- Chloe.
- What?
The original data on Sherek - was there
any indication of a secondary strike?
No. Everything supports that he was here for
the bombing. There was a time discrepancy.
- What?
- There was some high-probability chatter
indicating an attack at 8am.
The bombing was at seven.
They didn't give a window?
It was for a specific time?
Yeah, but the intel was off by an hour.
Driscoll thought it was close enough.
- You can't do that.
- What's your logon for Interpol overnights?
- I'm not comfortable doing this.
- Chloe, please.
You're in.
- Is this the source?
- Yes, that's the decipher.
An 8am strike, unless target deviates. Trains
don't deviate. They're on a fixed course.
Sometimes when Interpol's breaking codes in
communiqués, it won't use the exact wording.
What are you thinking, Jack?
Sherek didn't come here for a train bombing.
Something's gonna happen at eight o'clock.
That's ten minutes from now.
No, Paul. I don't wanna wait.
I'm gonna call my lawyer when we get back
to DC. We're gonna get this divorce moving.
- We said take a year and see what happens.
- Yeah, but it's almost been a year.
I don't wanna wait any longer.
Hang on.
Look, I gotta take this call. All right?
We'll talk when I get back to DC.
- Yeah, fine.
- All right. Bye.
-  Jack.
- Hey. I need to speak with your father.
- He doesn't want to be interrupted.
- It's urgent. I need to get clearance
so I can interrogate the suspect in
the bombing. Driscoll won't let me near him.
I believe he's got information
on a secondary hit, a larger one.
- It's supposed to take place at 8am.
- It's almost eight now.
- I know. That's why I need to speak with him.
- All right. Hang on.
I'm gonna speak at that rally
this afternoon, Dad.
And it's not because I hate you.
It's cos it's something I believe in.
Did it ever occur to you
that these people are using you?
Don't you realise they're letting you speak
for one reason and one reason only?
Because you are my son!
I wish I weren't.
- What is it?
- I'm sorry. It's Jack. It's urgent.
Excuse me, Richard.
What could be more important
than intimidating me?
I didn't know you were hiding in the car.
Richie, why are you doing this to Dad?
Can't you back off?
- I'm not doing anything to him.
- If you go to that protest, it's gonna hurt him.
Whatever it takes to stop what he's doing.
Jack, if I step on Driscoll's toes and it doesn't
pay off, I'll have political fallout to deal with.
I understand, but I wouldn't ask if I didn't
believe there was a threat to national security.
Share your concerns with Driscoll.
Let CTU handle it.
- Sir, there isn't time.
- It's the president.
Jack, it's the president.
I gotta go. I'll see you at Vandenberg.
Yes, sir.
How long have you been in Los Angeles?
Who are you working with?
We don't have time for this.
Listen to me.
Unless you start giving me answers, you're
gonna end up in a hole for the next 30 years.
Who are you working with?
Why did you bomb that train?
- How far can I push this guy?
- We have to find out who he's working with.
We should go as far as we have to.
Maybe we should bring Johnson in.
- Sorry, sir. This area's off limits.
- Oh, I'm looking for Erin Driscoll.
Jack! Jack, what are you doing?
Call security now.
- What is happening at eight?
- Son of a bitch. He's jammed the codes.
I am not messing with you. You are gonna
tell me. What is happening at eight o'clock?
Holster your weapon!
Jack! I said holster your weapon.
- Call medical.
- What is your primary objective?
- I'll order security to shoot you!
- Get that door open!
What is your primary objective?
Secretary of Defense!
Heller.
- Secretary Heller?
- Yes.
Secretary Heller's the target.
Call Secret Service now.
- Call now! Get a team on the way.
Secret Service now.
Yeah, I'll hold.
The president wants us back in DC tonight.
- What meetings can we eject?
- Not Vandenberg. The media's expecting you.
Maybe we could skip Paradigm and handle
that with a teleconference next week.
Come on, pick up the phone!
Tell the president we'll rearrange
and fly back this afternoon.
- Yeah.
- Audrey, it's Jack. Are you still at Richard's?
- Get your father out of there now!
The bombing this morning was diversionary.
Your father is the real target. Get out!
- Target?
- Audrey!
Oh, my God.
Audrey?
On your feet!
Jack! No! Jack!
- Audrey!
- Jack! Jack!
Let her go!
Let me go.
Jack! Help!
Visiontext Subtitles: Simon Campbell
ENGLISH SDH