This is Bauer.
Air Traffic Control received
a VCI distress signal from your aircraft.
That authorises Logan to shoot you down.
Start taking us down.
Do it now.
Jack, the F-18 is within 15 miles.
My radar is locked on the target.
- Lower the landing gear.
- We're going too fast!
Touch it down.
- They're ready to move Bierko.
- Thank you. I'll be right out.
Vladimir Bierko, you are being transferred to
a primary holding facility at our headquarters.
The attorney general's
on his way to his office now.
He'll be ready in ten minutes.
Chloe, I want you
to prepare the recording for playback.
Apply a digital signature so we can establish
a chain of evidence. Work alone.
We got the evidence. President Logan's
gonna pay for David Palmer's assassination.
The spectacle of a sitting president
on trial for murder would be devastating.
Yes, it would.
If only we could keep such a trial
from taking place.
Mr. President?
Miles Papazian. I work under Karen Hayes.
- What is this about?
- It's about a recording, sir.
If leaked, it could significantly compromise
national security.
- Why are you telling me this?
- I feel compelled to intervene.
And I just wanted to make sure
that you would approve.
I do, Mr. Papazian. I do approve.
Get out of here, Miles.
- I'm just doing my job, Chloe.
- If your job is to slow things down.
I'll tell Karen you'll be ready.
- The attorney general will be ready in five.
- Did you tell him this implicates Logan?
No. I feel he needs to hear it
directly from the source.
Fine.
- What's your status?
- Everything is set up.
I've got a T1 line to the attorney general.
- The other two lines are secured.
- What other two lines?
Someone from the House judiciary committee
and a Congressional liaison.
We need their support to call for Congress
to begin impeachment proceedings.
What about an arrest warrant?
We'll never get justice
to indict a sitting president.
Removing him from office is
a necessary step to begin a full prosecution.
All right, Chloe. Let's check the sound levels.
Play the recording.
- What's wrong?
- I don't know!
- Where's the recording?
- This is what's on the digital media.
That's impossible. See if there's an overlay.
Check your connections.
- There are no mistakes.
- Dammit, Chloe. What the hell happened?
I don't know. If there was something
on this chip, it's been erased.
- Yes?
- The attorney general is on the line.
- Ms Hayes?
- Bill will take the call in a moment.
I'll tell him we're having technical difficulties.
- Someone got to that recording.
- Perhaps it was damaged.
It wasn't.
- Who had access to this room?
- No one.
Someone did.
Who had access? Think about it!
- Miles was in here.
- What?
You sent him in here to check up on me.
I never sent him in here.
Jack.
- Security, stop him.
Mr. Bauer.
Jack. Jack, stop.
- You son of a bitch.
- Let go of me, Bauer.
Do you know how many people died
so I could bring that in?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- We know it was you.
Let him go, Jack. Jack, let him go.
Where are you going, Miles?
I've been transferred.
I was told to report immediately.
- The order should come through any minute.
- Transferred to where?
The White House.
How could you do this, Miles?
This is not over.
There will be an investigation.
Do what you have to do, Karen.
But I work for the president now.
Jack, I am so sorry. I don't know how
he did it. He didn't even touch the recorder.
Karen, Audrey heard the recording
when I played it for Heller.
- I know that she will sign an affidavit...
- Jack, not now.
Chloe, take the recorder down to Processing.
See if you can restore anything.
Fine.
Ms Hayes. The president is calling for you.
Line two.
- Mr. President.
- Karen.
What's this I hear about a conference call
you've scheduled with the attorney general?
It's nothing, sir. A mistake.
The conference call was cancelled.
Good. I'm glad to hear that. Listen,
the real reason for my call is Jack Bauer.
- What about Jack Bauer?
- After further review,
it appears that the evidence against him is,
at best, inconclusive.
I will have our lawyers continue to work on it,
but for the time being,
I'm suspending the arrest order.
- You're dropping the charges against Bauer?
- That's correct.
Mr. President, you have had this office,
other agencies and the military
dedicate all manpower and resources
into apprehending Bauer.
Yes, based on evidence
I initially thought was credible.
Now I have new information that's convinced
me that the original intel was faulty.
- Am I to release Bauer, sir?
- I'll leave that to your discretion.
Thank you, Karen. Good work.
We'll be in touch.
Yes, Mr. President.
- He's letting me go as he knows he's won.
- What does he gain by releasing you?
I'll be on my own.
Alone, unprotected - a perfect target.
- Word just came in. Bierko's escaped.
- What?
- How long ago?
- The convoy was hit ten minutes ago.
They took out all our agents except one,
Davis, on line three.
- Davis, Karen Hayes. What happened?
- Our lead car got taken out by an IED.
I counted six attackers. Bierko got away
before I could call in backup.
- Did you see the vehicle?
- Negative. I blacked out when I got hit.
- There's a medevac team on the way.
- I overheard Bierko talking to his men.
- He said they're not finished.
- Not finished?
Yes, ma'am. I'm certain he said something
about a nerve gas canister.
- Did he say anything else?
- I'm sorry. That's all I heard.
All right, Davis, stand by.
The medical team will be there in a minute.
Why would Bierko mention the Sentox?
I assumed all the canisters
were destroyed in the explosions.
How many canisters are accounted for?
After the fires, there was not enough left
to do a full accounting.
- Dammit.
- Bill, raise an interagency alert.
I need LAPD to do a sweep
of the ambush area for witnesses.
I want search helicopters. I want Chloe to
have full domain over surveillance satellites.
This is priority one.
We have got to find Vladimir Bierko.
We held one in reserve, just as you ordered.
But I still don't understand why.
We can't do much damage
with one canister of nerve gas.
You're so wrong.
Let's go.
E- e-excuse me, Agent...
- It's Agent Cole, ma'am.
- Cole, I'm sorry, Agent Cole.
My husband said Pierce had been transferred
to Washington, and this is his phone.
I was wondering if you'd make sure
that it's returned to him.
Of course.
Was there anything else, ma'am?
No.
There's nothing else.
Oh, my God.
I'm sorry about this, Aaron.
Listen to me, Aaron.
You think you know what's going on?
- I'm here to tell you that you don't.
- Why don't you explain it, Mr. President?
I understand Jack Bauer led you to believe
that there was a recording -
something that tied me
to David Palmer's murder.
- That recording doesn't exist.
- That's not what I've been told.
You're not hearing what I'm saying.
The recording doesn't exist.
It's over.
You have a choice here, Aaron.
You are a good man.
You're a fine agent.
I see no reason to throw away your career.
But I need to know
that we can put this behind us.
Give me your word you will let this drop,
and I will make sure that you are reassigned
to whatever post you want...
except for the White House, of course.
So...
what's it gonna be, Aaron?
Are my terms acceptable?
There is nothing that you have said or done
that is acceptable to me in the least.
You're a traitor to this country,
and a disgrace to your office.
And it's my duty to see that you're
brought to justice for what you've done.
Is there anything else... Charles?
I know Pierce, Mr. President.
I've served with him for five years.
His loyalty is to David Palmer. Believe me
when I tell you he's going to be a problem.
Mr. President. I confess
I didn't expect to hear from you again.
The situation's changed.
Everything's under control.
The recording's been destroyed.
It's no longer a problem.
That's very good news, but what about
the people who have heard it?
They can't do anything without proof. I don't
think any further action needs to be taken.
And you've got
the rest of your house in order?
If by that you mean my wife, yes.
Yes, she's cooperating fully.
As for Aaron Pierce, that's another matter,
but, um, I'm taking care of that.
Of course. What about Jack Bauer?
I've given Karen Hayes permission
to release him.
The arrangements that we discussed
about taking him out have been set in motion.
You have everything well in hand,
Mr. President.
Yes, yes. I said I would handle it, and I have.
The situation's contained.
There's nothing more to worry about.
I'll call you back.
Mike?
- Sir.
- What is it, Mike?
I just got off the phone with Karen Hayes.
- Vladimir Bierko has escaped.
- What? How?
The caravan transporting him to District
was ambushed.
Dammit! We rolled CTU into Homeland
Security to avoid screwups like this.
There's more, sir. They have reason to believe
Bierko might be readying another attack.
- What kind of attack?
- CTU's working on that now.
I want constant updates.
You keep me apprised of their progress.
Yes, sir.
- Chloe, any luck?
- Only the bad kind.
None of these satellites were positioned
toward the ambush site. I tried to redirect.
- Did you try Caltrans?
- I'm backstreaming. So far, it's dry.
- We've gotta get an ID on the vehicle.
- I know.
That was LAPD Command.
They can't find any witnesses.
- None?
- 4am in a curfew. No one was there.
Then we have nothing.
- Henderson.
- What about him?
He set up Bierko with the nerve gas.
He won't talk to us, and you know that.
If Henderson's the patriot he says he is,
he won't want those terrorists to succeed.
- Trust me, he's not gonna help us.
- He will if we offer him a deal.
- And that's not gonna happen.
- Jack.
No. Not this time. Not this man.
We're running out of options. This is
about saving lives, not indulging a grudge.
You think this is about a grudge?
He killed an ex-president.
He tried to kill the secretary of defense.
You want him to have full immunity?
It's about doing what has to be done.
Nobody knows that better than you.
Bierko's gonna kill innocent people.
Henderson's our only chance to stop him.
Jack. What would David Palmer
want you to do if he were here?
The best way to honour his memory
is to make the choice to save others.
I can't stop you from doing this. If you're
gonna give him a deal, let me present it.
- All right.
- Thank you.
Since you're clearly no longer a fugitive,
I assume they retrieved that recording.
Someone got to it and erased it.
I'm not here about the recording.
Bierko escaped half an hour ago.
He's gonna carry out another attack.
I'm sure he will. You bruised his ego
when you stopped his first attempt.
You know him. You know how he thinks.
You studied him before you set up this deal.
- What's he gonna do?
- Why should I help you?
You call yourself a patriot. Prove it.
These terrorists are gonna attack the country
that you love because you betrayed them.
Why don't you help me
put out the fire that you started?
They sent you in here
to broker a deal, didn't they?
What's the offer? Full immunity?
It just must be really eating you up inside.
What do you think? You were responsible for
the murder of people that I cared about.
I am sorry about David Palmer, I am, but
what I did was in the interest of this country,
and I'm not talking about the version
you read in the New York Times.
I'm talking about the politics of survival.
The way the world really works.
You want immunity or not?
- Immunity is worthless.
- Yeah?
Jack.
That recording was my only immunity.
They give me a piece of paper,
I walk out of here, I'm a dead man.
Two days, two hours, two months,
who cares? They're gonna take me down.
Who's "they"?
Same people who made Walt Cummings
look like a suicide.
Come on, Jack. You can't really believe
that Logan masterminded this by himself?
- Give me the names.
- You can't touch them.
But they can touch you.
I'll help you catch Bierko,
but not for an immunity deal.
I need something more,
and you can make it happen.
- What do you want?
- To disappear. Just like you did.
I won't make your mistake. I'm gonna
leave the country, and take Miriam with me.
- You don't need my help for that.
- My contacts are still loyal to the president.
I need somebody I can trust
to cover our tracks.
I need somebody to do a better job of it than
the incompetents who failed to cover yours.
What makes you think that I'm not gonna
kill you the second this is over?
Because you're gonna give me your word.
And I know what your word is worth to you.
So it's all I need.
Let's say that I agree to this.
Anything less than Bierko's head on a plate -
this deal is off.
Fine.
Now, Bierko is gonna hit hard,
so you'd better think fast.
Chloe, do a phone check on these 14 names.
I want you working out of the situation room.
- What do we have?
- Henderson gave us 14 names.
- Chloe's pulling up relative data.
- Is Tactical standing by?
On priority alert.
I put Manning in command, if that's OK.
- I trust your judgment, Bill.
- Henderson's coming in here for a debrief.
Excuse me for one second.
Audrey.
Jack, I just heard about the recording.
- President Logan managed to get to it.
- My God.
- We have a more immediate problem.
- Bierko. I heard. I was hoping I could help.
Why is Henderson coming out of Holding?
We're using him to help us find Bierko.
Audrey, Karen made a deal.
She gave him immunity.
What? Jack, how can you let this happen?
We didn't have a choice. Bierko's planning an
attack. Without Henderson, we won't find him.
Jack, I think we've got something.
Audrey, I'm sorry. I gotta go.
What do we have?
- Only one of the 14 has an active cellphone.
Joseph Malina.
Malina's an arms dealer. A military contractor
until they accused him of selling secrets.
- But they couldn't prove anything.
- You know him?
I did business with him
before and after he was arrested.
What do you have on him?
- A 12-second call on his phone at 4:03am
from a payphone in Van Nuys,
not far from the ambush site.
A minute later the same payphone
got a callback from a GSM sat phone.
He took the number down,
and called from an untraceable line.
- Sounds like our guy.
- Tell Curtis to mobilise his team.
Hang on, hang on.
What good is that gonna accomplish?
You bring Malina in,
you think he'll roll over on Bierko?
He didn't cut a deal before,
he's not gonna cut a deal now.
And even if you can crack him, you're
gonna need hours. You don't have hours.
- What do you suggest?
- I suggest you send me in to talk to Malina.
I'll find out what Bierko got from him.
- I don't think so.
- You know you can't get anything out of him.
His computer makes this place
look like an internet café.
He's got the absolute most sophisticated
security system, including a Phoenix shield.
- We get through it.
- Not a Phoenix. It's a poison-pill firewall.
Any attempt at circumventing it
and the hard drive does a cold start erase.
You can forget about retrieving any data.
Take him back to Holding.
- I don't think we have a choice here.
- Karen, please. Don't do this.
Jack, I know how you feel,
but Henderson's right.
- We can't afford to gamble on this play.
- You cannot trust this guy.
I agree. That's why I'm sending you with him.
I want him under your guard on a tight leash.
If he tries anything,
I swear to you, I will kill him.
Then don't let it get to that point.
Get in.
Adams, listen to me.
You don't have to do this.
Logan isn't worth protecting. He's not gonna
get away with any of this. Neither will you.
- Get in the trunk.
- Use your head.
Logan wants me dead because
I know too much, I'm a liability.
How soon before you're just another liability?
Agh!
What are you doing?
Ma'am, please stay where you are.
Aaron?
You're going to shoot me?
I'm the first lady.
You're gonna shoot the first lady?
- Who are you calling?
- Mrs. Logan, this is my last warning.
Agh!
Martha.
Aaron. Oh, God.
Aaron. Stay with me.
Aaron, oh, God. Oh, God, Aaron.
Jack. We're coming up on Malina's place.
Curtis, set up a perimeter.
A man on each possible escape route.
- You got it.
- You got ten minutes.
You don't get the intel by then,
we come in and interrogate him.
Interrogating won't work.
This guy won't break.
You better hope your way does.
Give me an audio pack.
- Undo your shirt.
- You can't wire me.
- Why not?
- Think about it. You read Malina's file.
He didn't get here by being careless.
He's got a scanner, God knows what else.
The second I walk through that door with
a wire, the bells go off, this thing's over.
Look, you don't trust me - fine. And just
so we're straight, I don't trust you either.
But neither one of us
can afford to blow this operation.
We're all set. They're in position.
No games, Christopher. I don't need
another reason to put a bullet in your brain.
You got ten minutes.
- Patch CTU in. Monitor channel eight.
- Got it.
Hold up.
Go.
Who is it?
- What do you want, Chris?
- We have to talk.
- What, at 4:30 in the morning?
- About Vladimir Bierko.
You don't waste my time,
I don't waste your time.
You're gonna wanna hear what I have to say.
Hey! What's so important it couldn't wait?
- What are you looking for?
- Is there another way outta here?
What are you talking about?
I don't like this. What's Henderson doing?
I don't know yet. Maintain your position.
- Secure files, anything you can't do without.
- Why?
Because there is an entire phalanx of CTU
agents outside, including ex-agent Bauer.
- He's selling us out, Jack.
Bauer is running me.
But I know he's gonna kill me
first chance he gets.
- Curtis, move your teams in now.
- All teams, move in. Now!
- Bastard, you brought him here!
- He was coming here anyway!
Secure the files, crash the system.
Stop wasting time and do it.
Give me your weapon.
Freeze!
Agh!
- Cover Malina.
- Christopher! Let me see your hands, now!
Slowly, stand up.
Put the weapon on the counter.
Step back.
- Curtis! How are your men?
- My men are fine. I've been hit. I'm OK.
Call in Medical. Get 'em to CTU.
What's Malina's condition?
- Gunshot to the hip. He's losing blood.
- Stabilise him. Keep him alive.
I had him. 30 more seconds was all I needed.
- You played me. This is over.
- No, you blew it, Jack.
- What you talking about?
- I got him to lift the firewall.
He was about to dump all of his files onto
a flash drive before you jumped the gun.
You're gonna waste a hell of a lot of time
trying to decrypt those files.
So you better pray
there's something on there you can read.
Cuff him.
Bill, get Chloe to open a channel. I'm gonna
send you some files from Malina's computer.
- I'm on it, Jack.
- Find which files were last open.
They'll tell us what Malina sold Bierko.
- They're coming through now. Hang on.
- Curtis was hit. He's coming back to CTU.
- All right. I'll tell Medical.
- Send a chopper to this location.
As soon as we know the target,
we need to move fast.
It's gonna take me some time
to decrypt the files.
Do it as quickly as you can. Bierko's gonna
release the gas soon. We need to know where.
There, you should have everything.
Let's go.
Aaron.
Charles lied to me. He said
you'd been transferred to Washington.
That... agent, um...
Adams, my husband ordered him
to kill you, didn't he?
Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry to tell you the president was
involved with much worse things than that.
I know.
I was gonna let him get away with it. All of it.
I was gonna keep quiet.
We have to do something.
I'll hide the body. I'll get him in the trunk.
But I can't drive it out of here.
The president has to believe that I'm dead.
I need to lay low. Keep out of sight.
- I can do it.
- No.
- Yes, Aaron. I can drive it.
No, you need to get back inside the residence.
Your husband can't suspect
that anything has gone wrong.
You need to find Mike Novick.
- Mike?
- Tell him everything.
- And tell him to meet me here.
- OK.
Aaron, promise me...
promise me that...
if something goes wrong,
and you're in danger of getting caught,
you will find a way off these grounds,
and you will leave.
Promise me.
You have my word.
- Secure him on the tailgate.
- Yes, sir.
- Buchanan.
- Bill, how's Chloe doing with the files?
- Almost there, Jack.
- OK, I got it.
Wait, there's something more.
Classified defence contracts and plans.
It's a Russian submarine.
The Natalia K 524 Delta IV class.
It's scheduled for inspection by our navy.
Why is the US navy
inspecting a Russian submarine?
It's part of the treaty that Logan and Suvarov
signed. It calls for the sharing of technology.
- Where is it docked?
- Docking station eight. Port of Los Angeles.
- I'll deport tac teams to the port.
- Good.
Chloe, hold on.
What is the armament package
on a Russian Delta IV class sub?
- 12 Scorpion land-attack missiles.
- Are they nuclear?
No, but they carry multiple warheads.
One could take out several city blocks.
Uncuff him.
- Karen, it's Jack. Are you still there?
- I'm here.
I need you to put me in touch
with the ranking US officer on the Natalia.
We need them to lock out
their onboard weapons systems.
I'll have Audrey call DOD and open a priority
line to the sub. She'll get back to you.
- OK. Thank you. You're coming with me.
- I found Bierko's target for you.
- The deal was Bierko's head on a plate.
- What do you want me to do? Kill him?
The only reason you're going with me is
because you know the weapons system.
Get in.
Let's go!
Bauer.
I've got the ranking officer
on the Natalia. I'm putting you through.
- OK, Audrey, stay on the line.
- All right, Jack. Hold on.
- You're on with Jack Bauer.
- What is this about?
We believe the Natalia
has been targeted for a terrorist attack.
Secure your vessel. Lock down
your weapon systems immediately.
Skeet, call all hands. Set condition Delta.
Seal the bridge and aft hatches.
- Aye, sir.
- Put your men on alert.
- There's a threat to your submarine.
- Horosho.
- Now, what is the nature of this threat?
- The terrorists are after your missiles.
I'm gonna check right now.
- Sailor! I've got that. Report aft.
- Yes, sir.
Bauer. I'm checking topside.
Lieutenant!
- Dammit, Audrey, I've lost him. Notify DOD.
- I'm on it.
Captain, we need to move.
It's ready.
- Captain, how far out are we?
- Just over five minutes, sir.
- That way.
- Mhy syuda.
Read me the code we got from Malina.
Alpha two five five Tango Romeo nine nine.
Good.
We have control of the weapons system.
Are the missiles loaded?
Vertical tubes are loaded and ready.
Loading horizontal tubes now.