We have a problem. If that hard drive
is discovered by the Americans,
it'll jeopardize the next phase of our plan.
- It's not here.
- Keep looking.
Agent Drake?
Drop the weapon now!
- Jack's on the line.
- Jack, what is it?
I pulled data off a hard drive
in Anderson's apartment.
I believe Mitch Anderson's
trying to steal a Stealth fighter.
We have reason to believe a Stealth fighter
has been stolen by a terrorist.
- It's in your airspace as we speak.
- Just how sure are we about this?
It's a near certainty, Mr President.
This is a Stealth aircraft.
If he finds you, he may be on you
before your fighter escort can react.
Mitch Anderson, we know who you are,
we know what you're trying to do.
Captain Anderson? Captain Anderson?
We've been cut off.
Is there an override channel?
He cut off all communication circuits.
We can't do anything.
Dad.
I'm scared.
Air Force One has been fired on.
Repeat, Air Force One has been fired on.
Oh, my God.
Was Air Force One just hit?
Escort pilots report...
Air Force One has suffered an indirect hit
by an air-to-air missile.
Pieces are falling to the ground
over the desert.
This is Air Force One,
declaring an emergency.
Repeat, Air Force One
is declaring an emergency.
Copy. What is your condition? Over.
Extensive damage
to the portside wing and fuselage.
We've lost pressurisation.
Losing fuel pressure. Lower hydraulics...
- Are those the coordinates?
- They're 20 nautical miles northeast of Indio.
Edgar, contact local PD and EMS.
- Alert them of the situation.
- On it.
Tony, do we have
any CTU support teams in the area?
The Las Vegas office
has two satellite teams available.
I'm gonna dispatch coordinates
to all teams in LA and Vegas
so they can start for the site now.
Steady glide.
Left wing flaps damaged.
Edgar, pull up satellite on the national park.
Pinpoint any possible landing scenarios.
Chloe, what's happening?
We've lost the signal.
They're moving and losing altitude.
Change the frequency.
- OK, I've got it.
- ... six knots. All engines are out.
Going through 7500 at 210 knots.
Roger, 210 knots. Sir...
- Are you still reading coordinates?
- They're making the turn.
Roger, I'm close to a stall.
We are putting her down.
- No gears deployed. We are still hard and fast.
-  OK. Roger that, Air Force One.
Air traffic control, this is CTU. We are sending
EMS, police, and rescue teams to the site.
-  Copy that, CTU.
-  Descending through 5500, 160 knots.
- Chloe, what's showing on radar?
-  We are on the deck. Going in.
Chloe!
- Air Force One is down.
-  Air Force One?
Air Force One, do you read?
Air Force One is down.
I got a confirm of scattered ground flashes
from the DOD satellite.
Edgar, bring that up.
- What's the status?
- It's down.
- What's its crash like?
- Rough. We don't know if there are survivors.
- Patch coordinates to all agencies.
Got it.
- Anybody try subchannel comm stat?
- No.
Secret Service has at least five personnel
on board. All of them have private channels.
-  Comm stat three, operator.
- This is Bauer, password F-H-Ralphie-four.
-  Go ahead.
- Flood AF1 with an acknowledge signal.
Copy.
Comm stat three calling AF1
one through five, please acknowledge.
AF1 channels one through five,
please acknowledge.
-  Channel three.
- Who's this?
-  Patterson. We're down.
- What is the status of the president?
I don't know. I can't move.
Agent Patterson, my name is Bauer,
I'm with CTU. Rescue units are en route.
What else can you tell me?
I see some bodies.
I think we have some survivors.
Mr Vice President,
I've just received confirmation.
Air Force One sustained a hit
from an air-to-air missile
fired from the stolen Stealth fighter.
- Is the president alive?
- We don't know at this time.
- When will we know?
- Hopefully within the next few minutes.
Charles.
We've known each other for 15 years.
If I can offer some advice?
Of course.
We all hope President Keeler is alive,
but even if he is,
it's very likely he won't be
in any shape to run the country.
You need to make arrangements
to be sworn in to office as soon as possible,
and the media should provide live coverage.
The American people need to be reassured
that their leadership is intact.
That's good advice, Mike.
I'll take it under consideration, but...
I don't want to act prematurely.
I understand.
Well, we have to get to the White House.
I've arranged for a security briefing
with the Pentagon.
That's good.
By now you all know
Air Force One has been shot down.
One of the pilots following Air Force One
managed to get a visual of the fighter used.
Pilot engaged and shot down the Stealth.
The status of the president
is unclear at this time.
Rescue teams are minutes away.
We'll know very soon.
The man responsible for what has transpired
today, Habib Marwan, is still out there,
and likely planning further attacks.
I want every one of you
to rededicate yourselves to finding Marwan.
I don't want a single lead ignored,
or shred of evidence missed.
Let's get back to work.
Michelle, let me talk to you.
Uplink leads to a station
so we can start work on a priority list.
We might not know exactly where Marwan is,
but he has to be in a 50 mile radius...
Jack, I'm sorry, I just got off the phone
with the secretary of defense,
and there's a higher priority than Marwan.
- What?
- Recovering the nuclear football.
- Didn't it go down with Air Force One?
- Not exactly.
The missile inflicted enough damage
that it left debris.
A lot was sucked out,
including the football.
There's a transponder in the casing
so we know its location.
Then the retrieval team
should have no problem.
The secretary wants you to head that team.
- Why?
- It's his top priority.
That case contains the codes and locations
of our entire nuclear arsenal.
Nothing is more critical than getting it back,
and as quickly as possible.
Fine.
- I'll organise your team, mobilise the units.
- Thanks.
- What's the location of the football?
- 40 miles northeast of here, in the desert.
Hey! Hey.
What's wrong? What else is happening?
Paul may have to go back into surgery.
Apparently the bullet
did more damage than they thought.
Sorry.
If I had handled things differently,
if I had trusted him...
Audrey, you are not responsible for this.
I, and I alone,
made the decision on how to handle Paul.
If you want to remain effective,
to be able to do your job,
you have to let it go.
Jack, that's your gift.
You're able to block things out.
I can't do that.
Jack, the chopper's waiting.
- I have to change and get ready.
- All right.
Honey?
What's wrong?
I don't know. Something woke me. It sounded
like some kind of explosion or something.
Explosion? Nearby?
I'm not sure.
- It was probably just a bad dream.
- Yeah.
You're still stressed, aren't you?
I want you to try and forget about work, OK?
Just focus on what we came out here for.
To relax,
and to make a baby.
Look.
- What?
- Watch your step.
- OK.
Oh, my God.
Kelly!
What is it?
If the president is unable to fulfil his duties,
Vice President Logan will assume office.
- Cabinet will need to be briefed on the crash.
- I'll take care of it.
Not all members are equal. State and Defense
need more detail than, say, agriculture.
Yeah, I can handle it.
- I want to make sure the transition is smooth.
- I understand, but I do know what to do.
All right.
Tony.
I've noticed a little hostility on your part.
If it's because of me and Michelle...
It's none of my business.
And as far as the hostility goes,
I can promise you it's over with.
Whatever you say. One more thing.
I think the world of Michelle.
Loved working with her.
Outside work, we never got off the ground.
She never said why, but it didn't take a genius
to figure it out. She cared about you.
If you ask me, she still does.
Mr Buchanan,
rescue teams are inside Air Force One.
We're picking up a live feed now.
There's damage
to the fuselage and hatch.
Go and check... check to see if he's alive.
Check him. See if he's alive.
Got a body here. She's dead too.
The president
was in the conference room.
Copy.
He was in the conference room.
-  What?
-  Got a survivor!
I'm going in. Keep close.
Looks like the president's son.
He's dead.
- Where's the president?
-  This may be him.
-  Wait, hold on. This may be him.
-  It's the president.
He's still alive. I repeat, the president is alive.
We need medevac teams in here ASAP. Do
you read that? We need medevac teams here.
- Novick.
-  I have Buchanan.
Yes, he's right here. Bill Buchanan.
- Bill.
- Mr Vice President.
I'm in direct contact with the teams
at the crash site of Air Force One.
President Keeler is alive.
- Thank God.
- Yes, sir.
But he's in critical condition.
He's unconscious, he's lost blood,
there's no chance he'll be able
to lead this country, not for days,
and probably much longer.
- Mr Vice President?
- Yes, I'm here.
This is all confirmed?
The president is being medevacked
to the emergency centre as we speak.
Sir, I recommend
you invoke the 25th Amendment
and take control of things
as soon as possible.
I understand.
Thank you, Bill.
Keeler's alive, but he's incapacitated.
We should probably
contact the cabinet members.
Actually, I've already put that in motion. Most
are standing by, the others will be very soon.
- You did that without my permission?
- You had enough to worry about.
I thought it best to be prepared.
Yes.
All right.
Thank you.
Shall I begin the process of collecting votes?
Yes, go ahead.
I can't get a signal.
Try up here.
- Got it.
- Kelly, look at this.
- What is it?
- I'm not sure, but if it's what I think it is...
I read this article, it's a funny name... I can't
remember, but it's got our nuclear codes.
It goes everywhere the president goes.
He can launch an attack from it.
- We gotta call somebody.
- Who are you gonna call?
I'll start with the police, I guess.
They'll put us through to the right people.
The football transponder's
signal's still strong.
- Hello?
-  Hey, it's me.
- Hey.
- When I walked away from you at CTU,
I felt like you didn't understand
what I was trying to say.
I'm not telling you that you shouldn't care.
I care.
I care about you,
I care about what happened to Paul.
I feel responsible.
But this country is under attack.
I've got a job to do. I don't have a choice.
Jack, I understand
what you have to do is very important.
I just didn't want us to leave things like that.
I'm glad. Me neither.
- Hold on a second. I gotta take this call.
- Wait, Jack. Take the call, all right?
Stay focused on what you have to do.
- Yeah, I'll talk to you in a little while. Bye.
- OK.
- This is Bauer.
- Jack, it's Tony.
I got a guy the police put through.
He's in the desert, says he found a case.
- Jack, this guy found the football.
- OK, let me speak to him.
His name's Jason Gerard. We're running
a check. I'm patching him through now.
OK, Tony, stay on the other line.
- Mr Gerard?
- Call me Jason. I'm with my wife, Kelly.
My name is Jack Bauer.
I'm an agent with the Department of Defense.
My colleague says you found
what we refer to as the football.
It looks that way.
I don't know much about this sort of thing.
- My wife and I are here on a camping trip.
- Why don't you describe what you found?
Sure. It's a black leather briefcase, it's got
a number panelling over by the handle.
It was in a case
with the presidential seal on it.
That sounds like it. Right now I'm
in a helicopter. I'm about 20 minutes away.
Look, I just want you
to hang out there and wait for me.
I think someone beat you to the punch.
I see headlights.
- How far away?
- It's hard to tell. A few miles.
OK, just hold on a second, Jason.
Tony, this kid says
he's got headlights headed towards him.
- Do we have any ground units in his vicinity?
- No.
Highway patrol, park rangers?
- How can that be?
We're spread thin, Jack. All state agencies
are still assisting with the evacuation.
- Jason, are the headlights headed for you?
- Yeah, they're coming this way.
Dammit! This situation
just got a lot more complicated.
- What do you mean?
- The football has a transponder.
It allows anyone to pinpoint its location,
as long as they've got the frequency.
You think someone's got it
who's not supposed to.
- We have to make that assumption.
- Who do you think it is?
The terrorists who carried out today's attacks.
We don't have time.
Remove the transponder and take the football
and get away from there as far as you can.
All right.
Flashlight. I need your light.
OK, go ahead.
The transponder's tiny
and it's hidden in the case.
- It's designed not to be found.
- How will I find it?
- Do you have a compass and a flashlight?
- Uh, yeah.
- Get the compass.
- OK.
OK. I want you to move the compass
over the surface of the case, slowly.
The transponder puts out an electromagnetic
field. It should move the needle.
Just move the compass over
the surface of the case and watch the needle.
Here, here, here, here.
- Keep the beam on the compass.
- OK.
I think I got it. I found it. I found it.
OK, good. Take a knife or a sharp rock
and start scratching the surface, hard.
- Hurry.
- Dammit!
- Jason, they're coming.
- Come on, Jason. Talk to me.
I am working on it.
OK. I think I got it.
OK. Take the compass, put it over the scraped
area and tell me, is the needle moving?
- No. No, it's not.
- You've disabled it. How far is the vehicle?
- Not far.
- OK. Take the football and start moving.
I don't care which direction,
start moving now. I'll get back to you.
We gotta go. We gotta go now!
Tony, I'm going to need surveillance
of the entire area put up to my screen.
Why are we stopping?
- We've lost the signal.
- How is that possible?
- Maybe it was damaged on impact.
And it just happens to malfunction
now that we're getting closer?
Scan the area for cellphones.
Active and passive signals.
- Yeah?
-  Jason.
We found a reserve power station
half a mile north of you.
- That's right. I remember it from the map.
- I want you to go there.
- OK, yeah. We'll get there.
- The station's a large, unmanned facility.
I want you to break in and hide. Avoid using
your flashlight, and as soon as you hang up,
- take your cell batteries out.
- The batteries?
It'll prevent passive triangulation. In other
words, it'll stop you from being followed.
- What if I need to contact you?
- Put them back in, but only if you have to.
I'm gonna give you my direct line.
Have you got a pen?
- Yeah. Hold on. Go ahead.
- 310...
597-3781.
"781." OK, yeah, I got it.
- Start moving now!
- OK.
He said to take the battery
out of the cellphone. Come on. Come on.
I had a cellphone signal for a few seconds.
It was moving, but it's gone now.
- Did it move enough to yield a vector?
- Wait.
Yes. It was headed a few degrees
west of north just before it cut out.
Check the map.
See if there's anything near there.
There's a reserve power plant.
A kilometre away, maybe less.
Whoever has the football,
that's where they're heading.
This is it.
Stay back.
We're not in any danger, right? I mean, how
could anyone even know that we're here?
We're just being safe. A nice,
relaxing weekend in the desert, just like I said.
They're here. I gotta call Jack.
Come on.
- This is Bauer.
- It's Jason. These terrorists, they're here.
- How many?
- I just saw two Jeeps.
- Where are you?
- Inside the plant. When will you get here?
- Soon. Just stand by.
- Go, baby. Go! Come on. Just keep moving.
Tony, it's Jack. We're out of time.
We need schematics for the plant now.
Yeah, it should be on your screen
in a few seconds.
OK, I got it. Thanks.
- Jason, are you still with me?
- I'm with you.
- Which side of the building did you enter?
- Uh, the south side.
This is a large facility. I want you
to go to the lower level, southeast corner.
- I'll find you there as soon as we land.
- OK. Hey, Agent Bauer? Please hurry.
We are.
Find them.
There's got to be stairs somewhere.
Come on.
- There. There they are.
- Wait. What if it's a dead end?
Keep going!
- A man and a woman.
- Where?
This way.
They went down here.
Follow them and flush them out.
Go around and cut off the exits.
Come on. Keep going.
Come on. Go up there. Go up there. Go on!
- Come on. Come on, come on, come on!
- OK.
- Anything?
- Nothing.
Helicopter.
- Intercept it.
- Yes, sir.
Jason.
- Where are you?
- We've just landed. Where are you?
Inside the plant, on the lower level.
Jack. Jack!
- Are you there?
- I'm here.
They're inside.
We cannot keep hiding, they're gonna find us.
I know. You gotta keep moving.
I'll get right back to you.
- Stiles.
- It's Jack. I need to speak to Audrey, now!
- Ms Raines, Jack's on line one.
- Jack.
I'm taking fire. The other agent's dead.
I need the code for the football.
All right, hang on.
Just take the football.
Take the football. Come on!
Come on!
- Jack, *76114.
- I got it.
- Hey.
-  Jason.
I need you to open the case.
The combination is *76114.
- Why? What is the point of this?
- Just do it. *76114.
He wants us to open the briefcase. *76114.
- OK, it's open.
- OK.
Inside should be a phone,
a control board, and the playbook.
I want you to remove the book,
give the case back to your wife.
The two need to stay separate.
- Why?
- The board is useless without the playbook.
I need you to split up.
- He wants us to split up.
- I can hear him.
- I am not leaving my wife.
- You have to.
- Forget it.
- Jason, please. Listen to me.
I know how scared you are, but if he gets
what he wants, he'll kill both of you.
Right now, the only chance you have
to survive is to separate. Do you understand?
It's OK, Jason. He's kept us alive this far.
Let's just do what he says.
- Just get here as fast as you can.
- I will.
I love you.
Give me the backpack.
Listen.
- Here, you take the phone.
- OK.
I want you to go to that top level there,
all right? I'm going to stay down here.
- You just find a place to hide, all right?
- OK.
Go, go, go. Go! Go! Go! Hide! Hide!
Hey!
I've got him.
He's clean.
- Where's the control board?
- I don't know what you're talking...
- Tell me what I want to know.
- I swear, I don't know. Please.
It doesn't have to be this painful.
Bauer.
- They got my husband.
- Where are you? I'm on the lower level.
We had to leave. We're on the second floor.
I don't know where.
- OK, I'm on my way.
- They're gonna kill him.
Kelly, stay on the phone. Keep talking to me.
- I can't.
- Kelly!
- Oh, please!
- Where is the control board?
Stop!
I have what you want.
- Give it to me.
- First you let my husband go.
No!
OK.
I'll give it to you if you promise not to kill us.
I won't kill you. I promise.
It's over there.
It's behind the pillar.
- It's locked.
- What is the code?
It's, uh... star 7-6-1-1-4.
It's here.
Let's go.
OK. It's OK.
Kill them.
No!
This is Jack Bauer, I need a medic.
Second level, north end of the building.
On our way there now.
It's all right. He's gonna be OK.
Help is on the way. Where is the football?
They have it.
They went out that door. I'm sorry.
Don't be. You did great. Thank you.
Air support, two hostiles left the building.
I do not have possession of the football.
Repeat, I do not have the football.
Air support, football is in the lead Jeep,
headed north. Take it out.
I repeat, take it out.
Put your hands where I can see them.
Air support, I cannot see the football
in the vehicle. Shine your spotlight on me.
And follow.
Air support, I'm in possession of the football.
Go after the other Jeep.
- Almeida.
- It's Jack. I've got the football.
Three hostiles down, one escaped.
I'm not positive, but I think it was Marwan.
I'm sorry, but I had to make a choice.
Marwan gave us the football
to buy his freedom?
- Yeah, that doesn't sound right.
- What are you thinking?
I don't know.
Let me ask you something.
Is anything missing?
No. All the components are here.
Hold on one second.
I was wrong. There are pages missing.
Look, the sections are colour-coded.
What's missing?
Red chapter, section three.
- Get Audrey.
- All right. We'll call you right back.
- All right, take care of it.
- Yes, sir.
You're worried about him.
I am. He seems unsure of himself.
Oh, Mike, trust me.
He's spent his whole life preparing for this.
He's just being cautious,
feeling his way along. He'll be fine.
- Yeah.
-  The call came in, all in favour.
All right, thanks.
The vote was unanimous. The 25th
Amendment's been officially invoked.
Tell the press we're ready. Let's get this done.
Mr Vice President,
the 25th Amendment is in effect.
- Any dissenting votes?
- None.
We should proceed with the swearing in.
Yes. The ceremony will take a minute,
then you can address the nation.
I'm still not certain a live address
makes sense this time of night.
After what's happened,
an aawul lot of people are wide awake.
I'm sure they'd like to hear from you directly.
Yes, of course.
We're ready, sir.
Please. Please.
Thank you very much, ladies and gentlemen.
- Yeah.
-  Jack, it's Tony.
- Is Audrey there?
- Jack, I'm here.
Tell me the contents of the pages.
It's the section which contains
warhead locations and activation codes.
We started cancelling codes
as soon as Air Force One went down.
But there are thousands of warheads.
It's gonna take an hour.
In the meantime, if they get ahold
of a warhead and a matching code,
we will not be able to stop them.
Copy that. I'll get back to you.
-  Mr Novick's office.
- Let me speak to Novick.
Yes, sir. Right away.
I solemnly swear that I will faithfully execute
the office of the president,
and will, to the best of my ability,
preserve, protect and defend
the constitution of the United States.
Mr President, I appreciate it.
I appreciate you coming.
- As most of you know...
- Novick.
Mike, it's Jack. We got a problem.
...this oath under tragic circumstances.
Words cannot express the sense...
The football's been compromised.
Yes, I'll tell him.
...due to injuries sustained during the crash.
He is in our prayers, as well as our hearts.
Mr President.
- I've just received a phone call from CTU.
- Yes?
I'm sorry, sir, but it appears
at least part of the nuclear football
has fallen into the hands of terrorists.
Visiontext Subtitles: Jo Clarke
ENGLISH SDH