Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net
Abu Fayed, a citizen of your country,
enters the United States,
detonates a nuclear bomb, killing thousands.
Next, Assad attempts to
assassinate the president.
You know we have cooperated with you
since the inception of this crisis.
- I had an understanding with your president.
- Now have one with me.
You help us find those nukes
before another goes off,
or I'm gonna unleash
our military on your country.
- I'm terminating the American. Confirm?
- Yes.
- The American shot Vasili in the basement.
- Shut down the phone lines, DSL, everything.
- Morris, I know how to find Gredenko.
- (static on phone line)
- Morris?
- Jack?
Jack?
Jack Bauer is being held
in the Russian consulate.
Doyle will help you put a tactical profile
together for an assault on the consulate.
Our primary objective
is to abduct Anatoly Markov, the consul.
Markov knows how to find Gredenko, who
controls the remaining three suitcase nukes.
- The Americans are coming.
- I thought you had that under control.
- They'll soon have your position.
- The drone is ready to launch. Arm the bomb.
- What's going on at the Russian consulate?
- Jack is somewhere inside. We have to go in.
Drop your weapon!
My name is Jack Bauer.
You need to contact Buchanan.
Fayed and Gredenko
are in the Shadow Valley.
Patch me in with Buchanan.
- Medevac's on the way. How are you?
- I'm fine.
He may have rib fragments which can cause
internal bleeding. He needs to be stabilised.
I'm fine. I wanna be involved in this.
CTU has the ball, Jack.
Right now, this is out of your hands.
We believe Gredenko has at least five RQ-2
aerial drones somewhere in Shadow Valley.
RQ-2s?
Unmanned aircraft which can be
remotely piloted from anywhere.
He's arming them with the nuclear weapons
he provided to Fayed?
Yes, sir. We're redirecting
satellite coverage over the desert.
The air force is scrambling F-16s.
But you have no idea how close they are
to launching these drones?
No, sir, we don't.
- All right, Bill. Keep me updated.
- Yes, sir.
- Bring the trucks around. We are moving out.
- What's wrong?
How many drones have been armed?
- Just this one.
- Dammit!
We need to launch it now. Get it ready.
- Go, go.
- Tell me what's wrong.
- What's wrong?
- The Americans know our location.
How?
It was Markov, huh? Markov told them.
All that matters is they know we are here. We
need to launch the drone before they close in.
We have three bombs and three targets.
We'll find a way
to deliver the other two bombs.
All this time,
we've tolerated your condescension,
berating us for losing the other bombs.
But now it's your fault. Markov was your man.
Blame me all you want,
but if we stay here we'll be captured or killed.
Refit the bombs into their casings
and load them on the truck.
Do it now! Take them out!
- We're accelerating our schedule.
- Why?
I don't have time to explain.
I need you to launch drone 0709.
I haven't finished implementing
the evasion vectors.
- They'll shoot it before it reaches its target.
- Launch the drone.
You'll execute evasion tactics
once it's in the air.
Yes, sir.
We need to leave now.
Come on, let's go.
We're repositioning our satellites, sir.
As soon as we make visual contact,
we'll uplink a feed to you.
(man) Just get me that intel, Yassir.
Lives are at stake.
Yes, sir.
Are you OK?
The truth? No, not really.
We're gonna get through this, OK?
I hope so.
- Is there a problem, Chloe?
- Yeah.
Are you gonna tell us what it is?
I was installing upgrades and I noticed
you were using Milo's clearance code,
which, if you didn't know,
is a felony security breach.
No, my system's been glitchy and I think I...
It's not a glitch. She's been working with your
ID, so unless she stole it, you gave it to her.
Milo was just trying to help me do my work.
Homeland Security sent down an order
restricting my access
because I was born in the Middle East.
I've heard of that directive.
It's wrong to racially profile our agents,
but it's still a felony
for you to be using Milo's code.
Chloe,
look, we...
If you report this...
We can't help the situation
if we're fired and arrested.
If I wanted to report you,
I wouldn't be talking to you.
I'm telling you this so that you'll be careful.
I mean, I noticed it. Someone else
is gonna notice it sooner or later.
(phone rings)
- (Buchanan) Nadia?
- Yes, sir?
Morris has a satellite visual
on Shadow Valley.
It looks like they've launched a single drone.
- I'm conferencing with General Walsh.
- I'll be there, sir.
Coordinate with first responders
in all target zones.
- Put General Walsh through.
- (woman) Sir, Bill Buchanan.
- This is Walsh.
- (Buchanan) We have contact with a drone.
- We're tracking it.
- It's heading northwest out of Shadow Valley.
Altitude is 3300 feet and climbing.
Velocity is 360 miles an hour.
I'm looking at the specs on the RQ-2 now.
It's got a low-profile design,
virtually impossible to detect by radar.
We'll need to
manually guide F-16s to intercept.
- We're uplinking a video feed now.
- Have you determined its intended target?
Yes. The closest target is downtown
Los Angeles. That's a four-minute window.
Maximum airspeed of an RQ-2
is 400 miles per hour.
My F-16s should be able to intercept it
within two minutes.
That may be a problem. I can't find the drone.
- The drone's gone.
- How can it be gone?
- It was passing between grids, but...
- Use projected vectors.
I am. It's just not where it's supposed to be.
Until you find it,
I'll have my F-16s stay in a holding pattern.
(phone rings)
- Yes?
- I've accessed our connection to CTU.
I've disabled their tracking capability.
Then they cannot detect the drone?
No, and I'll be able to keep it hidden
from their satellites until we've hit the target.
Good. I'll contact you again
once we are out of the area.
Sir, I was talking to Bill Buchanan.
They were tracking one of the drones.
- They've now lost visual contact with it.
- Lost visual contact?
It's unclearjust how, sir.
They just simply can't find it.
We have the most sophisticated
satellite network. How did this happen?
- CTU is still determining that, sir.
- What about the military?
They've got squadrons looking,
but these drones are invisible to radar
so the pilots are limited to making visual ID
at night over hundreds of square miles.
CTU has a ranked list of potential targets.
They're running civil disaster scenarios.
- Lisa?
- Sir.
Advance the meeting with the Joint Chiefs.
- When do you want it to happen?
- Right away.
Wait, sir, why are we assembling
the Joint Chiefs?
I warned the ambassador, Tom.
You heard me tell him
that I'd hold his country responsible
if another weapon was detonated on our soil.
Sir, there is absolutely no evidence
that his country either sponsored
these attacks or is even in support of them.
His people need to understand
that I'm notjust rattling my sabre.
They need to see with their own eyes
that I will answer this threat
with an in-kind military response.
Wait. "In kind", sir?
I want the Joint Chiefs to draw up
our own target list for a nuclear strike.
I won't let another attack
go unanswered, Tom.
At its speed, the drone should've reached
LA, so we can eliminate us as a target.
Soon I can take Santa Barbara
and San Diego off the list.
How many targets does that leave?
Counting cities
with populations over a million, 15.
We have to narrow it down.
Assuming they want the maximum civilian
death toll, how many likely targets in range?
Areas with the highest population density
are San Francisco, Las Vegas and Phoenix.
Confirm that first responders
have deployed in those cities.
Make sure the air force
prioritises their search on that basis.
(Morris) Yup.
Give me the projected coordinates.
Bill. Bill, did we pick up Gredenko?
- We're working on it.
- Bill, what happened?
Gredenko escaped,
but not before launching one of the drones.
- How close is the air force to intercepting it?
- Minutes away when it disappeared.
We're still looking for it.
Jack, get to Medical.
There's nothing you can do here.
- Just keep me informed, please.
- I will.
I want you to run point
on the search for Fayed and Gredenko.
Milo's in the situation room. I'll be right there.
- I'll see you over at Medical.
- Yes, sir.
- Hey. Can we have a moment, please?
- (woman) Certainly.
- They said you were hurt.
- I'm not. I'm fine.
As soon as all of this is over,
I'll come by and check on you and Josh.
I always regretted
things didn't work out between us,
and...
I always believed you did too.
Maybe I was wrong.
No, you weren't.
Listen, Marilyn,
before I was taken prisoner by the Chinese,
I was with someone.
She doesn't even know I'm still alive.
I need to talk to her,
see what happens.
Are you talking about Audrey Raines?
Yeah.
You don't know, do you?
Jack, I'm...
I'm sorry to be the one
to have to tell you this.
Audrey's dead.
I don't know the details, just what I read
in the paper about her accident.
- What accident? When?
- It was a few months ago.
It was a car accident, somewhere in China.
China?
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
I have to go.
(Chloe) There'll be channels open
for first responders in at-risk cities.
All first responders should coordinate...
Why the hell didn't anybody
tell me about Audrey?
Mr Buchanan didn't wanna tell you because
we all thought Fayed was going to kill you,
but I probably should have.
- I'm sorry.
- She was in China looking for me?
She was the one who figured out
the Chinese had you.
Apparently, she spent the past year
going through back channels to get you out.
The rest of it's classified by Division.
I don't know any more.
We were asked to send DNA records so they
could ID the remains, which I guess they did.
I want that file.
- All right, Jack.
- Now!
- I have to dig it up in the archives.
- Just do it.
The secretary of defense
and the chairman will be attending.
The State will monitor via satellite and
the cabinet will be provided with transcripts.
You should also know
that Karen Hayes will be attending.
I thought I told you
I wanted her excluded from this.
She supported Wayne Palmer's policy
of appeasement. She's gonna be a problem.
There was nothing I could do.
She's still acting National Security Advisor.
But I believe, given the circumstances,
any objection to your plans
will not be able to gain traction.
Well, I've known Karen Hayes for many years.
It's always been a mistake
to underestimate... her.
Hello, Tom. Did somebody
push you down the stairs?
No, Karen. I tripped over your ineptitude.
On that subject, welcome back.
Look, Tom, I don't wanna play games.
I won't let you blackmail me again,
so do what you need to.
I am here to represent the president
and I intend to stay, all right?
Fair enough.
Karen? No one is sorrier than I am
about what happened to Wayne.
Well, at least we have that in common.
(man) Karen.
Please be seated.
As many of you are aware, the terrorist
who attacked us this morning, Abu Fayed,
with the help of Dmitri Gredenko,
has launched an aerial drone that we believe
is armed with another nuclear bomb.
Efforts are ongoing to locate this drone,
but should those efforts fail,
we're looking at a second attack
on our country in less than ten hours.
I am determined not to let this attack happen
without a military response on our part.
A military response
directed against whom, Mr Vice President?
We were under the impression
the terrorists were stateless.
Secretary Kanin,
that is the fiction they hide behind,
but everyone in this room knows
that elements within Abu Fayed's country
train and fund terrorist organisations like his.
It is time to hold them accountable.
The ambassador's just been informed that if
the nuclear weapon on that drone detonates,
we will retaliate with our own nuclear strike.
Now, this will be a warning shot,
not a full-scale attack.
The Joint Chiefs have been instructed
to identify an unpopulated area
where there will be
limited civilian casualties. Admiral?
The closest match we have to that scenario
is a territory near their northern border.
This should result in fewer than 2,000 deaths.
The damage from radioactive fallout could
double that, depending on ground conditions.
I can accept that.
You're aware that our intelligence suggests
their government can't control Fayed either.
They are doing the best that they can.
And I'm saying they need to
figure out a way to do better.
Something tells me
that once this bomb hits, they will.
If this bomb hits, the opposite will hold true.
Moderates will be driven from power,
the terrorist position will be strengthened,
and I don't hear anyone talking about
the Chinese or Russian response to this.
We could start another world war.
If I thought that was likely,
I wouldn't be suggesting this.
Mr Vice President, the stakes are too high
for this decision to be based on
your personal judgment.
It is my opinion that this course of action
would be dangerous and reckless.
Consider your concern registered, Karen.
But the debate is over.
America must start to stand up for herself.
The attacks on this country must stop.
As acting commander in chief, I believe
this is the best way to make that happen.
Admiral,
have a nuclear-strike sub standing by.
Yes, Mr Vice President.
Nadia. I never got those files
you were gonna send me.
Yeah, your system was overloaded
so I gave them to Morris to take care of.
- Morris?
- Yeah.
You really think he can handle it?
Well, he seems to be himself again.
You mean he's himself
because he had a drink and he smoothed out?
I don't think so.
Hey, what are you doing?
Setting up a reverse data stream
on the drone's satellite intel, OK?
Morris seems better.
Is that a question?
- Is he?
- Yes.
- Look, I need you to do me a favour.
- No.
I need you to check his breath.
If he's better, great. If he's headed for
another crash, we need to know about that.
Fine.
Thanks.
- What was that for?
- Just checking your breath.
- He's fine.
- Thank you.
Got to love this place.
- Tom? Tom.
- Yes, Karen. I hear you.
You can't be in favour
of Daniels' plan for a nuclear strike.
You heard the vice president.
It's a warning shot into an unpopulated area.
It is a military offensive on foreign soil,
and you and I both know
it will be impossible to contain.
You know this is insane. I know you do. I saw
you in that meeting, the doubt in your eyes.
Do not presume to know
what I am thinking or feeling.
I serve at the discretion of those above me.
You serve the interests of the president,
and Wayne would not sign off on this action.
Wayne was wrong.
Every decision he made today was wrong -
rejecting my security initiatives,
using Assad as an appeal to extremist groups.
- Look what we've been led to.
- You can't seriously believe that.
It doesn't matter what I believe.
As long as the president is in a coma,
Daniels is the acting commander in chief.
If you want him to abort that missile launch,
you had better pray
that CTU can find and stop that drone.
We've got ground teams
looking for Fayed and Gredenko.
Sat support's dedicated to the drone
so there's not much to go on.
Caltrans doesn't have cameras
in the outlying areas.
We figured out how the drone
can stay hidden from our satellites.
Whoever is piloting it
can anticipate our directives,
- flying through the gaps in the images.
- How?
Our data is being relayed to the drone pilot
through a work station here.
We have a leak.
- One of our own people?
- It looks that way.
- Can you isolate the work station?
- No, it's being masked.
Morris is working on it now, but there are
over 50 stations. It could take an hour.
We don't have an hour.
Run a trace match on Nadia Yassir's station.
- Why Nadia?
- Do it.
- Just because she's Muslim...
- It's protocol.
She's already been tagged
and given restricted clearance.
And, yeah, she is a Muslim.
That's enough to go on.
Everyone here is thinking it,
even if they won't say it.
- You're a racist.
- Milo, I understand your distaste.
But we have to vet every system.
There's no reason not to start with hers.
No, sir, there's every reason. Nadia is 100%
loyal to this country. She is not a terrorist.
Is this based on knowledge?
Or because you're itching to sleep with her?
- You son of a...
- All right! That's enough.
Agent Doyle, that was way out of line.
We don't have time for personal differences.
We have to find who's subverting our system.
It is Nadia.
- The signature trace matches her computer.
- Shut down her station.
I'm trying. The only way
is to reboot CTU's mainframe.
We'd be without system power
for 20 minutes.
Get security on the floor now.
- Surrender your station.
- Excuse me?
- Who are you streaming data to?
- What?
- Where is the pilot?
- Doyle, dammit, that's enough!
- Take her to Holding.
- Bill, don't let him do this.
Bill, I'm innocent. I'm not a traitor.
Let go of me!
Morris, secure her station.
See if you can run a back trace on that leak,
find out where the feed is going.
Excuse me.
Victor,
what is the drone's current position?
130 miles southeast of the target.
Have you locked in the GPS coordinates?
Yes. The bomb will detonate
over San Francisco within 20 minutes.
Yes.
15cc's, and I want the drip to stay steady.
Add in some glucose after about an hour.
If you see any movement,
a twitch of the eyelids, you get me. Got it?
(woman) Yes, sir.
- Dr Welton, I need to speak with you.
- I don't have much time, Ms Hayes.
- What's the president's condition?
- It's worsened.
There was a build-up of pressure. We had to
induce a coma to relieve the swelling.
- I see.
- The good news is we stopped it in time.
Doesn't seem to have been any damage
and his vitals are surprisingly strong.
He's a fighter. We have that much
going for us. Excuse me.
- Doctor?
- Yes.
Is there any way to bring the president
back to consciousness?
I know this is an unusual request,
but it's a matter of national security
that I speak with him.
It could pose a serious risk to his life.
I couldn't authorise it.
Who could?
I'd need consent from his family.
His sister's here, but I'd advise against it.
If the swelling isn't contained, the president
could suffer permanent brain damage.
I have to go, Ms Hayes.
This is insane.
- Nadia can't be involved in this.
- The signal was routed through her station.
You really believe
that Nadia's helping the terrorists?
I don't wanna believe it,
but I really don't know.
- (Milo) Doyle's an ass.
- He's doing his job.
If we want him to stop,
we have to prove she's innocent.
- Hello. I think I've got something.
- What is it?
I've set up a feedback pulse. Whoever Nadia's
feeding her data to will read it as static,
but we may be able to ride the pulse back
to its source, find the location of the pilot.
- I've got it. 1530 Hillcrest.
- Hillcrest? That's close.
- Bloody close. Three blocks away.
- Tell Buchanan.
I'm asking you once again, cooperate.
Help me put an end to this.
I'm warning you, I will do what's necessary
to get the answers I need.
Do you understand?
I understand everything.
I read your file.
I know what you did in Denver.
You enjoy hurting people. You get off on it.
We're not here to talk about me.
We're here to talk about what you know.
I don't know anything!
Get away from her, Doyle.
- I said, let her go.
- What the hell are you doing?
We got the drone pilot's location
through Nadia's computer.
- Where is it?
- Three blocks from here.
1530 Hillcrest.
We're not through with her, Milo.
Are you OK?
Milo,
you know I didn't have
anything to do with this?
Get out of here.
(man talks indistinctly)
- What's going on?
- We have a location on the pilot.
We're mobilising now.
As you know, whoever's piloting the drone
is operating in close proximity to CTU.
I'm instituting a level-one security lockdown.
All provisional safeguards are in effect
until further notice. Let's go to work.
Marcy.
Contact LAPD. Have them coordinate
with Tactical. Seal off the perimeter.
Yes, sir.
Chloe, did they confirm the address?
- It's a relay station. I have the building specs.
- I need a PDA and a phone.
- I'll get them.
- Thanks.
- Jack, what are you doing?
- I'm going with the team.
- You're injured. You should be in Medical.
- You should've told me about Audrey, Bill.
We were asking for your life.
It wasn't right to tell you about her accident.
- She was murdered.
- No one knows for sure.
I do.
Audrey gave her life trying to get me out of
prison because she thought I was worth it.
I'm not gonna let her die for nothing now.
I'm gonna finish this, then I'm gonna track
down the people responsible for her murder
and I'm gonna take care of them too.
Please, you have to let me finish this.
All right. I'll tell Doyle you're running point.
Thank you.
The drone is approaching the city.
Beginning descent.
How long until the bomb detonates?
At its current speed, the drone will reach
the target perimeter within three minutes.
It will detonate
when it reaches the perimeter line.
I'll bring it in at an altitude of 500 feet
to achieve maximum damage.
Don't worry. Everything is set.
It will happen exactly as you planned.
Concentrate on the task at hand,
then call me when it's done.
Yes, sir.
We're in position. The gate was open.
There's a truck parked behind the building.
The intrusion into our system is coming from
a room in the northwest corner.
I'm looking at a schematic. Your most
direct route is through the entrance to the left.
- OK. You get that?
- Yeah.
- Do you want me on point?
- I got it. Let's go.
Whatever you say.
(clatter)
What was that? Go check.
(Doyle) Get a medic.
It's Jack. Do you copy?
- We copy.
- What's your status?
The drone pilot is down. I'm at his controls.
The target is San Francisco.
Repeat, target is San Francisco.
Alert law enforcement and first responders
and open a channel
with the control centre up there.
These are for navigation.
There is no way to deactivate the bomb.
- CTU, we're linking you in.
- It's coming.
Is there any way for you to determine
the triggering mechanism?
They wired a GPS module into the bomb.
It'll detonate as soon as it crosses
its perimeter. I'm trying to steer it away.
Don't turn it too sharply
or it'll stall and you'll lose control.
Copy that.
On its current course, the drone will cross
the perimeter and detonate in 30 seconds.
(beeping)
- Jack, you're getting a stabiliser warning.
- I see it.
- 20 seconds.
- Come on.
Ten seconds.
(Jack) OK, it's turning.
- It did not cross the perimeter.
- I'm fighting a stall.
I'm losing control.
I need to find a place to land it.
According to the specs,
it's gonna need 500 feet of runway to land.
Closest to the drone's position,
there's a residential road straight ahead.
- Negative. Find an area that's unpopulated.
- Hold on.
If you can get farther east, there's an
industrial park. I'm uploading the coordinates.
Have Regional Command
deploy units immediately.
(woman) Operations.
Come on.
The drone is down.
None of the first responders are reporting
a detonation. The bomb did not go off.
- Jack, did you copy?
- Yeah.
Can we get a visual from anyone at the site?
I'm showing a fire-and-rescue unit
already arriving at the scene.
- What's the status on the pilot?
- He's alive, barely.
Do whatever you have to
to get him conscious.
(sirens)
(machine beeps)
- Get the Geiger counter.
- Yes, sir.
(machine crackles)
Move out!
There's radioactive material in this area.
- Fall back and wait for hazmat.
- (man) Move it!
Sir, I have Bill Buchanan on line one.
- Bill, what do you have?
- Mr Vice President.
The drone was intercepted
before the bomb detonated.
- Thank God.
- Congratulations, sir.
We were able to take control of the aircraft,
crash-landing it at the edge of the city.
But the bomb's core was compromised
and radioactive material was released.
So what we're dealing with is a dirty bomb?
Sir, this was not a dispersal device.
It was a radiological spill.
It was an attack on our nation.
- Are there casualties?
- Local responders got there first.
They were exposed to fatal radiation,
but so far it appears that radioactive material
was not widely dispersed.
Casualties should be minimal.
At least we've got that
to be grateful for. Thanks, Bill.
- Proceed with the warning strike.
- Sir, the primary attack was averted.
CTU was successful.
There will be civilian deaths
as well as environmental damage.
I hardly consider that a success!
The damage will be minimal
compared to what we avoided.
Sir, I think we should
consider ourselves fortunate.
Tom?
Sir.
Mr Vice President, we were led to believe
that this warning shot would be fired
only in response to
the detonation of a nuclear device.
That is a technicality, Tom.
I gave fair warning to the prime minister
and I intend to carry it out.
Secretary Kanin,
how long will it take
to move the submarine into position?
Once you've given the order,
within the hour.
The order's given. Launch the missile...
as soon as they're in range.
Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net