We'll release the Sentox here
and 200,000 people die.
We need access to the control room.
Jack, Bierko will be ready
to deploy any minute.
If we ignite that gas before it leaves
the plant, the Sentox will be incinerated.
Bierko!
Give me a hand.
Organise an escort team.
You get him back to CTU alive.
You got it.
I just got word from the FAA
about a hijacking aboard a diplomatic flight.
- So what?
- Jack Bauer is the hijacker.
What is he doing on that flight?
He's looking for the recording
that implicates me in David Palmer's death.
Order the plane down
and grab Bauer before he can hurt us.
We need to take him down now, dead or alive.
- Mr. President.
- I don't care if Bauer is making threats.
That plane has to land immediately,
and when it lands,
I want my Secret Service
detail to take him into custody.
- Sit down!
- He has a gun!
Everybody, stay in your seats
and no one will get hurt.
Captain, this is Jack Bauer.
I'm speaking to you on a discreet channel.
The person that I'm looking for
is sitting next to you.
He's your copilot Scott Evans.
You need to open the door.
Could you, uh... take the stick for a second?
I'm the only one who can fly this plane.
Give me the recording.
Advise CTU I have the recording.
I'll be on the ground in less than 15 minutes.
Bauer's got the evidence.
He is in control of the plane.
- What do we do?
- You have to shoot down that plane.
Otherwise you go to prison.
For treason and murder.
Sierra Tango clear to flight level 220.
520 Sierra Tango, descend to flight level 220.
- We can expect the approach to Van Nuys.
- Good.
- Can you patch me through to Karen Hayes?
- Hold, please.
- You broke my nose.
- You'll get medical attention on the ground.
Your only concern
should be flying this plane.
- Jack Bauer on line one.
- Put him through.
- You are connected.
- The recording was on the copilot.
- The copilot?
- Yeah. He was working for Henderson.
I've secured the copilot.
We're en route back to Van Nuys.
- What's our ETA?
- 21 minutes.
We're gonna be on the ground
in 21 minutes. Listen.
This recording proves Logan
was complicit in Palmer's murder.
It is imperative we do not let it fall into
the hands of anyone loyal to the president.
I'm gonna need you to provide me
with a safe corridor back to CTU.
Jack, it's Bill. I'm here with Karen. We can
dispatch a team to meet you at the airfield.
They can take you into protective custody.
OK, good. Bill, how is Audrey?
Curtis just brought her in. She's in Medical,
but it looks like she's going to be OK.
Thank God. OK, I'll get back to you
as soon as we're on final approach.
All right.
I just got off the phone
with the county general.
I have some great news.
Your father survived the crash.
- He's alive?
- Yeah.
One of our teams picked him up
30 minutes ago at the accident site.
He's still in ICU,
but they expect him to pull through.
Oh, my God.
We have a team stationed at the hospital.
He'll be well protected.
Thank you.
I have to take this.
Curtis...
- Thank you so much.
- You're welcome.
- Manning.
- Is Henderson secured?
- He's in holding room three.
- I need you to pick up Jack.
- Where is he?
- He's on a plane heading towards Van Nuys.
- ETA is 20 minutes.
- Why is he on a plane?
He had to commandeer the plane in order
to secure the evidence against Logan.
I'll brief you en route.
I cannot emphasise strongly enough
the explosive nature of the evidence.
I need you to put him into protective custody
and bring him back here to CTU.
- Understood.
- Logan will send his men to retrieve it.
- You've got to get to Jack first.
- We will. I'm heading out.
Yes?
We have a solution
to allow the plane to be shot down.
I sure as hell hope so. I may be the president,
but there are certain protocols in place.
- This will circumvent your protocols.
- What is it?
We're going to simulate a VCI distress signal.
It will be broadcast on the plane's code,
and will appear to come from Bauer's flight.
Hold on. What is a VCI distress signal?
It indicates that there's
a hijacking in progress,
and that the aircraft
is to be used as a weapon.
It'll give you the pretext to shoot it down.
There really is no other
legitimate response to this scenario.
All you need to do
is appear to struggle with the ethics,
and then give the order.
- Mr. President?
- Fine.
All right.
You sound reluctant.
I can't believe it's come to this.
I'm going to shoot down
a plane full of innocent people.
None of us is happy about this,
but you don't really have a choice.
Bauer has evidence
implicating you in this conspiracy,
and I don't have to tell you what
the consequences will be if it's released.
We should contact Chloe and bring her in.
We'll want her help bringing Jack to CTU.
Fine. Send an escort.
Karen, I appreciate this. I know you're
putting everything on the line to help us.
This recording better be
everything Jack claims it is.
I know Jack. I don't always agree
with his methods, but I trust his judgment.
I'll go make that call.
- What's Buchanan doing out of Holding?
- The situation changed. There's new intel.
- What new intel?
- I don't have time to explain now.
- What?
- I'll brief you when I've got the chance.
Have you completed the orders
for Bierko's transfer?
- I'm still working on it.
- Let me know when you've got them.
What is it?
A situation has come up
regarding the hijacked plane.
- Tell me what's happening.
- The FAA picked up a VCI distress code.
- It originated from flight ST 520.
- What's a VCI distress code?
VCI is a coding system that was recently
installed in all commercial airliners.
This code indicates a hijacking is underway,
and that the plane is going to be used
to target installations on the ground.
- Oh, my God.
- Admiral Kirkland is on video conference.
He's ready to brief you with the details.
Admiral Kirkland, I'm Mike Novick.
I have the president here.
- Mr. President.
- Mike's told me about this VCI signal.
How could that be sent
without Bauer's knowledge?
Most likely one of the pilots secretly activated
the transponder code.
At last report,
Bauer was in the passenger cabin.
Does this mean that he's now in the cockpit?
It appears that way, sir.
- What do we do, Admiral?
- The protocols are clearly specified.
We're compelled to take pre-emptive action.
- What action?
- The aircraft must be shot down.
We've scrambled an F-18 out of Point Mugu.
We just need your approval to engage.
There are over 50 people
on that plane, Admiral.
We have to think of the people on the ground.
Over 20 million citizens live in Los Angeles.
Each one of them is now a potential target.
- I don't believe this.
- If I could interject.
It's hard for me to accept Bauer intends to use
the aircraft as a weapon against civilians.
Jack Bauer is a distraught individual
with a history of erratic behaviour.
Jack Bauer has spent his entire career
protecting American lives.
- There's a reason he's doing what he's doing.
- What would that be?
I don't have the answer,
but we should try to find out.
- We don't have the time.
- We could have the F-18 shadow the aircraft.
We could issue a standing order to fire only
if the target deviates from its present course.
- It's not a viable option, Mr. President.
- Why not?
The plane is over the desert.
In 15 minutes, it'll be above Los Angeles.
If we shoot it down then,
there'll be massive casualties.
We must consider the possibility that Bauer
intends to attack the presidential retreat.
- The retreat?
- You're inside the target zone.
Bauer has already been accused
of killing one president.
The simple fact is
we don't know what his intentions are.
- Mr. President...
- Mike, stop.
I've made my decision.
I'm authorising you to shoot down that plane.
- Yes, sir.
- Mr. President...
Mike, please.
Don't make this any more difficult for me
than it already is.
Ms Hayes. This just came in
over the interagency subnet.
What is it?
We have to alert Jack.
This is Bauer.
Air Traffic Control received
a VCI distress signal from your aircraft.
- That authorises Logan to shoot you down.
- Shoot us down?
An F-18's been scrambled out of Point Mugu.
You have eight to ten minutes.
- Patch me through to the pilot of the F-18.
- No chance.
It's a coded frequency.
I can get in touch with the White House.
And tell them what? They don't want to hear
anything I have to say.
- We need to land now.
- We're 100 miles from the nearest airport.
They're going to shoot us down.
We need to get on the ground now.
You didn't hear me. There's nowhere to land.
- How much runway do you need?
- At least 5,000 feet.
- Bill?
- Yeah, Jack.
Look for a stretch of freeway at least
5,000 feet long. Straight enough to land on.
I'll pull up maps of the area, Jack.
Get back to me
as soon as you got something.
- We can't land on the freeway.
- Yes, we can.
It's late, there's a curfew,
there won't be any cars on the freeway.
Cuff your right hand
to the flight controls now.
All the way.
Just start taking us down.
Do it now.
- What's Chloe O'Brian doing here?
- I don't know.
Ms Hayes.
- You can go.
- What's going on?
- An F-18's been sent to shoot Jack down.
Can you open up a socket
with the ATC radar tracking plot?
- I think so.
- Do it.
We need to know the amount of time
Jack has before the plane reaches him.
Look at this. We have two possible
landing sites. This one's the best shot.
I agree. Let's get Jack on the phone.
I need to speak with you.
We need to make an emergency landing.
Get your passengers ready.
- What's happening?
- Everything'll be fine. Get them ready.
OK.
OK, listen up, everybody. We're going
to prepare for an emergency landing.
- Bauer.
- I think we've found something.
Bill, hold on one second, I want to
put you on speakerphone. Go ahead.
It's a stretch of the 118 freeway
between mile-markers 91 and 92.
- 4,000 feet, then there's an overpass.
- That's not long enough.
- It's the best we can do.
- Copy that, Bill. Hold on. Give me a second.
You can either try and land this plane
on the freeway, or I will.
Give me the coordinates.
3450.2 north by 11030.4 west.
- We need to know where that F-18 is.
- Jack, it's Chloe. I'm working on it.
- Manning.
- We have the exact location.
- Go ahead.
- 118 freeway. Mile-markers 91 and 92.
- He should be there within minutes.
- Redirecting.
- 118 freeway.
- Yep.
We're five minutes away.
I'm patching us in with the pilot of the F-18.
Go ahead.
Bravo One, it's Kirkland. You're on
with the president and myself. Report status.
My radar is locked on the target.
- OK, I've got the ATC radar plot.
- Put it on the main screen.
Jack, the F-18 is within 15 miles.
- He'll be within range in two minutes.
- You're not descending fast enough.
We won't be able to pull out of the dive.
We don't get on the ground before that F-18
reaches us, it's not gonna matter. Descend!
Put the oxygen masks on!
Target has increased angle and rate
of descent. One minute from missile lock.
Jack, they're almost within weapons range.
- The aircraft can't take this. I have to pull up.
- Not yet!
I can see the freeway!
Come on.
OK, level up now. Now!
We can't pull out the dive.
I need your help. Pull!
Ground proximity alert.
20 seconds to missile lock.
Target's at 1,000 feet and levelling.
- Levelling?
- Affirmative, sir.
What does that mean?
Target may be preparing to land.
The objective seems to be the 118 freeway.
- Lower the landing gear.
- We're going too fast!
Lower it!
Lowering his landing gear.
The F-18's in range.
- I have missile lock.
- I recommend we abort.
- What?
- The parameters have changed.
I want that plane shot down.
Order your man to fire, now!
Mr. President. Admiral Kirkland is right.
The aircraft's not a threat.
There's no reason to do this.
I implore you to reconsider.
Sir, we have a lock.
What are your orders?
- Abort.
- Yes, sir.
But if they don't land, I want you
to shoot that plane down immediately.
Yes, Mr. President.
Bravo One, hold fire. I repeat, hold fire.
Copy, base. Bravo One, holding fire.
We have marine units deployed in the area.
I want them to apprehend Jack Bauer.
Yes, sir.
- 500 feet.
- We're not gonna make it.
CTU.
I've spotted the plane. They're coming in.
We're heading towards them.
I'm handing the controls back to you.
Touch it down.
- We're still going too fast!
- Touch it down!
Target's touched down.
All clear. Returning to base.
- Bill, we made it. We're down on the ground.
- We've redirected Curtis to your location.
I'm just east of the Balboa overpass.
Have him meet me there.
Send a secondary team to pick up the copilot.
Got it. Get out of there, Jack.
Everyone keep moving
to the rear of the plane.
Exit from the rear, now!
You should have ordered that pilot to fire.
They were landing on the freeway. I had no
pretext to shoot them down. I had to abort.
It's gonna be much harder to contain
now Bauer's on the ground.
Even before the plane touched down, I
ordered two battalions of marines to the area.
They're cordoning off the landing site,
even as we speak. Bauer has nowhere to run.
I hope you're right. This is our last chance.
I know.
I know what's at stake, Graham.
I'll get back to you
as soon as I have any news.
- Yeah?
- Curtis, it's Jack.
The marines are moving in. Where are you?
We're approaching your position
from the north.
OK, I got you. I'll meet you
on the north side of the freeway.
- We gotta get outta here now.
- Move.
Dammit. You're gonna have to try
and talk your way through the roadblock.
- Get your hands up!
- Everybody in the vehicle, hands up!
- Hands where we can see them.
- We're federal agents.
Los Angeles Counter Terrorist Unit.
We have to detain
everybody inside this perimeter.
We're on the same team.
We're trying to apprehend the hijacker.
- Jack Bauer?
- That's right. Now, let us do our job.
I need to see individual IDs.
I'm gonna call this in.
The longer we sit here,
the better chance Bauer has.
- This will only take a minute.
- A minute is all Bauer needs to escape.
We're not prepared to let that happen.
We're moving out.
If you really want to fire on federal agents,
that's your call.
- Stand down.
- Move out.
Stand down.
- Head east for a while, then turn south.
- Yes, sir.
- Buchanan.
- We've got Jack. We're heading back.
- OK, Curtis.
- Marines are everywhere. We barely got past.
They must be taking direct orders
from Logan.
We can't run into any more patrols.
We'll use back streets.
Understood.
- Hayes.
- I wanna know what's going on.
Miles, I said I would tell you
when the time was right.
I'm watching you work with two people
under arrest for aiding and abetting a fugitive.
If you don't talk to me,
I'll have to get my answers somewhere else.
I'll be right there.
- Don't tell him.
- I can't hold him off any longer.
- You really think that's a good idea?
- I have to trust him.
He's been nothing but loyal. I probably
shouldn't have kept him in the dark this long.
I'll be right back.
- I don't appreciate being threatened, Miles.
- And I don't appreciate being shut out.
We've worked a lot of years together, Karen,
and I have never wavered in my allegiance.
I don't deserve this.
No, you don't.
Come with me.
Jack Bauer's acquired evidence implicating
President Logan in David Palmer's death.
- Have you seen this evidence?
- Bauer's bringing it here.
- What is it?
- A recording of a conversation.
You haven't heard it. That's what you're doing
with Buchanan and O'Brian? Helping Bauer?
Yes.
Logan has done everything in his power
to keep Jack from getting back here alive.
You're working against the president
and you haven't actually heard the evidence.
- This is why I didn't ask you.
- You knew I'd talk you out of it.
I know what I'm doing is risky.
If I'm wrong, my career is over.
- Not just your career, Karen.
- I believe that Bauer is telling the truth.
But you don't know. OK, OK.
Let's say he is. Let's say
that recording implicates Logan.
Then what are you gonna do?
Are you gonna arrest
the President of the United States?
- That will be up to the attorney general.
- You're...
- Sorry to interrupt.
- Yes?
- They're ready to move Bierko.
- Thank you. I'll be right out.
Look, I have to go over the transfer protocols.
I know what I'm asking from you is difficult.
Everything rests
with what's on that recording.
- Tell me what you need.
- Bauer will be here any minute.
The best way for you to help me
is to keep things running smoothly.
- All right.
- Miles. It's imperative this stays between us.
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
We have a full tactical complement, enhanced
ordinance package, two-vehicle escort.
Vladimir Bierko, you are being transferred to
a primary holding facility at our headquarters.
- Let me know the second he arrives.
- Understood.
Let's move out.
Let's go.
- Where is Novick?
- He's on his way.
- You told me that three minutes ago.
- Yes, sir.
I'm sorry.
I was on the phone with Colonel Owens.
- He's the field commander on the site.
- Is Bauer in custody?
- No, sir.
- What happened?
As ordered, the marines sealed off
a one-mile radius around the landing site.
- They've completed a sweep of the area.
- And?
And it's Colonel Owen's estimation
that Bauer is no longer inside the perimeter.
- He got away?
- It appears so, sir.
I can't believe this.
Mr. President, it's only a matter of time
before Bauer's apprehended.
Sir, are you all right?
Thank you, Mike. I need some time alone now.
The attorney general's
on his way to his office now.
He'll be ready in ten minutes.
OK, good. Chloe, I want you
to prepare the recording for playback.
Apply a digital signature
so we can establish a chain of evidence.
Work alone. I don't want
anyone else near that recording.
- Don't let it out of your sight.
- I won't.
You said I had ten minutes.
I'd like to see Audrey.
- Of course. She's in Medical.
- Thank you.
- He's in ICU.
- When will I be able to speak with him?
- I'm sorry, I really don't know.
- All right. I understand.
Just let him...
Can you please tell him that his daughter
called and that she loves him very much?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Thank you.
- It looks like my dad's gonna be all right.
- Yeah, I know. I heard.
Oh, God, I'm so glad to see you.
Me too.
We did it.
We got the evidence.
The attorney general's going to hear it.
- So it's over.
- Yeah.
President Logan's gonna pay
for David Palmer's assassination.
Thank you.
Close your eyes.
I'm gonna sit with you for a minute.
- Yes?
- Graham.
- I've been trying to reach you.
- I know.
- Bauer slipped through, didn't he?
- Yes.
I've just been told that the attorney general's
office received a phone call
from the director of CTU.
I think it's fairly obvious
they're in possession of the recording.
I think that phone call was about you.
I didn't expect it to happen so soon.
I am sorry, Charles. You don't deserve this.
Listen, Graham.
Despite how things turned out,
I still believe that we were in the right.
I still believe that we acted
in the best interests of the country.
And we have to keep putting
the country's wellbeing ahead of our own.
The spectacle of a sitting president
on trial for murder would be devastating.
Yes.
Yes, it would.
Aside from the psychological damage
to the country,
a trial would expose certain realities
that should never see the light of day.
If only we could keep such a trial
from taking place.
That thought occurred to me as well.
I'm glad we agree.
I've taken steps to ensure that you and your
associates won't be implicated in any of this.
I appreciate that, Charles. We all do.
I have nothing more to say.
I'm going to hang up now. There are a few
things I'd like to take care of before...
Goodbye, Charles.
Goodbye, Graham.
Martha, may I come in?
- Now you want to talk?
- Marty, please.
What do you want?
Is there something else you wanna confess?
No.
I wanna tell you how sorry I am.
For everything.
When you forget to give me something
for my birthday,
that's when you say you're sorry.
I know what I did was wrong. It was horribly
wrong, and unforgivable. I know that.
But what I can't live with
is the fact that I hurt you.
That's the last thing I wanted to do.
Marty? Marty, please.
That's the truth.
The truth?
You know what really gets me, Charles?
- What?
- That you had me going for so long.
I had no idea you were such a good liar.
If I wasn't so horrified by that fact that I'm
married to you, I might actually be impressed.
- Yes?
- I'm sorry to disturb you, sir.
I have an urgent call coming in from CTU.
- I don't want to talk to anyone from CTU.
- He insists that you'll want to speak with him.
He says it's concerning Jack Bauer.
- Put him through.
- Yes, sir.
- Go ahead. You're on with the president.
- Mr. President?
- Yes, go ahead.
- Miles Papazian. I work under Karen Hayes.
- What is this about?
- It's about a recording, sir,
that Jack Bauer
has just delivered here to CTU.
Sir, my understanding is it's a recording
of a conversation of yours that, if leaked,
could significantly compromise
national security.
- Go on.
- My superior, Ms Hayes,
is working with Bauer and Bill Buchanan.
Their intention is to play the recording
for the attorney general.
- Why are you telling me this?
- Because, sir,
I feel compelled to intervene.
And I just wanted to make sure
that you would approve.
I do, Mr. Papazian. I do approve.
Listen, um... I'm going to text you
my private number.
Let me know how it goes.
And Miles...
I promise you I won't forget this.
Thank you, sir. That's all I wanted to hear.
Mr. President, I look forward
to speaking with you again soon.
How long before the teleconference starts?
Five minutes. Get out of here, Miles.
- We'll be ready?
- Not if you keep interrupting me.
- I'm just doing my job, Chloe.
- If your job is to slow things down.
- I'll tell Karen you'll be ready.
- Thanks.