Transcript by Addic7ed.com
Corrected by Arcinboldi
Hassan isn't happy
about Taylor's response
to the ultimatum.
If he wants to take it up
with President Taylor,
he can do it when he's...
- Put your gun down.
-    Omar, what are you doing?
Mr. President...
My life or tens of thousands?
I couldn't live with that.
What if they
blow up the bomb anyway?
At least I've tried
to stop the attack.
We've got less than five
minutes, we gotta move.
Mr. President,
you can't trust him!
Don't move, hands
where we can see them!
Is he still alive?
Yes, ma'am.
Where is President Hassan?
I don't know.
Don't lie to me!
They have Hassan;
we have the bomb.
The bomb's at Amsterdam
and 93rd.
We know that President
Hassan was handed over
approximately ten minutes ago.
We have an ambush point yet?
Yes, intersection of
161st and Amsterdam.
CTU is following you.
Can you find me an exit?
There's one between 158th
and 159th... parking garage.
Damn it, they've made us!
He's breaking left!
I repeat, he's breaking left!
I've got him, he's going
back into the garage.
He's coming straight
at me, damn it!
You know where to go.
- Have you got Hassan?
- No.
The driver managed to transfer
Hassan to another vehicle
before I could get to him.
Someone inside CTU's
gotta be tipping them off.
It's only a matter of time
before this gets
traced back to me.
I need to get the hell out
of here while I still can.
Uh, excuse me, Ms. Walsh?
I need to see your passkey.
What's this about?
It's a new security protocol
because of the EMP attack.
Nobody gets in or out
without personally being
cleared by Mr. Hastings.
I can't let you through.
You haven't been coded out.
Well, I'm not leaving.
I'm just going to my car.
I'm sorry, you'll have
to talk to Mr. Hastings.
Hastings is in the middle
of a crisis.
It'll just be a couple minutes.
No one will even
know I was gone.
Look...
I just want to go get
my migraine meds.
Please don't make me beg.
All right, tell you what,
I'll have one of my men
run out to your car,
grab your medication.
Give me your keys.
You know, that's fine,
your men are busy enough.
I'll talk to Hastings.
- You sure?
- Yep.
Thank you, Jim.
Only one car left
the parking garage.
One minute after the crash.
Northeast exit,
a blonde woman was driving.
Hassan was probably in it.
Can you track it?
No, it left
the satellite grid.
Damn it.
Put out an APB on that car.
- Yes, sir.
- Scan the NSA servers.
- See if they've picked up any chatter.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Hastings, the
President's on line one,
- she'd like an update.
- Great, thank you.
Madam President, Brian Hastings.
Mr. Hastings, I saw the crash.
Please tell me
President Hassan survived.
Actually, we just learned
that President Hassan was not
in the vehicle.
I don't understand.
During the pursuit,
we believe
he was switched
to another car.
We're trying
to track it now.
- Then he's still alive.
- It appears so, ma'am.
If the terrorists
wanted him dead,
they would've killed him on site.
They must have another agenda.
I don't even want to speculate
on what that might be.
We will keep you apprised,
Madam President.
Thank you.
What is happening?
Is my father alive?
We think so, but he's
still in the hands
of the terrorists.
Now, CTU
- is searching for him now.
- Then there's still hope.
- Yes.
- Excuse me...
Madam President, the Russian
Foreign Minister is outside.
He wants
to speak with you.
I'll be right there.
I can't imagine how hard
this is for both of you.
Please know that
I'm committing
every resource at my disposal
to finding him.
Mr. Novakovich.
What can I do for you?
Thank you for seeing me,
Madam President.
I know that you are very busy.
It's all right.
Please.
Can I assume there is no change
in the status
of President Hassan?
I'm afraid not.
Then he is still being
held by terrorists.
For now, yes.
Are you hopeful that
CTU can recover him?
We're following a lead now,
and, yes, we are very hopeful.
What is the nature of the lead?
I'd rather not
get into specifics.
You'll be told the
second we know more.
Madam President,
I need to stress
that if Hassan is not found,
his government
will be in disarray.
The peace agreement will
have no chance of success.
I'm aware of that, but there's...
there's no point in speculating
on the worst-case scenario;
we're not there yet.
I just want to make
our position clear.
If Hassan dies,
there is no agreement.
If I didn't know better,
I'd think you were hoping
for that to happen.
- Madam President!
- You believe this treaty
weakens your influence
in the region.
Your country has been looking
for any excuse to pull out.
I realize you are under
a great deal of pressure,
but there is no reason for
these baseless accusations.
My country has been
more than supportive.
We are here, are we not?
Perhaps I spoke too harshly.
I just don't need
you to remind me
how perilous this situation is.
I do appreciate your support,
and I hope that
I can count on it
until we find President Hassan.
Of course, Madam President.
Chloe, can I talk
to you for a second?
We've got a problem.
Jack thinks that
someone inside of CTU
is working for
the terrorists.
Why does he think that?
They must've been warned
that they were being followed.
That's why they transferred
Hassan to a different car.
Yeah, that bothered me too.
And then there was a satellite
glitch that happened earlier.
- What glitch?
- The glitch that allowed
the terrorists to get away
in the first place.
It was a little too unlucky;
especially for us.
Jack recovered Tarin's
cell phone from the crash.
If someone did call
to tip him off,
we can get the number
off the memory.
Jack's on his way
back to CTU now.
He wants you to call him
on a proprietary line
so he can upload the data.
- All right.
- Go.
I'm ready to receive.
I'm calling Jack now.
This is Bauer.
Jack, it's Chloe,
Renee filled me in.
Good, I'm going to upload
the cell phone data
to your station.
- What's your I.D. number?
- 91770.
91770.
Chloe, it's encrypted... you're
gonna have to work fast.
Excuse me, sir, I need
to access your workstation.
What for?
I want to make sure all the
parameters reset properly
- after the EMP.
- Can't that wait?
No... if the parameters are off
we could lose more data.
- How long?
- Couple minutes.
Go ahead.
Hastings.
Mr. Hastings, it's Chloe.
I need to talk to you at my
station, it's important.
What is it, Chloe?
I'll explain when you get here.
I'm on my way.
Let me know
when you're finished.
All right, what is it?
We think someone inside of CTU
is working with the terrorists.
What are you talking about?
They switched Hassan
to a different car
because they knew they
were being followed.
Jack recovered Tarin's
cell phone from the crash.
Chloe's decrypting
the data right now.
Who the hell is it?
The data's coming in now;
it'll take a second.
Okay, there.
These are all the calls
that Tarin made
in the past hour.
That's one of ours.
It's one of the cell phones
NSA provided to us
right after the EMP hit.
Who was issued that phone?
They were logged in
by hand; hold on.
That's Dana's phone.
Where is she?
I checked with Hastings;
he cleared me through, Jim.
How's that migraine?
Worse than ever,
thanks to you.
Sorry about that.
Just doing my job.
Stay where you are
and keep your hands...
Security monitors, main screen.
We need a medical team
to the main entrance.
What's going on?
Why is there a 112
out on Dana?
She's working with the terrorists.
Just shot two security guards.
She's trying
to leave the building.
Wait a minute, what the hell
are you talking about?
We traced a call
from her cell phone
to one of the terrorists.
She's been working
with them, Cole.
What the hell
did you know about this?
Nothing, sir!
She just entered
the parking garage.
She's heading for
the north end of level two.
- She's going for her car.
- Cole... Cole!
Notify Security,
lock down the exits.
Get out of the car now!
Who are you, you lying bitch?
Who are you?!
Cole! Let her go!
Cole, let her go.
Cole...
I said let her go.
Where's Hassan?
You're going to talk to me
one way or the other.
I said, where are
they taking Hassan?
I want to talk to Jack Bauer.
You want answers...
get Bauer.
Get her out of here.
If her name's not Dana
Walsh, then who is she?
Her real name's Jenny Scott.
At least that's
what she told me.
I don't know
what to believe anymore.
But she said she did
some bad things in her past.
That's why she had
to change her identity.
What bad things?
She was involved with a felon.
They committed
some armed robberies.
Someone got killed.
Look, that's all I know,
but it's not relevant
to finding Hassan.
You let me decide what is
relevant and what is not.
Why and hell didn't
you report any of this?
Oh, I just found out
about it a few hours ago.
That is not an excuse.
I know, sir.
I guess I was just
trying to protect her.
I wasn't thinking straight.
So when you and Dana,
or whatever her name is,
went AWOL,
what was that about?
It's a long story, sir,
and it won't help us
find President Hassan.
I'll make a full debrief
once this is all over,
but until it is,
please, let me stay on duty.
I know I screwed up, but I've
been running Hassan's security
for the last month.
Give me a chance
to make this right.
Hastings.
Sir, you wanted to be told
when Jack Bauer got here.
He just arrived.
Send him to interrogation.
Yes, sir.
You get over to debrief.
Sir, you need me on this.
I need people I can trust.
You want
to make this right?
Then start by getting down
everything you know.
Then we'll talk.
What's happening?
You were right. They had
someone inside of CTU.
Dana Walsh.
She's an analyst.
We checked the phone
data you sent over.
She's the one that called
Tarin before he crashed.
She must've warned him that
he was being pursued.
Anybody know
who she really is?
She's not saying anything
until she talks to you.
Me? Why?
She won't say.
- Jack, are you up to speed?
- Yeah.
I just spoke with Agent Ortiz.
You know he was her fiancé.
Well, that would explain
a few things.
He doesn't know much,
only that she had
some kind of criminal
past, and altered
her identity to infiltrate CTU.
Not an easy task.
Well, she obviously
had help from someone.
However she did this,
we need to find out.
You think Cole's clean?
I think he's telling the truth,
but after this,
I'm not sure
I trust my own opinion.
I thought I knew Dana Walsh.
Cole's clean.
Why does she want
to talk to you, Jack?
Don't know.
Just met her today.
But I think
we should find out, don't you?
Open up.
You stand down for now.
Just so we're clear,
as far as I'm concerned,
I kept up my end of our deal.
The nuclear rods
were recovered.
The only reason why
I'm still here is because
I gave President Taylor my word
that I would protect
President Hassan.
I know.
Okay, thank you.
Biometrics ready?
Yes, sir.
They said I was the only one
you wanted to talk to.
Why?
Because you're the only one here
who doesn't have his head
up his ass.
So let's not
waste any time.
You want President Hassan,
I can get him for you.
I know where they're taking him.
I know what they're planning
to do.
What do you want?
You know the drill.
Full immunity, clean record.
And I want
to be compensated.
Compensated?
When you get these IRK agents,
you're gonna get your hands
on their cash.
I want my share.
I lost a lot of money
when this deal went south.
You're telling me
all of this is about money?
Isn't it always?
If I'm going to take this
to the President,
I need proof that
you know something worthwhile.
Well, in about a half an hour,
you will have
all the proof you need...
Hassan's head.
You little bitch.
Let me explain
something to you.
Damn it, Jack!
The only reason you've got
any leverage right now is
because President Hassan
is alive.
So stop screwing with me!
They are going to force him
to make a statement,
and then they're going
to kill him,
live over the Internet.
So I suggest
we stop haggling
and you start
making this happen.
Fine. I'll take this
to the President.
But you better understand
that if we don't recover
President Hassan alive...
you get nothing.
Nothing.
It's why I asked for you,
Mr. Bauer.
It's part of the deal.
You're going
to handle this operation.
Hassan is heavily
protected.
I need someone with your
experience running the show.
There's been enough
screwups for one day...
don't you think?
Earlier, you said
you lost a lot of money
because the deal went bad.
Who was supposed
to pay you?
Tick-tock, Mr. Bauer.
You're running
out of time.
Open the door.
So what do the
biometrics say?
Autonomics are stable.
No deception.
I wouldn't put much faith
in those readings.
She's a sociopath.
She cannot be trusted.
Renee's right... this isn't just
about the money for her.
She's hiding something.
But given the timeframe
that we have,
we need to follow
through with this.
How do you want to play it?
We need to call the President.
Hassan is here.
They're bringing him up.
Samir, we should
kill him now.
The entire city is
looking for him.
It's not enough to kill him.
We heed him
to confess his crimes,
renounce his lies.
The longer we delay,
the better the chance
the Americans will find
him and try to rescue him.
He will never be rescued.
He will die
right here.
Samir?
Do you remember me?
I was a young man when we met.
You were a general
in the Revolutionary Guard.
I had the honor
of briefing you
on our operations
in Abul Province.
You were a great leader then.
What happened?
Why did you turn
your back on our country?
It is you...
...you who has betrayed
our country.
No.
I'm fighting to keep us strong.
You have chosen
to surrender to the West.
It's not surrender.
It's an honorable
peace... that will
strengthen our country.
I do remember you.
Do you remember
the campaign
we fought to secure
the perimeter
of Abul?
Yes, I do.
The other generals said I was
leading my men into defeat.
But we fought.
For four long days.
I believed in my heart
that victory was possible.
And I was right.
I'm not saying I'm never wrong.
But I believe...
just as strongly in
this peace agreement.
All I'm asking...
is that you put your faith
in me once again.
I implore you
to stop this madness.
The next thing you say...
will be an apology to
every citizen of the IRK.
You will beg forgiveness
for your treason,
and you will renounce
the peace agreement.
That will never happen.
I'll never do that.
I will never do that.
Oh, you will.
It just depends on
how long it takes.
And how much pain
you can endure.
This immunity agreement's
made out to "Dana Walsh."
But it's my understanding
that's not her real name.
The lawyers are aware
of that, ma'am.
They say the agreement
will hold.
Too bad.
I thought for a moment there
we had a way out.
I'll get these to
CTU right away.
Thank you, Tim.
Thank you.
Ethan.
Still here, Madam President.
Are you going
to be all right?
I'll let my doctors
field that one.
They're running tests.
Good.
Madam President,
what's the situation
with Hassan?
Is he safe?
They have him, Ethan.
The IRK agents have Hassan.
Oh, dear God.
They're going to kill him.
Not if CTU can
get there in time.
There's a rescue
operation underway.
They know where he is?
They will shortly.
The terrorists had someone
working for them inside CTU,
an analyst named Dana Walsh.
I've agreed to a conditional
immunity deal
in exchange for her cooperation.
Conditional on what?
Omar Hassan's safe return.
Ethan...
there's a real possibility
Hassan won't survive this.
I hate to even think about it,
but we have to be prepared.
Is there any chance that
the person who succeeds Hassan
will be someone
we can deal with?
The IRK constitution is vague
when it comes to succession
of power.
There's no telling who'd
take his place.
Besides, Hassan
barely was able
to form a consensus in
his own administration.
It took a man of
his charisma
and passion to achieve that.
I'm sorry to be so negative,
Madam President,
but we have to be realistic.
Without Hassan,
there can be no peace.
They're ready to start
the briefing with Dana...
or whatever her name is.
- Arlo?
- Yeah. I heard you.
You work with someone for a year,
you think you know them.
How did we all miss this?
I always knew there was
something wrong with her.
She was a little too perfect.
But I never imagined
she'd be a terrorist.
I should've seen it.
She was acting weird all day.
Maybe if I'd been looking
in the right spot,
like somewhere
in the vicinity of her face,
I might've noticed
something useful.
She played us.
Get over it.
Sit down.
I'm only telling you this
because you're going
to find out soon enough.
Dana's been given provisional
immunity by the President.
What?!
She's providing us
with intelligence
as to the whereabouts of the
people holding President Hassan.
I don't care what
she's providing.
She's a traitor and a murderer!
Cole...
You can't let her walk!
Not her!
Stop.
I know you've been burned...
professionally,
personally.
Get over it.
Jack Bauer's heading up the
operation to rescue President Hassan.
He wants you on his team.
But Dana
is briefing the group.
Do you have a problem with that?
No, sir.
I'm fine.
Good.
Stand by outside
the conference room.
His name is Samir Mehran.
Before the IRK planted him here,
he was a soldier with the
Revolutionary Guard.
Altogether, he has about
six men left.
You killed the rest.
You're absolutely sure that's
where they're holding Hassan?
Yes. The entrance
to the tenement
is on Holland Avenue with
exits to the rear and east side.
He'll have at least
a couple lookouts stationed.
What's the apartment number?
I don't know.
If I knew, I would tell you.
Somewhere above the
first floor.
What makes you say that?
Because the building
is populated.
Some families.
Samir will want to use them
as human shields
in the event of
a frontal attack.
We got what we need.
We have to move.
Secure the prisoner.
Take her to holding.
Hey. You all right?
Yeah, I'm ready to go.
Get your men and assemble
them in the motor pool.
Let's move.
Let's go.
Just read the statement, Omar.
Put an end to this.
This is only going to get worse.
Tell the people you've
made a terrible mistake.
Atone for your sins.
You are wasting your time.
I will never do what you ask.
Read the statement, Omar,
or I will start cutting
pieces from your body.
Whether I live...
or I die...
this peace will happen somehow.
And men like you
will have no place to hide.
This peace dies
right here with you!
You said the drug would
break down his resistance.
It should be working.
Give him another injection.
Any more could kill him.
I don't care.
Do it.
Samir, we can't continue
this forever.
If he won't read the statement,
we must think of something else.
He will break.
I know it.
He's stronger
than we thought.
We need to accept it.
Stop.
Prepare the Internet feed.
What are you going to do?
I will tell the world
of his crimes.
And carry out his sentence.
Madam President,
I just got word from CTU.
Their tactical team is
approaching th staging area.
They also have
real-time uplink.
Dalia and Kayla Hassan have
asked to speak with you.
They're in the
waiting area.
I was told
you found my husband.
He's being held in
an apartment building.
CTU is preparing to go in
after him.
Do they know if
he's still alive?
We believe that he is,
but we can't be sure.
We have our best
men in the field
and they're going to do
everything they can
to save your
husband's life.
But you cannot guarantee
he will be saved.
I'm afraid not.
But I assure you,
we're going to do everything
we can.
Thank you, Madam President.
Madam President, we need you
in the situation room.
We'll know something very soon.
NSA just red-flagged a live feed
going out on the Internet.
It's President Hassan.
Put it through.
President Hassan is
a traitor to his country.
His belief that we must
capitulate to the infidels
nearly condemned our people
to a life of subjugation.
What follows is a list
of his crimes.
You will see that he deserves
the harshest punishment.
Hassan has tortured
and sent his bulldogs
on other leaders
of the society.
The scholars...
Does the video give us any clue
to Hassan's location
in the building?
Look at the shadows
behind his head.
The light coming from
the left is natural light.
It's a window.
You're sure that's daylight?
Yes, the light temperature
is 5,600 degrees Kelvin.
That's the building where Dana
said Hassan is being held.
Based on the angle
of the shadows,
they're in an east-facing apartment.
By the height of the
surrounding buildings,
they're on the fourth floor.
Sir, the drone
is in position.
There are two lookouts
on the roof.
Patch me through to Jack.
It's Bauer.
Jack, we've got a good fix
on Hassan's location.
We think he's in an east facing
apartment on the fourth floor.
We also confirm two look-outs
on the roof, both armed.
- North and south corner.
- Copy that.
You need to hurry, Jack.
The terrorist is running
a live Internet feed.
He's reading a list of
Hassan's so-called crimes.
As soon as he's done,
he's going to execute him.
We're at the staging area;
I'll let you know
as soon as we're moving in.
- Is this everyone?
- Yes, sir.
Okay, Cole, I want you and your
team to take down the lookouts;
I want coordinated kill shots
and I want you to cover
the perimeter
as we move in.
Charters, Bank, you're
gonna be with me.
We're gonna use audio
surveillance to locate
the apartment where they're
holding President Hassan.
I want all of you to silence
your weapons.
The only way this
operation works
is if we take these
terrorists by surprise.
If they get a sense that
we're moving in on them,
President Hassan is dead.
I don't have to tell you
what we're up against,
and the significance
of this operation.
Trust your training
and let's get this done.
Check your comms, we'll meet at
the rally points in two minutes.
Renee, I need to talk to you.
I want you with me
on the assault team.
I thought you wanted me
running ops.
In order for this to work,
I need every agent with
experience I can get.
But you need to understand
this goes against
every instinct I have.
So you need to promise me
that you'll stay
right behind me and you'll
do exactly as I say.
Okay.
- No, I need you to promise me.
- I promise.
Get ready.
Target A acquired.
B Target moving towards you.
20 feet... 10 feet...
On my mark.
Now.
Lookouts are down, you're clear.
CTU, we're moving in
towards the building now.
We see you, Jack.
It has become a tool
for truth-hiding,
misinformation
and propaganda for his regime.
..openly supports the masked
poisonous vipers of America.
This man is not
our President!
He's an arrogant pretender
who would sell our women
and children to the infidels
and the imperialists
of the West.
His terrible crimes against our
people demand retribution!
We're not terrorists,
as President Taylor and her
other rats would label us.
Don't move.
Federal agent.
Get down on the ground now.
Get down on the ground.
Hastings, we just took a hostile
out on the second floor.
Are we still good to go?
Yes, Jack, you
are still good.
Cover that, we need to move now.
...corruption and promiscuity
over our country
and bringing back
foreign domination
over the Islamic Republic
of Kamistan.
This is the dog that we sent
to speak for our country.
He's Taylor's puppet!
He who is guilty.
That's it, Jack.
It's all right.
We're not here to hurt you.
Where's your mommy and daddy?
Federal agent!
Get on the ground now!
One more word
and I will kill you.
On the couch now.
Jack, looks like Samir's
wrapping it up.
You need to get
in there right now!
Taylor and her country want to
strip our nation of progress
and all defense capabilities.
She sees our great nation
rising together,
making strong advancement
in nuclear technology.
...so much that she
would charm Hassan
and make him
her subordinate.
And Hassan's own
greed-fueled lies and promises
that he never intended to keep.
I have a visual on Hassan.
Ready to engage.
...you would do the same if
your homes were occupied.
We have thousands of volunteers
who have promised their service
and are willing
to give their lives.
No...
No!
All he sought to create
is a hollow, soulless nation.
You will soon hear the cry
to rise up and renew.
We will take back our country.
Remember this day as the
beginning of a revolution.
It is the day we
eliminated a tyrant.
Hassan has torn us apart,
muzzled us, divided us
with his condescending
peace treaty
of subjugation to the Americans.
For this treachery,
the penalty is death.
I'm sorry.
I will carry out
this sentence myself.
The time has come for this
criminal to pay for his treason.
Our country demands justice.
Omar Hassan shall pay
with his own blood.
Oh!
Oh...
Jack.
Jack, talk to me.
The, uh, statement
was prerecorded.
He was dead before we got here.
Oh...
Oh.
Call CTU.
I want to know what
the hell went wrong.
And clear the screens.
We were too late.
We weren't able to save him.
I'm sorry.
- No...!
- I'm sorry.
Transcript by Addic7ed.com
Corrected by Arcinboldi