-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
&
... ::: www.SubCentral.de ::: ...
proudly present
24 - Season 7
Episode 10
***
Madam president, we have your husband, but
he sustained a gunshot wound to the chest.
Is my husband going to be okay?
We're not going to know anything
until the doctors see him.
Since your husband was the only
leverage that Dubaku had left,
it's safe to say that he's
trying to leave the country now.
Whatever we're going to do to find
him, we're going to have to do it fast.
Whatever it takes, I want
that son of a bitch found!
Have someone find my daughter,
Olivia, and bring her to me.
What is it that's so important for my mother to
steal me away while I'm trying to do business?
It's your father. He's been shot.
My, god, I ...
Do you think I'm a fool, Mr. Burnett?
If anything should happen to
me on my way out of the country,
a data file with all the names and
bank transactions of all those involved
will be sent to the justice department.
You told me that once Dubaku served
his purpose, you'd take him out.
Why are we still helping him?
He's threatening to expose us using a database he's
kept with names and accounts of everyone involved.
Including mine?
We don't know where the file is, so
you just better pray that he gets away.
I'm begging you, Marika ...
- FBI! Don't move!
- Get on your knees! Now!
- Where is Dubaku?
- Who?
Don't play games with me! Ike Dubaku!
You know this man?
She was going to meet him.
When the car arrives, we would
like you to go with the driver,
so that we could follow
you back to Dubaku.
You want her to go to him and face him?
It's the only chance we have of finding
him before he disappears forever.
I'll do it.
You keep her safe, you hear me?
We will.
You're less than a mile
behind the target car.
I got metro pds trying to
build a roadblock around us.
We can't afford to lose them, Jack!
I gave this woman my
word we'd protect her.
Get out of the car, right now!
Federal agent! She's a federal agent!
Your girlfriend's
been turned by the FBI.
If you let her come to you, you're
risking your chances of escape.
I'll call my driver,
have him take care of her.
No. I'll take care of her.
***
Yes, it's under my authority.
Sean, I need to talk to you.
- Is it important?
- You tell me.
- Did you issue a federal warrant on this vehicle?
- What?
I found a digital footprint on
server four's backup partition.
It originated from your station.
- I'd like to know what the hell is going on!
- Keep your voice down.
You want to get us caught?
I sent out the warrant, to
sideline Bauer and Renee.
They were closing in on Dubaku.
I thought you said Dubaku's
on his way out of the country?
He is, but his
girlfriend's talking to FBI.
They used her to track him.
- Oh, my god.
- Don't worry, i took care of it.
Bauer and Renee are in police custody.
By the time they're released,
Dubaku will be long gone.
Are you sure?
I'm positive.
Why didn't you just tell
me what was happening?
'Cause I knew you'd react like this.
The last thing I need right
now is one of your meltdowns.
Now, listen, I got you into this, and I'm going to
get you out of it, but not if you start panicking.
- You've got to keep it together.
- I'm just really scared, you know?
I know. I am, too. I'm just a little
better at hiding it than you are.
I've got everything covered.
I ran a bounce-tap into the conference
room speakerphone that they'll never find,
and I can hear
everything they're saying.
Now, sit at your station.
Try and act normal.
Let me worry about
Bauer and Renee. Okay?
The man that we were tracking is
responsible for today's terrorist attack.
If you don't let us go,
he's going to get away.
Look, my captain's on the
phone with your superior.
You're making a mistake!
You've got to let us go!
That warrant had to be sent out
by one of Dubaku's operatives.
I know.
Then Dubaku knows that
Marika is working with us.
He will kill her, Jack. We should
not have used her like this.
We didn't have a choice.
She was our best asset.
She's not an asset,
Jack. She's a human being.
Colonel.
The FBI is still looking for us, sir.
I'll do this quickly. Wait there for me.
Samuel.
- What is it? Sweetheart, what's wrong?
- Give me your cell phone.
My cell phone?
I know you've been talking to the FBI.
You've been working for them, Marika.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What are you doing?
I trusted you!
How could you do this to me?
The FBI told me who you really are.
About the terrible things you've done.
- And you believed them?
- They showed me proof!
They showed you lies
created by my enemies!
You don't know me.
And you don't know my country.
I brought peace to Sangala.
No. Don't be afraid, huh?
It's just ...
when I heard what you had done, it was like
you had driven a dagger through my heart.
I'm a forgiving man, Marika.
I still want you to come with me.
I want to give you the
life that I promised.
I can't go with you.
I don't know who you are.
You do. You do.
If you look past your fear, you'll see that
I am still the man that you fell in love with.
I won't leave without you, Marika.
All right.
You won't be disappointed. Come.
The FBI may be close.
Your story was verified by FBI.
I'm sorry about the misunderstanding.
Did FBI find Marika Donoso?
I don't know. You can ask them yourself.
Agent Moss wants to talk to you.
Larry, where are they? Where's Marika?
We lost her cell phone signal.
- What do you mean? What happened?
- Don't know.
- Just went dead about three minutes ago.
- Where?
In an alley on the northeast corner of Ann and
10th street. I'm looking through traffic cams now.
All right, we're going to comm. Standby.
They lost Marika's signal.
- That's it.
- There.
Jack? We got a make on the car.
It's a dark gray jeep grand cherokee, turned
south on 11th street about two minutes ago.
Copy that. Moving to intercept.
- Did you see Marika?
- Yes. She got in the car with Dubaku.
Chloe, stay on those traffic cams.
I'm on it.
We're ten minutes from the
airfield. Is my plane ready?
Fueled and waiting.
Did you take care of the problem?
She's had a change of
heart. She's coming with me.
Colonel, she was working with the FBI.
You were almost arrested because of her.
She's not your concern.
You just worry about getting
me out of the country.
Who was that?
It was a government official. He's
been working for me. A very corrupt man.
I look forward to no longer
dealing with people like him.
I want to spend time with
people I really care about.
They're still on 11th. They just
crossed over to New York Avenue.
Copy that.
- Come on!
- Jack, they're turning left.
Hold on.
- FBI.
- Go! Go!
Hold on!
Get on top of the car! See
if you can maintain a visual.
Marika! Marika!
Jack, they crashed!
Go!
Get back in your car!
Larry, Dubaku's vehicle's
been involved in an accident.
- We need an ambulance, now!
- Copy.
Back away!
Stay on your knees!
Get on the ground, now!
Now!
I got Dubaku.
Agent Walker, the car is on fire.
Get out of there!
I gave her my word,
so back off or help me.
It's her leg--
it's pinned.
Hold on.
Pull... pull!
Go!
Jack.
Go.
You all right?
Larry, where is my ambulance?
Dubaku's badly injured. He's
unconscious. I need that ambulance now.
They're on their way, Jack.
Admiral Smith estimates we'll have the
capitol of Sangala secured within the hour.
He's surprised how little resistance
our troops have encountered.
And you'll be happy to know we have liberated
the refugee camp in Kasanga Province.
2,000 civilians are
safe from Juma's forces.
Madam president?
I'm sorry, Ethan.
Oh, my god, Kasanga Province.
That's ... that's very good news.
Uh, maybe we should
finish this another time.
Can I get you anything, madam president?
No, thank you.
Would you like to talk about it?
What happened to Henry
was my fault, Ethan.
He never believed our
son committed suicide.
He was right.
And I didn't listen to him.
And if I had, we wouldn't
be here right now.
Henry wouldn't be fighting for his life,
and we might have exposed this conspiracy.
Our government wouldn't be paralyzed.
I didn't believe Henry,
either. No one did.
But I'm his wife.
He deserved my trust.
Madam president?
I'm sorry to interrupt.
It's all right, Bill. Go ahead.
I just spoke to Larry Moss
at FBI. We captured Dubaku.
He was seriously injured in a
car crash during the pursuit.
- How bad?
- Critical, nonresponsive.
Jack Bauer and Agent
Walker are with him.
They'll be there to question him
should he regain consciousness.
So, you're saying that if Dubaku dies, our
chances of uncovering this conspiracy die with him.
He could be the only one who knows the names of
everyone in the government he's corrupted-- yes.
Madam president, given this latest news, I
don't think it's safe for you to remain here.
I strongly urge you to
return to the white house.
I'd prefer to stay with my husband.
You're too exposed. I can't
effectively protect you.
Am I any safer at the white house?
My administration has
been corrupted, Bill,
and now you're telling me we're
about to lose our only lead.
Madam president, I assure you I've taken
every precaution to secure the white house.
It's the safest place
for you to be right now.
Henry will be in surgery for
several hours, madam president.
There's nothing more we can do here.
You are needed in the oval office.
All right.
I'll have the cars brought around.
I'll also redirect your daughter's
escorts to the white house.
Thank you, Bill.
What are we going to do, Ethan?
How can we possibly run this government
when we don't know who we can trust?
We'll just have to pray Jack Bauer
can get those names from Dubaku.
You got him stabilized?
Yes, sir. We're
transporting him right now.
Bring him around. I need to talk to him.
Sir, he's in no condition
to speak right now.
This man has information vital to
national security-- bring him around now.
Now!
One milligram epinephrine.
I know you can hear me.
You're in federal custody.
These paramedics are
trying to save your life.
You want them to continue, you're
gonna tell me what I want to know.
I want the names of everyone in the united
states government that you've been working with.
Come on. You and i both know
the game. It's over for you now.
There's no sense in
trying to protect them.
You and I, we're both soldiers.
I know you don't care about your
own life, but you got a family.
I know where your son is in Sangala.
I know where he lives, and I swear
to you, I will track him down,
and I will make him suffer, and I will make
sure that he knows his father was responsible.
All you got to do to make
me stop is give me the names.
Just give me the names.
Don't hurt my family.
I have a list ... list.
Where is the list?
- His bp's spiking.
- Give me the list. Where is the list?
- He's going into cardiac arrest.
- Bring him back!
Get the paddles. Start
at 200 joules. clear.
No response-- there's a
glitch. Once more. clear.
There it is again.
Electronic interference.
This could be it-- feels like
a metal plate or something.
All right. Amping up to 300. clear.
- Where's the plate?
- All right.
He's stabilized--
let's get him boarded.
- Where's the plate?
- It's below his rib cage.
Open him up.
Sir, we don't have time. I
have to ask you to step aside.
You open him up now. Do it.
Sir, this man will die if we
don't get him to the hospital.
Get him out of here.
FBI.
Patch me through to Agent Moss.
- This is Moss.
- Larry, it's Jack.
Go ahead, Jack.
I found some kind of digital storage
device implanted under Dubaku's skin.
- What is it?
- In an effort to protect his family,
he said he would provide me with a list
of all of his U.S.Government contacts.
He said it was on him; he meant, in him.
Larry, this is his insurance
policy. I'm sure of it.
Jack, we need that data as soon as
possible. Can you upload the files to FBI?
I don't think so. I've
never seen anything like it.
Hold on one second. Officer. Officer.
My name is Jack Bauer.
I'm working with the FBI.
I need you to get this device
to regional headquarters.
I want you to give it
to an agent, Larry Moss.
You put this in his hands,
his hands only. You understand?
- Yes, sir.
- Do it.
Larry, you got a
chopper coming your way.
You should have the drive in five
minutes. We're gonna stay with Dubaku.
Get back to us as soon
as you got anything.
Copy that.
Sean. What is it? What's wrong?
Just listen to me, and
try not to overreact.
Okay, we have a situation, but
I think I have a way to handle it.
What situation? You told me you
had everything under control.
I do ... but they have Dubaku's database.
What?
Sean, our names are on that list.You
told me that you were taking care of this,
and now you're telling me
that they have our names?
No, they don't have our
nes yet, so here's the plan.
Sean, we have to get out of here.
We have to get out of here right now!
- I'm not going to jail, Sean! Do you hear me?
- Nobody's going to jail. I promise.
I'm sick of your promises. You promised
me that this is all taken care of.
You promised me you're
leaving your wife.
You make all these promises,
but you never keep any of them!
Stop talking, and just listen to me--
now, I told you I have a way out of this,
but I need your help,
do you understand that?
Now, listen ... okay?
As soon as O'brian downloads those files,
we're gonna crash the entire system,
every single server on this floor.
That's crazy.
No, it's not crazy. We're gonna
go up to the mainframe room...
initiate a system-wide reformat.
We'll wipe everything clean, and
they won't be able to stop it.
We're gonna have to bypass a
lot of safety protocols, okay?
But nobody's better at dealing
with those servers than you are.
Isn't that true?
I need your help. I
can't do this without you.
Erika?
Yeah. Okay.
We're gonna have to ...
tie the main servers together.
I need an AVI motherboard, but you're gonna
have to reconfigure it for a macro uplink.
Okay, and we have to hurry.
The drive is gonna be here any minute.
Go up to the mainframe
room and get started.
I'm gonna prep the motherboard.
I'll meet you up there.
- Okay.
We're gonna be fine.
I love you.
- I love you, too.
- Okay, let's go.
These are Marika
Donoso's personal effects.
- Thank you.
- Copy that. Get back to me.
That was Larry. They got the drive.
Chloe's gonna be working on them.
They should have something
in the next few minutes.
That's all that matters, right, Jack?
I don't like what happened to
Marika any more than you do.
We did what was necessary. You better
figure out a way to live with it.
How, Jack? Pretend that it never
happened? Is it that easy for you?
I'll let you know when
Chloe's got something.
Here it is.
This is a PX-1-7 drive. It's
got an auto-erase function.
We've only got one download.
Where have you been?
Just took a little
longer than I thought.
- What are you doing?
- Checking surveillance.
Got to keep an eye on Larry and O'brian.
Once we do this, they're gonna realize
someone's up here in a few seconds.
We'll have to make a clean exit.
How much longer is this going to take?
I just have to bypass safety protocols.
Once they're down,
I'll start the reformat.
Go ahead.
Dubaku hasn't arrived at the airfield,
and he's not answering his cell phone.
- What's going on?
- FBI got him.
What?
How long have you known about this?
They're not going to get anything out
of him. He's unconscious in the hospital.
There was a crash during a chase.
Listen, the FBI recovered that database
you told me about, the list of names.
I'm in the process of deleting it.
I'm going to erase every trace of it.
I don't have to tell you what
will happen if they get that list.
They won't. I'm gonna
take care of the database.
You need to take care of Dubaku.
- Don't worry about him. You just make sure ...
- Damn it!
I got to go. What's wrong?
- It-it isn't working. - What
do you mean, it isn't working?
All the inputs are active, the servers
are aligned, but the reformat won't start.
It doesn't make any sense.
Okay, well, just-just think
it through, Erika. Right?
- You can do this.
- Would you just shut up? Okay?
Okay. Has to be server three. all right,
server three was upgraded last week.
Which means they stored the partitions
to the system default settings.
How could I be so stupid?
I just have to configure the parameters.
Okay.
Okay? Is that it?
I think so.
Program's running.
What? What's happening? What's going on?
- The hard drive's reformatting.
- What?
The files are being erased.
We're losing everything.
- Well, make it stop.
- I don't have the access.
- Get the PX-1-7 out.
- It's too late. It's erased.
This is deliberate. It's not a glitch.
Someone's trying to crash the system.
- Where's your mainframe room?
- Come on.
Here they come. We
got to get out of here.
- Almost there.
- Erika ...
- It's done.
- Are you sure?
Yeah. It'll take a few minutes for the reformat
to be complete, but there's no stopping it.
- Oh, baby. I knew you could do it.
- Yeah. We gonna be okay?
We're gonna be fine.
Sorry.
- Get on the floor!
- It wasn't me!
Get on the floor!
Larry, it wasn't me.
Chloe!
Larry, I followed her up here.
She was trying to crash the system.
She shot me!
I went for the weapon, and it went off.
Security, this is Agent Moss.
I need a team to lock
down the mainframe room.
And get a medic up here!
Chloe, can you recover the files?
- I don't know yet.
- What files? What the hell is happening?
You tell me what the
hell is happening, Sean!
You were shotting me out, Larry,
so I looked around on my own.
I found out that Erika was
rerouting the sub-cam channel!
What the hell was she doing?
She sent out a-a warrant on
a vehicle with two suspects.
I knew something was wrong.
That's not part of her job.
I asked her about it,
and she tried to deny it.
She was acting very strangely.
Why didn't you say anything?
I don't know what the hell it meant,
so I hacked into her hard drive,
and I found schematics
for the main server.
Bypass codes for the safety protocols.
I followed her up here
to see what she was up to.
The second I realized she was trying
to crash the system, I-I confronted her.
She shot me.
I went for the gun.
Larry, I didn't mean to kill her.
Halt! Halt!
Larry, it's too late. The system's
fried. Dubaku's files are gone.
Are you sure? Can you recover anything?
The server's wiped
clean. She got everything.
Is this everything you got?
No, it's not. I didn't have time
to print out every single message
that came through Erika's workstation. That's
everything she was doing for the past three days.
Look, Larry, I told you what happened.
I feel like you owe me an explanation.
What the hell is going on here?
The government's been
compromised by Dubaku.
FBI, secret service. God knows who else.
That's why I shut you out,
brought in Chloe O'brian.
We were in the middle of decrypting a file that
had the names of everyone on Dubaku's payroll.
Erika erased it when
she wiped the server.
That was our only lead.
You should have told me about
this. You should have trusted me.
Sean, I didn't know who to trust.
You all right? How's your arm?
It hurts like hell. It's fine.
When you're up for it, I'm gonna
need you to write a statement.
Okay.
And keep your mouth shut.
We don't know who else in this building
might be working for Dubaku. Yeah.
Larry, don't ask me how, but I did it.
You did what?
I recovered Dubaku's files.
What?
I was running a mirror
file on an outside server.
I always do that when I'm
dealing with sensitive materials.
Erika's parameters were
too narrow to catch it.
How soon can you have it decrypted?
It's decrypted. It's been
decrypting this entire time.
Dubaku kept detailed
evidence on everyone.
Phone logs, financial
records-- it's all here.
Listen, I'm gonna need you to
cross-check with FBI personnel.
Sean said Erika was working by
herself, but I got to be 100% sure.
- Okay. Hold on.
- Yeah.
Chloe recovered the files.
That's great.
- I should get to that statement.
- Yeah.
Sean?
When you're done there, I want you
to go downstairs and see Dr. Weber.
You shot a fellow agent. You're
gonna want to talk to somebody.
Yes, sir.
Hey, do you have any idea
what's going on with the servers?
Not a clue.
The whole system's down.
I tried to get into the mainframe room,
and security has got it locked off.
Ask Larry about it, Janis.
Where are you going?
- I got to run an errand.
- Now?
- All right, all right.
- Hold off.
You better start
talking to me right now!
I'd like to speak with my attorney.
Put him in holding.
Yes. Sir.
Get me Bill Buchanan at the white house.
Where is my sister? Where's Marika?
There was an accident.
What happened?
Marika didn't make it.
What-what do you mean?
There was a crash. Uh, it
happened during the pursuit.
Marika was killed.
I don't understand.
You said that you'd protect
her. You said she'd be okay.
We wouldn't have caught
Dubaku without Marika's help.
She was very, very brave, Rosa.
What is this?
This is supposed to
make everything okay?
Marika was all I had!
I trusted you with her
life, and you let her die?
- I'm so sorry.
- Don't touch me!
You killed my sister!
You didn't care how you
did it or who got hurt!
Agent Walker?
Excuse me.
I just got o the phone with
Larry. Dubaku wasn't lying.
On the drive was a list of everyone
he was working with in the government.
They're getting ready to
make arrests. It's over.
It's not over for Rosa.
What happened to Marika was a tragedy.
But I'm not going to stand here and tell you
what we did was wrong, because we weren't.
She made a choice, a brave one,
to get involved, but she made it.
God, listen to yourself, Jack. You don't
even sound human. Don't you feel anything?
We had a job to do!
To protect the hundreds if not thousands of
innocent lives that would not have had a choice
if we let a terrorist attack take place.
What we did wasn't
wrong. It was necessary.
I read your file.
When your wife was killed, did you feel that or
did you just tell yourself that that was necessary?
What do you want from me?
I just want to know
that you feel something!
I want to know that you feel
the same kind of pain that I do!
Do you feel that? Do you feel that?
It's all right.
You're going to be all right.
It's going to take a while.
But you will learn to live with it.
What if I don't want to
learn to live with it?
Then quit.
And by the way, that stunt
you pulled by the car ...
you ever pull your weapon on my
again, you better intend to use it.
I did.
- Olivia.
- What's going on?
How's dad?
He's still in surgery.
We're waiting for word.
Is he going to be all right?
He was seriously injured.
The bullet went through his lung.
Livy.
The doctors are doing
everything they can.
Who did this?
It's complicated.
I want to know who shot my father!
Your father found out about a
conspiracy inside the government.
The people behind it tried to kill him.
Who are these people?
We're trying to find out right now.
That's all i can tell you.
Okay, I want to go to the hospital.
- I want to be there when he wakes up.
- I can't let you do that.
The people who shot your father
are still out there. It's not safe.
I don't care, I want to see dad!
This is not a debate.
I'm not going to risk
anything happening to you.
You're staying in the white
house, and that's the end of it.
Madam president, Bill
Buchanan is here to see you.
I'll be right out.
There's a lot we need
to talk about, Olivia.
We've been ignoring
things for far too long.
It took dad getting shot for
you to finally want to talk?
Let's not go down this path.
Not again. Not today.
We'll talk later.
One of the guards will take
you up to the residence.
All right, Bill. What is it?
I have very good news.
Jack Bauer just recovered
a database hidden on Dubaku.
It contains the names of everyone in
the government who was working with him.
How many?
Close to a hundred people,
across all agencies.
- Some at very high levels.
- My god.
Dubaku kept detailed
files on every person.
This is exactly what we've been
working toward, madam president.
We can finally put an
end to this conspiracy.
I assume you've already begun
acting on this information.
Yes. As a matter of fact, Larry Moss
just identified two more individuals
working within FBI who were on the list.
He's confident the bureau is secure.
What's the next step?
I'm working with FBI to
coordinate an interagency sweep.
We should start making
arrests within the hour.
Bill, I don't know what
to say to thank you.
What you have done here today
puts all of us in your debt.
I appreciate that, madam president,
but there are a lot of people to thank,
including Jack Bauer.
He's scheduled to resume his testimony
before the senate committee tomorrow morning.
I'm aware of that.
Madam president, forgive
me if I'm out of line,
but I feel senator Mayer is on
a personal crusade against Jack.
He's already taken his pound of flesh.
He dismantled CTU, attacked the reputations of
people who've served this country with honor.
Now he wants to make an example of Jack.
It isn't right, madam president,
especially after today.
What are you asking me to do, Bill?
I'm asking you to
speak to senator Mayer.
Jack Bauer helped save this country.
He doesn't deserve to spend
the rest of his life in prison.
I appreciate your sentiments, Bill, but
I'm going to have to think about this.
That's all I'm asking,
madam president. Thank you.
What the hell are you doing here?
- I need to talk with you.
- About what?
I told you I was going
to follow up on a lead.
No, you said you were going to turn
yourself in as soon as this was over.
And I will. But this ain't over yet.
There's going to be
another attack. Here in D.C.
Dubaku is in custody.
He's already provided us with a list of eryone
in the government that was working with him.
It's not Dubaku.
It's his boss, Juma.
He knows he's about to
loose control of his country.
So he's going to try and rally his people
behind him by striking back at the U.S.
How do you know this?
- I tracked down a source.
- What source?
He was one of the men I
worked with on Emerson's crew.
He had a direct line of communication
with the Juma regime in Sangala.
It wasn't easy getting the information out
of him, but I'm convinced it's accurate.
- Then you should hand it over to FBI.
- No.
My source tells me that the
window opens at 1900 hours.
By the time the FBI wades through their
procedures and red tape, it's going to be too late.
What's the target?
He doesn't know the exact target,
but it's definitely going to be
of high value and high impact.
He gave me the name of somebody
who's been involved in the planning.
Who?
Ryan Burnett.
Senator  Mayer's chief of staff.
That's right.
He's been involved
from the very beginning.
- What about Mayer?
- No. He's not involved.
- You're sure about that?
- Yeah.
You better not be lying to me, Tony.
This is real, Jack.
Burnett will be on Dubaku's list.
As soon as he finds out that Dubaku's
in custody, he'll start running.
You don't have a lot of time.
I've already got a tail on him.
Listen, Jack, if you're with me, meet me
at the corner of first and constitution.
I need your help.
Thank you for your patience.
As I'm sure some of you already know,
our government and its ancillary agencies,
including this office, have been infiltrated
by operatives in league with Ike Dubaku.
Yes, senator?
Ryan, can you step in here?
Yes, sir.
- I'm going to the white house.
- Sir?
President Taylor wants to speak
to me regarding Jack Bauer.
Bauer? What about him?
I don't know, but we'll
find out soon enough.
- It's odd, though.
- What is, sir?
Bauer was pulled away from the senate hearings
this morning to help the FBI with an investigation.
And now the president wants
to talk to me about him.
I don't like the timing of this.
Grab your laptop, Ryan.
I want you there with me.
Yes, sir.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
Units in Place. Operation on schedule.
sync: