Transcript by addic7ed.com
I think she
went to meet
some guy.
Take a look at this.
You think you can find her?
You promise me
I do this one thing for you,
and then you'll leave me alone.
That's not gonna happen.
This is a sweet operation
that we got going here.
You know? You getting
the access codes,
and us pulling the jobs.
You can't do this to me, Kevin.
You know who I am?
All I know is
that there's
a very powerful man
in the Russian Syndicate
who's been trafficking
weapons-grade uranium.
Who do you work for?
I'm not at liberty to say.
Dmitri, work on him,
until he's ready
to tell us everything.
(yelling in pain,
electrical zapping)
(gunshots)
It's over, you
know that, right?
You want to know
where the rods are?
I will tell you.
But I want full immunity.
Amanda, are you seeing this?
Where the hell are the rods?
We've picked up
trace radiation signatures.
The rods were here.
I told you, they were there.
I had two of my men
guarding them.
We found their bodies;
both shot.
(quietly):
Josef.
I wasn't sure I believed Josef
that you would betray
your father.
You were upset that he was
holding up delivery of the rods.
Now I've gotten them for you.
When will you get here?
Less than five minutes.
Just have my money ready.
*
(speed-dialing phone)
CTU. O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Jack.
Do you have Hastings there?
Yes.
Are you ready to
trace the call?
We're ready.
As soon as Bazhaev gets
his son on the phone,
we can begin
to triangulate.
Okay, hold on.
(phone ringing)
Farhad, where are you?
You're late.
Josef, it's me, your father.
Don't hang up.
Stay on the line.
Please.
I know you
have the rods.
Yes.
I wanted you to know.
The police know, too.
They're here.
You told the police?
Of course not.
It was Vladimir's buyer--
he's a Federal agent.
JACK:
Josef, just so we're
up front, I'm here
with your father.
My name is Jack Bauer;
I work with CTU.
Well, do what you want
with him; I don't care.
Maybe you don't--
but your father cares
about you.
He negotiated immunity for you.
All you need to do
is bring the fuel rods in,
and you can put
the rest of this behind you.
It's the only way
you'll be safe.
Safe? Did my father tell you
about my other brother?
What he did to him?
Oleg was dying;
you know that.
Yeah, we could have saved him.
He would be alive if not
for your precious deal.
You are right, maybe you
are right, I don't know,
but... that doesn't
bring Oleg back,
and I cannot bear
to lose another son.
Don't worry about me.
I'll be fine.
No, you won't be.
You won't be anything.
It's over.
Federal agents are here
going through
everything.
The entire city
is under guard.
If you don't bring
the rods in, they
will hunt you down.
They will kill you, Josef.
I won't be able
to protect you.
I don't want to see you hurt.
If I hand over the rods,
how does this work?
Tell us where you are,
and we'll bring you in.
Oh, just like that?
After everything
we've done?
Yes, I told you-- they
have given us immunity.
Please, Josef, please.
This is your last chance.
Are you there?
Yes, I'm here.
You need to bring him in now,
before Farhad
gets there.
Josef, did you hear that?
You need to move.
Josef?
All right, I'm on my way.
I'll call you from the road to
let you know where to meet me.
Careful with the rods.
(shot booms)
Sounded like
shots fired.
You need to help him!
Where is he?!
I don't know.
Chloe, did you get a
trace on that call?
Not exactly, but it
looks like he was
in central Queens
near Flushing Meadow Park.
I want units
combing that area.
Jack, bring
your suspect
back to CTU.
Copy that.
Get him ready
for transport now.
Is he dead?
Yes.
We need to hurry.
(over phone):
The boat is waiting for us
at the port.
The port may not
be the right thing.
What do you mean?
The authorities know our plan.
We need a new one.
Hey.
Did you get that?
Yes, Jack. We're
trying to get an I.D.
off the voice print.
So far, no luck locking
down a location.
Copy that.
We're on our way back now.
We need to hurry.
Take the van and get the rods...
We've got a match for the voice
at the end of the call--
Farhad Hassan.
So, he got
his fuel rods.
Any I.D. on the
other man we heard?
No, sir.
Mr. Hastings,
Rob Weiss for you.
Tell him I'll be
right with him.
Give me an ETA on Bazhaev.
Yes, sir.
Start the interrogation
as soon as he gets here.
(phone rings)
Yeah?
Jack, it's Chloe.
Hastings wants your ETA.
He's anxious to
interrogate Bazhaev.
I'm about
15 minutes out.
But I wouldn't count on
getting anything from him.
If Bazhaev could have told me
how to get to the people
that just killed his
son, he would have.
Jack, I heard about
what you went through.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine. Thanks.
How's Renee?
Pretty worried about you.
They've still got her
in medical.
Yeah. Could you
patch me through to her?
Hold on.
Okay.
(phone rings)
Hey.
Rene, I have Jack.
Jack.
How are you?
Uh, fine, I'm fine.
What about you?
We had a line
on the fuel rods.
We lost it.
So what's the plan now?
It's Hastings' call.
I'm bringing the prisoner
back to CTU, then I'm out.
They ask you about what
happened, about Vladimir?
Uh, yes, Chloe did.
Chloe did the debrief?
Yeah. I mean, I wouldn't...
I wouldn't really
call it a debrief.
We talked, uh,
mostly, and, uh,
then I wrote a statement.
And you explained how
you acted in self-defense?
Yes, like we agreed.
That's how it happened.
Renee, you've got
to stick with that.
Yeah, yes, I'm gonna try.
I know this is hard for you,
but you did nothing wrong,
and you need to start
believing that.
Okay?
(exhales):
Okay.
Jack, I don't...
I don't know how to say this,
so I'm just gonna say it,
'cause I need to make sure
that I'm not
misunderstanding, but..
when you say
that I "have you"...
I meant it like it sounded.
So now what do we do?
We'll figure it out.
Okay.
I'll be in in about 15 minutes.
Bye.
Rob, it's Brian.
I just got a flash
from your office how this
immunity situation the
president authorized
played out.
It's not good, Brian.
Really not.
Now, as I understand it,
Bazhaev's son swiped
the rods from his father
before we got there.
That's correct.
And now the son
is dead.
Yes.
Do we know who
has the rods now?
Apparently, it's
Farhad Hassan.
And where is he?
We're looking.
Meaning you have no idea.
Brian, I pushed the president
to resurrect CTU
with you at the helm.
Now, you tell me you can do
the job, I believe you.
I can do the job.
Good to hear it.
'Cause when things get
this colossally screwed up,
people look for
someone to blame.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying I don't want
that person to be you.
I put you there;
you're my guy.
If you fail, I fail.
And that cannot happen.
Are we on the
same page here?
So what have you got in mind?
Renee Walker.
She killed one of our main
leads, isn't that correct?
He was a psychopath--
she was defending herself.
She stabbed him 15 times.
What, are you saying
it was murder?
I'm saying that's
for lawyers to decide.
We're talking about a woman
who put her life on the line
when she didn't have to.
I'm sure that will
weigh in her favor.
You know what
a conviction would mean--
she'd go away for years.
Well, someone has to
pay for this, Brian.
so you tell me-- who
do you want that to be?
I'm sending someone over
from Justice.
A Kristin Smith.
She'll take care of everything.
What do you need from me?
Just open the door
and get out of the way.
We did a sweep, sir.
No trace of any
hazardous materials.
Fine. Finish up,
get back to base.
Yes, sir.
(phone rings)
Arlo?
Yeah.
Find Dana yet?
I think so.
I'm tracking the GPS
coordinates off her phone.
All right, send
them to my PDA.
Are you sure that's a good idea?
I mean, there could be
a reasonable explanation...
Hey, you're the one
who stuck his nose in all this.
Just do it.
Okay.
Coordinates are
on your phone.
Thanks.
Look, I'm sending
everyone back to CTU.
What are you
going to do?
I'll be there within the hour.
If Hastings asks,
just tell him
I'm following up a lead.
Look, I know Dana means
a lot to you,
but do you really think this is
worth going AWOL over?
She's my fiancee, Arlo.
Jim, I'm taking your vehicle.
Find Owen, have him
take SWAT back to CTU.
Say I'll be
right behind them.
No problem, sir.
(faint music from van radio)
(rock music plays loudly,
indistinct conversation)
(chuckles)
Is Dana back yet?
I don't think so, sir.
Do you need her
for something?
Do I need her for something?
Yes, Arlo,
she's my chief data analyst.
I need her to do her job.
You track her down,
and you let me know
when you find her.
Mr. Hastings, Kristin Smith
from the Justice Department
is here to see you.
Thank you.
Ms. Smith.
Mr. Hastings.
Did Rob Weiss brief you?
He did.
I have to interview
a Renee Walker.
I read her statement
on the way over.
Did it appear to you that
she's guilty of murder?
Mr. Weiss warned me you might
have issues with this.
With hanging a brave woman
out to dry?
Yes, I do.
There are major discrepancies
between her statement
and the forensic evidence.
All I'm asking her to do
is to set
the record straight.
I feel it would be prudent
to restrict surveillance access
to this interview.
Fine.
But I would also like
a video record of it
in the event
of legal proceedings.
Can I ask you to provide that?
Yes. Right this way, please.
This is a transcript
of your statement.
You should review it
before you sign it.
How far out did Jack
say he was?
15 minutes.
This is Kristin Smith
from Justice.
She needs to
talk to Renee,
so if you'll
excuse us, Chloe.
Talk to her about what?
Now, Chloe.
Thank you, Mr. Hastings.
What is she talking
to her about?
She was about to sign
her statement.
I already
debriefed her.
Kristin just needs
to fill in a few details.
I already filled in
the details.
I know that you are
protective of Renee.
I respect that.
Than let me sit in
on the interview.
Why?
Was your debrief not
a full and honest
statement of the facts?
We have nuclear materials
in the hands of terrorists.
Now, I need you back
at your desk focused on that.
Yes, sir.
What is this place?
A staging area.
It belongs to a businessman
who supports our cause.
I don't want
to delay too long.
We need to find
another way
to get the nuclear rods
out of the country.
You heard what the American said
to Bazhaev's son.
They already know
what we're trying to do.
Which is why we need
to move quickly.
The Americans are not
stupid, Farhad.
If we go near
any airfield
or harbor now, the radiological
detectors will spot us.
Who are these men, Samir?
These are men I have recruited.
Our men.
What are they doing here?
They're going to unload
the rods.
We need to get rid
of the van.
And then what?
You should rest.
I don't need to rest.
I need to know
what we're doing.
We can't get the rods
out of the country.
So let's use them.
Use them? How?
As a weapon.
A radiological bomb.
Wel show the Americans
how strong we are.
Show them how strong we are?
Are you out
of your mind?
If we use the rods
against the Americans,
they will destroy our country.
They'll bomb us, invade.
And if we do nothing,
they'll invade us anyway.
That's what this peace treaty
with your brother is all about.
They're trying to turn us
into another corrupt,
Mid-East regime with
your brother as dictator,
kept in power by
American guns
and money.
Isn't that what we came together
to prevent?
Is there no other way?
America will always
be our enemy.
Remember, my friend--
even a giant can be toppled
by a single stone.
We need to make them fear us.
Then I'm with you.
SMITH:
So you said in your statement
that you killed Vladimir
Laitanan in self-defense.
Is that correct?
Yes, that's why it's
in my statement.
What I didn't see
in the statement
was any mention of your history
with Laitanan.
You did have a history with him.
I worked an undercover operation
with the FBI six years ago.
Vladimir Laitanan
was the target.
And during the course
of that operation,
you had to get close to him.
He became obsessed with you.
He tried
to rape you.
Yes.
But you were able to stop him.
I fought him.
Put me in the hospital
with two broken ribs.
I'm sure that's in there, too.
You were able to fight off
a stronger, violent man.
It's impressive.
But this time
when he attacked you,
you didn't fight him off.
I couldn't.
He had his hands around my neck
trying to strangle me.
I understand.
You thought he was going
to kill you.
You were in fear for your life.
So what happened next?
He was choking me.
I grabbed the knife
and I stabbed him.
In self-defense?
Yes.
You stabbed him
in self-defense... 15 times.
15 times.
The first blow alone
could have stopped him,
but you didn't stop.
Look at me, Renee.
You were an investigator
for the FBI.
By all accounts,
one of the best they had.
Put yourself on my
side of the table.
Look at what
I'm looking at.
There's a dead body.
On the one hand,
I have your statement
saying you acted
in self-defense.
On the other, I have these.
Evidence of a sustained
and furious assault
with clear intent to kill.
Now as an investigator,
you know which version
is true, don't you?
I acted in self-defense.
Let me tell you
what I think happened.
You used an operation of
unparalleled importance
to seek revenge against a
target without any regard
for the final
outcome.
I'm telling you,
he attacked me first.
Ms. Walker, I'm well aware
of your sacrifice
in service to this country,
but I do not think
that it is fair or right
that CTU should be taken down
because you used this
operation to seek out
your own personal
vendetta
against Vladimir Laitanan.
I looked at your file.
This isn't the first time
you lost control.
You almost killed Alan Wilson.
That's why you got fired
by the FBI, isn't it?
Yes.
I can see what this is
doing to you, Renee.
It is tearing you
up inside.
Let it out.
Tell me the truth.
You killed Vladimir Laitanan
because the thought
of him touching you again
was intolerable.
Do the right thing here.
That's what happened,
isn't it, Renee?
Is that right, Renee?
(tires screeching)
Put him into holding.
No phone calls.
No communication.
I would like
to see my son's body.
We haven't found him yet.
What's wrong?
I've been trying
to reach you.
It's about Renee. She's
being questioned again.
I thought you said you already
completed the debrief.
I did. Hastings ordered it.
He called in some woman
from the Justice Department.
Where's Renee now?
She's in medical.
Can you get eyes
in that room?
No. He cut off
all access.
What is going on?
They're setting her up
to take the fall
for the failure
of this mission.
Sorry, sir.
No one's...
They're setting you up.
Don't say another word.
It's too late.
What do you think you're doing?
Get out of here now.
How dare you?
After everything
she sacrificed.
she's lost.
Have you no decency?
Jack.
(groans)
This is over.
Hands in the air.
Do it now!
Son, you better
put that down
or you're going
to get hurt.
It's all right.
Go.
(electricity crackling,
screaming)
Ma'am, hands
in the air.
(groans)
Do you have what you need
to turn
the rods into a bomb?
We're gathering
materials.
Must be difficult
at such
short notice.
Explosives, no.
Detonator?
We're working on it.
I might know somebody.
A professor in the city.
With expertise
in electronics.
You sure
he can be trusted?
Yes.
He will help.
He will do
whatever I ask.
But still...
I will bring this
up very carefully.
I need to talk
to him in private.
Very well.
There's a phone
in the office.
Ali will take you.
(engine starting)
What is the target?
Is that decided?
So many targets in New York.
It will be hard
to choose.
(screams)
(groans)
Samir!
Over here!
(shouting in native language)
It was Farhad.
He escaped.
Find him!
Now!
(man shouting
in native language)
Cuffs off.
Give us the room.
Sit down, Jack.
I'll stand.
So, this is the new CTU--
you hang your own.
If you mean Renee Walker, we're
just asking some questions.
Standard procedure.
Standard procedure is a debrief,
which Chloe completed.
But instead, you've got
some hack from Justice in there
trying to initiate
a criminal prosecution.
We're just trying to
establish the facts.
You're trying
to save your ass.
I was there when you
asked her for her help.
And she gave it to you,
and we acquired the target.
And this is how
you pay her back.
I'm not going
to let you do this.
I'll call
the White House first.
The White House knows.
Rob Weiss
sent that woman over here.
Sorry. Maybe I wasn't clear.
I meant I'd call the president.
Well, good luck with that,
Jack, because I think
the president takes
murder pretty seriously.
My recollection? She
prosecuted her own daughter.
Now, I'm not asking.
Sit down.
Sorry to interrupt.
We're busy, Chloe.
I don't mean to intrude,
but I've got Farhad Hassan
on the line.
Farhad Hassan?
I didn't believe it, either,
but the voice prints match.
Can you tell where he is?
No. He's on a secure line.
Can I just put him through?
Mr. Hassan.
This is Brian Hastings,
director of CTU.
There are people chasing me.
They have the rods
you're looking for.
I thought you
had the rods.
No. No more.
They turned against me.
They have their own plan--
an attack on New York.
An attack on New York?
When, exactly?
Soon.
Very soon.
Who are these people?
They are IRK operatives
working in this country.
Okay, I need names.
Just get me out of here.
I'll tell you everything I know.
We'll get you out, Mr. Hassan.
I give you my word.
Now, where are you?
Forest Hills.
Uh, some kind
of boat warehouse.
Hurry. I'm injured.
They're hunting me.
Hold on and keep
this line open.
What do you
want me to do?
Pinpoint his location
and get me Cole.
I can't.
What do you mean,
you can't?
His team came back.
He didn't.
Owen said he was
following a lead.
All right, fine.
Get me Owen.
Tell him he's going
to be leading the team.
Owen? Are you sure?
Just do it, Chloe.
(sighs)
They're going to take
you down and process you.
I want you out of this building.
Fine.
(rustling and banging)
(van door opens)
(rock music playing)
Hey, hey, come on.
What's the hurry?
Your friend's
a total freak show.
I know, but come on.
Don't go.
I'll make it up to you.
Okay? Come on.
At least let me give you
a ride back into town.
We'll walk.
Night, ladies!
(laughing)
(both sigh)
Gonna take a leak.
All right.
(banging)
(guy laughing)
*
Cole, what are you doing here?
You're asking me that?
We're in the middle
of an operation, Dana. You
can't just abandon your post.
I can explain.
You can explain later.
Right now, I'm taking you
back to CTU.
We can deal with
our personal problems
after we've secured
the nuclear materials.
It's not what you think.
Yeah? What do I think?
I am not sleeping with him.
Save it.
I saw the pictures.
What pictures?
Just get in.
I am not leaving!
Why the hell not?
Because if I leave,
this will never end.
What will never end?
You do not understand.
Then make me understand,
damn it!
I don't think that I can.
Try.
Okay.
(door slams)
We don't have a lot of time.
So you better start talking.
(sighs)
My name is not Dana Walsh.
It's Jenny Scott.
Yes?
You find Farhad?
Still looking.
I injured him badly.
He won't get far.
We don't know who he
might have contacted.
I'll be traveling with the
rods to a secure location.
Do you want me to come in?
No.
You stay here,
and you find him.
(clattering)
(shouts)
It's a six-acre warehouse
complex in Forest Hills.
Farhad is somewhere
in one of these buildings.
The rods must be there, too.
Drones are airborne,
but they won't have eyes
for another 12 minutes.
What about the police?
They're redirecting
their resources,
but it's a big area--
it's gonna take
a while to cordon off.
MAN:
Director Hastings.
You wanted to see me, sir?
In the absence of Agent Ortiz,
I assume you're ready
to take charge of the operation.
Yes, sir. Three
units standing by.
All right. I'll walk you out.
There's a lot of pressure
on you, Agent Owen.
Oh, I can handle it, sir.
All right, talk me through it.
What's the attack grid?
Our working theory's
that the nuclear materials
are still in the proximity
of Farhad.
Teams Alpha and Bravo are tasked
with locating
and securing the rods.
What about Team Charlie?
They're responsible
for the actual evac, sir.
It's a standard urban
search-and-rescue--
we're in, we're out.
Nothing standard
about it.
Wait here.
Jack.
You've got something
to say, say it.
Think about it. The people
that are chasing Farhad
already know they've got
a big security problem,
so most likely by the
time your men get there,
those fuel rods
will be long gone.
And you're down to one
team covering Farhad?
What if they run
into resistance?
What if they do?
Well, at that point, you
start shooting at people
that have a higher
intel value
than the man you're
going to try and save.
Agent Owen knows
the priority is to take
all hostiles alive.
Under fire?
No assignment's more difficult.
Agent Owen has
my full confidence.
Yeah. If that were true,
you wouldn't be standing
here talking to me.
You offering
to bring in Farhad?
Yes. If you drop the
criminal investigation
against Renee Walker.
Look, I know you don't
want to prosecute her.
I can be your out.
I hear what you're saying,
but I can't help you, Jack.
I've sat in that
chair before.
The chair you're
sitting in now.
I know what it's like.
There's a lot of
demands on you,
many of them
unreasonable.
But the people that last here,
the ones that mattered...
they knew when to say no.
It's the White House;
you don't say no.
You are the head of CTU--
you've got
a lot more juice
than you think.
Especially with a
nuclear weapon in play.
If we do this, Jack, it's not
for one rescue operation.
It's till this whole thing
is over and done.
You want Renee freed up,
you're not in and out anymore.
I want you in with both feet.
Deal.
I found an NYPD
evidence warehouse in Queens
with $120,000 from a drug bust
just sitting there.
It was only a matter
of getting them in and out
between patrols.
Wait, you actually
committed a robbery?
Put yourself in my place, Cole.
Kevin was going to tell Hastings
I'm a convicted felon.
He was going to ruin my life.
What would you
have done?
Not this.
Kevin promised
that if I went along,
he would never
bother me again.
Let me guess.
He didn't keep his end
of the bargain.
That's why you're
here, isn't it?
What do you mean?
What's in your hand?
You were going to kill them.
I don't know
what I was going to do.
You were going to shoot them
in cold blood.
Cole, listen to me.
I was wrong.
I see that now,
but I was scared.
I thought that I
was doing this
for us.
For us?
Are you out of your mind?
I love you, Cole.
Don't say another word.
Not one more word.
Cole, where are you going? Cole!
Stay in the truck.
Cole, don't do this.
Cole.
Please, I am begging you.
This is my problem, not yours.
Stay back.
What?
(coughing)
Hey, hey!
COLE:
Yeah, go for it.
That way,
I only have to deal
with one of you losers.
I think you got
the wrong address, pal.
Oh, do I?
Somehow, I don't think so.
Hey, maybe you should
just tell us
what it is you want.
Maybe you should shut up
and listen.
DANA:
Cole, please,
come on.
Let's just get
out of here.
I thought you looked familiar.
Looky here, Nick.
It's soldier boy.
Mm-hmm.
No kidding.
You know, it's a shame
that you and I can't
go grab a beer sometime.
You know, just
the two of us.
I'm sure we'd have a lot
to talk about.
I said shut up.
Now, the way I see it,
you guys have two choices.
One, you go back to prison
for grand larceny and
aggravated assault.
I go back to prison,
she goes back to prison.
My guess is,
she's prepared
to live with that.
Choice number two:
I let you walk.
You keep your
100 grand--
or what's
left of it--
and you go back to wherever
it is you came from.
That's it?
That's it.
But if I
ever see you
in this city again...
if I even hear
about you
crossing the
state line,
I'll skip the
formalities
and kill you myself.
Do we have a deal or not?
Yeah.
We got a deal.
Better be sure.
I don't want to see
either one of
you ever again.
Hey, what
are you doing?
Going after him.
Why?
Oh, we get rid of him,
we're right back in business
with her.
Come on, man.
We got what we came for.
We got more.
Now, let's just...
let's not push our luck.
All right?
Come on,
all right?
We're just getting started.
We're done.
Okay?
You got me?
(groaning)
Cole.
What you did back there,
I'll never forget it.
Let's just get back to CTU.
Cole, I'm serious.
Thank you.
Cole.
Jenny!
(gasps, whimpers)
(groaning)
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't
have come back.
Transcript by addic7ed.com