What happened to Palmer shouldn't have. He
got involved in something he shouldn't have.
- You know who killed David?
- He works for me.
You lied to me.
This entire day has been one giant lie.
- What you've done makes me sick!
- Martha, enough.
I need you to swear to me
that you will do as I ask...
for the country.
I hate you.
The situation with Martha is taken care of.
There are too many loose ends.
We cannot have her unravel everything.
She won't.
I have the recording.
- Have you destroyed it?
- No, sir, I have not.
You and I have been in this
from the beginning.
Destroying that recording protects both of us.
- I got O'Brian.
- Where is she?
She's working out of Bill Buchanan's house.
Did Chloe tell you why she
was helping Audrey Raines and Bauer?
She thinks Jack is innocent.
That President Logan framed Bauer.
This is Karen Hayes. Miles traced Chloe.
You have less than seven minutes
to get Chloe out.
- Karen, why are you warning us?
- Because I may have made a mistake earlier.
Chloe, if they find you here,
you'll be arrested. You have to go now.
Not yet.
It's over, Christopher. Turn around.
- Give me the recording.
- I don't have it.
Where is it?
Henderson doesn't have the recording.
There must've been a hand-off.
- Henderson rendezvoused with another car.
- Can you track the other car?
We're tracking it. It headed back to Van Nuys.
Looks like the civilian side of the airfield.
Pulled onto the tarmac.
Whoever it was got onto the plane.
It is a chartered diplomatic flight.
We've tried everything.
We can't delay the plane.
OK, call me when you got 'em. Yeah.
Are you out? The team's almost there.
Chloe's packing the comm gear she needs.
- Where is Jack?
- Van Nuys airport.
- He stowed away on a flight that just took off.
- What? Why?
He's trying to find a recording
that implicates Logan.
- And someone on that flight has it?
- Yes. Chloe's been trying to find out who.
Hang on. Yeah?
Field team's a block away.
I'll set up here for the debrief of O'Brian.
- No, put it in the situation room.
- I thought...
I want it in the situation room. Go.
The field team will be there any second.
Get Chloe out.
- How close are they?
- One block.
I'll run interference.
It's more important she gets away.
I'll bring you in. You'll be treated
as a suspect. We never talked.
- Understood. They're here. Out the back.
- Bill, wait.
Have Chloe call me on a dry channel,
either one-five or two-seven.
Dry channel one-five or two-seven. Got it.
There's a gate in the back.
Follow the path to the alley.
- Turn right.
- What about the curfew?
There's a hotel.
You should make it without being spotted.
- What about you?
- I'll be at CTU, probably in Holding.
- Why Holding?
- Karen will place me under arrest.
If you need anything, contact her.
Chloe, please, just go.
- Who is it?
Homeland Security.
Mr. Buchanan, we need you to open the door.
We're under order from Karen Hayes.
I'll be right there.
- What's going on?
- Step aside. We need to search the house.
No, I'm not stepping aside.
Do you have a warrant?
- Where's Chloe O'Brian?
- I have no idea.
Don't make us use force.
We know she's been here.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Where is she?
I don't know where Chloe O'Brian is.
She's not here.
Sir, this is a recent file from Comm.
Only O'Brian could access it.
Talk to us, sir.
I'm not talking to you. I'll talk to Karen Hayes.
- Papazian.
Mr. Papazian, we are on site.
It appears Chloe O'Brian was here
but she has gone.
- Is Bill Buchanan there?
- Yes, sir.
- We lost O'Brian.
- Dammit.
Put him on the phone, please.
- Hello?
- Don't play games with me.
Just give me O'Brian's location
or I will make it very bad for you.
From what I understand,
she got out of CTU right under your nose.
- You're the one who ought to be concerned.
- This is Hayes.
Tell us what you know now.
Stop wasting our time.
I'm not saying any more.
- This is Ed.
- Ed, bring Buchanan in.
Set up a search for Chloe. She's probably got
a car which means she's about 15 miles out.
Copy that.
But the agents on site
are trained for interrogation.
- Why are you bringing him in?
- I wanna run this.
- But now it's us who are wasting time.
- Don't worry. I will make him talk.
I'll be in my office.
- Yeah.
I'm at the Miramont.
Make sure no one looks here.
I'll take care of that.
Tell me what else you need.
Jack's on diplomatic flight 520.
Pull up the manifest.
Got it. Flight 520 to Frankfurt.
OK. Put everything you've got from that flight
onto the shared volume so I can get to it.
- Done.
- OK. I see it.
Thanks.
Yeah.
- Are you OK?
- Did you get it?
I got the passenger list.
I'll cross it against Henderson.
- What about the air marshal?
- In a minute.
- What's happening at CTU?
- They're still under orders to stop you.
- Karen Hayes is backing us.
- Openly?
No, but she's letting me help you.
If there's proof against Logan she wants it.
The proof is on this plane.
Check the manifest.
Figure out who has a connection
to Henderson. Find the air marshal's seat.
I will.
We could grab some shuteye.
- I don't think so.
Oh, hey. I was just asking.
You don't have to go all feminist on me.
You see that? 21st-century woman.
We'd better get used to it.
Yeah.
I found the air marshal.
His name is George Avila. He's sitting in 7 A.
- Is anyone sitting next to him?
- No.
Get back to me when you've got
the connection to Henderson.
Excuse me.
Excuse me. Is that seat taken?
No.
Thanks.
The stewardess said I could change seats.
I was next to the galley. It's kinda noisy.
I'm trying to get some rest.
Yeah.
The man you're looking for is in seat 12D.
His name is Hans Meyer.
He's been connected to Omicron
since the mid-1990s.
He's worked directly with Henderson.
That's it.
OK, I've got it.
- Mr. Meyer.
- Yes?
- My name's George Avila. I'm the air marshal.
- What's wrong?
We found something we think is yours. It
should've been in the baggage compartment.
We'd like you to come back to the galley
and identify it for us so we can stow it.
Please, sir. We'd really appreciate it.
- If you have any carry-on bags, bring them.
- I don't.
Very well.
- What makes you think it was mine?
- Ticket stub.
They have taken away all my medication.
I need it.
I'm sorry, ma'am.
They won't let me give that to you.
What do they think I'm gonna do?
Kill myself?
Over that son of a bitch?
I just called the President of the United States
a son of a bitch. No reaction?
He must have some kind of law on the books
against that. Or am I immune?
Just like he is.
Do you have a first name, Agent Adams?
It's Justin, ma'am.
You don't have much of a personality,
do you, Justin?
This is Novick.
I- it's Martha. Are you still on the retreat?
- Yes. I'm just down the hall from your room.
- I need you to come here right away.
I'll be right there.
- They've cut me off from my medication.
- You haven't been cut off.
Dr Hill said you had enough in your system
right now. You need to wait a few hours.
I don't want to wait a few hours, Mike.
I need something now.
- What's going on?
- I don't need counselling, Mike.
I just want a damn pill.
Sit down.
Thank you, Agent. You are dismissed.
We've, uh, been through
some tough times before, Martha.
Just follow the doctor's orders for now.
This is more than just a tough time.
None of this is gonna go away.
I just have to live with it.
What do you mean, it's not going to go away?
What are you talking about?
I shouldn't have said that.
Martha.
It's me.
You say what needs to be said.
What needs to be said I can't say to you.
Why not?
Listen, Mike, I-I just...
I just need to get some sleep.
I'm just...
My nerves are shot from today.
I just need something to calm me down.
I just need to get my medication.
The president doesn't want you
to leave the room.
Then you can bring it here.
I just want to take a couple of pills.
I need to sleep. You can watch me take them.
I'll see what I can do.
- Yes?
- Have they found Bauer yet?
- No, they haven't.
- That's not good.
I know that's not good.
I'm putting pressure everywhere I can.
I don't have to tell you how disastrous it'd be
if Bauer gets his hands on that recording.
That's exactly right.
You don't have to tell me. I know.
When I find him, I will call you.
Is there anything else?
No.
Good.
Mr. President.
- What is it, Mike?
- Something I should call to your attention.
Yes?
Your wife is in a very agitated state.
- I don't know how to proceed.
- Proceed with what?
She wants me to bring her
her medication against doctor's orders.
That's all I need right now, is to deal with her.
No, no! No more pills!
And she shouldn't be wasting your time
with this anyway.
Mr. President.
- Is there something I should know about?
- Why? What did she say?
She needs more medication
to calm herself down.
Something's clearly bothering her
but she didn't wanna talk about it.
I don't see where any of this
becomes your business.
I'll tell you where, Mr. President.
I'm your Chief of Staff.
If there's something going on that involves
national security, it is my business.
This isn't national security, Mike.
It's our marriage.
I think both of us realised today...
that our relationship
is nothing more than a facade,
and one that we'll have to keep up
for as long as I'm president.
I think that...
she's reacting to that, Mike.
I see.
- I'm sorry, sir.
- Mike.
Give her what she wants.
Lord knows she's in a lot of pain.
- Where are you hiding it?
- Hiding what? What the hell is this?
I know who you are.
I know your connection with Omicron.
Henderson asked you to take something
out of the country for him. Where is it?
Henderson. I have not seen him in months.
- Don't you lie to me.
- I am not lying, I swear.
I know Henderson,
but I don't know what you're talking about.
- Did you check your luggage?
- Yes.
Find it. Move!
What are you doing?
- Nothing.
- Homework?
- Homework, yeah.
I didn't know they had Wi-Fi in here.
Could you leave me alone?
I can't talk right now.
You're a little, uh, freaked out
because of the curfew thing. Join the club.
Yeah, OK.
When you come up for air, I'm buying.
- Airport customs.
- This is Chloe O'Brian from CTU.
I need to talk to Passenger Clearing.
- I'll need your verification.
- Agency ID CTU99A-12.
The captain turned on the "Fasten seat belt"
sign as we are expecting turbulence.
Please return to your seat and make sure
your seat belt is securely fastened.
The passenger in 12D must be in the lavatory.
Get him out. It's gonna shake pretty hard.
- There's nobody in those. I just checked.
- Then where is this guy?
I don't know.
Maybe he changed seats.
Call the captain. Tell him the air marshal's
down and a passenger's missing.
- What's going on here?
- Please be seated, sir. Now, sir.
- Yeah?
- The air marshal's been assaulted.
What? Assaulted?
What's going on back there?
He's been knocked out
and a passenger's missing.
OK. OK. Secure the cabin.
Keep the passengers under control.
- What's going on?
- There's a problem. Is our door secure?
- It is. What kind of problem?
- The air marshal's been knocked out.
Call LA Center.
Get vectors for an emergency return.
- Mr. Avila, what happened?
- The man seated next to me, where is he?
- I didn't see him.
- We gotta find him. Dammit!
- What?
- He's got my gun.
Mike, come in.
So, do you have something for me?
- This is enough for a couple of days. Dr Hill...
- Thank you, Mike.
I'll get ready for bed now.
Is there something else?
Yes, there is.
Earlier, you said something to the effect that
I didn't know everything that was going on.
I was confused. I wanted my pills.
- I don't think so.
- Are you calling me a liar?
I just spoke with the president
and I got the same feeling from him
that I get from you.
- Which is?
- That you're both covering something up.
You know, Mike, I'm the one around here
who's supposed to be paranoid, not you.
I know you, Martha.
And I know the president.
He said this is all about marital difficulties.
I think there's something else.
What is it?
Don't shut me out.
- Maybe I can help you.
- There is something else, Mike.
It's between me and Charles.
If that changes, I promise I'll let you know.
I don't know what you think
Henderson gave me. I saw no one.
I was picked up at the consulate
and brought directly here.
Is this your only luggage?
If you're lying, I'll know.
I am not lying. Please.
If someone on this plane
has something you want, it is not me.
Yeah.
- Jack, I don't think Hans Meyer is our guy.
- Why not?
The time line doesn't match.
He's been in customs for the last three hours.
The plane's turning. They know I'm on board.
- Chloe, keep looking.
- OK.
- Are you sure he's down there?
- There's nowhere else he can be.
- Tell the pilot he can do it.
- There's a passenger with him. He could die.
There's over 50 passengers up here.
Call them now.
Do it.
Captain, the air marshal says
the baggage area is secure
a- and that you should begin.
- Air's coming in.
- It's not coming in. It's going out.
- What?
- They're depressurising this area.
- What's gonna happen to us?
- If we don't get out we'll lose consciousness.
Jack, what's going on?
The security net issued a bulletin.
- Patch me through to the pilot.
- I don't know if I can.
They're depressurising this area.
We're gonna lose consciousness.
Yeah, Chloe.
Jack needs us to patch him into the pilot.
Can you get through on a CTU subchannel?
- I'll try. Hold on.
- I'll stay on the line.
- Air control officer 404.
- Yes.
Patch me through to the pilot
of diplomatic flight 520 out of Van Nuys.
Hey, what've you got?
A little voice-over IP going on there?
- Please leave me alone.
- No, seriously, I can help.
I know a way for you
to get some free bandwidth.
- Really?
- Absolutely.
- Sit down.
- Cool.
Wow, nice piece.
I've never seen one of these before.
What is that?
It's a CTU series four.
Chloe, they've opened the line to the pilot.
Thanks.
Jack, I'm putting you on with the pilot.
Go ahead.
This is Captain Stan Cotter.
Who am I speaking to?
My name is Jack Bauer.
I'm with CTU in Los Angeles.
- I'm in your baggage hold.
- What are you doing?
I'll explain everything,
but you have to restore air pressure.
Sir, I remind you I am a federal agent.
What kind of a federal agent
knocks out an air marshal?
I was patched through by CTU.
I couldn't have done that without clearance.
Look, you have a gun
and you've breached airplane security.
Captain, this is a matter of national security.
Now, open the damn hatch.
He couldn't have patched in through CTU
if he was hostile.
There's no point taking a chance. In a minute
he'll pass out. The air marshal can handle it.
Captain,
we are running out of air down here.
Captain, there is a man on board your plane
that is of danger to you.
That's why I am here. Open the hatch.
- I can't do that.
- OK, you son of a bitch.
Move forward.
- What was that?
- Aileron conduit's been breached.
- What?
- What do you think you're doing?
- You'll kill everybody on this plane.
- That's up to you. Open the hatch.
- I'm not letting you up here.
- Then you'll be responsible for everything.
All right, all right, all right.
I'm gonna stabilise the pressure
and let him up. Unlock the hatch.
The cockpit's secure. He can't get in here.
Yes, Captain.
- Hey, what do you think you're doing?
- The captain ordered me to open the hatch.
Both of you, turn around
and grab the wall. Now!
You, in the baggage hold.
Do it, now.
Close it.
Lock it.
- Take me to the galley.
- Get back to your seats.
- What's going on?
- Sit down!
Stay in your seats.
Put your hands on your head.
Do what I tell you and no one will get hurt.
If you don't, people will start to die.
- Get the captain on the phone now.
- Sir, he's in the main cabin. He has a gun.
- First class passengers to the main cabin.
- Everyone to the main cabin.
This is Bauer. I have no intention
of hurting your passengers.
- I need to find something that's on the plane.
- What do you want, Bauer?
Remain in a holding pattern so I can search.
If you're a federal agent
you know I have to land this plane.
- That won't give me enough time.
- Not my problem.
I have a gun. Your air marshal is down.
It is your problem.
- You need to remain in a holding pattern.
- You do what you have to do, Bauer.
My job is to land this airplane,
and that is what I am going to do.
Captain! Captain!
- That's all we have on flight 520, sir.
- OK.
Look, I want updates on the situation
on a minute-by-minute basis if necessary.
Yes, sir.
Yes?
I just got word from the FAA
about a hijacking
aboard a diplomatic flight
that left Van Nuys a half-hour ago.
So what?
- Jack Bauer is the hijacker.
- What is he doing on that flight?
He's looking for the recording
that implicates me in David Palmer's death.
Henderson handed it to somebody before he
was arrested. Jack must know it's on board.
You shouldn't waste your time
talking to me. Order the plane down
and grab Bauer before he can hurt us.
What are you saying?
That he hijacked the plane?
He has control of the cabin.
- The pilot is landing the plane.
- The recording?
There's no guarantee he'll find it
before the plane lands.
After that it's all over. The president will have
his people arrest Jack at the airport.
What are we supposed to do?
Just keep helping Jack.
Chloe, I need to see that evidence.
- Call me if you need anything from here.
- Fine.
Give me a second.
What's Bauer doing on flight 520?
You have no idea, you little ass-kisser.
You don't talk to my people like that, Bill.
Take him to Holding.
It's no wonder CTU fell apart under that guy.
Miles, I know you're trying to help,
but I'll take it from here, OK?
- Western Operations.
- Miles Papazian, Homeland Security.
Pass code 2166.
Put me through to Mike Novick.
One moment, please.
What is it?
I need your input, sir, because
I'm having a problem with Karen Hayes.
I'd like to preface what I'm about to tell you
by saying that I...
I don't have time for prefaces.
Hayes was called in to replace Buchanan.
- She was hand-chosen by the vice president.
- I understand that, sir.
Are you saying you feel
she's unfit to do the job?
Four hours ago she relieved Bill Buchanan
for ineffectual leadership.
He's been working covertly with Chloe
O'Brian to aid Jack Bauer, a federal fugitive,
which means he needs
to be dealt with appropriately.
- What has Karen done?
- She sent in a tac team to pick them both up.
By the time they got there
O'Brian was gone.
But instead of having the team
do the interrogation of Buchanan on site,
Karen wasted 20 minutes
by bringing him into CTU.
Maybe she felt the interrogation
would be more effective with CTU resources.
But sir, she isn't even using
rudimentary CTU resources.
She wants to do a soft Q and A by herself.
Any leads we may have had
on O'Brian have dried up.
Wait a second, Miles. I'm not going to pass
judgement on Karen Hayes at this point.
She's not interrogating a terrorist,
but a high-ranking federal employee.
Sometimes finesse and diplomacy
are better than coercion.
Your concern is duly noted, Miles. If you'll
excuse me, I need to see the president.
- Karen...
- Shut up, Bill.
We're offline. Now we can talk.
Look, you can continue this charade
if you want to, but Jack needs our help.
And he's getting it.
But I am still in charge of this facility
and until I see that evidence,
I must remain sceptical.
Have you talked to Chloe?
What's Jack's status?
He's searching the cabin
but the pilot is going to land.
- How much time does Jack have?
- 15 minutes.
To search 50 passengers? That's impossible.
Yes?
The president and Mike Novick
want an update on the hijacking of flight 520.
Put them through.
- Go ahead, sir.
- This is the president. Talk to me about 520.
We know that Bauer's involved,
but we don't know why.
Isn't it obvious? Bauer is a fugitive and he's
looking for safe passage out of the country.
- That's certainly a possibility.
- Listen to me. This man is desperate.
He will say or do anything.
He's not to be trusted.
We need to take him down now, dead or alive.
- Yes, sir.
- Mr. President.
Look. You call the pilot. You tell him that
I don't care if Bauer is making threats or not.
That plane has to land immediately,
and when it lands,
I want my Secret Service detail
to take him into custody. Is that clear?
- Ms Hayes?
- Yes, Mr. President.
The president had knowledge
of everything that's happened.
He wants that plane down before Jack finds
the evidence. We have to buy him more time.
I don't have the authority
to keep that plane from landing.
- Sir, this still doesn't make sense to me.
- What?
Jack Bauer has been on the right side of
everything that's happened today until now.
Well, right now he is hijacking a plane.
This man is not stupid.
He's appeared to do the right thing
but right now he's backed into a corner
and he's desperate.
- Do you really believe that, sir?
- I absolutely do. Bauer's lied to us all day.
He's played us all for fools.
- Flight Operations.
- This is Chloe O'Brian again.
The copilot Don Fagenson
didn't check in when he boarded 520.
- Mr. Fagenson didn't board.
- Why not?
- He was replaced at the last minute.
- By whom?
Scott Evans, the new copilot.
Here are your things. Go back to your seat.
- Jack, it's the copilot Scott Evans.
- How do you know?
He used to fly for Hatton Air, a charter
company that work exclusively for Omicron.
Evans flew Henderson around for over a year.
I need you to patch me through to the captain
so Evans can't hear me.
OK.
Sit down! Now!
Everybody, stay in your seats
and no one will get hurt.
- Are you OK?
- I'm fine.
- Incoming comm on 139.
- Go ahead.
Captain, this is Jack Bauer.
I'm speaking to you on a discreet channel.
The person that I'm looking for
is sitting next to you.
- He's your copilot Scott Evans.
- That's ridiculous.
Sir, Evans was a last-second replacement.
Can you explain to me why you're not flying
with your regular copilot Don Fagenson?
Captain, Scott Evans has been connected
to a known terrorist.
You need to open the door.
This conversation is over.
Dammit.
- What did he want?
- He's desperate. He wants us to land.
- This is messed up.
- Yeah.
- Bad luck for you, huh?
- Why?
Wasn't Don supposed
to have your seat tonight?
Yeah.
What happened to him?
I don't know. I got the call, so I'm here.
Yeah.
Oh, God.
What's wrong?
Could you, uh...
could you take the stick for a second?
- Are you OK?
Yeah.
Just got a cramp in my leg.
Yeah. Those are a bitch.
Yeah.
I'm the only one
who can fly this plane.
Now, you don't strike me as a man who's
willing to die for Christopher Henderson.
Give me the recording.
Do it.
Slowly get up.
Get back in your seat.
You're gonna land this plane
or I'm gonna put a bullet in your head.
- Yeah, Jack?
- Advise CTU I have the recording.
I'll be on the ground in less than 15 minutes.
Got it.
- Yes?
- Charles.
If I'm gonna live with this
then you're gonna have to help me.
- Help you do what, Martha?
- Understand.
I...
I know you're... a good man
and that deep down you...
you do what's best for this country.
- Of course I do.
- Then why...
why didn't you come to me? Why...?
I- I would have been there for you.
I... could've talked you through it.
For the last three years you've been one click
away from a nervous breakdown every day,
and I'm gonna come to you for advice?
- I have to take another call.
- Oh, no. Charles, no...
We'll talk later.
- Yes?
- Bauer's got the evidence.
- He is in control of the plane.
- How do you know that?
We just picked up a call
from Chloe O'Brian to Karen Hayes.
What do we do?
You are going to have to shoot down
that plane, Mr. President.
- What?
- It's the only option we've got.
Otherwise you go to prison.
For treason and murder.