This is Jenny's statement
to the press about the CTU bombing.
- Any casualties?
- Over a dozen so far.
Those people are dead because of you.
- You're out, Eric. Effective immediately.
- You can't dismiss me now, sir.
I need someone I can trust.
Reza may be involved with a terrorist.
He's been in contact with someone
who finances terrorist operations.
Trust me. He is not a terrorist.
I want you to drop this nonsense and start
treating Reza like a member of the family.
- How bad is she?
- She needs surgery.
- We can't do that in the field.
- George, we can't keep her here.
Everything on this nuke has been destroyed
apart from the database Paula sent the NSA,
- and they didn't get the code.
- Assign other IT people to retrieve it.
We don't have time!
- I wanna go with her.
- I have some questions first.
We got out in time.
She wasn't injured in the explosion.
Her head injury most likely
occurred before the blast.
- You don't think I did this?
- I'm gonna let the police sort that out.
Eddie said the job went off without a hitch.
What happened between then and now?
I killed them, for resisting arrest.
I'll kill you, too, Joe.
Whoever set you up to do this job, Joe,
they used you.
The woman who gave me the plans to CTU,
I only met her twice.
I can't go back to jail.
No!
None of these girders are stable.
I can't guarantee they're gonna hold.
And nothing behind this corded area's safe.
If I see anyone in here,
I'll shut the building down.
I don't care what the governor says.
No, don't even try that.
The switches were totally destroyed.
See if you can set up
a generator line to the A-Island.
We gotta get her outta here.
Progress here?
We're trying to bring her round
using stimulants and hydrating fluids.
- But it might make her more unstable.
- We're running out of time. Wake her up.
- Where are you headed?
- To follow up on a lead.
There's an LA connection to Syed Ali.
Well, look. Send somebody else.
I need you here.
To do what? Watch Paula die?
We gotta get the encryption codes out of her
or we lose everything.
You got it covered.
I'll follow up on this lead.
No. You're gonna stay here,
and that's an order.
There's a Middle Eastern businessman in LA
who's had contact with Syed Ali recently.
Now, Ivers and Nepel are dead.
Who do you want me to send?
Be reachable, all right?
- What are you looking at?
- Nothing.
- You putting band-aids on the network?
- Yeah. I'm on it.
Mr Mason? It's Jack Bauer.
- Jack? What is it?
- George, I got to Wald.
I found out who commissioned him
to take out CTU.
- Who?
- It was Nina Myers.
- Nina?
- She was his connection to CTU.
It makes no sense. She's been in prison.
He approached her before we took her down.
She sold him schematics, gate information...
This has to be connected to the nuke.
They bombed CTU
to cripple our response capability?
Yes, yes. I've already called Chappelle.
- You what?!
- I couldn't find you, George.
- What did he say?
- He agreed we need to talk to her.
He's having her transferred
over to CTU now for questioning.
Debrief at Division.
It's a total disaster here.
- What are you gonna do about Nina?
- I'll take care of it.
- Don't just hand her over to the FBI.
- Forget it, Jack. You did a great job.
OK? Go find yourself someplace safe.
George...
Michelle, can you get somebody
to set up an interrogation room?
- We got somebody coming in.
- Who?
- Nina Myers.
- The CTU agent that killed Jack's wife?
I need as close to maximum security
as I can get -
and three armed agents standing by.
We've reduced the likelihood on some of the
targets. We're left with six probable sectors.
The harbour, Port of Los Angeles.
One of the busiest ports in the world.
A strike there will knock out infrastructure...
Sorry to interrupt, Mr President,
but the ambassador's about to land.
- Any communication while he was en route?
- Not since this morning,
- when it was decided he'd come here.
- Is he alone?
No, he's being accompanied by Farhad Salim,
their ranking intelligence officer.
Get me anything new we've learned
about Second Wave since this morning.
Oh, and Lynne.
- Is Roger here yet?
- He's upstairs.
They're bringing him up to speed
on Rayburn's dismissal.
Good.
Dr Lazar to Radiology.
Everything's gonna be OK, Kim.
Tell you what.
You leave now, I'll tell the police
that it was just a misunderstanding.
If you don't, they're gonna arrest you.
- Arrest me for what?
- For kidnapping my daughter.
Where is Carla?
As soon as these officers talk to the doctor,
it'll be pretty obvious that you hurt her.
That's a lie and you know it.
I would never hurt her.
I've been protecting her from you.
The only thing that can be proved, Kim,
is that you took Megan
without our permission.
You beat up your wife.
Who's gonna believe you?
Carla will back me up. You know that.
I mean, if you don't believe me...
you can give her a call.
Wanna do that?
Go ahead, Kim. Call her.
You walk away, while you have the chance.
Otherwise you're going to jail.
Stay away from my family!
Don't ever come to my house again.
I wouldn't rule anything out, Mike.
If you co-opt local enforcement,
the story could leak.
And that's one of my biggest concerns here.
You know what? Roger's walking in.
I'll talk to you when you land.
- Mr President.
- Roger.
It's good to see you. Come into my office.
Afternoon, everyone. Be with you shortly.
Very good, sir.
I can't tell you how disturbed I was
with Eric's decision regarding the CTU.
29 dead - and counting.
It's inexcusable. There'll be a full
investigation, possible criminal charges.
You know I hate to meddle in your rice bowl.
But on a day like today,
I couldn't wait for you to arrive.
- Say no more.
- Are you caught up on everything?
Caught up.
I'd like to talk to you
about this meeting with the ambassador.
- What are your thoughts?
- We have everything to lose, nothing to gain.
What we have to gain
is stopping the nuclear bomb.
But this meeting benefits only the other side.
He wants to be able to say to the world
"Look, we tried to stop the bomb."
It's a ploy to gain access
to our intelligence, nothing more.
You might be right.
But I'm not as certain as you are.
- I'm gonna meet with him.
- Very good, sir.
- Anything else?
- Not at this time.
Hold on. Sir, off-duty agents
are finally arriving.
And Division called. The chopper
just lifted off, Nina Myers is on board.
Good. Let's set up the mobile video unit
for the interrogation.
Lori, I need you to call downstairs. Get Bill.
Have him bring up a video rack, OK?
Jack? What the hell are you doing here?
- I sent you to Division.
- I wanna do the debrief here.
Nina killed your wife.
I don't want you anywhere near her.
My goal is the same as yours,
to stop this bomb.
It makes sense to do the debrief here
because there is no information
on the Wald op at Division.
Please.
All right. Let me set you up
with Noel at tech support.
- What about Ivers?
- Dead.
- Clark?
- Dead. We lost a lot of good people, Jack.
- I'll get started on the debrief.
- Hey. Do us both a favour.
Finish, and go?
Yeah.
She's awake.
You'd better move fast.
I don't know how much time we have.
Paula, it's George Mason.
- Can you hear me?
- What happened?
We had a big explosion.
Do you remember the encryption codes?
You're the only one who has 'em.
- Stay with us, Paula.
- Paula.
You were transferring files out to NSA.
Do you remember that?
- Yeah.
- The transfer didn't complete.
They didn't have the source decryption key.
- The source?
- Yeah, the source key. That's right.
Normally you send it in a separate packet,
but the router was destroyed.
Did you make a copy
of the source key before you sent it?
Yeah.
What is it? Do you remember?
- Subvolume.
- OK.
- Which volume?
- Which volume? Which one?
Paula? Stay with us. Which one?
Paula, your disk is partitioned in over
50 volumes. Do you remember which one?
Etudes.
Hang in there, sweetie.
- That's it. That's it.
- Great.
Hey, you did good. What you just did
is gonna save a lot of lives today.
- Let's get her to hospital now.
- Move! Let's go.
She's in VTAC.
Everybody ready? Charge.
- Full charge, 360.
- Clear.
Nothing. Charging at 300.
- My charge.
- Your charge.
Clear.
- No rhythm.
- Flatline.
She's gone.
- I got it.
- You sure?
Yeah.
- Hey.
- So, how d'you like the house?
- You knew about it?
- Of course.
Why do you think I insisted you go with him?
Dad, it's not that I think
Reza doesn't love Marie.
- But if he's doing things that are illegal...
- You don't know that.
I know Ralph Burton found
a transaction in the company records
- that links him to a known terrorist.
- Ralph Burton is a PI.
He could probably connect me to
the Manson Family if he looked hard enough.
- Did they straighten out that lunch business?
- Yeah. Another crisis averted.
- Who's this?
- Hello, sir.
I'm Tony Almeida from Los Angeles CTU.
- This is Agent Richards.
- CTU. What... what is CTU?
Counter Terrorist Unit.
I'm looking for a Reza Naiyeer.
- What's this all about?
- It's a government matter, ma'am.
- A government matter?
- I just need to ask him a few questions.
Mr Almeida, right?
My daughter hired a private investigator
to do a background check on Reza.
- It's all been cleared up.
- Actually, Dad, it hasn't all been cleared up.
Can this wait? You see, today is
my other daughter Marie's wedding.
She's getting married to Reza.
I'm sorry for the bad timing, Mr Warner.
But no. This can't wait.
I'm authorised to interrogate Mr Naiyeer.
Are you gonna take me to him,
or do I have to find him myself?
Kate, go find Reza.
- What's going on here?
- I'm part of an investigation
involving national security.
I'm hoping Mr Naiyeer can assist me.
Hi, Kate.
What's up?
- There's a man here who needs to talk to you.
- Who is he?
He's from the government.
- The government?
- A counter-terrorism agency?
- What are you talking about?
- That's all I know.
What's this about, Kate?
I don't know.
Marie's in her room adjusting her dress.
Just make sure
she doesn't find out about this.
Sure.
- Reza Naiyeer?
- Yes.
I'm Agent Richards. Right this way.
Oh! What is that?
- Some lunch for you.
- Can you put it there?
I want you to know that since your
conversation with the prime minister,
we have taken four suspected members
of Second Wave into custody,
and we have begun interrogations.
- What have you learned?
- We are still questioning them.
As a ranking security officer, I assure you,
we are doing all we can
to clamp down on this kind of activity.
These satellite photos
were taken over your country an hour ago.
Doesn't look like
too much of a clampdown to me.
We don't have the resources that you do,
and surely even you can't tell me
that you are aware of every single
active paramilitary compound in the US.
If this bomb goes off, Mr President,
and you don't believe that
we did everything possible to stop it,
there will be heavy repercussions
for my country.
You have already made it clear that you will
have no choice but to retaliate against us.
We want to help.
- What do you propose?
- A mutual exchange of intelligence.
- What kind of exchange?
- We need access
- to your files on Second Wave.
- Our files?
Yes. Anything that pertains to
suspected terrorism in our country.
I'm not sure how much intel it's in our
interest to share with you at this time.
I understand your reservations, Mr President.
But be assured,
we want to prevent this... incident.
We are prepared
for an exchange in both directions.
We are willing to
open up our files to you as well.
- I'll have to think about this, Mr Ambassador.
- Of course.
We prepared a room for you.
You'll have our answer shortly.
Thank you, Mr President.
- Mr Ambassador.
- Mr Stanton.
Right this way, sir.
- We can't give them this information, sir.
- Explain. What's the downside?
We have agents in their country, right now.
- Those files would expose their identities.
- Fine.
Go through the files, take out anything
that would jeopardise our people.
- It's a dangerous precedent.
- We can't worry about precedent, not today.
Not under the threat of nuclear attack.
I guess my point is...
I don't trust the ambassador.
And we can't ignore the possibility that
his country is supporting Second Wave.
Lynne, what do you think?
I agree with Roger. I think it's too risky.
- Yeah.
- Dad, it's me.
- Kim, are you all right?
- I'm OK. What about you?
- Were you at CTU when the bomb went off?
- No, honey, I'm fine.
- Are you on your way to Aunt Carol's?
- I haven't left yet.
- What is going on? You sounded weird.
- It doesn't matter.
- Go to Aunt Carol's.
- I can't. That's why I'm calling.
- Why? What's wrong?
- It's Megan.
Her dad freaked out and hit her.
I'm at the hospital.
Sweetheart, you're gonna have to let that go.
It's not safe in Los Angeles today.
Why not?
Something bad's gonna happen.
Just trust me.
Dad, tell me.
Sweetheart, there's a nuclear bomb
in Los Angeles. It might go off today.
Oh my God.
All right. I'll leave, but I...
No buts, Kim. Go. Now.
Are you gonna meet me at Aunt Carol's?
As soon as I'm finished here at CTU. OK?
- All right.
- Kim?
Don't tell anybody about this, OK?
We can't start a panic.
OK.
- Call me as soon as you get there.
- OK.
Dad, I love you.
I love you too, sweetheart.
- Now go.
- OK.
George wondered if there
was anything I can do to help.
No, thank you.
I could fill out that boilerplate stuff for you.
Michelle, I know George wants me outta here.
Take my advice.
Don't get caught in the middle.
Hello, Nina.
So you weren't just working for the Drazens.
Selling information to anybody who'd buy it.
Presidential assassins,
terrorists, didn't matter.
What do you know about this nuclear bomb?
Here are the terms, George.
They're nonnegotiable.
I'll give up my contacts,
my background material, all my intel.
I'll work with whoever you want,
here or in the field.
For that, I want a full presidential pardon,
third party certification,
guaranteed in writing.
It's not gonna fly.
Then take me back.
You're not buying a used car here.
You have to deal
within the confines of reality.
You're not gonna get anything
unless you produce results.
It's in my interest to produce results.
Is this working? Then put me through
to Chappelle at Division.
Is she gonna help?
Finish your debrief, and go.
Ryan, it's me.
Excuse me.
Sorry about that.
So, as chief financial officer,
you oversee all the money that comes
in and out of the company, right?
Right. And in case you hadn't noticed,
I'm getting married today, so if we could
do this another time I'd appreciate it.
Could you sit down, please?
We're not done. Sit down.
Sit down.
- Why don’t you tell me about Syed Ali?
- I told you before, I do not know a Syed Ali.
You don't?
Then how do you explain the fact that
his name is in your personal computer files?
I don't know.
You don't know.
All right.
Why don't we start again?
- Where's Marie?
- Still in her room, working on the dress.
- How much longer is he gonna be with Reza?
- Sorry, sir, I don't know.
Dad, she's gonna find out
the second she walks out of the room.
Are we gonna be able
to go through with this?
- What do you mean?
- The wedding.
- Dad, it's in less than six hours.
- No one's cancelling anything.
Just... make sure Marie
stays away from these people, OK?
Roger, I want you to monitor
how they use our intel.
I'm not comfortable with this.
- We've flagged the restricted topics, so...
- It should be a one-way dialogue.
Mr President, it's Ryan Chappelle,
Division Los Angeles.
- Yes, Ryan.
- I have an update on Nina Myers.
She's demanding a full presidential pardon.
Here's my debrief. It's finished.
Thanks.
I am supposed to get you outta here.
That's not gonna happen, is it?
It's the first time I've seen her since...
Why are you doing this to yourself, Jack?
Mason's right. You should get out of here.
- Michelle Dessler.
- Is Jack Bauer there?
Hold on. Jack.
Jack. It's for you.
- Yeah?
- Jack Bauer?
- Yes.
- Hold one moment for the president.
- Jack?
- Mr President.
I want to thank you
for your good work this morning.
Yes, sir.
There's something else,
and I want you to hear it from me personally.
About Nina Myers.
I'm gonna have to grant her
a shadow asylum.
That sounds like a pardon, sir.
It is.
But only a couple of people
will ever know about it.
She'll be deported to another country.
Jack, I know how difficult
this must be for you to hear.
It was a painful decision.
But as you know, she has information
that can help us find this bomb.
I wish there was another way.
So do l, sir.
Let's just get through this day.
Eventually we'll make it right.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Jack.
What is it?
You're gonna let her go.
- Hello?
- I've been trying to reach you.
I had my cell off. We're recording.
- I need you.
- I really need you, too.
- Quit it, Miguel. I'm in trouble.
- What happened? Are you OK?
No, no, no. It's not me, it's Megan.
You have to come help me.
Help you do what? What's goin' on?
I can't explain it over the phone.
Just get over here, please. I really need you.
Kim, I have a whole studio full of people here.
You just have to trust me. I wouldn't
ask if it wasn't important. Miguel?
OK. Where are you?
President Palmer told me
he had to take a deal with Nina.
I want the case. I know how she thinks.
- Really?
- Yes, and you know it.
I'm not talking to you, Jack.
Because you're not here right now.
- Good. Set up here, have it ready to go.
- OK.
- Did you find it yet?
- There's no plus-five here.
Try the DC lines in the phone circuits.
Great, great. Skip the virus cycle.
Just get these all online.
I need Mason's log-in sheets.
I need to know everywhere he's been.
- You're not cleared for that.
- Then clear me for it.
- I'm right in the middle of this thing.
- What does it have to do with George?
I need to make sure he's fit to run CTU.
- Fit?
- I think something's happened to him.
Believe it or not, I used to run this place.
I know what I'm doing. I wanna help him.
Please. Get me those log-in sheets.
- Can you let me know when it's done, Cori?
- I will.
- Hi, Cori.
- Hi.
I'm starved, but I don't want to eat anything.
- Why not?
- Because the dress fits perfectly right now.
- Marie...
- Yeah?
- There's been a problem.
- Of course there has. It's a wedding.
- It's about Reza.
- Oh. Is he backing out?
What's going on?
Where's Reza?
He's in the dining room.
Marie?
- Who are you?
- I'm Agent Richards, CTU Los Angeles.
- Reza's in the room talking to another agent.
- What for? What does he want with Reza?
- Dad?
- Marie, um...
- I wanna see Reza.
- Sorry, ma'am. I can't let you in.
This is our house!
I want you out of here, now!
- Kate, do you know what's going on?
- Marie, come with me.
- Why?
- Please.
This whole thing started with me.
Please try and understand.
I saw something in the company books
that didn't check out,
so I hired a private investigator
to check up on Reza.
- You what?!
- He came across the name
of a man Reza's had dealings with.
A man involved in terrorist activities.
- What?!
- I did it for you, Marie.
- To protect you.
- Protect me?
All this time, you've been
checking up on Reza behind our backs?
These people found out
something about Reza, about his past.
If he's keeping something from you,
wouldn’t you rather know?
What business is it of yours? This is my life.
How dare you interfere with it like this!
It's my wedding day!
Hiring a private investigator?
That's insane, Kate. Insane.
Marie, just calm down, OK?
These men are gonna be
outta here in a few minutes. All right?
It's just a big misunderstanding. OK?
Let's try to remember that we're a family.
Not any more.
I don't want you at the wedding.
It is unacceptable
that she did this without telling me.
Marie, I'm sorry.
It was wrong of me not to tell you first.
Apology accepted.
- Now get out of here.
- No.
Marie.
Thank you very much.
- Miguel, where's the car?
- I let Rob take it. Why?
- We need it.
- We'll take a cab.
We can't.
Kim, what's goin' on?
- We need to get Megan out of here.
- What happened?
Gary threw her to the ground.
She hit her head.
The doctors think
there's evidence of other things, too.
- Did you talk to the police?
- I can't.
He threatened to arrest me
for kidnapping if I said anything.
- Kidnapping?
- I took her out of the house. I had to.
She's safe as long as she's here
at the hospital. You need to talk to Carla.
- It's too late for that.
- What do you mean?
You know that building that blew up today?
My father used to work there.
They go after terrorists.
I talked to him a half-hour ago.
He seems to think that we need to
get out of LA as soon as possible.
Why?
Come here.
He said there was a nuclear bomb in the city.
- And he thinks it's gonna go off today.
- Whoa!
I know.
- You believe him?
- Yeah, I believe him.
- Then let's get outta here.
- No, we can't. Not without Megan.
What are you doing in my office?
How long did they give you?
I know you were exposed to high levels of
radioactive materials in Panorama City today.
- How'd you figure that out?
- Your anti-nausea medication.
It's for radiation sickness.
I checked the logs, I made a few calls.
- You inhaled plutonium, George.
- So?
So I'm not the only person
who shouldn't be here today.
How long do you have?
I'll probably be dead by this time tomorrow.
Why? What's it to you?
I wanna know what your plans are for Nina.
Soon as we get a signature from Palmer
she'll tell us everything.
- Who's gonna be the handler?
- O'Neil.
Forget about O'Neil. I wanna do it.
I'm dying, Jack. I'm not crazy. You
and Nina together is a recipe for disaster.
If you don't do this, I'll tell District about your
condition. You'll be replaced within minutes.
George, we want the same thing.
We want to finish this job and find the bomb.
Let me do it.
Go ahead.
I'm sorry.
The ambassador's chopper just took off.
As soon as he gets on his plane, he and
Salim will conference with the prime minister.
How soon can we expect
the intelligence reports?
Within the hour. And then there'll be
updates every 30 minutes after that.
OK. You'd better set up a call
with the Joint Chiefs.
I have a feeling they're not gonna be happy
about the information exchange.
Right away, sir.
Mr President, take a look at this.
Internal feed from Fox News.
The press conference was scheduled for...
What was that?
Pull up. Did you see that?
- Just moments ago...
- Where is this, Los Angeles?
- No, sir. It's right here.
- ...broke up in midair...
- I don't understand.
- It's the ambassador's chopper.
- It crashed just after takeoff.
- ...smoke billowing from the area behind me.
I have no information at this time as to
who may have been on the helicopter...
First indications are there are no survivors.
...seemed to explode.
Again, all I know is at the time,
the helicopter,
apparently a military helicopter...
Stop treating me like a criminal!
The surveillance is all hooked up
in the interrogation room, Michelle.
- I'm gonna have to get back to you.
- All right.
Visiontext Subtitles: Paul Murray
ENGLISH SDH
www.tvsubtitles.net