Whatever you've planned next is going to fail,
just like everything else you've tried today.
Almost 40 dead in the train crash, many more
near the San Gabriel Island nuclear plant.
We managed to stop the other 103
power plants from melting down.
That's what America will remember,
that we stopped you.
No. This country will be afraid
to let their leaders appear in public.
For all the hatred that you have for this
country, you don't understand it very well.
Marwan.
In the next few minutes CTU will be alerted
that the pilot and his family are missing.
What do you think we should do?
We have to make sure CTU is too busy
to realise its significance.
Jack Bauer is alive and in my custody.
I will return him to you unharmed
in exchange for Behrooz Araz.
This is Bill Buchanan from Division.
He'll be overseeing the operation.
What happens if we don't
agree to the exchange?
- We don't get Bauer back.
- That can't be the deciding factor.
If we don't go through with this,
we may lose an opportunity to trap Marwan.
Is my mother in the van?
She was working with you. Where is she?
- I don't know.
- I don't wanna die.
-  Sniper's down! Move out!
Why'd you give 'em that kid?
He's double-tagged.
We'll be tracking him.
I managed to short-circuit
some phone lines.
If you can find two service obstructions at
the same coordinates, we can get to Marwan.
We have a location
where Marwan was holding Jack.
- Yes.
- There's a problem.
As I was about to do a pre-flight check,
they grounded the plane.
Resolve this now.
- Did you report to the chief officer?
- I'm about to head over there now.
Don't let me hold you up.
- It's just a false alarm.
- All right. I'll clear it for takeoff.
We placed multiple trackers on Behrooz Araz
but those are no longer transmitting,
which means that Marwan's men
destroyed them.
- Are you close to finding Marwan?
We may be.
Bauer tagged the location
where he was being held.
We're preparing to mount a raid as we speak.
I want Marwan found now. I've asked
Secret Service to secure a landing site
so I can be on the ground
to address the nation before 11 o'clock.
Sir, we believe that you're safer in the air.
I have been flying for 20 hours. The people
need to hear from me now, not tomorrow.
Then may I suggest
you do it from Air Force One?
It may not be optimal,
but at least you'll get your message across.
I appreciate your concerns, but I'm going
to give my speech when I get to Los Angeles.
I'll inform the press corps,
give them enough time to notify their outlets.
Yes, sir.
Make sure I'm briefed on Bauer's progress
before I go on the air.
Of course.
What's Jack's status?
His team just arrived.
They'll be in place in a few minutes.
-  CTU.
- Strike teams are moving into final position.
- We're five minutes out. How's your end?
- We're coordinating backup teams.
- Chloe?
- It's me. Michelle brought me back in.
Good. Are the satellites in position?
Yes. We've been monitoring the area,
but there's been no activity.
- How's Paul doing? Is he still in surgery?
- Uh, no, he just got out.
Chloe, I'm glad to have you back.
We're gonna need your help. Is Audrey there?
- I think so.
- Let me speak to her.
Hold on.
- Hello?
- Audrey, I have Jack on the line.
- Are you there?
- Yeah, I'm here.
- Hold for Jack.
- OK.
-  Audrey.
- Jack, you OK?
Yeah, I'm fine. How's Paul doing?
They just finished operating,
but they said he's gonna make it.
- I'm waiting to talk to the doctors.
- Good, I'm glad.
Look.
Audrey, I know we have to talk
about how I handled everything with Paul.
Yeah, we do. It's just...
- It's really hard right now.
- Yeah, I-I understand.
- Are you out in the field?
- We're getting ready to move on Marwan.
- Be careful.
- Yeah. I'll call you as soon as it's done.
Yeah.
Right.
I got off the phone with DOD.
They wanna know our status.
Jack's team has been deployed.
He should begin the assault soon.
- Do you know how many hostiles are inside?
- Based on the infrared scan, eight.
Did voice transmission indicate
one of them is Marwan?
No, but we know he was there
25 minutes ago when Jack left.
If that hard drive is discovered
by the Americans,
it'll jeopardise the next phase of our plan.
- It's not here.
- You haven't looked hard enough.
I've been searching for almost an hour.
Aziz told one of his men he hid a backup copy
of those files in his apartment.
Why didn't Aziz tell you where he hid it?
Because he was killed
before he could tell me.
Anderson shared this apartment with Aziz.
Maybe he knows where the hard drive is.
Keep looking. I'll try to contact him.
Bravo three-niner in the air, heading 552.
Roger Bravo three-niner.
You are cleared for 35,000ft.
Bravo three-niner ascending to 35,000ft.
Copy that.
I'm in the air.
I should reach the target in 45 minutes.
- We have a problem.
- What kind of problem?
Aziz. He hid a backup copy of his files
in your apartment on hard drive.
- We haven't been able to find it.
- Ask Aziz.
Aziz is dead.
- I don't know about a hard drive.
- You have no idea where it might be?
If I knew where it was, I'd tell you.
- I just don't want to get myself killed.
- I'll get back to you.
In order to flush Marwan out,
lead your men down the main corridor.
- He'll try and escape through the left flank.
- Tac teams are ready to go in.
- Have they set the charges?
- Yes.
Gentlemen, we are go.
We've got a green light.
Teams A and B, move into position.
- All teams move in on target.
-  All teams, all teams...
Prepare to ignite charges on my mark.
Three, two, one,
blow the door!
Go, go! Move!
Delete the files. Delete everything.
They're down! They're down!
All right, let's go!
- Hold your fire!
- Clear!
Marwan's not here. Notify the perimeter.
Teams one and two, Marwan is not
in the building. Maintain your perimeter.
Come on!
I can't stop this thing from deleting.
This doesn't make sense.
This room's hot. Get your men out.
Get your men outta here right now!
What's happening?
What's going on over there?
- You OK?
- I think so.
- Check your men!
- Jack, if you can hear me, respond.
Michelle, Marwan's escaped. He just blew up
the hard drive to all his computers.
He's covering his tracks. I'm going off comm.
If you want me, I'm gonna be on my cell.
Chloe, get data forensics in there now,
and start a hard target search for Marwan.
Get me a medic! Medic!
Too late. You can't stop it.
Stop what?
Within the hour.
What's gonna happen within the hour?
- Mrs Raines?
- Yes.
- Your husband's in recovery.
- How is he?
He's stable. One of the bullets
did some damage to his spine.
Right now he's paralysed
from the waist down.
- Is it permanent?
- It's too early to tell.
It'll take weeks or months before we
fully understand the extent of damage.
So he could regain the use of his legs.
It's possible, yes.
- But not likely?
- Again, it's too early to tell.
We could go over the details later,
but I'd be lying to you
if I told you I was optimistic.
A lot depends on his attitude,
his support system,
emotional as well as medical.
- Does he know?
- Yes, I just told him.
- I'm sure he'd like to see you.
- Thank you.
Excuse me, can you give us a minute, please?
Thank you.
Oh, no, don't you even
think of feeling sorry for me.
Whatever they say, I'm gonna walk again.
I know you will.
So, where's Jack?
He's still out in the field.
He called a little while ago
and wanted to know how you were doing.
He knows that bullet was meant for him.
I was trying to push him out of the way.
I didn't expect to get shot myself.
What you did was very, very brave, Paul.
LAPD's widening the search perimeter,
but so far they're coming up empty.
- Something might happen within the hour.
- We're gonna find him.
- Did you secure Marwan yet?
- He must have slipped through the perimeter.
- How could you let that happen?
- It doesn't matter how.
What matters is that he's gone and we're
doing everything we can to find him.
What exactly are you doing to find him?
We've widened the perimeter, set up a search
grid. State police are conducting a sweep.
- Jack says he's got something.
- Put him on speaker.
It's Michelle.
You're also on with Tony and Bill Buchanan.
OK, look. Marwan had an area
set up for forging documents.
Some of them survived the explosion.
We secured a number of names and faces.
Castle's uploading them now.
Cross-reference them with the watch list.
- We'll do it now.
- Get back to me if you've got a match.
Edgar.
- I'm initialising the software now.
- Good.
Michelle.
Listen, um, I'm sorry if I snapped.
It's OK. We're all under a lot of pressure.
You holding up?
I'm fine.
- Edgar, how's that uplink?
- Coming up.
Chloe, how long's Buchanan
been at Division?
I don't know. It took them a while to fill
Chappelle's position. Six months?
- Where was he before that?
- Seattle, I think.
Seattle?
That's where Michelle was posted
while you were in jail, right?
Yeah.
Thanks.
We got a match.
This is Bauer.
We have a match on one of those photos.
He's on the FBI watch list.
- His name is Mitch Anderson.
- What do we got on him?
Ex-military,
arrested for drug possession, served time,
was dishonourably discharged
four years ago.
He's been hired as a mercenary
in a number of conflicts.
- Came back to the US about a year ago.
- Is he under investigation?
He was moved up the list,
but he wasn't made a priority.
The bureau sent an agent to his apartment.
- Has the agent checked in?
- They may be in transit.
OK. Get me an address on Anderson,
start digging up information,
and get me a number for the FBI agent.
I'm on it.
FBI. I'm looking for Mitch Anderson.
This is FBI Agent Drake.
Please open the door.
- Agent Drake.
- Hi. My name is Jack Bauer. I work with CTU.
Your office said you were
investigating Mitch Anderson.
- I got to his apartment a few minutes ago.
- He's not there?
No. Why is CTU involved?
Is there new information about Anderson?
We have evidence connecting him
to a man named Marwan.
Marwan's responsible
for all the terrorist activity today.
- We believe he's planning another attack.
- How is Anderson involved?
- I'll advise you when I get there.
- How far away are you?
- About ten minutes out.
- I'll be here.
Thank you.
Yes.
We had a delay.
We're heading over there now.
- What about Anderson?
- He's in the air, on his way to the target.
He's on schedule. Are your people in place?
Yes. We're ready to deploy.
Good. I'll see you when we arrive.
I'm sorry, but this just isn't cutting it.
The tone is all wrong.
Maybe I could give them
a clearer idea of what you want.
This is one of the most traumatic days
in this country's history.
What I want is a speech
that is equal to the occasion.
Give me a few minutes, will you, Robert?
Let me think about this a little while longer.
Of course, Mr President.
Oh, and Robert,
ask my son to step in, will you?
Yes, sir.
Dad?
A quick trip to Mexico, a low-key state visit,
then we'd have some time to spend together.
It's OK. The, uh, press corps
has been keeping me entertained.
You know, ever since your mother died,
I promised myself I'd be there for you.
You were doing what you had to do.
I could use your help right about now. I'm
gonna address the nation in about one hour.
- I still don't have a speech I'm happy with.
- I'm no speech writer.
No, I know, but you've got a level head,
and you're about
the most decent person I know.
As far as I'm concerned, you represent
the very best this country has to offer.
So.
What do you wanna hear the president say
when he addresses you tonight?
The truth.
We've been attacked by terrorists.
Americans are dead.
The man responsible is still at large.
We are by no means certain
we can catch him before he strikes again.
What happened earlier...
may be nothing
compared to what happens next.
That's the truth, Kevin.
Is that what you think I should say?
I don't know.
Neither do I,
but the fact remains...
I have to say something.
Do you want me to help you figure it out?
Absolutely.
Agent Drake?
- Drop the weapon now!
- Are you Agent Bauer?
- Yes! Holster your weapon!
- I need to see your ID.
I don't have ID.
I'm working with CTU on a provisional basis.
I talked to you ten minutes ago.
You can confirm with Division.
Agent Drake, just take it easy.
He's with me. Agent Hart, CTU.
Now I'm gonna holster my gun,
and I'm gonna show you my credentials.
I'm sorry.
But with everything that happened today,
- you can't be too careful.
- I understand.
We just intercepted a call indicating Anderson
was in possession of computer files
that could tell us Marwan's next target.
- What's the source of the intercepted call?
- I'm still waiting for the details.
- Did you find the apartment like this?
- No. There may be a backup copy of the files.
I was trying to find it.
Right now Anderson's our only lead. We're
gonna stay here and help you finish the job.
Do a canvass. I'll take upstairs.
- Where are you?
- I'm almost in position.
- What's the problem?
- Is my cover in place?
I've told you before, yes.
You'll be 100 per cent safe.
Marwan, they have to believe I'm dead.
They will. My people have taken care of this.
They better,
cos once this is done,
the entire world is gonna be looking for me.
Recovery teams aren't gonna
be allowed in there for a few weeks.
- I understand.
- Would you pass along our condolences?
- I'll tell him.
- Sorry we couldn't help.
Thanks, Ruben.
- Edgar.
- Yeah?
I have some bad news. Do you want me
to tell you here or somewhere private?
What?
Ruben Weiss from OSHA said they're not
gonna be able to get into the area
where your mother died
for a few weeks or months.
- Why not?
- Think about it.
Half-life? Radiation?
- What does that mean?
- Well, he didn't spell it out,
but I think that means you're gonna have
to have your funeral without the body.
- Of your mother.
- I can't deal with this right now, Chloe.
Michelle needs a prioritised list
for Marwan's pursuit plan.
Oh.
OK, good.
- Do you want me to do that for you?
- No.
LAPD's locked down the area where Marwan
was last seen. Review the search grid.
- All right.
- Thanks.
Michelle.
- When were you planning on telling me?
- About what?
About you and Buchanan.
Never, because it's none of your business.
Michelle.
Before you worked with him at Division,
you worked with him in Seattle.
- Yeah.
- We were still married then.
Legally, yes.
Did you sleep with him
while we were married?
No.
- I didn't.
- But you are now.
Like I said, it's none of your business.
- Edgar, where are those updates?
- Coming right up.
Edgar, what are you doing?
- Ms Dessler. What?
- Edgar, wait.
Wait. I made a mistake. I used row-major
format instead of column-major.
Why would you do that, Chloe? Row-major
isn't compatible with our software.
- It'll bring all our processors to a crawl.
- I know. It was a mistake.
Well, fix it.
- Chloe, why did you cover for me?
- You're welcome.
You'd have your job back
if I'd handed her that disk.
I thought you had a lot on your mind.
- Agent Bauer?
- Yeah.
I checked with the neighbours.
Nobody's seen him.
- Did you talk to the manager?
- He kept to himself, paid his rent on time.
OK, thanks.
- Agent Drake?
- Yes.
Anderson was ex-military.
This bag is from Vanguard Mills.
They make medals for the armed forces.
There's a date stamp on it, three months old.
- Anderson left the military four years ago.
- You think he's posing as military?
There's a possibility.
Let your people know. We'll do the same.
- Have this scanned. Send it over to Chloe.
- You got it.
This is Special Agent Drake. Can you put me
through to Dawson, please? Thank you.
- CTU, Almeida.
- Tony, it's Jack.
Anderson might be posing as military. Update
the profile and see if anything comes back.
- All right, I'm on it.
- OK, thanks.
Yeah, this is Drake.
Listen, we just found credible evidence
suggesting that Anderson
is disguised as military.
That's right. Yes.
Fine.
Yes.
No, that's not a problem.
Good. All right, well, thanks.
I'll let you know if we find anything else.
Hey.
I found something. It's an external hard drive.
This is exactly what we're looking for.
That's good work.
Drop the weapon!
Son of a bitch.
Come on.
Edgar Stiles.
- It's Jack. Where's Chloe?
- She's busy doing a systems update.
Tell Michelle and Tony that the FBI agent was
an impostor working for Marwan. I killed her.
She took out my backup.
CTU needs to send out a team,
lock down the apartment and investigate.
- Do you wanna tell 'em yourself?
- No. Help me pull some data off a hard drive.
The directory's locked. Hold on one second.
I'm gonna put you on speakerphone.
- Go ahead.
- Can you get into the root?
- Yeah, but I can't open the files.
- Hold down tab arrow until the code appears.
OK.
What are the last three digits
on the part code?
R-2-5.
Escape out and enter pass code C-T-I-S-8-3-R.
That should backdoor you into the files.
Oh, my God.
- Jack, did it work?
- I'm in. I need to speak to Michelle now!
- Hold on, I'll get 'em. Jack's on the line.
- Jack, what is it?
I pulled some data off a hard drive
in Anderson's apartment.
On it is a flight simulator and full schematics
to an F117 A Stealth fighter.
- Anderson's an experienced pilot.
- I know. I also think he's posing as military.
I believe Mitch Anderson's
trying to steal a Stealth fighter.
- Almeida.
- Have you got anything from the air force?
Hang on, it's coming through.
An F117 A Stealth fighter took off on
a scheduled mission about 40 minutes ago.
The pilot did not call in on schedule.
That was about six minutes ago.
All attempts to contact that pilot have failed.
OK. We have to assume
Anderson's flying that plane.
- I agree.
- Is the aircraft armed?
- Yeah, standard non-nuclear ordinance.
- We need a list of obvious possible targets.
Yeah, right. I'm working that up right now.
Wait.
Air Force One is headed to LA.
- Jack, did you hear that?
- Yeah. What's the ETA?
11pm.
Oh, my God.
They're going after the president.
- I'll call Air Force One.
- We don't have a lot of time.
Get me the recall frequency for that squadron
and send Anderson's bio over to my screen.
- I'm on it.
- Where's Buchanan?
- He's in tactical.
- He has to tell the Joint Chiefs of Staff
that we believe the likely target
is President Keeler aboard Air Force One.
You really have been helpful, Kevin.
I think this speech strikes just the right note.
I'm sorry to interrupt. It's Dessler at CTU.
- She says it's urgent.
- Yes, what is it, Ms Dessler?
Mr President, we have reason to believe that
a Stealth fighter has been stolen by a terrorist,
and is in your airspace as we speak.
This plane is due to land. I'm about to address
the country. Just how sure are we about this?
It's a near certainty.
Your pilot is preparing to combine
evasive action with immediate descent.
You're cleared to land in Palm Springs.
I'm sure my escort fighters
are capable of protecting Air Force One.
Mr President, this is a Stealth aircraft,
invisible to radar.
If he finds you, he may be on you
before your fighter escort can react.
- What are the chances he'll find us?
- I can't be sure,
but the radar signature of a 747
and four fighter planes is unmistakeable.
You're telling me that this stolen Stealth
plane will attempt to shoot me down?
It looks that way, Mr President.
I see.
Dad?
It's gonna be OK.
Our plane may come under attack.
We're gonna take some precautions.
- Get me the vice president on the phone.
- Yes, sir.
All right.
It should be coming through right now.
- Yeah, I got it.
- Not much to go on. Parents deceased.
Has a sister named Alicia. It looks like
they lived together, so they might be close.
- Any contact information?
- I can find that for you.
- No time. Have you got the recall frequency?
- Yeah.
- Get ready to patch me through to Anderson.
- Copy that.
Air Force One is descending
through 20,000ft.
- The fighters have formed a protective shield.
- How long before it touches down?
- Nine minutes.
- And no sign of the Stealth aircraft?
- Not yet.
- Maybe it's not there.
It's there. We just can't see it.
We're being beaten by our own technology.
When you hit your intercom button,
you're patched through to the Stealth fighter.
Copy that.
Mitch Anderson, can you hear me?
Captain Anderson, do you read me?
My name is Jack Bauer. I'm a federal agent.
We know who you are,
we know what you're trying to do.
Sir, I know you can hear me.
Nothing you've done so far can't be undone.
All you have to do is change your vector
to heading 115 southeast.
That'll put you on a fast track to Edwards
Air Force Base. Once you touch down,
then we can discuss how you wanna
handle this. Please just talk to me.
Explain to me what you're trying to do,
what you're trying to accomplish.
Why?
I've been going over your service record.
It's very impressive.
Graduated top of your class,
Air Force Academy.
Highly decorated for your service in Desert
Storm including Air Force Silver Star.
What happened to you?
Explain it to me,
because what you're trying to do right now,
I don't think that's who you are.
I don't think that's how
you wanna be remembered.
If I go down, you have to stay the course.
Do you understand?
I'm sure it won't come to that.
Charles, you're the vice president.
The nation will be relying on you.
If the worst happens,
think of me as a casualty of war.
Don't waste time,
just pick up the torch and move forward.
Yes, sir, Mr President.
We think CTU is in communication
with the pilot of the stolen aircraft.
Patch it through.
I've just been notified by the FBI
that they've contacted your sister, Alicia.
They've advised her of what's happening.
She's scared.
She wants to talk to you.
All you have to do, Captain Anderson, is
respond to me and I'll put her right through.
Captain Anderson? Captain Anderson?
We've been cut off.
Is there an override channel?
He cut off all communication circuits.
We can't do anything.
Dammit!
Dad.
I'm scared.
Oh, my God.
Was Air Force One just hit?
Escort pilots report...
Air Force One has suffered an indirect hit
by an air-to-air missile.
Pieces are falling to the ground
over the desert.
Visiontext Subtitles: Margaret Burke
ENGLISH SDH