What if I can get us
a copy of Keeler's playbook?
- What exactly do you mean by playbook?
- His entire prep for tonight's debate.
- I told you to drop that.
- Listen. There is something you need to see.
- There's nothing I need to see.
- It's about Anne.
It's something we didn't know about her,
something that could damage us.
- Can I talk to you now?
- Of course. OK. What's up?
Chase and I have been going out for a while.
And it's starting to get serious.
I really care for him, Dad.
So what do you think?
I don't know what I think.
We want the release
of Ram贸n Salazar.
If you refuse to comply,
the virus will be unleashed.
It looks like the virus was delivered
in a crystalline form.
Maybe what you're looking for
is a white powder.
- So, it would look like cocaine? Or heroin?
- Yeah, that may even be the strategy.
Someone thinks they're selling coke,
in fact they're handling the virus.
- Where did you get that money?
- It doesn't matter. We needed it, I got it.
This is how you're gonna help your family?
By dealing drugs?
I'm not dealing 'em. It's a stupid delivery.
If that kid's got a bag of cocaine that's
got the virus in it and he doesn't know it,
I need to stop him putting it into circulation.
You didn't shoot up, did you?
You think you can hide it from me?
- I'm not trying to hide it. I'm trying to quit.
- People don't just quit.
I am not going on record with this addiction,
do you understand me?
You're the only person who knows,
and it's gonna stay that way.
Give me an update.
- Kyle's still in his house.
- What about the package?
- It's with him.
- And Ram贸n?
- Just waiting to come home.
- Good.
Have you downloaded everyone's folders?
Not yet. I'm pulling up details on the virus.
Don't waste too much time. All we need to
know is it kills within 24 hours of exposure
- and we believe Kyle Singer has it.
- I got all that. What's our approach to Singer?
Jack's meeting Nicole Duncan,
Health Services.
They're gonna take a Hazmat team over
to Singer's apartment. He's waiting for it now.
Son of a bitch.
- Hey, Jack. How you doing?
- OK, Nicole. How've you been?
Till this afternoon, I was doing fine.
You know, I tried to reach you
after I heard about Teri.
Yeah, I know.
After that I kind of withdrew.
I appreciated the calls, thanks.
We should get going.
I just ran Macer's epidemiological model.
Her estimates were off.
- Better or worse than we thought?
- Twice as bad.
She had 9% of the population infected
within a week but it's closer to 20%.
And the infection-to-mortality rate is higher
than her estimate. Almost 95% lethal.
I've been hunting germs for years,
I've not seen anything like this.
Great.
Are you feeling OK?
- Yeah, why?
- You're perspiring.
It's been nonstop since noon.
We'll be about eight minutes. It'd be great
to go over the quarantine protocols first.
- No problem.
- Good.
If you refuse to comply,
the virus will be unleashed.
- We want the release of Ram贸n Salazar...
- Gael!
Gael, take a look at this.
Closing in on the point of origin of this call.
- You see this code artefact here?
- Yeah.
We found a few more in this recording.
I think it's from a domestic switch-on mode.
Think the call was made from inside the US?
Maybe. I'm piping it over to your system.
- See if you can find a match.
- OK.
- But do it after the meeting.
- What meeting?
Tony's shifting resources to help Jack
in the field. He's closing in on the virus.
Gael. Jack needs the audio feed
when he gets to the apartment.
Tony needs me for something.
I'll do it after the meeting.
I need it before. Come do it now.
I can't! Stop bugging me.
I'll get it to you.
Fine.
Have you thought about how it will be
when Ram贸n comes back?
How it will be?
- Like it was before.
- Things have changed, Hector.
Nothing's changed.
He's only been gone three months.
You've changed.
You've been in charge
while he's been in prison.
Are you willing to give that up so easily?
- What is it?
- Bauer's about to intercept the package.
- How?
- I'm not sure, I'm about to find out.
- Is Gomez still on Kyle Singer?
- Of course.
He'll be fine.
Hey. How was the interview?
Fine.
What's up, Dad?
Your mother told me you paid the rent.
All three months we owed.
Yeah, I came into a little money.
How does a 19-year-old kid who doesn't
have a job come into a little money?
Tim and I, we went down
to the track the other day.
He knows this guy over at the stables
so, uh, we got a tip.
- Where did you get the money?
- Dad, what does it matter?
Honestly, the rent's paid for three months,
all right? The pressure's off us now.
Did you do something illegal?
No.
I told you, we went to Santa Anita
and we got lucky. I didn't do anything.
Don't lie to me, I got enough to worry about.
Now, this is my house. I pay the rent.
I take care of you and your mother.
Yeah, and when you get that job
you can go ahead and pay me back, huh?
- Wait, we're not done!
- We're done!
- Don't walk away!
- You should be thanking me!
Kyle! Kyle!
Open the door! Open the door!
His name's Kyle Singer.
We think he's transporting the virus,
- though it's likely he doesn't realize it.
- How could he not know?
Health Services believe it was made
to look like heroin or coke.
We know Singer was hired to deliver
a package from Mexico to Los Angeles.
- He thinks he's smuggling drugs.
- That's the working theory. Here's the thing:
Once Singer delivers the powder,
it's cut up and distributed around the city.
Then it's impossible to contain.
- Well, isn't LAPD grabbing Singer?
- No.
Why not? Can't they get there faster?
LAPD's not trained to handle a hot zone.
Jack's going in with Health Services.
We're running the operation from here,
updating the president in real-time. Now...
we have to approach Singer with care.
He has no idea how deadly the powder is.
What's going on?
-  He's locked himself in.
- Did you fight again?
I'm not fighting...
- He doesn't respect me.
- Of course he does.
You're going to have to talk to him.
How can I talk
when there's a door between us?
Give him the benefit of the doubt.
Maybe there's more.
- He said he won it at the track.
- He could've come up with a better lie.
- Maybe he was telling the truth.
- Come on, Helen. Where are you going?
- Wherever.
- Hey, hey, hey. What's in the bag?
- Clothes.
- Open it.
- What?
- Open the bag.
I'm warning you.
Open that bag or I'm gonna open it myself.
- Mom?
- Kyle, listen to your father.
- It's none of his business.
- While you live in my house it is.
Your house? This isn't your house,
you can't even pay the rent.
- Oh, Kyle!
- Hey!
- Aw, will you quit snooping, please?
- Don't even think about it.
What is this? Huh? Coke? Heroin?
- Give it back.
- What did you say?
- I need it.
- You need it? Are you some kind of junkie?
No. I'm just delivering it to this guy, OK?
- And if I don't get it to him...
- Who?
- It's just a guy, OK?
Give me a name.
Kyle. Answer your father.
Just give it to me, OK?
Stop it! Stop it, both of you!
Both of you! Both of you, stop!
Sam! Sam! Don't, Sam! Kyle!
I can't reiterate this enough.
This is a credible threat.
Salazar's people will release this virus
if we don't find it first.
So let's get going.
- Thought you were meant to be with Dad?
- I was. He sent me back here.
- Why?
- To question Parker.
He already turned in Singer,
what else can you get?
- Nothing. And that's the point.
- I don't understand.
Your dad's sidelining me, Kim.
He's making me sit out.
- Why?
- Why do you think?
Because of us? Chase, I'm sorry.
He says he's protecting me, but I'm not
the one he's trying to protect here.
- You're not blaming me, are you?
- All I'm saying is we shouldn't have told him.
What were we supposed to do?
Sneak around until someone catches us?
- Well, we could have waited.
- Until when?
He'd have the same response
no matter when we told him.
I gotta deal with this kid Parker.
Jeffrey, the food's exceptionally bad today.
Aren't there laws in this country
for cruel and unusual punishment?
Tell Annicon I'm ready to talk.
Bauer couldn't tell me, but Salazar's got
leverage, enough to get him released.
I won't let this son of a bitch
erase the last few years of my life.
Call your friend at the State Department.
See what he can tell you.
- Annicon.
- Mr Annicon?
- Yeah.
- This is Jeff Benson, Salazar's guard.
- I know who you are.
- Sir, Salazar asked to see you.
- Why?
- He says he's ready to talk.
I'll be right there.
- Don't ask me why, just do it.
- All right.
- I hope you can get a refund.
- A refund?
From whoever sold you that load of crap.
Keeler will use this against you in this debate.
Ignoring it won't make it go away.
Neither will dignifying it with a response.
He'll claim that Anne perjured herself.
Which, in case you've forgotten, is a felony.
Anne is no felon.
The allegation itself is enough to damage
you. Now, come on, David. Please, think.
You know you can't go into this debate
without some kind of response.
- What do you propose?
- Talk to Anne.
Make sure she's told you everything.
- She has told me everything.
- Are you sure?
Ever since I started seeing Anne,
you've undermined our relationship.
- Just because you don't like her?
- You're right, I don't like her.
This isn't about me and Anne,
it's about you and Anne.
If she's got nothing to hide, fine,
she's got nothing to hide.
But you'd better find out before you face off
with Keeler on national television.
Presidential flight check.
Did you ask your friend,
Jack Bauer, what's going on?
You did, didn't you?
But he wouldn't say.
It must be very frustrating, Luis,
being kept in the dark.
- You have something to tell me?
- I asked you here, didn't I?
Then start talking because
you used up my patience an hour ago.
Whoa. You are a dog with a bone, Luis.
Once you bite down, you don't let go.
When I'm out of here
I don't want you on me any more.
When you're out of here?
You are right.
In a few hours I am going home.
Really? And how will you manage that?
Hector's a good brother.
Unless he's got a key to this place,
you're not going anywhere.
But he does have a key. And when he turns it,
the last two years of your life,
all the hours you spent
away from your family,
all the work you've done to put me here,
will go away. Just like that.
I wanted you to hear it from me, Luis.
I wanted it to be the last thing you ever heard.
Argh!
Your son will be returned to you now.
I'm just saying that Kyle is in over his head.
We're not calling a lawyer.
He hasn't even been arrested.
- Not yet.
- Maybe he won't be.
If we leave it alone, don't do anything,
- maybe this will just go away.
- You can't be serious?
Why not, Sam?
Why do we have to let anybody know?
- Because it's against the law not to?
- What are you suggesting we do?
Call the police? Maybe they'll give us
a reward and we can pay our rent?
Right, that wasn't fair. I'm sorry.
Oh my God!
- What are you doing?
- Do you want to visit your son in jail?
Wait a minute! Helen!
Get back, get back!
- Kyle Singer! Kyle Singer!
- He's not here!
Isolate them. Draw blood for a full count and
get an oral swab. Seal all windows and vents.
No!
In here! In here!
Tony! The virus is out.
I repeat, the virus is out.
- Copy that, Jack. Where is it?
- The sewage system.
Get DWP to shut
all lines from ground zero.
It might be airborne. Get the fire department
and the LAPD to set up a perimeter.
- Tell them we've got a level three hot zone.
- Copy that.
Come in.
Wayne said you wanted to see me.
What's wrong?
Keeler.
He's bringing your ex-husband
into this debate.
The SEC's investigation into his company.
Ted was convicted
and served his sentence. You know that.
I know what you told me.
I told you all there is to know. Ted's company
was introducing a hypertension drug...
- And you reviewed the research?
- Yes.
- Which turned out to have been fabricated.
- Which Ted knew at the time and I didn't.
Now Ted's claiming that you both knew.
He can't reverse eight years
after giving testimony.
Well, he is. And he's willing
to go on record with the press.
- I don't know what to say except he's a liar.
- It's your word against his.
David.
You have reason to be suspicious.
God knows, you've been betrayed
by some of the people you've trusted most.
But I'm not Sherry.
I told you the whole truth once.
And I'm not going to defend it.
Because, if there's anything less
than complete trust between us...
I do trust you, Anne.
You should.
- Yes?
-  We need to talk.
I'm with Anne now.
- Let me guess, she denied everything.
- I believe her.
Well, listen. I might be able
to make this whole thing go away.
- How?
- Meet me in the auditorium. Alone.
All right.
Have you had a chance
to take a look at Nicole's field report yet?
- I'm almost done.
- What are your impressions?
- From what I've read so far, I'm optimistic.
- Think we'll be able to contain the virus?
- We should be able to limit casualties.
- Even if it's airborne?
There is a risk of it spreading,
but the team acted fast.
They evacuated and sealed off
the building and quarantined the Singers.
- When do we get their test results?
- Five minutes, ten tops.
- So, it looks like we lucked out, huh?
- Yeah, we deserve a little luck.
- I gotta go, but keep me in the loop.
- OK, you do the same.
LAPD's doing the perimeter. They need
wind vectors for the last 15 minutes.
Call meteorology. Extension 2112.
Tony, local news picked up the story about
the body being dumped at Health Services.
- They want a statement. What do I say?
- Nothing.
Tony. Warden Mitchell's on the phone. He's
calling from the prison, he says it's urgent.
Almeida.
- Mr and Mrs Singer?
- What the hell is going on here?
Because this is not about drugs.
- We think you've been exposed to a virus.
- A virus?
It's called the Cordilla virus. We believe Kyle
carried it in from Mexico without knowing.
- What do you mean? How?
- He thought he was carrying drugs.
So we've been exposed?
- I'm afraid so.
- What does that mean? Are we sick?
We'll keep you here until we get your results.
Excuse me.
- This is Bauer.
- Jack, it's Tony.
- I think Kyle's been exposed.
- We got an all-points on him.
- Have you set up a perimeter?
- We're doing all we can.
All agencies are in the loop
on a need-to-know basis.
- OK, good work.
- Listen, Jack, I know this isn't the best time,
but I just got some bad news
I figured you'd want to know.
- What's wrong?
- Luis Annicon was murdered.
- Murdered? How?
- Salazar's guard. We've got him in custody.
He claims Salazar had his son kidnapped
and threatened to kill him if he didn't.
- I'm sorry. I know you two worked closely.
- I'll have to get back to you.
- Is everything OK?
- I'm gonna get back to you.
- These results can't be right.
- They are.
- Check it again.
- I have. Blood, saliva and surface tests.
They're all negative. We can't find
even a trace amount of this virus.
What are you doing? You haven't showered.
- We're not at risk.
- What? I watched the powder get out.
It's harmless.
Some form of silicate, that's all.
- What?
- There is no virus in the powder.
We tested five samples,
there weren't even trace amounts.
Atmospheric and surface analysis
also came up negative
- and Kyle's parents tested negative as well.
- You're sure?
The only thing I'm unsure of
is being on the right trail.
The body dropped at Health Services
was linked to Singer.
Why would Salazar pay him
to bring a bag of worthless powder?
Fine, Jack.
But where do we even start looking?
I don't know.
Wait a second. Macer said the only way
to transport it was in crystalline form, right?
The only way it'll survive
outside a living body.
What if it was never outside a living body?
- What do you mean?
- Transported inside a living host?
What if Kyle Singer was infected
in Mexico before he even left?
Salazar has no power
if he's already infectious.
That's the point!
He wouldn't be contagious yet.
- The incubation period is 14 hours.
- Right. Think about it.
We know that Singer
was in Mexico 11 hours ago.
They haven't threatened to release it
for another three hours.
- The math adds up.
- We need to find Kyle Singer.
- Hello?
- Linda?
- Kyle, I told you, I have nothing to say to you.
- No, no, listen to me, OK? I'm in trouble.
- Yeah, because you're dealing drugs.
- I need your help.
- What happened?
- My Dad found the stuff.
We got in a fight.
I split, he's still got it.
I got to get this to them, all right?
These guys are hard-core.
I gotta make it right.
- Make it right? How?
- I don't know.
I was thinking I could pay 'em.
You know, just to keep them off my back.
- You want me to give you money?
- No, no. Just borrow.
How much?
- It's about 20 grand on the street.
- I don't have that kind of money, Kyle.
- Doesn't your Dad keep some cash around?
- Not that much!
Linda, listen to me!
These guys, they will kill me
if I don't give them something.
- Please. Please, anything will help right now.
- Now you want me to get involved in this?
Just... just let me borrow something.
Anything.
I will pay you back, I swear to God.
- Where are you?
- At the mall.
- I'll get there as soon as I can.
- Thank you.
CTU knows the powder's not real.
They're after Singer.
- What do you want me to do?
- Stay with him.
As soon as he's alone,
grab him and take him to containment.
We can't let the cops get him.
We need Singer to make this work.
Don't lose the boy.
Follow him and do what you have to.
I want nothing to happen.
- There's no way we'll ever release Salazar.
-  What are the alternatives?
- CTU's very close to containing the threat.
- So, we should hold on?
Yes, that's right.
All right, Stan, I'll make sure
you're kept in the loop.
- What is it, Wayne?
- I just spoke to Anne's ex-husband.
Now, listen. All Ted Packard wants is money.
- If we pay him, he'll recant before the debate.
- That's blackmail.
- That's business.
- I don't think so.
It's cheaper than trying to defend against
this allegation, which is going to hurt you.
I've faced down worse lies.
I think I've earned some credibility.
You read the polls this morning?
Because Keeler is closing the gap
and this race is much closer than it should be.
Now, listen, I know it's distasteful, David,
but in cost-benefit terms it's a no-brainer.
- Anne won't think so.
- Anne doesn't have to know.
I can't keep it from her.
Well, that's your choice.
But if this comes out
Anne will be on the front page
of every newspaper in this country.
She's not Sherry.
She's not equipped to handle that scrutiny.
And you will not be able to protect her from it.
Between this debate and the threat of
this outbreak, you have enough on your plate.
Don't be a martyr. Keep it simple.
We could have the money within the hour.
Do it.
What's going on?
They don't have their suits on. Are we OK?
- Yes. The powder was harmless.
- Thank God!
This was for nothing?
You scared the hell out of us.
Mr Singer, we still need to find your son.
- Is there anything you can tell us to help?
- Why? You said it was harmless.
We believe your son was infected with
the virus in Mexico before he came home.
We have three hours to find him
before he becomes contagious.
What are you saying?
That our son could die?
- Yes, that could happen.
- Oh, God.
Look, I know how difficult
this must be for you and I'm sorry.
But we need to find your son.
We need to find him now.
- Uh. Have you tried his cellphone?
- The line's been disconnected.
Oh, wait! Wait, wait, wait!
- He took my phone.
- What's the number?
818-555-0103.
OK. I'm gonna need one of you to call him.
This is my fault. Kyle never would've done
this if I could take care of my own family.
- No!
- Yes. You know it's true.
Tony, it's Jack.
Jack, I just spoke to LAPD.
They got a priority APB out on Singer.
Good. I think we've got a number on him.
All right. We'll thread the line
through a tracing matrix.
The number's 818-555-0103. I want you
to route the call back through my cellphone.
I need you to trace that number
and reroute the call through Jack's cellphone.
I'm going to need one of you
to make the call now.
I need you to keep him on the line
as long as possible so we can trace him.
What am I supposed to tell him?
The truth.
- Tony, you set?
- Yeah, we're ready.
- Linda?
- Kyle, it's your father.
- Dad?
- We need to talk.
Look, I don't know what you want to talk
about. I already know how pissed off you are.
Whatever you did, I know you were just
trying to help out your mom and me.
Well, unless you give back the stuff,
I gotta deal with the situation, OK?
Kyle, please, don't hang up. Please!
Just listen to me.
What I'm telling you is important.
- Please. You have to come home.
- Dad, why do you sound different?
I need you to trust me
on something I'm about to tell you.
- Dad?
- You may have gotten a virus.
Something you picked up in Mexico.
- What? How did you know I went to Mexico?
- It doesn't matter. But you may be sick.
And if you are then you need
to get checked out by a doctor.
Dad, I don't know what
you're talking about. I feel fine.
I know it sounds crazy, but it's real.
- There's some people here trying to help.
- Cops?
- Tony, have you got a lock on this trace?
- How much longer?
- I got a cell tower but it covers three miles.
- I can't believe this.
One minute you tell me that you love me and
the next you're selling me out to some cops.
They're not the police. They're just trying to
stop this virus before it becomes an outbreak.
Dad, I already told you, I feel fine.
They say you won't start feeling sick for
another few hours, but by then it'll be too late.
- Got a lock yet?
- How much longer?
- Ten seconds.
- What d'you want me to do? Turn myself in?
Because you may be sick. And if you are,
other people are going to get infected.
Tony!
Got it. He's at Los Feliz Mall,
between Vermont and Sunset.
Get his photo to mall security.
Tell them not to approach him.
Jack, you're 20 minutes away by car.
I can land a team there in ten minutes.
Fine. Tony, I don't want you taking Chase.
- Why not?
- I just don't.
Thank you very much. We'll notify you
when we have him in custody.
Please, help our son.
We will.
- O'Brian.
-  Chloe, Tony's off site for a while.
- He is?
- Yeah. I'm taking over for a few hours.
- OK.
- Let people in your area know.
- OK, I will.
- Thanks.
What was that?
- Michelle's taking over for a couple of hours.
- Where's Tony?
We've located Singer.
Jack can't get there so Tony's going.
What? Tony's not field ops.
They're really going out of their way
to cut you out of the loop.
Did you do something to piss off Jack?
Bad idea, Chase.
You're just gonna make things worse.
- Tony. I heard they found Kyle. Is it for real?
- We'll see. I'm meeting Jack there now.
OK, I'm done with Parker. He's said all
he's gonna say. I want back on the case.
We're handling that, Chase, all right?
Jack doesn't want me there.
Did he say why he's cutting me out?
He's your boss, it's his call.
This isn't right.
Did he tell you it's because of Kim?
He found out we're seeing each other
and this is how he's making me pay.
Take it up with Jack.
Just want to keep the line open for Tony.
- Leave a message for Jack Bauer.
- Dammit, Jack!
Chase. Chase!
I know my Dad can be hard,
but he'll come around.
- How do you know?
- Because I know my father.
Maybe you don't know him
as well as you think.
- What is that supposed to mean?
- Nothing. It's OK. Forget it, Kim.
Don't you think I feel bad enough already?
Because I do.
- We shouldn't have told him.
- Well, the only other option
is for us to stop seeing each other, which,
as far as I'm concerned, is not an option.
Or is it?
- Chase, what do you want?
- To be able to do my job.
Kim. We need you at your station.
Tony's about to land.
Tony Almeida, CTU.
We've found the guy you're looking for.
He's in the rotunda.
Bronson, watch down the east entrance.
Pearson, I want you in the security office.
- How long have you been using, Jack?
- What?
I did a rotation in rehab, you learn
to pick it up when someone's using.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- You know exactly what I'm talking about.
How long?
For a while now.
It was the only way I could maintain
my cover with the Salazars.
- Are you high now?
- No!
- It's empty.
- Nicole, I told you, I'm fine.
- I'm not so sure.
- Then turn me in!
I don't want to turn you in, Jack.
I'm worried about you.
You don't have to be. I've kicked it.
I have a responsibility to stop this virus
and I am taking a calculated risk
that you are more of an asset than a liability.
Just please don't screw this up.
I won't.
Yeah?
- We found Singer. We're gonna pick him up.
- OK, where are you?
Second floor rotunda,
top of the north escalator. You?
Unloading dock, north entrance. Got a visual?
Yeah.
- Where are your men?
- Posted on the main entrances.
- Good. We'll be there in a minute.
- All right.
Have your men cover
all the parking-level exits. Let's go!
I don't want to cause any kind of commotion.
- CTU's about to move in on the kid.
- Stand down, it's too hot.
- It's my only chance. He can't get caught.
- No, no. Wait!
- I can't wait.
- Gomez!
- Wait here. We want to make a clean grab.
- Yes, sir.
- Kyle?
- Who are you?
My name's Tony Almeida.
I'm a federal agent, but I'm here to help you.
What your father told you
about your being sick is true.
- I don't believe you.
- Come with me, I'll prove it to you.
Get out of the way! Move!
Nicole, he's been hit in the neck!
Jimmy, give me your walkie-talkie.
We have an officer down.
Singer is not in custody.
I repeat, Singer is not in custody.
Maintain cover on all exits.