- Has Bauer arrived at CTU?
- No, not yet.
I need you to clear an entrance.
Why are you tracking Jack Bauer?
I'm sure if they're tracking Jack Bauer,
they have a reason.
This man is a professional assassin. He killed
Dr Paulson. Did you let him into CTU?!
They told me he was here to place a tap
on one of the servers. That's all I knew.
- Who told you?
- The White House.
Mr. Cummings.
Palmer was murdered because
he was about to expose Cummings' link.
You want the gas,
Cummings is your connection.
Cummings is the president's chief advisor.
How do we get to him?
I secretly meet Mike Novick.
- Who did you tell? Who did you tell?
- I didn't tell anybody, Jack.
- Tell your men to stand down!
- Sorry, sir, we can't do that.
The gas is being smuggled out by separatists
who think they're going to use it
against Russians.
- However, it will never reach Russian soil.
- And you know this how?
We control the remote detonators
on those canisters.
As soon as they reach the terrorist base,
we'll trigger the canisters.
- You're a traitor.
- Let things play out as they are.
Otherwise, your administration will be
implicated, and your presidency destroyed.
Mr. President, my name is Jack Bauer.
I'm sorry to confront you like this.
But your chief of staff is withholding
information vital to this nation's security.
Stop this!
I'm done talking with you, understand?
So, for the last time, where is the nerve gas?
Stop. Stop! Stop! I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
It's on a freighter
leaving the port of Long Beach at 2:30.
CTU, we have located the target container.
No hostiles present.
You have a green light.
Open 'em up. Open 'em all up.
Moving on, moving on.
What have we got? Nothing?
There are no gas canisters here, CTU.
The nerve gas is not here.
- Where are the canisters?
- I've told you everything.
We know you've altered the arming codes.
Erwich, listen. We can negotiate something.
I don't negotiate with my enemies.
I eliminate them.
Your country is about to pay
a very steep price for betraying us.
I was approached six months ago by a man
named James Nathanson. He was my contact.
- Who is he?
- Former CIA.
Said he was recruiting like-minded
individuals for this initiative.
Initiative? Is that what you call this?
You helped terrorists
acquire weaponised nerve gas!
We were going to trigger the canisters
once they reached their base in central Asia.
- This was not supposed to happen.
- It happened!
You got into bed with them and they're
threatening to use the gas on US citizens.
You say it like our goal was to kill Americans.
What the hell was your goal, Walt?
Explain that to me.
We're patriots, Mr. President. We were
acting in the best interests of this country.
How is any of this in our best interest?
Shoring up a strategic partner
in the war on terror.
Ensuring a stable flow of oil. How is
any of that not in the national interest?
I have Chloe O'Brian
on the line for Jack Bauer.
- Chloe, are you set up for the trace?
- All set, Jack.
- We're ready to call Nathanson.
- How long do I keep him on?
Until I give you a signal.
Chloe, dial the number.
The line's disconnected.
There's nothing to grab onto.
- He must know something went wrong.
- Dammit, Walt!
I don't want this weapon deployed
on US soil any more than you do,
but Nathanson cannot help you now
and neither can I.
These terrorists are operating on their own.
Mr. President, I think he's telling the truth.
He can't help us, not any more.
Aaron.
- Get him out of here.
- Yes, sir.
Jack.
- What do we do now?
- I need to be debriefed. After that I'm leaving.
Given the situation,
things are more complicated.
CTU is gonna have to be responsible
for retrieval of the canisters.
Why are you leaving?
Sir, I have a daughter
that doesn't know that I'm still alive.
If I have to disappear again,
in all fairness to her,
I don't think she should know.
Jack, terrorists just threatened
to deploy chemical weapons on US soil.
- They have the ability to kill millions.
- I understand that.
I believe that CTU can handle this.
Jack, your experience could make
a crucial difference in stopping them.
Look, you and I have a complicated history,
I realise that.
And I'm not naive enough to expect
any special personal allegiance from you.
But I know your respect for this office
is just as strong as it was
when you served under David Palmer.
I'm asking for your help,
just until this crisis is over.
I will reinstate you.
I will give you all the support you need.
- Mr. President, you and I...
- Jack, please! For God's sake!
We need to recover this nerve gas
before it's too late.
The microcircuitry on this
has been tampered with.
As far as I can tell, unless we can repair it,
we can't arm the canisters.
Rossler will have a way.
He should have called by now.
Our real enemy is Russia. We should
be figuring out another way to get back home,
not wasting time
trying to use the gas against the Americans.
Question my orders again and I will kill you.
You understand?
They've closed the ports.
They will hunt us until they find us.
So if we cannot use the gas against Russia,
we will use it against America.
Get up.
- Hello.
- Lynn.
- Jenny, now is a really bad time.
- I know you're busy, but I need to see you.
- What is it?
- I need some help.
- You mean money.
- Lynn, I'm clean.
I'm working two jobs and busting my ass
to put my life back together.
- How much?
- 500.
Can I... can I come over there?
Absolutely not.
Why? Are you afraid I'll embarrass you?
Yeah, I am.
Lynn, I got nobody else to turn to. I just...
You know, I can't go back on the street again.
If you don't help me, I swear I...
I'm gonna hurt myself.
For God's sake, Lynn, I'm your sister.
Listen.
Jenny, listen.
There's a parking lot across from CTU.
I'll meet you there in 20 minutes.
OK.
Thank you, Lynn.
- The numbers we...
- Sorry I'm late.
I was explaining that Cummings provided us
with a schematic of one of the canisters.
Triggering mechanisms on the canisters
can only be activated via satellite relay.
Cummings says the terrorists
have invalid detonation codes.
- The canisters are useless.
- Unless they find a way to control the trigger.
- Are we running evacuation scenarios?
- Not without a time frame or a target.
Erwich's threat was intentionally vague.
- What are we doing to track them?
Chloe.
I pulled a voiceprint from Erwich's call
and I'm doing a scan of all Satcom chatter.
If he is in contact with anyone, we should
be able to intercept and trace the call.
We'd better get lucky cos we just got
an assessment from Civil Defense.
They estimate
the nerve gas from each canister
will create kill zones
between one and three square miles.
The terrorists
are in possession of 20 canisters.
We're talking about potential casualties in
the hundreds of thousands, perhaps a million.
- Yeah.
- Ivan Erwich?
- Go ahead.
- Jacob Rossler.
I was asked to call you by a friend in Moscow.
You've been briefed on our situation?
You need to reconfigure the remote trigger
for an A-tox chemical delivery system, right?
- Yes.
- You have the canisters with you?
Yes.
You'll need to start by cutting into them.
I'll give you the specifications.
- O'Brian.
- We got a pattern.
Send me the hit.
All interagency search protocols
are being run through CTU.
Ken, no one is going around you.
- We'll make sure you're apprised in real time.
- Audrey, I thought you should know.
Logan asked for Jack to be reinstated
provisionally with full autonomy.
We got a possible intercept on Erwich.
This just happened.
On the inner casing, you will find
a display with a seven-digit readout.
- I'll need that.
- Then what?
Then I will program
a new chip for your remote tracker.
- Put me through to Jack Bauer.
- Voiceprint is a 95% % match. It's Erwich.
He was on a sat phone. I can't trace it,
but it originated from a land line downtown.
- I have Jack Bauer for you, sir.
- This is Bauer.
- Jack, we may have a lead on Erwich.
- I'm listening.
We intercepted a call
between Erwich and an unknown associate.
We weren't able to trace Erwich,
but may have the associate.
22 North Figueroa, a penthouse.
- Chloe, bring up the building manifest.
- On it.
From what we heard,
Erwich is trying to acquire an activation code.
He's reconfiguring the trigger to disperse
the Sentox. We're running out of time.
OK, the penthouse is leased to a man
named Jacob Rossler. Cross-checking.
He's a software programmer indicted for
security code infiltration, identity theft.
I need schematics on the building
and vectors for every entrance.
We'll have it for you.
We're gonna need to go in covertly.
Have Curtis meet me with a small team,
but tell them to stay out of sight
until I get there. We'll be in touch.
This is our new destination.
They'll clear a landing zone for you.
This building's security system
uses proprietary technology.
It's a high-end platform
that's a bitch to hack into.
- So get Edgar to help you.
- Spenser is better.
- Chloe, out of the question.
- Spenser can do this faster than Edgar and I.
- He wrote a code that took months to hack.
That's a bad idea.
Stay out of this! He didn't know Cummings
was dirty. His polygraph proved that.
He was spying on us.
He was spying on you. He lied to you.
Sir, if you don't let Spenser help us do this,
we're not gonna get it done in time.
He has to wear a security wristband
and be under supervision.
Fine.
- Audrey Raines.
- Audrey, it's Jack.
I wanted to tell you the president asked me
to stay on until the canisters were retrieved.
Jack, you know what this means.
You'll be exposed. CTU can handle the crisis.
- The president thinks I can help.
- Jack, you don't owe them this.
The reason I called,
I need to ask you to do me a favour.
What?
- Kim doesn't know I'm alive yet.
- Do you want me to tell her?
No, I want you to call and bring her into CTU.
I'll see her when I get back.
- All right.
- Are you sure you're comfortable doing this?
- Of course.
- Thank you.
Sure.
Your swing arm needs to be replaced.
Yeah, we're open till five. Okey-doke.
Can I help you?
Do you have some kind of precision tool
for cutting metal?
- Sure.
- Where is everyone else?
Lunch. Why?
I need you to do some work for us
and we need it done fast.
- If you do it, you'll live, do you understand?
- Yeah. Yeah. Just take it easy.
Get the canisters.
Why haven't I gotten an update?
Bauer left here on some sort of lead.
Find out if CTU is any closer
to recovering the gas.
Yes, sir.
How are you feeling?
Remarkably well...
for someone whose husband tried
to have her committed without a goodbye.
I'm sorry.
I didn't come here to fight with you.
You have every right to.
The two of us used to be a pretty good team.
Do you remember?
I was the one you would
always come to first for advice.
- I remember.
- We've got to get back to that relationship.
You're right.
Things are gonna get rough for you.
And you are gonna need me
and everything that I can give you.
I don't know what to say, Marty.
Don't you ever do that to me again.
Mike, please, come in.
- Mr. President. Mrs. Logan.
- Mike.
Mike, I owe you a profound apology.
You were in an impossible situation.
I understand what you did.
No. I panicked, Mike. That's it.
Plain and simple.
I'm not proud of how I handled myself.
I intend to make it right from this point on.
- I would like you to resume your duties.
- Of course, sir.
Thank you, Mike.
CTU is tracking down the canisters, but we
have to deal with the issue of Cummings.
It's all right, Mike.
I would like Martha's input on this.
So, what do we do about Walt?
We can't detain him indefinitely.
We keep him out of sight long enough
to construct a credible narrative.
Mike,
are you talking about a cover-up?
I mean exercising discretion to spare
this country unnecessary humiliation.
Walt Cummings was complicit
in David Palmer's assassination.
He has allowed terrorists to get their hands
on gas that is, at this point, a very real threat.
With respect, Mrs. Logan,
if we go public, the president's reputation
won't be the only casualty.
The credibility of this office will be destroyed.
Charles, you are going to take a hit on this,
but it won't destroy you.
You did nothing wrong
except to trust someone who betrayed you.
You are human.
You might be overestimating
the public's capacity for forgiveness.
I'm not. The only thing
they won't forgive is being lied to.
I think you should issue a statement
to the press. And the sooner the better.
I agree.
Why don't you and I work on it together
and see what we come up with?
OK.
Chloe.
- Station three. We don't have much time.
- Thanks for getting me reinstated.
I did it cos I need help
getting Jack through the building,
not because I forgive you, because I don't.
Have a seat. We need to gain access
to the security server at 22 North Figueroa.
It's a proprietary network so get to work.
- Chloe, I swear, I thought I was following...
- I don't care, Spenser.
CTU. They've got eyes and ears
on the building.
We've got two units.
One east, one west of the building.
Chloe, do you copy?
We're here. Spenser's countervailing
the building's security protocol.
What? Spenser's under arrest.
- Buchanan released him from Holding.
- Fine. Give me Rossler's position.
I've hacked into the building's motion
sensors. Rossler is still in the penthouse.
I have two guards on the penthouse level.
- What about the ground-level entrance?
- One guard, three cameras.
Stand by to take out all security cameras
covering the front desk and the elevators.
I can only shut them down for 60 seconds,
then they reboot. That's as long as you have.
Copy that. Teams A and B,
remain in position till you get a go.
We are one minute out. We have to cross
the street to get to Rossler's building.
We are ready to cut into the canisters.
You have to cut precisely ten centimetres
from the bottom of the casing
to reveal the trigger.
How thick is the outer casing?
Five millimetres. Call me with the ID numbers
when you're done.
We're in position.
We're set. We're ready to go.
Just a few more seconds.
OK. Here we go, Jack.
On my mark, cameras dark.
Federal agent. Let me see your hands.
Let me see your hands!
Elevator code, let's have it.
Four, zero, seven, three, pound.
Unit one, status check. Lost cameras A and C.
Tell him you don't know why the cameras
went down, but everything is OK.
Base, status check blue. Don't know why the
cameras are out. Everything's fine down here.
Turn around.
Back up to me. Back up to me.
- Where are the elevators?
- Almost there. You have two floors to go.
The camera reboots in ten seconds.
Then you'll be visible.
Move. Move.
Unit one, status check. Where are you?
You tell him you had to use the men's room.
Base, headed to the men's room.
Something's wrong.
- Yes.
- Mr. Rossler, we may have a situation.
- What kind of situation?
- I'm not sure. Please remain in your office.
The guards look suspicious.
One has an automatic weapon.
Copy that.
Federal agent!
- You OK?
- Yeah. Go ahead. It hit my vest.
- Rossler's on the move.
- Where?
Nine o'clock.
Federal agent.
Drop the weapon. Drop the weapon!
Put your hands behind your head.
Do it!
Interlock your fingers.
Rossler is in custody.
Repeat, Rossler is in custody.
- Move in. I need a medic.
- Patching you to situation room.
- Someone else is in the penthouse, Jack.
- In the bedroom. To your right. North side.
- Curtis, cover him.
- I got him.
Let me see your hands.
Let me see your hands!
Don't shoot.
- Who are you?
- I'm Inessa.
Who did that to you?
- You are the police?
- Counter Terrorist Unit, Los Angeles.
He is holding me here.
I want to go home.
You need to cut into the outer casing
exactly ten centimetres from the bottom.
The casing is five millimetres thick.
You cannot puncture the inner lining.
- What's in these things?
- Do not worry. Just do what I say.
Just... Can't you tell me what this is all about?
Do you have a family, Cal?
A wife.
My wife is in prison.
She's been there for seven years.
Her only crime was to support me
while I fought for my country.
My son lives in a state-run facility.
He does not even remember what I look like.
You want to know what this is about?
It's about justice. It's about ending tyranny.
When you're finished, we will leave.
- You won't hurt me?
- You're not my enemy.
Your government is my enemy.
Hey.
You have my word.
Begin.
It's all right. You're all right.
All right, alpha team,
the building is secure.
Take a seat.
You're safe now.
Get a medic to have a look at her.
I want CTU to run a full background check.
I don't mind that they've dressed his wound,
but don't give him anything for the pain.
Curtis, put him in a chair.
All right, let's go. Get him up.
Easy on my leg.
My name is Jack Bauer. I'm with CTU.
25 minutes ago, you contacted a man named
Ivan Erwich. What did he want you to do?
- I want my lawyer.
- You'll get a lawyer when I get what I need.
Mr. Erwich is in possession
of 20 canisters of Sentox VX nerve gas,
which he has threatened to deploy
here in the United States.
I guess you have a problem.
No, you have a problem. You've been
conspiring with and aiding a known terrorist,
which means I get to hold you
for as long as I want.
Mr. Erwich can't deploy the canisters unless
he reconfigures the trigger mechanism.
Is that what he wanted you to do?
Trust me. You don't want
to go down this road with me.
Go to hell.
Agh!
That is exactly where I'm going to send you
unless you start to cooperate.
You like hurting girls?
Curtis.
By the time I'm finished with you,
you're gonna wish you felt this good again.
Where is Erwich?
I want full immunity,
unfreezing of all my assets,
and transport
to a foreign country of my choosing.
No.
And Inessa.
She comes with me.
That's the deal.
Maybe I'm not making myself clear.
We're not making a deal.
Curtis.
- Jack, it's Lynn.
- Go ahead.
We don't have the luxury
to engage in brinkmanship.
- He's gonna tell us what we want to know.
- We're not gonna wait to find out.
Accept the deal. That's an order.
Fine. It's your call.
We're signing off.
Make sure he follows through.
I'll be back in a few minutes.
I've been instructed to accept your proposal.
A certified agreement,
signed by the attorney general.
When I see that, I'll tell you what you want.
And remember, I want Inessa.
Your agreement's being drawn up.
Now I want something.
Where's Erwich?
I have no idea.
I don't know the man.
Not even what he looks like.
I first spoke with him 30 minutes ago.
We were put in contact
through a mutual associate in Russia.
- Who?
- Sergei Voronov.
A commander in the resistance movement.
- What does Erwich want?
- To reprogram the chip of that trigger.
He's calling back
with the identification keys.
- What's your time frame?
- Within the hour.
How is he going to receive the package?
I was going to deliver it.
We haven't agreed on the meeting place.
I want that chip.
It's in a safe place.
Once I see some paperwork,
I'll show it to you.
I want you to be ready to fit that chip
with a transponder so we can track him.
- Buchanan.
- Bill, it's Jack.
Where are we with Rossler's agreement?
We have the attorney general's sanction.
You should have it in a few minutes.
- Did we get any information on the girl?
- There isn't much. Inessa Kovalesky.
Reported missing 19 months ago from Kiev.
The assumption is she was kidnapped
by traffickers in the sex-slave trade.
She's 15, Jack.
15?
OK, thanks, Bill. I'll get back to you.
- You can't take the girl.
- Then no deal.
You'll have your immunity, your freedom.
Leave the girl out of this.
Inessa is all I care about.
She comes with me,
or you lose Erwich.
I've almost finished the protocols.
Whatever you have,
port it over to Edgar's station.
- Why?
- He'll be finishing that task.
Fine.
- Chloe, don't you understand?
- I know.
I'll bet you do.
You don't work here any more, Spenser.
That's what I'm trying to tell you.
Your reinstatement was just until
we got Rossler into custody.
- There's still stuff that has to be done.
- We pulled people from Division.
These men will escort you out.
I know that was hard. You did the right thing.
Shut up, Edgar.
You're right, we don't need that part.
OK.
"I promise a full and open inquiry
into this matter. "
"I will not rest until I've restored the faith
that you have placed in this office. "
"And I can demonstrate to you, the American
people, that I bear its mantle of responsibility
with respect and deep humility. "
This way, you're assuming responsibility
for Walt's actions,
but you're also personally
taking the initiative to bring him to justice.
Well, I'd like to run it by Mike,
but I think it works.
I think it's the right move, Charles.
Thank you for letting me help you.
I'm glad to have your help. It's been a long
time since you and I worked together like this.
Yes.
- Mr. President, Mike.
- What is it, Mike?
I think you should come here.
I'm in the west hallway.
- What's going on?
- Just come here, sir.
I'm on my way
Cut him down.
Thanks for meeting me. You got the money?
Jenny, I'm not here to bring you money.
Here's the name of a doctor. He's a good man.
I want you to call him. I'll pay all
the expenses. It won't cost you a cent.
- We'll call him together.
- I can't.
- Oh, God!
- Don't hurt him!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Hurry up.
Let's go.
- I'm so sorry, Lynn.
- Come on!
Rossler's been given a shot for the pain.
We have pursuit units on stand-by.
As soon as he moves out, we'll be ready.
No one's going anywhere unless Erwich calls.
Stand by the phones.
Excuse me.
- Audrey Raines.
- It's me. Did you get a hold of Kim?
No. I tried her, but she wasn't in.
I left a message.
- Would you mind trying again for me?
- Of course.
OK, thanks.
I want to contact my family.
They must be so worried about me.
I need to explain something to you first.
Please, sit down.
For now...
we need you to go with Mr. Rossler.
Just for now.
Men like me - agents -
are going to follow you.
And when we get
what we need from Mr. Rossler,
they're going to move in
and they're going to take you away from him.
You don't know what he does to me
when we are alone.
I promise I won't let him be alone with you.
- I don't believe you.
- Please.
- I won't do it.
Let me go.
- Please.
- I'm sorry, I can't.
Then you are no different than Rossler.
I am not Rossler.
Look at me.
I won't let anything happen to you.
I promise.
We need you to get dressed, please.
Thank you.
Good job.
That's it.
Load the canisters. Get rid of the body.
Pick it up.
Yes.
We have the identification keys.
I'm messaging them to you now.
I've got them.
How long will it take
to reprogram the chip and deliver it?
I'll be ready in ten minutes.
- We need a place we can meet.
- You're coming personally?
Unless you have someone who can install
and program an encoded binary chip.
I'll call you back with the location.
I'll be here.
Get him set up for a wire. I'll get the girl.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Rossler, in a minute
we're gonna be implanting a transmitter.
We're ready to go.
It's going to be fine.
Let's go.
We couldn't complete the trace, but we have it
narrowed down to a ten-block radius.
No! No!
No! Hold your fire.
Get a medic in here now.
Inessa, give me the gun.
I know you don't want to hurt anybody else.
Is he gonna make it?
No. He's dead.
He was our only link to those canisters.
Erwich's gonna call here any minute
and he's gonna expect to talk to him.