Jack Bauer's undercover with the terrorists.
They're expecting Jack to help them release
a canister of Sentox nerve gas
in the Sunrise Hills shopping mall.
Do you mean actually let them release
the Sentox? Are you out of your mind?
We're monitoring them.
We're certain that when they leave the mall,
they're going back to the remaining canisters.
I'll go along with your assessment.
Let them release it.
But you'd better find those other canisters,
or people will have died in vain.
There is still time to stop them
before they murder those people.
We have a directive from the president.
More people could die
if these men don't lead us to the canisters.
If you were Jack,
would you follow that order?
Stand and watch
as they murder those people?
If those were the orders of the president,
I'd have to.
It's reconfigured.
You can activate the canisters.
You'd better hope it works.
What's the code?
Jack, the unlock code is Alpha, Kilo, Charlie.
Echo, Bravo, Charlie.
Jack, this is a direct order from the president.
Now, enter the correct code
and let them release the gas. Now!
- Make it work!
- I told you, there's nothing I can do.
We have another way to release the gas.
I stopped the gas,
but some got into the ventilation.
- Evacuate the mall.
- What about the terrorists?
One's dead, one escaped.
Monitor the tracking device in the remote
trigger. The hostile still had it on him.
I managed to activate the valve before I got
away. At least some of the gas was released.
- What do you want me to do?
- Come back here.
You were followed.
You know what to do.
No! Hostile down.
Erwich and the canisters are gone.
We've got nothing here. Dammit!
Despite an attempt
to derail the process,
the treaty was signed today
by President Logan
and Russian president Yuri Suvarov.
Officials from each country are hailing it
as a major milestone in US-Russian relations.
The White House press secretary has called
this a critical achievement in diplomacy
and will set the course for President...
The Sentox gas is genuine.
The test was successful.
I spent a year securing a weapon
that would bring Moscow to its knees
and you waste it
killing a handful of American civilians.
We were betrayed, Bierko.
Someone must pay.
I agree.
You're the one who trusted the Americans.
Nathanson lied to us.
He plotted to turn the gas against us.
Your trust nearly cost us everything.
Since I anticipated this, I secured additional
men and resources at great personal expense.
Have you reconfigured the canisters
with dispersal mechanisms?
- Yes.
- Do it. Nathanson will be eliminated.
Then we will return to our original task -
striking at the heart of Russia.
- Where's Nathanson?
- I don't know where he went.
I swear I don't.
- Yeah.
- I took out Nathanson's man.
- But there is no sign of Nathanson.
- Find him.
- Alpha seven.
- It's Nathanson. Someone took out my man.
- Who?
- I think Bierko's hitting us back.
Destroy all your databases.
I know you're there. Pick up the phone.
Dammit, Jenny.
I need the key card from my wallet.
Look, I'll leave the police out of this.
You and your loser boyfriend can keep
the money, max out my cards, I don't care.
Just give me back my key card.
It's important.
We can't sell the key card.
Why can't we just give it to him?
I'm calling my brother.
- No, you're not.
- What is going on, Dwayne?
I'm handling this.
- Jenny.
Hold for the president.
Have your people
recovered the nerve gas?
- McGill!
- Yes, sir. I'm here. I'm sorry.
Do you have any leads?
Have you intercepted the terrorists?
No. The man we followed took his life
before he could be apprehended.
Dammit! I put this on you.
If you'd let the terrorists release the Sentox
in the mall, as I agreed to let you do,
we wouldn't be where we are right now,
which is nowhere.
- Mr. President...
- Stop!
Stop making excuses.
Take responsibility and do your job.
Although we limited the casualties,
the attack indicates
that these terrorists intend to make good their
threat to release the nerve gas on US soil.
Unless we catch a break, we can expect
multiple attacks resulting in mass casualties.
I assumed you'd want me
to start without you.
Just tell me where we are.
LAPD is setting up a perimeter
around the terrorists' last location.
We've activated
satellite and Caltrans surveillance.
But we don't have any real leads, do we?
If Jack followed orders,
we could have intercepted these people.
We don't know that for sure. Jack's field
decision saved over 800 innocent people.
It may well cost us 100 times that many.
We contained the threat and the media's
awareness, which would've triggered unrest.
You tell yourself that.
The fact remains that terrorists are at large
with 19 canisters of Sentox, and we
don't know where or when they'll hit us next.
- We're all aware of the threat, Lynn.
- Then why does she keep defending Bauer?
I want Bauer placed in custody. I want him
brought in here and held responsible.
Jack can be disciplined later. Taking him
out of the field right now is a mistake.
- Don't tell me how to do my job.
- He was authorised.
He works for me.
So do you. I want him here now.
The rest of you, maintain search protocols.
Send reports to my screen in ten minutes.
It's all right. We're all under a lot of pressure.
Let's get back to it.
- Manning.
- It's Buchanan. Bring Jack in.
We weren't able to confirm his identity.
Take his picture, lift his prints,
get him over to CTU.
We've got nothing. We'll have to run him
through NCIC and Interpol databases.
I just got off the phone.
McGill wants me to bring you back to CTU.
He's on some kind of warpath.
Because I didn't think letting terrorists
release Sentox in a mall was acceptable?
We lost our only lead.
Lynn's looking for someone to blame.
I was appointed by the president.
It was a field call.
I know, and between you and me, I think
you made the right call back at the mall.
- I'm calling the president.
- Look, Jack, the trail's gone cold.
There's no point in fighting it.
Let's just go back to CTU and square it.
- Fine.
- Look, I'm sorry...
but I also have to take your gun.
Jack, don't make this
any more difficult than it already is.
Fine.
- We can't afford to decommission Jack now.
- I agree.
- Well, what can we do about it?
- Nothing, while Lynn's in charge.
He may be in charge, but he is not in control.
- Ms Raines, you have a call.
- Thank you.
I'll be filtering intel at station three.
Audrey Raines.
If you try to trace this call,
or put anyone else on the line, I will hang up.
- Who is this?
- My name is James Nathanson.
I'm sure Walt Cummings
has already told you all about me.
- You sold the nerve gas to the terrorists.
- That's close enough to the truth.
- What do you want?
- Transfer me to Jack Bauer on a clean line.
- Why Jack?
- That's not your concern.
You're getting to Jack through me.
That makes it my concern.
I'm going through you because I know
you have a special relationship with Bauer.
I know all about you,
which is why I'm counting on you
to recognise an opportunity
when it presents itself.
- What opportunity?
- I can help you find this nerve gas.
How do I know you're telling the truth?
You don't. Now put me through to Bauer.
- This is Bauer.
- Jack, I'm assuming you can't speak freely.
It's Audrey. It's personal.
- Go ahead.
- Thanks.
I'm on the phone with a man who claims
to be James Nathanson, Cummings' contact.
He says he has information,
but he will only talk to you.
- Why me?
- Hang up, Ms Raines.
My phone has a node monitor.
- I'll know if anyone else comes on this line.
- Jack?
- It's all right, Audrey. Hang up the phone.
- All right.
- What do you want with me?
- The terrorists are trying to kill me.
If the terrorists figured out you rigged
the Sentox to blow up in their faces,
why do you need me?
The authorities will protect you.
Cummings isn't the only one behind this who
works in the government. I need your help.
You had me take the fall
for Palmer's assassination.
What makes you think I won't kill you?
Because you want to stop the Sentox gas
being released on American soil. So do I.
- Where are you?
- There's a phone booth south of Moorpark.
Be there in ten minutes or I'll be gone.
- Moorpark. Got it.
- Jack.
Audrey, I'll explain everything
as soon as I get back to CTU.
Thanks.
It's gotta be strange for her.
Audrey.
Just yesterday, she thought you were dead.
Yeah.
I know this is none of my business,
but she's a good person, Jack.
I hope you two get half a chance.
Thanks.
Jack!
Don't fight, Curtis. Don't fight it.
I'm sorry.
- Lynn McGill.
- It's Curtis. Jack escaped.
What?
He got a call. Next thing I know,
he blindsided me and took my car.
- Who called him?
- He said Audrey, but he may have been lying.
Lynn.
We can track your vehicle's transceiver.
I tried bringing it up on my PDA. He's either
disabled or shut down the transceiver.
Curtis, how could you let this happen?
I'll get dispatch on it. One of my team's
en route to pick me up. We'll find him.
You don't know where to look.
Get back. We'll deploy from here.
Dammit!
Chloe, run a triangulation on
Jack Bauer's phone. Find out where he is.
Yes, sir.
Have you talked to Jack
since he's been in custody?
- No.
- He's not in custody any more.
He assaulted Curtis and stole his car.
- Why would he do that?
- Maybe you can tell me.
I don't know where Jack is
if that's what you're asking.
- You have no idea?
- No, but I'm sure there's an explanation.
Mr. McGill? We're not getting a signal from
Jack's cell. The SIM must be out of his phone.
- If you think of anything, let me know, right?
- Of course.
Thanks.
O'Brian.
Chloe, what I'm about to tell you
needs to stay between us.
It involves Jack.
What is going on?
It came on my screen Jack's gone missing.
He's following a lead on the gas.
He needed to go alone.
I transferred a call from my station to him.
I need you to delete the record.
- If Lynn finds out we're working behind...
- Believe me, I know. But this is the only way.
There isn't a lot of time.
When did you call?
- Communications archive.
- This is McGill.
Bring up the phone logs
of Audrey Raines' station.
Yes, sir.
I found it. I can't dump just one call.
They're cross-indexed.
- Can't you unlink it?
- No, it would take two hours.
OK, Mr. McGill,
the call logs should be on your screen.
Scroll through to station five.
That's the one we dedicated to the DOD.
The only way is to dump the entire log -
all the calls you've made and received today.
Do it.
It's done.
Thank you, Chloe.
... a day to be remembered
as a step forward for the US and Russia.
President Logan and President Suvarov are
expected shortly to deliver closing remarks.
Following this, the Russian head of state...
- What now?
- There's a call you need to take.
It just came in on this.
- And what is that?
- Walt Cummings' phone, sir.
It's been in Secret Service custody.
They brought it to me.
The caller's claiming he has the Sentox gas.
- Is someone tracing the call?
- They can't.
It's being sent through multiple relays.
I'm not talking to a terrorist.
You talk to them, find out what he wants.
Mr. President,
he's demanding to speak with you.
All right. But put him on speaker.
This is President Logan. Is this Erwich?
Ivan Erwich is no longer with us,
Mr. President.
His attack on your shopping mall
was unsanctioned and unwarranted.
It didn't serve our interests.
- What is it you want?
- To release the Sentox nerve gas on Moscow.
Since that is impossible, I am forced to strike
at Russia on foreign soil, with your help.
- My help?
- I want the route of Suvarov's motorcade.
His entire route to the airport,
along with a full profile of his security detail.
- I don't personally have that information.
- Then get it.
Make no mistake, Mr. President,
it's our Russian oppressors I mean to hurt,
not your people.
However, if you refuse to cooperate,
I will have no choice
but to release all of the Sentox gas
in areas far more populated
than your shopping mall.
You just said that killing Americans
didn't serve your interests. This...
- This would be senseless murder.
- Yes. It would.
So give me Suvarov's route.
- I'll need some time.
- You have 15 minutes.
I'm not sure...
He wants to assassinate Suvarov.
We can't let that happen.
If the Russian president is killed on US soil
it wouldn’t just nullify the treaty,
it would destroy
our relationship with Moscow.
- Get me Suvarov's route from Secret Service.
- Mr. President...
I haven't made any decision yet, Mike,
but whatever I decide, I better have the route
in hand when he calls back, don't you think?
Yes, sir.
Somebody's screwing with me, Bill,
and I won't tolerate it.
- Screwing with you how?
- Audrey's phone log has been erased.
What?
Take a look.
- Probably a system glitch.
- It wasn't a glitch. She did it on purpose.
- You think Audrey did this?
- I know she did.
- She's one of the most by-the-book people.
- You don't go by the book hiding something.
She was on the phone with Jack
before he attacked Curtis.
I didn't know that. What does that prove?
Something's going on with these two.
What's their history?
You know their history, Lynn.
They worked together at DOD.
- There's more than that, right?
- It got personal later on, yes.
Personal? You didn't think it was important?
No, I didn't. What difference does that make?
When did she find out Jack was still alive?
This morning, with the rest of us.
- You sure about that?
- I was there. I saw her reaction.
- It could've been an act.
- You sound paranoid.
I don't care. From this point,
I want our people on a tight leash.
If someone has a hidden agenda,
I wanna know.
CTU's become too porous. That's your fault.
- I don't need to hear this from you.
- You don't wanna hear this?
Then tell me why
Audrey erased her phone logs.
Slow down!
- I'm here. Where are you?
- In a minute.
I wanna make sure you weren't followed,
or there's no deal.
Take the alley between the buildings across
the street from you. I left the gate open.
Listen to me. I don't know what you think
I can do, but you committed treason.
I don't see it that way. I love this country.
You're never gonna be able to justify
killing David Palmer.
That was an unfortunate necessity. We
admired Palmer, but we had other priorities.
This country needs a reason
to secure its oil interests in Asia,
one Russia and the world can get behind.
I've heard your reasoning from Walt.
It's treason.
No, it's a real politic.
- Do you see the open door ahead?
- Yeah.
Enter it. Make two right turns
and walk back the direction you came from.
Hold on.
You have hostiles coming from the adjacent
parking structure. Do you have a weapon?
- Yes.
- Where are you?
- Second floor.
- Make your way to the roof. Stay on the line.
All right.
- All right, I understand.
- Audrey.
DOD wants a fuller explanation about the
mall. I told them we're trying to find the gas.
I just spent the last five minutes
getting grilled by Lynn.
- About what?
- You and Jack. Your relationship.
- What did you tell him?
- The truth.
That you and he were involved,
but now I'm not sure.
- That's not his business.
- He thinks it is.
He thinks you had something
to do with Jack breaking from custody.
- Did you?
- Not exactly.
- What the hell does that mean?
- A man claiming to be Nathanson called here.
He said he had information on the terrorists,
that he would only give it to Jack.
- Why didn't you tell me about this?
- I was afraid. I didn't know what to do, Bill.
So Jack's meeting this man alone,
without backup. Where?
- I don't know. He dropped me from the call.
- Who else knows?
- Chloe. She helped cover the call from Lynn.
Audrey.
- Sign here.
- District elevated the threat level.
I'm briefing first responders on multiple
attacks. I need to review DOD protocols.
- All right, I'll send them to your screen.
- We can do it here.
- Unless you have a problem working on this.
- No, no, no. It's fine.
Excuse me.
- Bauer?
- Yeah, where are you?
- I'm in the freight elevator.
- You need to get out now. You're cornered.
- Bauer, where are you?
- I'm almost there. Just keep moving.
Nathanson, stay down!
Stay down!
Nathanson!
Look at me. Look at me.
How do I find the canisters of Sentox?
How do I find the canisters?
In my pocket.
What's on the chip?
Please! What's on the chip?
- He's dead, but there was someone else.
- Who?
I don't know, but he took out three of my men
and disabled the helicopter.
Nathanson may have given him information
that compromises us.
Keep looking until you find him.
Critics have said
by signing this treaty,
we as the United States
are taking on our allies' enemies
as well as having to deal with our own.
Diagram seven lays out the hierarchy.
Civil-defence protocols
for each agency are well-defined.
Shouldn't you get that?
- Audrey Raines.
- Nathanson's been killed. He gave me intel.
Uplink the data.
Sorry, Steve, you have the wrong extension.
I'll transfer you to IT.
Overlapping responsibilities
default to federal, then to state.
- O'Brian.
- It's Jack. What's the hell's going on there?
It's Lynn, he's shadowing her. He thinks she's
been talking to you, which I guess she has.
Listen. I have a ThumbDrive
that's gonna help find the Sentox.
- I need you to data-mine the files.
- Upload the drive to my socket.
Access code 5 J55 J.
Hold on.
You should be getting it now.
Chloe, I need you to keep this under the radar.
You mean keep it from Lynn.
Until we know what we've got.
My number come up?
- Yeah.
- OK. I had to switch out phones.
- If you need me, call me on that number.
- OK, I will.
Suvarov's motorcade route
and security detail.
Sir,
if President Suvarov is killed
and the Russians find out
we supplied his killers with this information,
it would be considered an act of war.
The motorcade has a security force.
I see no reason to believe
that the terrorists would even be successful.
Maybe we should have an analysis done,
determine vulnerable points along the route.
Sir, we can't do that
without giving away the fact
that we had advance knowledge of an attack.
What attack?
It's nothing that you need
to be concerned about.
Charles, you invited me into this circle.
What attack?
The terrorists want
the Suvarovs' motorcade route.
They've threatened to deploy
more Sentox gas if I don't give it to them.
You're not seriously considering it, are you?
Martha, Charles believes an assault
on the Suvarovs has a good chance...
Will you please
let the president speak for himself?
May we have a moment?
- Charles.
- Martha, please.
If I don't give them the information they want,
tens of thousands of Americans will die
on our soil, maybe hundreds of thousands.
All right. Charles, there's got to be another
way. Change their itinerary. Delay Suvarov.
It's all over the news
that they're leaving after the statement.
If there's any deviation,
the terrorists will know I alerted them.
Charles, what are you telling me? That we will
stand in front of the world with the Suvarovs,
you'll look him in the eye
knowing you're sending them...
If we were in Russia and Suvarov got this
ultimatum, do you think he would spare us?
I'm not talking about Russia
or about Suvarov. I am talking about you.
You are the President
of the United States of America.
My God, Charles!
You're talking about murder!
Martha, my back is up against the wall.
You... Give me another solution.
You stand up to them.
Refuse to negotiate with them.
Isn't that the policy of this country?
Isn't that the point of the treaty you signed?
It's not that simple, Martha.
It never is.
Dammit!
- Buchanan.
- This is Chloe.
- What is it?
- Jack just sent me the data he got.
My filters weren't working
and I just realised why.
- The drive's DOD-formatted.
- DOD?
I don't know how Nathanson
got a highly classified D-drive.
Audrey's the only one with clearance.
- Lynn's got her tied up.
- Exactly.
- How much time do you need?
- To decrypt it? Three minutes.
Hang on.
Lynn, do you have a minute?
- What is it?
- You were inquiring about the phone logs.
That's right.
I had Felson run a diagnostic
to trace the terminal that dumped the log.
We can key in the user ID
from your office to find what we need.
We just have to use your key card.
Why are you so interested in this?
- I'm serious about all breaches of security.
- What was that?
- What?
- That last window you closed. What was it?
- It was just the DOD protocols.
- What is going on here?
Will you please just calm down?
Don't tell me to calm down.
You're up to something. I won't stand for it.
You're protecting her, she's protecting Bauer.
- I can explain.
- So can I.
- This was an attempt to circumvent me.
- We are on the same side.
If your father wasn't secretary of defense,
I'd have you thrown out.
I don't have that problem with you.
Can I have security to station five, please?
Right away.
- What are you doing, Lynn?
- Place him in custody. Take him to Holding.
- You are making a mistake.
- Audrey.
I want everyone's attention.
I'm putting a section two-three redundancy
into effect as of this moment.
Your stations will be mirrored
and monitored through my office.
Now get back to work.
We need Bill to get through this. You are
jeopardising our chances of finding that gas.
I'll make DOD
and the secretary of defense aware.
Don't threaten me, Ms Raines. I promise
you, you do not want to threaten me.
- What have you got?
- A company called Terra-Dyne.
Over three years they've acquired
over 100 pounds of raw strontium isotope,
used to create Sentox nerve gas.
- Where do I find Terra-Dyne?
- La Canada. It's a subsidiary of Omicron.
- Did you say Omicron? Are you sure?
- What's wrong?
Pull up their roster.
See if Christopher Henderson is on the list.
- Why?
- Just do it, please.
Here it is. Christopher Henderson.
Senior vice president of research
and development. Do you know him?
Yeah, I did once. Listen,
send me the decrypted files over to my PDA.
That's gonna be hard to do.
Lynn is watching everyone like a hawk.
- Can Buchanan help?
- If he weren't in Holding.
- What?
- Lynn detained him for insubordination.
- How can he do that?
- He's losing it.
The president's putting pressure on him
to get those canisters. He can't handle it.
I need the files. You're gonna
have to find a way to get them to me.
I'll try.
- They haven't called yet?
- No, they haven't, sir.
President Suvarov's waiting.
We'll be out in a minute.
Excuse me.
Martha.
Please?
This is a difficult decision for me,
both politically and personally,
and maybe I won't have to make it.
Maybe CTU will find the canisters
before the Suvarovs have to leave.
That's what I'm praying for.
But whatever happens,
I need you to understand.
I do... understand, Charles. I do.
Mr. President.
It has been a challenging day,
so I especially appreciate
how professional you have all been.
Your president is fortunate to have such
talented people working for him. Thank you.
Yuri.
Anya.
Mr. President,
I'm glad we have this opportunity
to thank you and Mrs. Logan personally
for your hospitality.
Mr. President, it's been our pleasure.
Yes.
Hold on.
We would love that.
Wouldn't we, Martha?
Yes. It would be lovely.
Martha,
thank you again for being so kind.
I read the text of your statement.
It was excellent.
And congratulations again
on your handling of the crisis at the airport.
Thank you, Yuri.
And thank you for your steadfast support.
Have there been
further developments?
No, no, none at all.
There's always pressure.
- But everything's under control.
Yes.
Ladies, the photographers are waiting.
Thank you, Mr. President.
The motorcade will take
service roads to the 118,
and then to the 5 Freeway South.
- Charles.
- Martha, please, just...
just smile and wave.
The motorcade will take Suvarov
through this downtown corridor.
That will give us our best shot
at destroying all the vehicles.
Tell our people
this is where I want them to strike.
All right, that's it, folks. We need to move.
- Come on.
- Charles. You can't let them get in that car.
- It's not too late.
- Lynn McGill is calling from CTU.
- What about?
- He didn't say. He asked to speak with you.
Excuse me.
I'm afraid I have to say my goodbyes here.
Affairs of state, the pressures continue.
Yes, I understand, of course.
Thank you, President Logan, for everything.
Thank you. Anya.
Charles.
- Mrs. Logan.
- Aaron.
I've decided to drive to the airport
with the Suvarovs. You can have a car follow.
We're not detailed for that.
- I'll ride up front.
- No, Aaron. No. That's not necessary.
Yes, it is.
Thank you. Would you...
tell my husband where I am?
I hope you don't mind if I accompany you.
- Are you sure your husband won't mind?
- Of course not.
This way we'll have more time to talk.
I'd like that.
Ma'am, the president is being briefed by CTU
right now, but I left word for you.
Thank you.