Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net
This was the last model the Soviets produced.
Is this what you need
to reprogram the trigger?
In less than an hour, it will detonate and strike
a blow that the Americans will never forget.
When you've finished,
meet me at the safe house.
I think some people in this place
have a connection with the terrorist attacks.
- (Sandra) How would you know that?
- They used one phrase several times.
"Khamsa ziwar".
Pass that on to the FBI.
I approved the agreement with Assad.
I am prepared to offer you full protection
and a pardon for all crimes in the past.
Is that acceptable?
(Assad) I need to see this in writing.
You were right about Curtis and Assad
having a connection. Curtis was in the army.
His squad was ambushed by Assad's people.
They killed five of Curtis's men
and took two hostage.
Assad's lieutenant
personally beheaded them both.
(Jack) Oh, my God.
You still don't remember?
Special Forces Battalion.
Curtis, put your weapon down!
- Stay out of this, Jack!
- I can't.
I gave him my word that
we would protect him.
I can't let this animal live.
(Buchanan) Curtis didn't
leave you any choice.
That's what I keep trying to tell myself.
We're gonna find that suitcase nuke
because of you.
Tell the president that I'm sorry.
I can't do this any more.
Mr President, we believe
we've found the suitcase nuke.
(Chloe) TAC team is ready.
(Sabir) Do it now! Do it!
No!
I just got a message from the FBI.
It's some Arabic phrase.
"Khamsa ziwar".
It means "five visitors".
Assad said "visitor"
was a codeword for "weapon".
There are four more of these things out there.
The unthinkable has happened. Terrorists
have exploded a nuclear weapon on our soil.
Over one square mile of Valencia,
a suburb of Los Angeles, has been destroyed
by the most devastating attack
in the series of terrorist activities
that began 11 weeks ago.
And one can only imagine the cost in lives
and the suffering of survivors.
Judging from the direction in which
the mushroom cloud is heading,
winds may be blowing the airborne radiation
away from the more heavily populated areas.
- How many people died in this?
- Initial estimates, no less than 12,000.
Mr President, I just got off the phone
with Bill Buchanan at CTU.
He has intel that four more nuclear weapons
were stolen along with the one that went off.
- Do we have any idea where they are?
- We do not.
- I want a meeting with the Joint Chiefs.
- I've told them.
- Has civilian air traffic been shut down?
- Yes. As soon as the FAA were informed.
Mr President.
Given the current situation, we've decided
to move you down to the bunker.
All right. But Tom, I have to
get in front of the American people.
I wanna make a televised speech
within the hour.
- Yes, sir.
- All right, let's go down.
The Department of Emergency Services and
Public Safety urges everyone to return home.
We will have an expert in nuclear physics
on our programme...
Have we heard from any of the secondary
teams that were converging on Fayed?
We lost communication
as soon as the blast hit.
- Milo, can you get a visual?
- I just checked the satellite. All...
All of our field teams were too close
to ground zero. They're all dead.
- What was the last you heard?
- They had engaged the hostiles.
So they were closing in on Fayed. We need
to know if he was in the bomb's radius.
Absolutely.
Mr President, your office has been prepared.
Continuity of operations plan
has also been activated.
The vice president has been alerted
and is following protocol.
The Joint Chiefs and most of the cabinet
are on their way here.
The remaining cabinet members
are being routed to Site R.
Right this way, sir.
(phone rings)
- Yeah?
- Bill? Are you all right?
We're fine. What's going on over there?
We've moved to the bunker. The president
is about to meet with the Joint Chiefs.
Do you have anything new?
The bomb went off
as we were moving in on Fayed.
Do you think that prompted the detonation?
It could have. It's possible they were hoping
to move the bomb to a more populated area.
Is there any chance that Fayed could still
be alive and have those four other bombs?
- We don't know. We're running the intel now.
- And what about Assad?
He's on his way here.
We're hoping he can help us find Fayed.
Keep me in the loop.
And Bill, please, be careful.
I will.
It's a lot to process.
So many people.
Yeah.
And Curtis? I can't believe this.
I know you and he were friends.
Why do people I know keep dying?
- Did you find anything out about Fayed?
- No, we're still positioning satellites.
(sighs)
We've got massive packet loss.
Do you wanna help boot up routers?
Who wouldn't?
- Open Études Five.
- OK.
I just have a really bad feeling
about everything.
Did you know Jack quit?
Yeah, Buchanan said.
What's that all about?
I'm sure it's because
he was forced to kill Curtis.
You know I'm here for you, right?
Yeah, I do.
(people shouting)
- (woman) We need help!
- Keep going. Keep going.
(man) Ma'am, we're doing the best we can.
Over here!
They discovered our location.
The bomb never reached its target.
I sold you the weapons. You could've warned
me before you blew them up in my city!
- It wasn't supposed to happen the way it did.
- A little late for apologies, don't you think?
My engineer died in the blast. The device
used to reprogram the trigger was destroyed.
That's my problem?
I have four more bombs whose triggers
need to be made operational.
Sorry, Fayed.
- I'm going to Vegas.
- Find me a way, McCarthy.
I'll pay you more. Double the amount
from our previous transaction.
That's interesting.
You need someone who can replicate
what that device did, with modern equipment.
That's advanced stuff.
I'd have to do some checking.
Do you know someone who can do this?
Even if I found someone who can,
I doubt they will.
I don't care how you get them to comply.
I need someone within the next few hours.
Are you in or not?
I'll do some research and get back to you.
Help! Somebody help!
Look, I-I-I can't get through to 911.
Would you help? I need a doctor.
I need a doctor. I need a doctor.
- (woman) Get out of my way!
- I need a doctor. Our helicopter went down.
There are two others. One's dead,
one's unconscious. Please, please help me.
I'm sorry. Show me.
I don't remember anything hitting us.
Itjust went out of control.
- You were hit by a shock wave.
- A shock wave of what?
- A nuclear bomb.
- What?
What are you talking about?
Can you hear me? Can you hear me?
Chuck, is that you?
Yeah, I brought help.
We're gonna get you out.
- Be careful, it's about to fall.
- It's jammed.
Ready? One, two, three.
Go!
Stay here.
- Are you OK?
- I think so.
(dials phone)
- This guy says it's a nuclear bomb.
- That's Valencia. That's where I live.
- My wife and kids are there. I gotta get them.
- You can't. The radiation will kill you.
- You'll die!
- (woman) CTU.
- This is Bauer. Let me speak to Buchanan.
- Right away.
You wanna save your friend,
don't let him go home.
- (Buchanan) You all right?
- I'm fine.
- Where are you?
- I'm still in Granada Hills.
You're upwind. Don't go any further north.
- How bad is it?
- It took out a square mile.
- Do we know if this was Fayed's endgame?
- It wasn't. There are four more nukes.
- You need to pick me up.
- You said you were out.
- Not after this.
- Tell me where you are, I'll send a car.
- I'm on the corner of Glasgow and Fifteenth.
- We'll be there.
Fayed has to be at least partially state
supported. Have you identified a country?
Not yet, sir. CIA's narrowed down a list.
It's on your screen in the short brief section.
Have you contacted
the ambassadors of these countries?
They all extend their condolences, and have,
of course, disavowed any role in the attacks.
Well, we know at least one of them's lying.
Maybe all of them.
I'm not sure we know that, John. But let's say
it is true. What are you suggesting?
We have carriers on standby
in the Persian Gulf
capable of striking multiple targets
in each of these states.
We've been playing games
with these terrorists for 11 weeks now.
The only language they understand is force,
so let's speak it to them real clearly.
I guarantee if these countries had to sustain
three major metropolitan nuclear strikes,
they'd no longer have the time
or the resources to play in our sandbox.
If these people wanna live in the Stone Age,
I say let's put them there.
I am very sure your emotions are shared by
many in this room and across this country...
It's notjust emotions. Duty demands...
The president is talking, Admiral.
Do not interrupt.
We will retaliate, Admiral.
But we will do so, sir, carefully,
and with our sights locked on our enemy
and only our enemy.
What has CTU learned
about the remaining weapons?
They're assessing
the satellite intel and forensic data.
So what do we know?
We're assuming the bomb was meant
to be detonated in a more populated area
and was only being assembled in Valencia.
- By the scientist that I released?
- Yes. The scientist was killed in the blast.
And CTU is trying to determine
where Fayed was at the time.
The worst-case scenario is that he is still alive
and has the remaining nuclear weapons.
Tell them we're safe.
That we're moving away from it now.
Mr Buchanan, this is Hamri Al-Assad.
Mr Buchanan's the director of CTU.
Mr Buchanan, I know that
you see me as your enemy,
but today, I assure you I am not.
Follow me.
There. All right?
Why are we treating Assad, one of the most
violent terrorists of our time, like a VIP?
No holding room.
Audience with the White House? Sure.
How would you like your mineral water,
Mr Assad? Room temp?
Please have a seat.
Ready?
Bill Buchanan, director of CTU Los Angeles.
I'm here with Hamri Al-Assad.
Less than 30 minutes ago Abu Fayed
detonated a nuclear weapon in Los Angeles.
We believe he's still at large
with four more tactical nuclear weapons.
- Four?
- That's right.
Please, you must understand,
I came to the United States to stop Fayed.
I knew he intended to damage,
but not that he had nuclear weapons.
There has to be a trail. There had to have been
many people involved in the planning of this.
It was planned after
Fayed betrayed me six months ago.
- When he learned of your peace plan.
- Which I still intend to broker.
But you knew Fayed was coming to the US.
This information came
only days before the attacks began.
- From whom?
- I'm a well-informed man, Mr Buchanan.
Are there any other paths
that can lead us to Fayed?
- Yes. The source.
- The source of the bomb?
A year ago, I sent Fayed to negotiate
with an ex-Soviet general
about tactical nuclear weapons,
but there was no transaction at the time.
- What was the name of the general?
- Dmitri Gredenko.
- Can you tell me anything about Gredenko?
- Nothing. Nothing. I've never met the man.
Continue questioning him.
I'm gonna check this out.
- Gredenko. You got that?
- I'm opening a Russian database now.
Let me know what you find out.
- What about this with Gredenko's name on?
- It's a link we're using as a match basis.
- No, I understand that...
- Hey, hey, hey.
I just compiled a list of people in LA who've
had contact with Gredenko on business.
- That's a lot of names.
- Yes.
But one of them kind of floated to the top,
if you know what I mean.
Put it on Buchanan's screen.
Wow.
- (woman) Sir, have you arranged it?
- Yes, they'll fly him up.
- I'll let them know.
- All right.
Morris just put something on your B window.
Gredenko contacts. Good.
Look at number 17.
Chairman of BXJ Technologies.
Phillip Bauer.
Jack's father.
- Did you get anything more specific?
- No. BXJ does business in Eastern Europe.
- This could be a purely coincidental link.
- What if it's not?
Their contracts are confidential,
but I'll look into it.
- You calling Jack?
- Yeah.
- This is Bauer.
- Jack.
Assad gave us the name of a Russian general
Fayed contacted a year ago about the nukes.
- General Gredenko. Do you know him?
- No.
It turns out your father does.
My father? Are you sure?
Gredenko did business with BXJ
Technologies specifically with your father.
- What kind of business?
- We don't know. We wanna talk to him.
Is my father a suspect?
No, his name came up on a list of people
who have had contact with Gredenko.
We're gonna question him.
I wanted to see if you could shed any light.
I haven't spoken to him for nine years.
We'll send someone to talk to him.
Bill, wait.
I should do this.
- Jack, we can run this.
- You don't have enough time.
He'll talk to me if I go alone.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Tell Stokes we'll pick him up.
You take the car.
Thanks, Bill.
You need to pull over.
- (woman) Is he still there?
- Yes, he is. But I don't know exact...
The FBI's here. I gotta go.
- Why did they send you?
- I didn't want to arrest you or your friend.
This is Agent Jennings.
He'll be working this with me.
- What exactly will you be doing?
- Walid heard conversations about the bombs.
He heard a fragment of a conversation.
If there is an active cell inside that detention
facility, we need Walid to find out more.
Agent Jennings will be putting a wire on him.
Putting a wire on him? I thought you were
replacing him with an undercover operative.
- Walid isn't trained to do something like this.
- He's already in place.
He's established a confidence.
- How will you be putting a wire on him?
- Just let us do ourjob.
Have you heard anything more?
- About what?
- Like what's going on out there.
- Well, how would I know that?
- I thought...
I was just wondering if you knew anything.
- No more than you, my brother.
- (speaks Arabic language)
- I'm sorry, I have to get back.
- Sure.
Walid Al-Rezani.
- Yes?
- You and I have to talk.
- About what?
- You don't ask the questions, son of a bitch.
I do.
Get out. Get out!
- We know who you're involved with.
- I told you people, I work for the IAA.
- I'm not involved in any terrorist activities.
- You're lying!
- I'm no terrorist!
- (Walid groans)
- What's he doing to him?
Don't worry, he's not going to hurt him.
It's just for show.
- That doesn't sound like it's just for show.
- Ms Palmer, I advised you to leave.
If you wanna stay,
keep your comments to yourself.
- Explain what was in your wallet.
- What are you talking about?
You know damn well
what we're talking about!
He's wiring you. It's a two-way radio.
Now you're gonna tell me what we found
in your wallet. Understand?
- What do you know about this guy? Huh?
- (Walid groans)
- This is ridiculous.
- Sit down.
Tell me or I'll take you to the
interrogation room. You don't want that.
- I don't care what you do to me.
- You will!
You're gonna say that I asked about this man.
Make them believe you're working with him.
I'll be back for you!
- What did they do to you?
- Nothing.
I'm fine.
They think they can do anything to us,
those bastards.
We've got a clear signal.
(phone rings)
- Hello?
- Sam, is that you?
Yes. Who's this?
- It's Jack.
- Jack?
- How are you, Sam?
- We thought you were...
- Where are you calling from?
- I'm in Los Angeles.
I need to speak to my father.
It's really important. Is he there?
- No, he's not.
- Where is he?
He left yesterday without saying where
he was going. I haven't heard from him.
- Can I reach him on his cell?
- He left it here.
I must admit it's all a bit mysterious. I tried
calling your brother. He didn't know either.
- Where is Gray?
- He was at work earlier, but who knows now.
- Can I get his cell number?
- Yeah. 818-555-0175.
If you speak to my father, tell him to get back
to me. Did my number show on your screen?
- Yes.
- It's really important.
I hope you find your father soon.
I know he would wanna talk to you.
He regrets the way things ended
between the two of you.
- (Jack) Yeah, me too.
- (Sam) Be well, Jack.
(Jack) Thanks, Sam.
(dials phone)
(man) Yeah?
It's Liddy. You'll never guess
who just called here.
- Who?
- Your brother Jack.
Jack's rotting away in some Chinese prison.
No, actually he's here in LA.
- How the hell did that happen?
- I don't know.
- What's he want?
- He's looking for the old man.
- Why?
- He didn't say, but...
if I were you, I'd expect a call from Jack.
Your name came up.
We should've killed Jack
instead of handing him to the Chinese.
We tried.
This isn't good. My brother has a way
of digging things up that need to stay buried.
(phone rings)
- Hello.
- It's me. Jack.
Jack?
Yeah.
Sam said you called, but I didn't believe him.
Are you OK?
- Yeah, I'm fine. Is everyone safe over there?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah, we're cool, Jack. Wow!
It's blowing my mind hearing from you.
When Dad and I found out that you were
in China, we tried everything to get you out.
- Thanks.
- Yeah. How did you get out?
- Some sort of exchange.
- For what?
- I'm not really sure.
- It must've been one hell of an exchange.
I'm working with CTU,
trying to help them with something.
Yeah, Sam said that
you were trying to find Dad.
- Yeah. Where is he?
- I don't know. He took off yesterday.
I assume he went to visit one of his
girlfriends. One of 'em's really kind of hot.
- Why'd he leave without his cellphone?
- I guess he didn't want to be bothered.
Gray, I need your help.
I need to find him. It's important.
Whatever you need. I'll make a few calls.
Can I get back to you at this number?
- Yeah.
- OK. You got it.
Thanks.
(phone rings)
CTU. O'Brian.
- I need you to help me find an address.
- Whose?
Graem Bauer.
- Your brother?
- Yeah.
It should be in my family file.
I haven't seen him in years.
Is he still in Malibu?
No, he's in Indian Falls. 226 Pinecrest Road.
Do you want his cellphone number?
No, I already have it. I just talked to him.
Why didn't you ask him where he lives?
I'll get back to you.
(TV) California Highway Patrol
wants to make it clear that it is essential
their emergency personnel be allowed
to reach those injured in Valencia.
So please keep the streets clear. Once again,
a nuclear bomb has gone off in Valencia...
- Dad!
- The president will address the nation.
- You and your mom doing OK?
- Yeah. They're talking about nuclear fallout.
We'll be fine. In a weird way,
we're actually safer now.
They've made their big show in LA with this
nuke. Next, I'm sure it'll be in another city.
- OK?
- Yeah.
I need to talk to your mom alone.
All right.
I just got off the phone with my brother Jack.
Jack? How? I thought
the Chinese were holding him.
He's back in Los Angeles.
That's impossible.
Apparently not. He's looking for Dad.
- Is he coming here?
- Why? Are you hoping he will?
Don't go there.
I'm looking for a little honesty. You weren't
over Jack when we married. You're still not.
OK, how's this for a little honesty:
insecurity in a grown man is not attractive.
"The latest terrorist incident"?
This was a nuclear bomb.
Can we call it what it is?
It gives the president more flexibility. Use the
word nuclear and they'll hear nothing else.
No, they will hear the truth.
Everybody in this country
knows what happened,
and they want reassurances that no matter
how ugly this is, the president is in charge.
Listen, we don't have any tangible leads
and confidence is low.
Now, if I go out there and lie to the American
public and tell them we're on top of this,
then another bomb goes off somewhere, they
won't believe a word I say. That can't happen.
I agree, sir, and that's why
I see an opportunity.
Opportunity?
This bomb removes any remaining doubt that
we should take more aggressive measures.
Suspension of certain freedoms,
internment, deportation.
Now is the time to hit those topics.
Tom, you are counselling
that we embrace the politics of fear.
I am saying that we embrace reality.
We are afraid.
But if fear consolidates public support
for measures that save our nation from
extinction, then you bet I'm in support of fear.
Tom, the people cannot be
any more afraid than they are now.
I'd like this message to have a calming effect.
We will call this a nuclear bomb,
because that is what it is.
But if we expect civil order on those streets,
we cannot stoke the panic.
We're not gonna mention policy.
The American public just needs to know
that this administration
is working with the sole purpose of restoring
order and making our streets safe again.
I don't need a list of names,
I need one person who can do the job.
(man) I'll get back to you.
(car horn)
What took you so long?
Why couldn't you have
picked me up at my place?
Instead of leaving me on some
street corner looking like some hooker.
Just get in the car.
Do not... talk to me...
like one of your bimbos, you got me?
They just said on the news...
that if the wind changes, we're screwed.
I just wanna get out of the city
and get to Vegas.
We're not going to Vegas.
Oh, no, I'm not going to Palm Springs. Again.
Just drop me off right here. That place
is like assisted living for an entire city.
We're not going there either.
We have some things we gotta do here first.
What are you talking about? A nuclear bomb
just went off, like, 25 miles from here.
- I'm talking about a lot of money. Shut up.
- Darren...
Stop talking! Now!
(dials phone)
- Things are looking up.
- What does that mean?
It means I might be able to find
someone to do your dirty work.
- How soon?
- I expect to have good news within the hour.
- Just make sure my money is ready to wire.
- The money is ready now.
McCarthy will find someone for us. Tell the
men these bombs go off today as scheduled.
I finished with Assad. He gave me a few more
names, but nothing he thought would help.
- What else did he say?
- He wants peace.
You believe him?
Yeah.
The president would like you
transported to Washington, DC.
You'll be leaving out of Port Hueneme
on a military jet.
Some of the information
you gave us checked out.
Good luck here in Los Angeles.
I hope the worst is over.
Thank you.
Sir, the FBI just upgraded one of their leads.
They're sending us live audio.
- What kind of audio?
- They got a guy wearing a wire at Anacostia.
One of the detainees may have
information about Fayed.
Give it to Chloe, make it a priority.
(in Arabic language)
- Walid should not be doing this.
- He'll be OK.
- That is not the point.
- It was his decision, and it was the right one.
Usually it takes weeks to develop a cover. He
might be able to find something within hours.
If this works, he'll have done an heroic thing.
Please, don't give me speeches, OK?
"If it works"?
What if it doesn't
and they find out he's wearing a wire?
- Guards inside are keeping an eye on him.
- Right.
- It's not the best thing that you're here.
- Walid is my client...
I know what you told me, and frankly
that carries no weight with the FBI.
Let's be honest, the only reason you're here
is you're the president's sister.
Then you remember that and we'll be fine.
You have no trouble bending the rules
when it's to your advantage, do you?
(Salim speaks in Arabic language)
What did they want with you?
I shouldn't bring you into this.
It's all right. You can talk to me.
I heard the guard say
he found something in your wallet.
- Yeah, they confiscated it.
- What was it? What did he find?
A phone number.
Whose?
Listen to me, if you and I are in the same
situation here, we should know each other.
- Talk to me.
- Maybe I shouldn't have gotten involved.
- I met some people through my organisation.
- What organisation?
The IAA. I'm Regional Director.
Go on.
Most of what we do has no... teeth. I was
introduced to a man who was more active.
- I wanted to help him.
- That's good.
We set up a meeting,
but before I had a chance, I was grabbed.
Who is this person?
Abu Fayed.
You know him?
No.
But please, join us, brother.
- He did that well.
- What happens now?
He's going to have to sell himself
to the others before they open up.
(doorbell)
Jack! Uh, I didn't know
that you were coming here.
- We need to talk.
- Yeah, sure. Yeah. Come on in.
Man, Jack, it's good to see you.
Good to see you.
(clears throat) Um...
- You've never been here, have you?
- No.
God, when was the last time
we saw each other?
- When Teri died.
- That's right, at the funeral.
- Have you found Dad yet?
- No. I made some calls, but so far nothing.
Hey, Josh, come here.
Josh, this is your Uncle Jack. You two
have not seen each other in a long time.
- Hey.
- Hi, Josh.
- How you doin'?
- OK, I guess.
It's kind of been a weird day.
- Yeah, I know.
- (mother) Josh.
Give your father some privacy.
- (Josh) Maybe we can talk later.
- I would like that.
I'm sorry for the intrusion. I just need some
information about our father, then I'll leave.
Well, that was pleasant, wasn't it?
Come on, let's go to my office.
- Have a seat.
- I'm fine.
OK. So what are we doing here, Jack?
Our father did business with an ex-Russian
general named Gredenko. Do you know him?
Um... no, it must be one of the old guard.
We can't believe
the drinking buddies Dad's cultivated.
There was one time we were
down in Venezuela, this was before...
Gray.
I didn't come here to listen to your stories.
I'm serious. I need to find Dad.
OK, we will. Boy, Jack, you could neverjust
walk into a room and get along, could you?
I mean, I know you must've
gone through hell in China,
but look at the bright side,
you got out, you're here. Just relax a little.
If you try and raise your voice,
I will rip your tongue out. Are we clear?
Gray, people in this country are dying,
and I need some information.
Are you gonna give it to me,
or do I have to hurt you?
- Actually, you're hurting me now.
- Trust me, I'm not.
(knock at door)
- The speech is in the Teleprompter.
- With the latest changes?
Yes, sir.
OK.
Are you all right, sir?
I can't let the American public
see how scared I am.
No, you cannot.
But we got hit by a nuclear bomb. Bravado
would be no more appropriate than fear.
Thank you, Tom.
My fellow Americans,
there is no easy way to say the words,
"America has been hit by a nuclear weapon".
But, as you know, this is now a fact.
The question remains, what do we,
as a country, as a people, do about it?
How do we rationalise
the fear and sorrow that each of us feels?
Do we let our anger
guide us down a dangerous path?
Or do we come together,
continuing to show courage and strength
in the face of our enemy?
This horrible act of evil
which has struck our great nation
is the cowardly action of barbaric men.
Say one more thing I don't wanna hear,
and this will hurt.
- What do you want from me?
- The truth!
That is the truth!
I swear to you on my family's life.
Not good enough.
You brought this on yourself.
Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net