-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Proudly Presents
Sync: YTET-ÅÝÅÝ·É °îµÂÖí
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Season 07 Episode 11
*******
Have you made the preparations?
Are you sure you want  to leave now,colonel?
Can't imagine general juma will be pleased to learn
that you're abandoning your mission.
The mission is over.
You think I'm a fool,mr.Burnett?
If anything should happen to me on my way out of the country,
the data file with all the names and bank transactions of all those involved
will be sent to the justice dertment.
When the car arrives,we would like you to go with the driver
so that we could follow you back to dubaku.
You want her to go to him and face him?
It's the only chance we have of finding him before he disappears forever.
I'll do it.
You keep her safe,you hear me?
We will.
Colonel!
Fbi.Go!Go!
I want the names of everyone in the united states government
that you've been working with.
I have a list.
I found some kind of digital storage device implanted under dubaku's skin.
Can you upload the files to fbi?
Marika didn't make it.
You killed my sister.
I'm so sorry.
What do you want from me?!
I just want to know that you feel something.
I want to know that you feel the same kind of pain that I do!
Do you feel that?!
I'm working with fbi to coordinate an interagency sweep.
We should start making arrests within the hour.
What you have done here today puts all of us in your debt.
There are a lot of people to thank,including jack bauer.
What are you asking me to do,bill?
I'm asking you to speak  to senator mayer.
Jack bauer helped save this country.
He doesn't deserve to spend the rest of his life in prison.
-I'm going to the white house.
-Sir?
President taylor wants to speak to me regarding jack bauer.
Grab your laptop,ryan.
I want you there with me.
There's gonna be another attack.
Here in D.C.My source tells me that the window opens at 1900 hours.
What's the target?
He doesn't know  the exact target,
but it's definitely going to be of high value and high impact.
He gave me the name of somebody who's been involved in the planning.
-Who?
-Ryan burnett.
Senator mayer's chief of staff.
That's right.
***********
hold on a second.
Go ahead.
icu.
One moment,please.
Corinna,you got a call on three.
-Who is it?
-Dr.May.He's got a question.
Doctors are so helpless.
Dr. May? Hello?
There was no one there.
If he calls back,tell him I'll call him back in a minute.
code blue.Code blue!
We have a code blue in the icu!
Get agent walker down to icu now!
Swift and decisive  is how the pentagon describes  the U.S.Invasion  now underway in sangala.
"Sporadic resistance,minimal casualties.
"  This in direct contrast  to assertions made  by sangalese leader  benjamin juma  on state-supported television.
Our brave soldiers are beating back the enemy all across sangala city.
History is on our side,my friends.
We survived their slave ships,and we will survive their warships,too.
Declaring victory while his own troops are fleeing the capital,
and his palace lies in ruins.
When do we think this was made?
My guess is these recordings were made some time before the invasion,ma'am.
Which begs the question,john.
Where is h and why haven't we found him yet?
Special forces teams all over sangala city are searing for him.
There is some intelligence to suggest he may have fled the country.
Admiral smith,you and i both know that juma must be captured.
He must be tried and convicted of his crimes against humanity.
Otherwise,we've as good as failed.
He can't go far,ma'am.
No country on earth will grant him asylum.
Then find him,admiral smith.
Wherever he is.
General juma?
Beautiful,isn't it?
Sir?
It's not a trick question,laurent.
It is beautiful.
Why not?
It is almost time.
The men-- are they ready?
Yes,sir.
Are they afraid?
I don't know,sir,but some of them are praying.
It's good if they are afraid.
It means they will fight bravely.
Have you heard from my father yet,sir?
I thought he was supposed to be meeting us here.
Don't worry,laurent.
He will be here.
Yes,sir.
Colonel dubaku is dead.
Are you certain?
The dose I administered was catastrophic.
His son just asked me about him.
He must never know about this,or about his father's cowardice.
He won'T.
Then nothing will stand in our way,udo.
But hurry.The attack window is narrowing.
The timing must be precise.
-Doctor: Clear!
-Yes,sir.
Clear.
One more time at 360.
clear.
Nothing.
Going again,doctor?
no.
That's it,everybody.I'm calling it.
Time of death: 6:06 P.M.
Drstahl,what's going on?
A massive heart attack.
You said that he was stable,that he was going to be okay.
So,what happened?
I'm not sure.
Maybe a preexisting condition.
The autopsy will tell us.Excuse me.
The wide extent of the corruption requires a coordinated approach.
We know the government's been compromised.
We just don't know at what level.
Presently,chloe o'brian is vetting the names department by department.
I'm prioritizing secret service,so the president is secured as soon as possible.
Team leaders will then receive their assignmes--
defense,treasury,state,et cetera--
and make their arrests contemporaneously across the district.
-o'brian.
-Chloe,it's jack.
Have the names from dubaku's database been handed over to the arrest teams yet?
Not yet.
Okay,listen to me.
I've just learned that juma's operatives are planning another attack.
Jack,they're telling us here it's over.
That's wrong.
Tony's my source on the intel.
Do you know what the target is?
Only that it's high value,high casualty,
and that it's happening now,which is why I need your help.
There's a man on the list,a ryan burnett.
He's senator mayer's chief of staff.
Mayer?
Isn't he the guy who grilled you this morning at the senate subcommittee hearing?
Yeah,but the senator's not implicated in the conspiracy.
But burnett has been providing support for juma and dubaku all along.
Chloe,I need you to delete his name from the list.
What?Why?
If the fbi start to move in on him,he'll lawyer up,
and no one will get the information on time.
Where is he now?
Jack: He's at the white house with the senator.
They've got a meeting with the president.
I'm on my way there now to be debriefed by bill.
I'll take care of him then.
Jack,you don't expect to interrogate a suspect in the white house?
Let me handle that.
Chloe,just get his name deleted from the list.
I'll get back to you.
She's in.
How close are we?
Close.
Is there anything I can do to help?
I'm just cycling through the last layer of data now.
You know,it might be quicker
if you send the subsets to my station one by one.
Good idea.
And then that way I can get to work on distributing them.
-Okay,then.
-Thank you.
Listen,jack,ybe you should reconsider.
Reconsider what?
Taking bill into your confidence.
Look,I mean,he's been a part of this operation since the get-go.
I don't know what it's going to take to get burnett to talk.
If I have to use extreme measures...
I don't get it.What,you don't think he'll go there?
I'm driving off a cliff here,tony.
I don't need to put bill in the passenger seat.
All right,then,fine.I'll go with you.
You're a wanted felon.
You wouldn't get past the first checkpoint.
Besides,with all of the government agencies still compromised,
it might be up to you to stop the attack.
See you on the other side.
Yes?
Can you extend the attack window?
Not without risking the entire operation.
Why?
There's been a complication.
I may be stuck here longer than I anticipated.
I'll call you back.
Mr.Kanin.
Ryan burnett,senator mayer's chief of staff.
We've spoken on the phone.
Many times.It's good to finally meet you.
Likewise.The senator's inside.Right this way.
Senator?
Well,senator,I see you've found the bar.
Mind if I join you?
Something I never knew.
If it ain't from kentucky,you can't call it bourbon.
Spare me the southern gentleman routine,ethan.
The president didn't call me up here at the ass-end of the day
to drink her booze and flip through a briefing book.
I thought it might be helpful,before your meeting,
to bring you up to speed on the events of the last ten hours.
Okay.
I'm up to speed.
Senator,surely you have some reaction to what you just read.
Damn right I have a reaction.
I want to know what all this has to do with jack bauer.
I mean,that's the reason I'm here,right?
Without mr.Bauer,we would never have uncovered the conspiracy
in the first place nor the people behind it.
His efforts,in conjunction with those of the fbi,
are largely responsible for the arrests being made right now across the district.
You're not saying that he's acting in an official capacity?
I don't have to tell you how this looks,ethan.
Colluding with a rogue operative from a disbanded agency.
I'm sorry you see it that way.
How else am I supposed to see it?
The way the president does-- that jack bauer saved lives today,
plain and simple,including her husband'S.
Look,senator,I know this isn't easy for you.
The public battle you've waged against detainee abuse
and human rights violations...
are you seriously asking me to look the other way on this?
I have been after this son of a bitch for years.
He's a thug,ethan.
He's exhibit "A.
" The president is prepared to reverse policy
and support your amendment to the war crimes act.
In exchange for what exactly?
The hearings.
Declare a recess till after the holidays
and then quietly let mr.Bauer's subpoena expire.
And if I refuse to go along?
The president is prepared to invoke executive privilege.
Executive privilege-- meaning what exactly?
Well,that's for the president to decide.
Are you talking about a pardon?
I wouldn't rule it out.
Well,if that's how the president wants to play it,
you can tell her she just walked into a street fight.
You can tell her yourself.
-Jack.
-Hi,bill.
You got here sooner than I expected.
jack.
Put down your weapon now!
Step away from the desk!
Take a seat.
Sit down,bill!
Okay,okay,I'm sitting.
Now,what's this all about?
-Where is ryan burnett?
-What?
Senator mayer's chief of staff-- where is he?
I'm not saying anything until you tell me what the hell's going on.
Tony doubled back to one of his contacts,
who gave him information of a second attack.
It's going to take place here in washington within the hour.
Juma's operatives are carrying it out.
Burnett's been supporting them all along.
He knows where the attack's going to take place,
so you can either tell me where he is or I will find him myself.
Jack,I can'T.
Fine,put your hands behind your back now.
How good is the intel?
Good enough for me to need to talk to him.
Don't you move.
Jack,let me have him arrested.
There are other ways to deal with this.
The attack window's open.
We're out of time.
Jack,listen to me.
I spoke to the president on your behalf.
She's going to intervene with senator mayer,
stop the hearings.
You can get your life back.
You do this,you're throwing it all away.
I wish I thought there was another option.
Let me help you at least,jack.
Y-you don't have to do this alone.
Yes,I do.
It's the only way I can make sure to keep you out of this.
-Jack.
-Bill,I'm sorry.
Jack,w-w-wait!Jack!
It's all right.
don't fight it.
-this is moss.
-Larry,it's me.
Dubaku's dead.
I thought the doctors said he was stabilized.
What happened?
Officially,they're characterizing that it was a coronary brought on by systemic shock.
Sounds like you don't believe it.
I did a follow-up with the hospital admin.
She confirmed that there was an eight-member team on duty when dubaku flatlined.
Yeah?
There was a ninth man in the icu just before the code was called-- an orderly.
I ran back the tapes on the ward and that's when I spotted him.
The thing is: I've asked around and nobody seems to know who he is.
Renee,wait,a-are you saying you think dubaku was murdered?
I'm saying that there was an unidentified man in with dubaku just
before he went into cardiac arrest.
What does the admin say?
She says that they often use floaters--
personnel from other area hospitals filling in from time to time.
Said it's not uncommon for the regular staff not to know who they are.
She's double-checking with payroll now.
Right,so there's your answer.
Still it seems odd.
I mean,what if dubaku knew something and they needed to shut him up?
Is this bauer's theory,too?
Jack's not even here and,you know,I resent that implication,larry.
-What implication is that?-That I'm not the one calling the shots.
This has been my investigation from the beginning,
not jack bauer'S.
I was just asking a question.I wasn't implying anything.
You there?
I'm sorry.I guess I'm a little sensitive on the subject.
Look,everything we needed from dubaku,we got.
Names and bank accounts of every corrupt official on his payroll.
Teams are in the field as we speak.
So you're saying you want me to come in.
We need you back in the office soor than later
to help process all these arrests.
Larry,look,I've got security searching the hospital a nd reviewing more video.
So,what,you want to follow that up first?
Fine,call me when you clear it.
I will.Thanks,larry.
Excuse me,agent walker?
That orderly you were looking for--
one of our parking lot cameras picked him up getting into his car.
-When?
-Uh,about 15 minutes ago.
I've got a screen grab of his license plate.
Thank you.
This is agent walker.Put me through to our dmv contact.
Are you busy?
I'm just reformatting the server,so,yeah,I guess I am busy.W?
Well,I was cross-referencing dubaku's offshore accounts
and I came across an orphaned header fragment.
-What are you talking about?
-Take a look.
Okay,see,there,right there,right there.
It's a remnant file header.
It's probably just a phantom data string.
No,it isn'T.
I ran a systems analysis.
The coding is not random.
It can be traced back to one of the accounts.
Also,it looks like a name was deleted from the lis
why don't I run a recovery program?
Well,you're very busy with the reformatting and all,
so why don't I just upload it to my station and take care of it there?
Well,that's okay,I can do it faster.
No offense.
I'll let you know if I retrieve anything.
Sure.
-Thanks.
-Thank you.
yeah.
Have you gotten to burnett yet?
Working on it.Making my way over to the west wing.
Someone here has figured out that a name has been deleted from the database.
I don't know how much longer I can hold her off.
Do they know it was burnett?
No,but it's just a matter of time.
Okay,I'll get back to you.
Great.
Senator,I'll head back to the hill and get with sandy.
We should have a press release drafted by the time you finish your meeting.
I'm also going to need a sit-down with your friend hauser at the post.
Off the record,I assume.
We've got to make pardoning jack bauer
as politically toxic for the president as possible.
She's a woman in a highly emotional state.
Her husband's been shot.
You suggesting her judgment's impaired?
I'm suggesting that a case could be made.
excuse me,senator.
President taylor is ready to see you now.
Go ahead,senator.I'll get this to the ag,
tell him you want the option to go ahead with the hearings tomorrow as scheduled.
Thanks,ryan.
Yes?
It's burnett.
You took care of the problem?
I'm leaving now.
Good,then we rendezvous at 2130 hours,as planned.
I'll be there.
Excuse me,I'll be out of here in just one second.
You and I... ...we're going to have a talk.
We've got a command post set up at eeob,
and we'll brief cia and diplomatic security,
but not until after the first sweep of arrests.
Look,nobody is going anywhere,phil.
We've dropped a ne on the city.
And I'll let you know as soon as that happens.
All right.
I'm sorry to interrupt,but I need you to listen to something.
-May I?
-Yeah,that's fine.
She's supposed to be this whiz-bang systems analyst,
which is actually what tipped me off in the first place.
-Her demeanor is so bizarre...
-w-w-whoa,janis,janis,slow down.
-Who are you talking about?
-Chloe o'brian.
I ran a systems check on her work,and it turns out there's evidence of file tampering.
Plus she's been scrambling all her out-of-office phone calls,
so I had operations archive her cellular traffic.
I did a work-around.
Listen.
Have you gotten to burnett yet?
Working on it.
Making my way over to the west wing.
Someone here has figured out that a name has been deleted from the database.
Longer I can hold her off.
Do they know it was burnett?
No,but it's just a matter of time.
Okay,I'll get back to you.
Becker.
In the conference room.I want chloe o'brian detained.
And get her off that server.
Get me the white house.
Let me just remind you,madam president,you
supported the effort to ban abuse and torture.
You campaigned to reform
the intelligence agencies.
These past ten hours,senator,things haven't
appeared as black and white as they once did.
Well,there's nothing
gray about jack bauer.
The man has committed atrocities.
Prisoners have died in his custody.
Bauer has served under the aegis
of three presidents,not just me.
Is it any more lawful or any less repugnant
if it's authorized at the highest level?
A state of war is not a blank check
for the president or for anyone.
Oh,don't lecture me,senator.
I am well aware of
the limits of my power.
Due respect,madam president...
your power is great.
Just be careful that you use
it to send the right message.
All I'm asking you to do is
excuse mr.Bauer as a witness.
It's not a message.
It is an expression of gratitude
for what he's done today.
Mayer: You're asking me to excuse
him as a target of the investigation.
And the message is clear.
Under certain circumstances,you
believe his methods are acceptable.
Some would argue that they are.
And they would be wrong.
Under any military or moral standard.
America has been down this
road before,madam president.
You yourself called it a national trage.
It was a tragedy.
I still believe that.
Pardon jack bauer,and you're telling every
interrogator in the field that it's open season again.
I'm sorry to interrupt,madam president.
There's an urgent call
from larry moss at fbi.
- Put him through.
- *******
Agent moss is on the line.
Agent moss,this is ethan kanin.
You're on speaker with the president.
Madam president,forgive me for
coming directly to the point.
You have a meeting this
evening with senator mayer?
In fact,I do.I'm with him right now.
Did the senator's chief of staff,ryan
burnett,accompany the senator to the white house?
Yes,he did,agent
moss-- why?
I have reason to believe that jack bauer is carrying
out an off-book interrogation of mr.Burnett as we speak.
I can pull the trigger 128 more
times before this battery dies.
I'm telling you,I don't know
anything about an attack.
Stop lying to me.
I'm not lying.
What's the target?
I can't tell you what I don't know.
Mr.Burnett,you are a
traitor and a terrorist.
I'm not.I love my country.
that was 1,200 volts of current.
Now,when I eject this cartridge,
I access the drive stun mode,upping the
voltage 40 times when directly administered.
All you need to do is talk to me.
Mr.Burnett,it's really simple.
Just tell me what the target
is,and this will be all over.
I promise.I have no idea
what you're talking about.
This is your last chance.
If I knew,I would tell you,I swear it.
What do you want me to say?
Just... just tell me what
to say,and I'll say it.
don't you even try and
play that game with me.
Mr.Burnett,I've been doing this a long
time,and I can tell the difference,
especially when a man is under duress,if he's got
information that I need or if I'm just wasting my time.
And I promise you,I
am not wasting my time.
the next jolt is gonna
be in your throat.
Anything above your neck runs the risk
of a complete neuromuscular shutdown.
That means you run the
risk of becoming paralyzed.
No,please.
Mr.Burnett,you built the
entire federal case against me.
You of all people should know how far I am
willing to go to stop this attack from happening.
So,I'm gonna ask you one last time.
Where is the target?!
I... Okay,okay,okay.
I'm listening.
Soldiers.
- How many?
- A unit.
Juma's presidential guard.
When?
It already started.
Where?Where?!
Mr. Bauer,this is president taylor.
Where is the target?
- Mr. Bauer...
- wher!
Mr. Bauer,I am ordering
you to answer this page.
Mr.Bauer,do you hear me?
Damn it!
Madam president,this is jack bauer.
I don't know what you've heard
so far,but this thing is not over.
There is another terrorist attack
going to take place within minutes.
There will be no discussion
until you unlock this door.
Madam president,the
attack window is open.
Juma's men are movg.
What you're doing is
against the law,mr.Bauer.
I am your commander in chief,and
I am ordering you to stand down.
how much longer,sergeant?
Good to go,ma'am.
Do it.
Where's the target?
Where is the target?!
Where is...?!
I had him!
Man down.
Emts to the visiting dignitary suite.
You're done,bauer.
You're finished.
He was talking.
Whatever's going to happen is happening
now,and it's on your conscience.
My conscience has a lot less
to answer for than yours.
Mr.Bauer,you say an attack is imminent.
My source intel is good.
Who is your source?
I'd rather not say.
The name,mr.Bauer.
Tony almeida.
Tony almeida-- the
man's a fugitive.
Without tony almeida,we would
never have recovered the cip device.
Madam president,I don't care if his
source is the blessed virgin mary.
Nothing justifies what
went on in this room.
Even if he's right,blaine?
Even if it means we could save lives?
Look at that,and tell
me it's not barbarism.
Is that something you can live with?
Jack: Earlier today,madam president,two
airplanes were brought down.
Is that something you can live with?
You're reprehensible,bauer.
And you,sir,are weak!
Unwilling and unable to look
evil in the eye and deal with it.
Ethan,step out for a second.
Suddenly,it's not so hypothetical,is it?
In your opinion,is bauer's
intelligence actionable?
If bauer says there's going to be an attack,my
belief is,there's going to be an attack.
Torture was originally intended
to force false confessions.
Now we use it to try and find the truth.
These people murdered
your son,madam president.
They attempted to murder your husband.
They will stop at nothing.
Sergeant,take mr.Bauer away.
He's under arrest.
You should have come to me.
You should have presented your case.
We didn't have time.
And would it really have
made a difference,ma'am?
Madam president... you're
doing the right thing.
271 dead already.
I wish to god it felt
more like the right thing.
Ethan,raise the threat levels.
Tell homeland they have until 7:00
come  with a response scenario.
And get tim down here.
Also,I want to talk
to mr.Burnett myself.
Let me do that.
I know the man.
Apparently,you don'T.
Ethan: Got it.
Tim,I understand the threat level has been raised,but
only for first responders and federal agents.
There's a concern that mass evacuation by the public
could hamper efforts to thwart an attack when it comes.
What about the airspace over washington?
Restricted.
Military flyovers are commencing.
Dod has recommended that we deploy mobile teams to
sweep the area for radioactive and biological signatures.
I'll call phillip at the
pentagon and push it through.
What about nsa?
There's elevated anti-american
chatter coming from the usual web sites
and telephone traffic,but
nothing specific to the attack.
Thank you,tim.
I'll see you upstairs in 15 minutes.
Yes,ma'am.
Which means our best source of intelligence
is still right here under our noses.
You realize we're gonna have to
offer this bastard a free pass.
With coercive measures off
the table,it's our only option.
Uer's going to prison,and
a traitor walks.
What's wrong with this picture?
I need a minute with the prisoner.
Mr.Burnett,you will be charged with treason under
title 18,section 2381,of the united states code.
Giving aid and comfort to the enemy and
directly causing the death of american citizens.
Do you understand?
Surely,you have something
to say for yourself.
I demand my right to counsel.
You'll have your counsel,mr.Burnett,but
first,you're going to tell me everything you know.
Not in this lifetime.
What did you say?
I said,not in this lifetime.
Don't be so quick to make
up your mind,mr.Burnett.
In exchange for information which stops
or significantly mitigates this attack,
the president is prepared to grant
you full immunity from prosecution.
I'm sorry.
I can't help you.
If you and your family are
being threatened in any way...
do you realize what the
president is offering you?
Treason is a capital offense,mr.Burnett.
If you don't cooperate
with us right now,
I will make it my personal mission to see that
you pay the ultimate price for your crimes.
I won't condone
torture,but in your case,
I would have no problem
with the death penalty.
Where's my lawyer?
Walker.
Moss: It's me.That situation at
the hospital you told me about?
Yeah,I'm on it,larry.
I traced a license plate
to an import/export firm.
Tell me.
The orderly I mentioned-- he just
joined up with about a dozen soldiers.
Africans.Heavily armed.
Where are you?
44543 lambourne
marina,near johnson park.
I'm in the warehouse basement.
Renee,we have intel on another
attack by juma's people.
It's happening in
D.C.,Sometime after 1900 hours.
This is it,larry.No question.
All right,listen,sit tight.
- I'm on my way with back.
- Make it quick.
Janis,scramble a chopper.
On the roof in two minutes.
Okay.
- But also...
- janis,just do it.
This is larry moss.
Put me through to metro police.
Charters,turner--
with me.
General,there is no sign of my father.
I just spoke with him.
Unfortunately he won't
be able to join us.
Why not?
Because he got delayed in his attempt to
secure safe passage for us from the country.
Then,sir,let me take his
place on the assault team.
Spoken like a true dubaku,laurent.
But you are also my only
reconnaissance officer.
- But,general...
- no,I need you on the perimeter to provide intelligence
and also to disrupt whatever
rescue operations there may be.
Understood?
Understood,sir.
Make your final preparations.
It is time for us to go.
Yes,sir.
yeah?
Larry,hurry,they're moving out.
We're ten minutes away.
Is it possible that juma
himself is leading this attack?
Juma?Why do you say that?
I know it sounds crazy,but
i swear that I just saw him.
What?!Here?!
Are you sure?
Unless he has an identical twin.
All right,I'll alert homeland.
Good work.
Any idea what the next target is?
Negative.
See if you get a fix on
that.But,listen,don't take any chances.
All right?
I won'T.
Okay,thank you.
Sir.
You should have an
emt take a look at you.
I'm fine.
Is bauer in custody?
Yes,sir.He's in holding.
That'll be all.
tony,it's bill.
Bill.
Jack's under arrest.They've got him
locked down in a holding cell here.
- Listen to me,bill...
- no,you listen.
We still don't know where
this attack's taking place.
Burnett didn't break?
No.They stopped jack before
he could get the information.
And burnett didn't go for
the president's immunity deal.
You were the one who
brought jack the intel,right?
That's right.
How real is it?
Very.
Who was your contact?
It was a guy in emerson's crew
with a direct line to juma.
Any chance we get
another crack at this guy?
That's highly unlikely,to say the least.
What are you telling me,he's dead?
That's right?
I wish to god you'd
brought me in on this.
Jack didn't want to put
you in that position.
For what it's worth,he was
trying to protect you,bill.
Did you have a fallback plan,at least?
Immunity for burnett was the fallback.
That's it?Nothing else?
No.Nothing.
I keep trying renee,and I
keep getting her voice mail.
What the hell's gog on?
There's something wrong with her phone.
What do you mean,something's wrong?I
just spoke to her five minutes ago.
Can you triangulate her position?
I can'T.
Why not?
There's no signal.
Either the battery's dead,or
her cell got damaged somehow.
All right,keep trying.
Get back to me when you know something.
Okay.
From our location it is approximately
100 meters to the entrance.
From this point forward,we maintain
radio silence until the target is secure.
Understood?
Yes,sir.
You all have your assignments.
May god be with us.
Laurent,take your position.
Yes,sir.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-Proudly
Presents
Sync: YTET-ÅÝÅÝ·É
°îµÂÖí-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
24Season
7 Episode 11