- You killed Tariq?
- You can't let Father know.
He wants me dead
because I messed up with Debbie.
You ordered Tariq to kill him.
To kill our own son.
Nothing will stand in the way
of what needs to be done.
Not him, not you.
Your father's following us.
- What?
- It was the only way I could save you.
Mom!
I think I got it.
I can turn off the override
and stop the remaining plants
from melting down.
- I did the best I could, sir. I hope it works.
- So do I.
Edgar, what's going on? Why are some
of the reactors still not shutting down?
Six of them were immune to the kill sequence.
Contact Bauer. Either he finds the people
responsible for planting the override,
or we're looking a nuclear holocaust.
Bauer and Audrey left five minutes ago.
- Where'd they go?
- Felsted Security.
You're going to need
to set things up on your end.
When Bauer and Audrey Raines are killed,
CTU is going to know
that someone inside leaked their location.
- Divert suspicion.
- Fine.
The device maintains heat levels
of the reactors.
They can melt down each of those plants.
The man you saw when you
were held captive, he's our only lead.
Stop. There. I think that's him.
- They're sealing us off.
- Should we call CTU?
No. CTU's been compromised. That's
the only way they'd know we were here.
- Then who are you calling?
- The only person I can trust right now.
I'm empty.
Tony!
Is there any chance this is a mistake,
that the remaining six reactors
are just taking longer to shut down?
No.
Those plants are in the grip of the override,
which has been sealed off.
Did you send the list of cities
to the president?
- Yes.
- What about evacuation procedures?
We alerted the National Guard. We'll see
how the president wants us to proceed.
Ms Driscoll, the president's ready.
OK, put him on. Mr President.
I understand we've been able to shut down
98 nuclear power plants.
Yes, sir.
But it appears that our shutdown will not be
effective with the six remaining reactors.
Not going to be effective?
What exactly does that mean?
I'm afraid it means that we could have
six nuclear disasters on our hands.
What are the casualty projections
if all six plants melt down?
450,000 deaths in the first 24 hours.
Longer-range estimates in the low millions.
And that's not taking into account
the resulting cancers and birth defects.
Why were we able to shut down
the other power plants but not these six?
They're still being controlled by the terrorists.
- Because of the override device?
- Exactly.
We have to find the override device itself.
It's a prototype.
The terrorists have the only one.
Then let's find it.
I'll order the evacuation of those six cities.
-  Jim, keep me posted.
- Yes, Mr President.
All right, let's get back to work.
- Yeah?
- Mr Secretary, it's Jack.
Don't let anyone know it's me.
We've got a problem.
I understand, Marcy.
Let me see what I can do.
- I have to take this call.
- Yes.
All right.
These are the projected numbers.
What's going on?
Audrey and I are safe, but there was an
attempt on our lives at Felsted Security.
What?
A group of assassins
took out our entire security detail.
Send a forensic unit to identify the bodies,
but I don't want CTU to know.
Why not?
I think someone at CTU
was complicit in the attack.
How do you know that?
Sir, CTU is the only agency that knew where
we were. No one else had that information.
- Is one of Erin's people with the terrorists?
- I think so. I just don't know who.
But it's clear that they didn't want
Audrey to make the ID of the man she saw.
I'm sending a Secret Service detail
to pick you up.
- Please don't. That's not the right thing to do.
- Why not?
I don't want anyone to know where we are.
That way I know we'll be safe.
How should I handle this?
- Remember the Melbourne situation?
- Yes.
Try that. I think it'll work.
OK.
I've got to go.
I'll get back to you when we're safe.
- Jack, take care of Audrey.
- Yes, sir. I will.
- Are you OK?
- I'm almost getting used to this.
Yeah.
- Is it possible that we've been followed?
- No. We're clear.
- Where are we going?
- We need to lay low for a while.
- What communication do you need?
- A wi-fi and a hardline.
- All right. We'll go back to my place.
- OK.
Thank you, Tony.
Wait till you see it before you thank me.
No, I mean for picking us up,
for saving our lives.
- I'm sure you're wondering what's going on.
- Not really, no.
- Something wrong?
- What could be wrong?
I'm not in federal prison
thanks to you and President Palmer.
Michelle left me. I...
You know what, never mind.
Why don't you tell me what this is all about?
- You heard about Audrey and her father?
- Yeah.
We were at Felsted so Audrey could make an
ID of a man she saw during the kidnapping.
- I don't get it. Why?
- The kidnapping was just a cover.
The terrorists' objective
is to gain control of power plants.
The man that Audrey saw is our only lead.
- I thought you weren't in the field any more.
- I'm not.
The secretary's my responsibility.
I got caught up in it.
Listen to me.
I don't want to get caught up in it.
So you do whatever you need to do
at my place. I'm staying out of it, all right?
Understood.
Today continues to be a challenge
to the strength of the American spirit.
We have a condition in six cities
across the United States
in which nuclear power facilities
may become unstable.
While we work to regain control
over these facilities,
I am also asking our National Guard
to assist local authorities
to effect an immediate evacuation
of those six cities.
This evacuation is only being issued
for all persons living or working within...
The president didn't mention
that there isn't time for complete evacuation.
If those reactors melt down,
there'll be at least 50,000 dead per city.
We still have time
to find a way to prevent that.
I can tell you now, Erin, the chances
of doing that from here are very low.
We have to find the people
who have the override device.
What about the hospitals north of there?
All right. Keep checking.
- I called Dina's sister. There's no answer.
- I'll take care of it.
- You and Ravi check the station again.
- OK.
The Americans have been able
to shut down most of the reactors.
- How many are under our control?
- Six.
More than enough to break their will.
I'll have to manage the override personally.
Make sure those six melt down on schedule.
- Is there anything I can do?
- Yes.
Take care of your mess.
Don't worry, Marwan.
I give you my word.
My wife and son will be dead
by the end of this day.
- We have to get you to a hospital.
- No.
Your father knows I've been shot.
He'll be looking for us in all the hospitals.
We're going to have to take a chance.
You're hurt.
- I'll be OK.
- No, you won't.
You need to get to a doctor.
I'm not afraid of Father.
You should be.
He tried to kill me,
and then he did this to you.
He is not my father any more.
Mom, please.
All right. Drop me off at an emergency room,
but then you have to drive away.
No. Whatever happens,
we're staying together.
I'm running a filter for Driscoll.
Could you baby-sit it?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
-  Yes?
- I couldn't take your call. I was in a meeting.
- Bauer and Audrey Raines are alive.
- My information was accurate.
Yes. Their location was correct,
but they survived the attack.
- Are they headed back to CTU?
- I haven't heard anything.
- Bauer didn't call in?
- Not that I'm aware of.
That doesn't make sense.
It makes perfect sense.
He knows there's been a breach
and he's told someone. I gotta get out.
No. You have to stay in
until we take care of Bauer and the woman.
What about me?
I won't spend the rest of my life in jail.
You'll be taken care of.
You know that. Now, go.
There you are.
- What?
- Division's waiting for those projections.
- They're ready to be sent.
- Then send them.
Yeah?
Sir, your assistant Scott Borman just arrived.
Should I send him in?
Thanks.
Mr Secretary,
it's good to see you safe and sound, sir.
Thanks, Scott. Sit down.
- Is there a problem, sir?
- There's a big problem.
Someone inside CTU is leaking information
to someone on the outside.
- What do you need me to do?
- I need you to go to Erin Driscoll.
Tell her that Jack Bauer
is no longer at Felsted Security
and that he's watching surveillance videos
at the old CTU substation in Torrance.
- Anything about when Jack will call?
- When they identify the man Audrey saw.
I take it Jack and Audrey
are nowhere near the substation?
Right. We're trying to flush out the mole.
Then you'll need me to put a DOD Comsat
envelope around this place.
If anyone sends out a communication
containing the information you planted,
that's the spy.
- Yes, sir.
- Let's go.
Watch your step,
the dog next door likes our yard.
Well, here we are. Home, sweet home.
Just stay here.
- Oh, God! Who the hell are you?
- Jack, it's OK.
- This is my friend, Jen.
- Tell him to play with his guns outside.
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
I'm sorry.
- I thought you were working.
- I'm going in late.
This is Jack and his friend Audrey.
This is Jen.
Hi.
I saw you on TV today. You're the daughter
of the secretary of defense.
You and your old man
were kidnapped this morning.
- Yeah.
- What's going on?
- I'm helping them out.
- Could you be more specific?
We need to use Tony's computer.
What, they don't have computers
where you work?
Listen, we have a situation here, all right?
They need to lie low for a little bit.
We can't let anybody know
they're here, all right?
Whatever. I'm leaving, anyway.
- Tony.
- Jen, you can't go anywhere.
- Why not?
- We can't leave till Jack and Audrey take off.
- We can't take a chance.
- What kind of chance? I work at a bar.
- I'm sorry, Jen. We're not gonna be long.
- Stay as long as you want. I have a job.
He doesn't.
Jen, can I talk to you for a second?
Please.
Sorry.
No, she seems real sweet.
Look, we were fighting for our lives
a few minutes ago.
If it hadn't been for Tony,
we'd have been dead.
I've been through a lot today and I'm sure
when this is over, your boss will understand.
And if he doesn't?
I can have him killed.
- Knock yourself out.
- Thank you.
How are you guys making out?
I have to convert this so I can read it,
and then hopefully you can make an ID
from the surveillance video.
- I have some software for that. I'll dig it out.
- Thanks.
You told me about Tony,
but I didn't know Michelle left him.
- Yeah, after he got out of prison.
- I thought he went to prison because of her.
He saved her life
and she paid him back by leaving him?
That's the way Tony sees it too.
It didn't happen exactly like that.
When he got out of prison he was angry. He
couldn't get a job. I don't think he wanted one.
He started drinking.
And he pushed her away.
- What is she doing now?
- She's a deputy director over at Division.
- I hope he can help us.
- If he can, he will.
- Here we go.
- You got it?
Yeah, got it right here.
Thanks.
We're in.
- Did you start the ball rolling with Driscoll?
- Yep. I'm headed to her briefing.
She won't be happy when she knows
we're using her to find the mole.
I'm surprised you felt the need
to keep her in the dark.
As long as there's a leak in CTU,
we keep everyone in the dark.
Make sure you're on line
and your databases are unlocked.
As soon as Jack sends the image, we need to
move as quickly as possible to make this ID.
Why is Jack doing this at the old substation?
There's technical reasons.
I didn't speak with him.
- Who did?
- I did.
He also asked that his whereabouts
be kept strictly internal until he contacts us.
All right. Let's go.
Old CTU substation in Torrance.
I remember this lady.
We saw him around here.
There he is.
- Are you sure that's him?
- Yes.
- I'll route this through the DC office.
-  I was there on Friday.
Tony, she's on the phone.
We can't have her making calls.
Give me the phone.
- I can't go to work, I can't talk on the phone?
- Give me the phone.
- Go to hell!
- Give me the damn phone!
- Fine!
- Go ahead.
- Thanks.
- This is Marcy.
- It's Jack.
I'm sending you the image we need ID'd.
- We're ready to receive.
- OK.
- You're positive this came from her system?
- Yeah.
The voices were digitised, but we were able
to make out the words "CTU substation".
- Where's security?
- On their way.
Thanks, Scott.
Yes, Mr Secretary?
- Erin, there's been a breach in CTU.
- What?
- The information Scott gave you is false.
- What do you mean, false?
Jack and Audrey were ambushed
at Felsted Security. They survived the attack,
but it's clear
that someone in this office gave them up.
With all due respect, sir,
you knew about this and you didn't tell me?
Being left out is not something
you should be concerned about.
I assume you're telling me because
your operation yielded a result.
Yes, it did. Read that.
- Where is she?
- She's about to be taken into custody.
Join me.
- Ms Driscoll, what's going on?
- Go with these men.
- What for?
- You're under arrest, Gavin.
- You've been passing classified information.
- What?
- What are you talking about?
- Take her to holding.
Holding? Ms Driscoll!
What are you doing?
Ms Driscoll, I haven't done anything.
Ms Driscoll, this is a mistake.
What is happening?
Will you tell me what's going on?
I didn't do anything. Please!
Get back to work.
I don't care how you divide up her files. I want
everything off her system and sent to me.
- And enter new pass codes.
- We can't just do this on your authority.
Edgar.
- It's OK.
- But he works for DOD, not CTU.
Well, he's the one that found the mole, right?
And Heller wants him to have joint authority.
Finish up here and get back to station two.
The program you set up for the reactors
is almost finished compiling.
- Can I see this?
- Sure.
What makes you so sure Sarah's the mole?
She sent out encoded information
about Bauer.
She wouldn't compromise
Bauer or the investigation.
That's how she fooled us.
She's the last person you'd expect to do it.
All right. Just give me those files.
It's right here. "2:22pm, message sent.
Old CTU substation in Torrance. "
It doesn't seem weird
that she'd leave it on her system?
- It was encrypted.
- With a Bainbridge algorit
It's so old school it's like saying
"Please decode me".
Let's face it,
Sarah wasn't the sharpest knife in the drawer.
Please, Ms Driscoll. I promise you
there's been some kind of mistake.
How? Your system was isolated, the message
was sent from it while you were there.
Somebody set me up.
It's the only explanation.
Tell me how.
Someone backed into my system,
planted something.
We checked.
None of them were compromised.
Let's stop playing games.
Thousands of lives are at stake. Where
are the people who control the override?
I don't know. That's what I was working on.
- Who did you send the message to?
- I didn't.
Ms Driscoll...
I would never betray our country
or endanger lives. You know that.
Is it the contact who coordinated the attempt
on Jack and Audrey's life at Felsted Security?
- I don't know. It wasn't me.
- I learned my lesson today with Sherek
and I am no longer gonna err
on the side of caution in these interrogations.
Do you get my meaning?
I don't know what to say.
Eric, no!
Please don't do this.
Eric! Ms Driscoll!
- Please stop.
- If you want it to stop,
you tell me
where the Dobson override is and who has it.
I swear I don't know anything.
Wait!
There has got to be an explanation for this.
You've got to give me some time to think.
Talk to me, Sarah. Talk to me.
Ms Driscoll...
I'm not a spy.
I'm not. Please believe me.
Ms Driscoll, please.
- I'm concerned.
- Do you think you can break her in time?
I can break her in time if she's guilty.
According to Scott,
there is no way that this could be a mistake.
I agree it's hard evidence,
but I've known Sarah for eight months
and she doesn't fit the profile.
How do you want to handle it?
I'll watch for a few more minutes,
then I'll go back in.
I'll brief Jack.
Eric, please!
Please!
Eric! Eric, no!
What are you doing?
I'm checking the surveillance
to see who he was talking to.
- Did you find anything?
- No, not yet.
- Anybody want a beer?
- I could use one.
- This is Bauer.
-  We found our mole.
- Who is it?
- Sarah Gavin. Works in comm.
- Is she working alone?
- As far as we know.
I'll call Marcy, tell her the CTU channels
are open. We'll start sharing data.
How's Audrey doing?
She's good. She's resting.
I think now would be a good time
to have her picked up.
We're at 21408, Kipling, North Hollywood.
What's there?
A friend.
I'll send the Secret Service.
Thank you, sir.
Your father's sending someone over
to take you back to CTU.
OK.
Don't you think you've made me
miss enough TV today, Jack?
Why didn't you ever call me?
For what?
I've been there. I could help.
I'm considered a traitor to this country.
My wife left me.
So how are you gonna help me, huh, Jack?
Yeah.
Look...
I owed you for getting me out of prison,
but today I repaid that debt.
To tell you the truth,
all you do is remind me of a past
I'm trying to forget.
So why don't you do me a favour?
Do what you need to do here,
and let's leave it at that.
All right?
Yeah.
How did this happen?
I was working in the yard and backed
into a nail that sticks out of our gate.
Ow.
This looks like a gunshot wound.
I'm afraid it was nothing that exciting, Doctor.
It was my fault.
I was supposed to fix that gate last week.
All right. You're gonna need a tetanus shot.
Then I'll stitch it up.
Thank you, Doctor.
Yeah. I'll be right back.
Go watch him.
- What's going on?
- He said something to the nurse.
Did he make a phone call?
- Not that I could see.
- Did she?
- No.
- Good.
Maybe it wouldn't be so bad
if they called the police.
- The police could protect us from Father.
- It would be bad.
To go to jail for the rest of our lives?
That's what would happen.
Where are we going to go
after we leave here?
If we can get out of the city and stay
somewhere for a couple of days,
I can arrange for us to get out of the country.
- Yeah?
-  Jack, it's Marcy. We got a match.
- Who is it?
- His name is Henry Powell.
- I've posted everything on the secure site.
- Hold on a second.
OK. I got it.
He was a computer consultant
for McLennen-Forster.
Wait a second.
They designed the device
controlling the power plants.
He's not there any more,
but he freelances for them. He's in LA.
- How do you know?
- He's trying to leave the city.
He's scheduled a chopper
to meet him in Van Nuys in 15 minutes.
- I thought air traffic had been grounded.
- It is. He got a special clearance.
- Son of a bitch. Where in Van Nuys?
- The helipad at the Larchmont building.
I want you to ground his flight,
but not until I get there.
- They're here.
- Can you make it in time?
I'm gonna try.
Go get your things. We've got to go.
- Davis, Secret Service.
- Jack Bauer.
- Take Audrey back to CTU.
- Those are our orders.
- OK. You got a car for me?
- It's right over there.
Thank you. Audrey, they're ready.
This is Agent Davis.
He's gonna take care of you.
- Be careful.
- I will. You too.
- CTU.
- It's Jack. Let me speak to Erin Driscoll.
Right away.
I just got the file on Henry Powell.
I'm going through it now.
He's leaving the city.
I have to get to Van Nuys.
- You want air backup?
- No. I want a low profile.
- I don't want to spook him.
- A ground package is gonna be 30 minutes.
- That's too long.
- When is his flight due to take off?
- Less than 15 minutes.
- What do you want to do?
He's most likely on his own.
I'll have to handle this myself.
- All right. I'll send a team anyway.
- I'll be in touch.
- What will you handle by yourself?
- It's covered.
It would be pretty stupid of me to let you die
after I risked my life trying to save you.
Could you use my help?
- Yeah.
- All right. Let's go.
- Curtis.
- Yeah, Edgar?
- Has Sarah confessed to anything?
- No.
- What are they doing to her?
- Don't worry about it. Just get back to work.
Curtis, what did Edgar want?
- Why?
- Let him know we need his full attention.
Get back to your station.
What's that?
Just something to numb the arm
so that I can close the wound.
OK.
I really wish you'd let me admit you.
This wound is serious.
There's a chance of an infection here.
No, Doctor, please.
Do whatever you can and we'll leave.
- Behrooz, where are you going?
- I'll be right back, Mom.
- The police are here.
- Did you call them?
- This is a gunshot wound.
- I told you it wasn't.
- Then why are you acting so strangely?
- Let's go.
You shouldn't leave! You need treatment!
Susan! Susan!
Wait.
Let's go.
Come on. Come on.
Marianne?
What is it?
You asked me
to bump up your security clearance.
I was a little busy with the override,
but I finally got it for you.
Great. Thanks.
What?
You'll need to pick a password.
I set up the screen on server five.
There you go. Use the same password
as the one that unlocks your system files.
OK.
Edgar.
- Why do you keep looking at me?
- I don't.
Let's go outside. I want to talk to you.
I don't want to talk to you.
I have a lot of work to do.
It is getting incredibly tedious, Edgar,
to have to remind you repeatedly that I could
step into Driscoll's office and have you fired.
- Curtis. I need to talk to you.
- What is it?
- Walk with me to Driscoll's office.
- Walk with you?
Please, Curtis.
Let's go.
If Sarah is guilty, we shouldn't need...
- Sorry to interrupt.
- What is it?
- You got the wrong one. Sarah's not guilty.
- How do you know?
I just sneaked into Marianne's system. She
used Sarah's to communicate outside of CTU.
Sarah's station was isolated from the subnet.
- She didn't use it.
- How did she do it?
- She use a plain old AC power line.
- What?
That's the last place anybody would
ever look. Plus it has plenty of bandwidth.
Where is she?
She's trying to leave the building.
Lock down the exits!
There she goes!
She's heading out the southwest side door.
Side door.
You're under arrest.
Examine the contents.
Impound the car, strip and search it.
I got her.
- Mr Powell?
- Yeah, let's go.
- We can't.
- What?
- The flight's been grounded.
- McLennen-Forster has special ordinance.
- I know, but the order was superseded.
- By who?
The Department of Defense.
- You're going to fly me out of here.
- Please. Sir!
Now! Get in.
- All right. Where are we going?
- Just get us in the air and fly east.
There it is.
Do not take off!
- Do not take off!
- Get us in the air! Go! Go!
- Shut it down!
I said now!
Come on! Move! Hurry up!
Drop the weapon now! Now!
Step out! Get down! Now!
Get out of the helicopter. Move! Move!
Let me see your hands! Now!
Get up!
Move!
Where are you taking me?
I haven't done anything.
Put your hands on the roof of the truck.
- The people I know, they'll pay you.
- Shut up!
I got his cellphone! Bring me the bag!
Put your hands behind your back.
Who are you guys? Police? FBI?
- Actually, I'm currently unemployed.
- I'll make it worth your while.
- Put him in the back.
- Come on.
He's dead, Jack.
Dammit!
Visiontext Subtitles: Sarah Johnston
ENGLISH SDH