Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net
You didn'tjust betray me,
you betrayed your country.
I swear to you, I didn't know.
The Russians know about the component,
and they're threatening military action
if we don't get it back.
You're gonna go back to your boyfriend,
make him believe
that we have the component back.
When you go back to Mr Bishop, you will find
a way to excuse yourself from the room,
to allow him time to access your PDA.
If you can feed all this convincingly to Bishop
he will relay it to his Russian contact.
President Suvarov will call off
his threat of military action.
(Miller) I'm always worried
the next crisis is around the corner.
(Bishop) I know how
to take your mind off of it.
Head east 153 metres.
That will put you directly beneath CTU.
This is Nadia. Code Red is confirmed.
Lock this place down.
Everyone on the floor!
- Are you all right?
- Yes. Jack, what do they want with Josh?
- (Jack) What do you mean?
- (Marilyn) They came here to get him.
- I'm not leaving you.
- We're gonna be following you.
Just go. Keep going.
- Put your weapon down on the ground now!
- I'm putting it down.
- The boy's escaped.
- Get the boy back.
I don't care what you have to do!
I'm going to give you ten seconds.
If you don't show yourself by the time
I've finished counting, she dies.
The operation was successful.
My men have your grandson.
Call me when I can talk to the boy.
Finished repairing the sub-circuit board?
Almost. I'll return it
when you bring me my grandson.
Who is in command?
I am.
Milo Pressman.
I'm acting director of CTU.
Cheng, I'm sending the boy to you now.
(Marilyn) What?
Get him into the tunnel, now.
Josh! Josh, no! Josh!
(Jack) Marilyn!
- What do you want with him?
- (Jack) Marilyn. Marilyn!
Help, please! Please!
They're taking my child! Please!
Leave her alone.
- He's just a boy. He didn't do anything!
- Shut up!
Wait! Please. Please.
I can help you calm her down.
Please, let me just help you.
(Marilyn sobs)
Get on your feet.
- Keep her quiet.
- Thank you.
Marilyn.
All of you, listen to me. Pay attention.
We're moving you to a secure room,
then we will leave.
Do what I tell you to do
and no one will be hurt.
Come on.
Let's go.
We're moving you in two groups.
- Group one, on your feet.
- (man) Get up.
- What are they doing?
- They got what they want.
Now they wanna stop us from following them.
We're gonna try and get Josh back.
I need you to be at the front of our group.
You need to be at the front.
Group two, on your feet.
(Jack) OK, stand up.
Go.
Nadia.
If they lock us in the holding room, we'll lose
our chance to get that component back.
- So we have to do something now.
- Yeah. But you need to understand,
this is a long shot at best - there's a good
chance we won't make it through this.
I understand.
Stay close to me. As soon as I make
my move, take the first man on the left.
- What are you guys talking about?
- Chloe, keep going.
Morris, stay alert.
(shouts in Chinese)
- Are you all right?
- Yeah.
Teams B and C, are the hostages secure?
(man over radio) Copy. All hostages secure.
Cheng's men attacked us.
They were after my nephew.
It has something to do with the component -
otherwise, why would they take the risk?
I need a tactical setup and comm,
I'm ready to go.
But you're still under arrest.
I know the schematics of this building
better than anyone. I can find them.
- OK. I'll release you, but Doyle's in command.
- Fine.
- Get him whatever he needs.
- (agent) Yes, ma'am.
How many casualties did you sustain?
One. Milo Pressman.
- Are you OK?
- No.
- I'm set. We need to go.
- Use my cell until comm's up.
You did great.
(Doyle) We're on the move. Let's go.
That was really brave.
We need to restore comm and satellite.
There may be more server capacity
in data storage.
Try it.
Keep going.
- Climb up.
- All right.
- Hello, Josh.
- Who are you?
- Start loading. We're moving out.
- What do you want?
(speaks Chinese)
- (Phillip) What took you so long?
- I have the boy with me.
Put him on the phone.
Your grandfather wants to speak with you.
- My grandfather?
- Yes.
Take the phone.
Grandpa?
Hello, Joshua.
Look, I'm sorry -
I know you've been through a lot.
"I'm sorry"? A few hours ago you pointed
a gun at my head and said you'd kill me.
- I never would have hurt you.
- I heard you say it!
I had to make it sound convincing, to you
and to Jack, or I wouldn't have gotten away.
But I wouldn't hurt you.
Not for anything.
- This way.
- What do you want from me?
- To protect you.
- From what?
From your father's mistakes.
If you stay here, they'll never let you
forget what your father did.
I'm taking you away from this ungrateful
country - someplace we can both start over.
- Where?
- China.
Within a decade, they will have
surpassed this country in every possible way.
And we can be part of it.
I am going to give you the future
I promised you when you were born.
I don't know what you're talking about.
No... I didn't think you would.
But you will.
I'll explain everything when I see you.
Right now, all I need
is for you to keep an open mind.
Let's go.
Wait. I don't wanna be with my grandpa.
- I'm afraid of him.
- He's a visionary.
You should be grateful for the opportunity.
I don't wanna be with him, though!
(shouts order in Chinese)
(shouting in Chinese)
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
Cheng's using the boy as a shield.
Hold your fire. Hold your fire!
Move! Move!
I've got two hostiles at the SUV.
Cover me now.
(speaks Chinese)
Go, go, go, go, go!
I got one hostile down.
I'm moving towards the roof.
(Doyle over radio) Copy that, Jack.
Go, go. Go.
(speaks Chinese)
Josh!
Cheng, it's over!
Put your weapon down. Now!
Put it down!
Where is the boy?
Tell me where the boy is and I won't kill you.
- Help!
- Josh!
- Josh?
Help!
(Jack) Hold on.
Josh... you need to grab my arm.
Do it now. Now!
Now!
You OK?
Mike, I'm on the roof.
I lost Cheng, but I've got Josh.
I need to secure him.
On our way up now. We're setting up
a perimeter around the building.
Josh, the man that had you,
his name is Cheng.
Did he explain why he tried to take you?
No, but he made me
talk on the phone with Grandpa.
- He did?
- Yeah.
- You talked to your grandfather?
- What'd he say?
- He said that he loved me,
that he wanted to take me to China,
and that I was his legacy.
I think he's out of his mind.
Josh, listen to me. I need your help.
Was there anything you heard that could
help us figure out where your grandfather is?
- No.
- Josh, think.
- I don't know. I'm sorry.
- Josh, hey.
It's all right.
It's all right. Come on,
let's get you back to your mom.
Jack! CTU has a team on the way
to secure the area.
Let them know
my father's still involved in this.
- He's involved with the Chinese? Why?
- I don't know.
I'll ask him when I find him.
(knock on door)
- Sir?
- Come in, Karen.
I just got off the phone with the Pentagon.
The latest intel indicates
the Russians are moving two mechanised
divisions into the Central Asian theatre.
- Within striking distance of our base?
- Yes. Troops are at the highest level of alert.
Tom Lennox was supposed
to be on the call with me.
I couldn't find him
or get him on the telephone.
Is there something that I should know about?
Tom is out in the field,
running a classified operation.
He figured out who the leak was.
- Who?
- Lisa Miller.
Lisa Miller is spying for the Russians?
No.
The man Lisa's romantically involved with is.
For the last year, this man, Mark Bishop, has
been passing Lisa's emails to the Russians -
along with other things
that she told him in confidence.
And that's how the Russians knew
the Chinese had the component?
- Does Lisa know?
- She does now.
Tom sent her back to this man Bishop
with a cover story and falsified emails
that we hope will convince the Russians
that we destroyed the circuit board
before the Chinese could get it
out of the country. With any luck,
Bishop will forward those emails
to the Russians and they'll back off,
and we'll have bought time to actually retrieve
the component from the Chinese.
Well, I hope that works, sir.
Karen?
Sit down.
You're wondering
why you were kept out of the loop.
It had nothing to do with you,
and everything to do with me.
I... I don't understand.
At the same time Lisa was with Bishop,
she and I were...
in a relationship as well.
Needless to say...
I am ashamed.
Well, sir... I think you're being
a little hard on yourself.
You and Lisa were both single.
There was no way you could know
what she was doing behind your back.
It's a question ofjudgment. I trusted her.
And unless Tom's plan succeeds,
that mistake will bring us to war.
(gasps of pleasure)
And finally, we're done. There we go.
You OK?
I'm great. That was great.
It felt like you were somewhere else.
I'm just tired.
It's been a long day.
I'll be right back.
Do you think he's just concerned,
or suspicious?
I don't know. But she is leaving him alone
with the PDA - this could be it.
Making his move. He's making his move.
That must be the device he's using
to forward the emails to the Russians.
Gentlemen, he is taking the bait.
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on.
Send these emails.
(agent) He's not going to, sir.
He's putting her PDA away.
Sweetheart, I'm just gonna pour myself
a glass of wine. You want something?
Sure. I'll have what you're having.
No.
I don't think it's just that you're tired.
What are you talking about?
The way you were in bed -
something's wrong.
- We may have a problem here.
- Everything's fine.
Then why can't you look me in the eye?
You're making me nervous,
staring at me like that.
Can we stop talking about this?
- I know you. You don't get nervous.
- You're hurting me.
- What's going on?
- Nothing!
- You're lying!
- I'm not!
Tell me!
This is not good.
All right, I'll tell you what's going on.
What's going on...
- Get in there quick!
...is you're a lying son of a bitch!
I put myself on the line for you!
All you were doing was whoring yourself
to the Russians, stealing my emails...
- Do you realise what you've done?
- Bitch!
They'll charge me with treason -
I'll be put in jail!
Agh!
(gasps)
Who knows about me and the Russians?
Who knows?
Freeze! Get him off her.
Put Mr Bishop in the bedroom.
(agent) She's got a pulse.
It's faint, but she's breathing.
Let's get an ambulance here fast.
Mr Bishop, I guess you already familiarised
yourself with the White House staff.
May I have a moment alone
with the prisoner?
We have incontrovertible evidence
you were spying for the Russians.
We have recordings of you on the phone
with the agent running you,
and now, of course, we've got this.
Do I have your attention?
All right. So here it is.
You are going to
upload the emails on Ms Miller's PDA
to your Russian employers.
Additionally,
you are going to call your handler
and back up the story these emails tell -
namely that our country destroyed the
circuit board before it fell into Chinese hands.
Now, if you comply,
we'll push for leniency in your sentencing.
If you do not,
I can all but guarantee you the death penalty.
(phone rings)
- What is it, Cheng?
- I lost the boy.
- Who has him?
- CTU and your son.
This is totally unacceptable. The boy
was my price for repairing the circuit board.
I lost many men
trying to give you your price, Mr Bauer.
I really don't give a damn
about your operational incapacities.
- Our arrangement is over.
- It cannot be over. You have our component.
You failed to hold up your end of the deal.
The circuit board is no longer yours.
Repair the circuit board and return it to us,
or there'll be serious consequences!
You listen to me. I'm not afraid of you, Cheng.
And the next time you threaten me, the
consequences will be serious - but not for me.
(speaks Chinese)
- Any luck?
- No.
Have our teams located Cheng
or the sub-circuit board?
- Nothing yet.
- What's the status on our satellite?
We rerouted circuits
through an undamaged subsystem.
- The grid should be back up in ten minutes.
- Try to make it five.
- Nadia Yassir?
- Yeah. Can I help you?
My name is Ben Kram.
I'm from Division.
You should have received a memo
alerting you of my arrival.
- Our systems are still down.
- That's exactly why I'm here.
I've been authorised to compile
an assessment of your security breach.
We're right in the middle
of a recovery operation, and it's 3am -
this isn't the best time
to be questioning my people.
Frankly, I don't particularly care
what you think.
- Excuse me?
- This represents a serious breach in security.
One that resulted in
the loss of a number of CTU personnel.
Obviously mistakes were made,
errors in judgment -
like my accepting
Bill Buchanan's recommendation
to leave someone with
your limited experience in charge.
So, can I count on
your full cooperation or not?
- I never said otherwise.
- Super.
I'll need a full staff roster
and access to all departments,
plus some kind of a station
to set up my investigation.
You can work out of
that conference room there.
Thank you.
- (man) Operations.
- Nadia Yassir.
There is a group from Division here
in conference room B.
- Please give them whatever they need.
- Yes, ma'am. We'll take care of it.
- Nadia.
- Yeah, Morris?
This may not be my place, but don't let
those buggers from Division get to you.
- You're not responsible for what happened.
- Of course I am. It happened on my watch.
There's nothing you could have done.
Do not let them hang you out to dry.
People are dead.
Milo is dead because of me.
That's ridiculous.
There's nothing anyone could have done.
No, I... I could have stood up.
I could have said something.
There was no time. Milo jumped in.
There was time.
I just hesitated.
- I was just...
- You were just afraid?
Yeah, I have a bit of experience with that.
I'm not one to advise on how to handle
self-recrimination, but I know this -
Milo was a brave man.
He never would have sacrificed himself
if he knew you'd allow others
to lay his death at your feet.
He'd want you to stay strong,
stay in charge.
- (intercom beeps)
- (Melinda) Sir, Tom Lennox is on the line.
Thanks.
Tom. I'm with Karen.
That information we planted for the Russians,
that has been sent on to Bishop's contact.
Good. Do you think
it's made its way to Suvarov yet?
I'm confident it has. But I do think a call to
the Russian president, giving him the news,
that might well strengthen
the credibility of our story.
I agree.
- Tom, thanks.
- Sir, there is one other thing.
- What's that?
- We had some complications, and, uh...
Lisa was injured in the operation.
- How badly?
- She had a loss of oxygen to the brain.
We won't know
till she regains consciousness.
- She is on her way to hospital.
- How the hell did this happen?
She attacked Bishop. Before we could even
get in there, he almost strangled her to death.
And what were you doing during all this?
Where was Secret Service?
Sir, we did everything we could.
Itjust happened too fast.
All right, thank you, Tom.
All right. I'll be back there shortly.
I'm so sorry, sir.
I know that, despite her betrayal,
you still have feelings for Lisa.
Unfortunately, we do have
a pressing matter to address.
(sighs)
- Suvarov.
- We've got to call him immediately,
tell him that the Chinese no longer have the
component, and that it has been destroyed.
- Set it up in the TelePresence suite.
- Right away, sir.
We're gonna get you back
to your mom soon, OK? Just sit here.
I'll be right back.
(dials phone)
- (man) Operations.
- This is Jack. Patch me through to Marilyn.
We searched the area and Cheng's vehicles -
no sub-circuit board.
- What about aerial surveillance?
- Nothing. We just now got satellite back.
- It looks like Cheng got out.
- Get your men. We'll go back to CTU.
- (Marilyn) Hello?
- It's me.
- Did they tell you Josh was safe?
- That's all they'll say. When can I see him?
We should be back at CTU in a few minutes.
Marilyn, the Chinese
were doing this for my father.
- They were trying to get Josh to him.
- You sure?
- Yeah. Josh spoke to him.
- What did he tell Josh?
He said he wanted to take him back to China,
that Josh was his legacy.
That's it? That's all he said?
Yeah.
- Can I talk to him?
- Of course. Hold on one second.
Hey, it's your mom.
- Mom.
- Hey!
Hey. Are you OK? Did they hurt you?
No. I'm all right.
I don't know what I would do if I lost you.
Mom...
Uncle Jack, he saved my life.
I know.
I love you so much.
I love you, too, Mom.
I'll see you soon, all right?
OK, honey.
You OK?
Come on. We need to go.
Sir, President Suvarov is standing by for you.
Whenever you're ready.
Let's do this.
President Suvarov, you have a secure
conference with Vice President Daniels.
Mr President,
I have some good news to share with you.
What is this good news, Mr Vice President?
We were successful
in taking out the Chinese agents
attempting to smuggle
the FB-sub-circuit board out of the country.
You have the component
back in your possession?
No, sir.
The sub-circuit board was destroyed
when we attacked the Chinese.
I see. I assume you have proof of this.
Yes, we do.
In addition to fragments
from the destroyed component,
I'll give you whatever images
or documentation you need
to assure you
that this threat's been neutralised.
Do you mean the same documentation
you planted with one of my agents?
- Excuse me?
- The same images
you coerced him into sending to my people
of a strike that accomplished nothing
but destroying an empty building?
Yes, I know you exposed
one of my operatives.
I had him under surveillance, which is how
I know about your raid on his apartment.
- Mr President...
- If the Chinese agent
in possession of the sub-circuit board
is allowed to transfer it to his government,
the entire Russian defence system
will be compromised.
I told you I would hold you
and your government responsible.
I will not tolerate any threats
from you, Mr President.
We're doing everything in our power to
ensure the component doesn't reach China.
I have already given you
ample time to recover it.
Now I am feeling less generous.
If you do not deliver concrete
and irrefutable proof to our embassy
that you have recovered or destroyed
this component within two hours,
I will have no choice but to extend
my country's forward perimeter,
to compensate
for our defensive vulnerabilities.
You are talking about attacking
one of our military bases,
and I would urge you
to consider the consequences of that.
We have just as many troops in that area,
and allies will not look kindly upon
any unprovoked aggression on my country.
You and I both know it will not be unprovoked.
This is a matter of survival for us.
It is in both our interests
that you get that component back.
You have two hours.
- It was all for nothing.
- Excuse me, sir?
This ruse, it bought us nothing.
We're about to go to war
over a piece of circuitry.
The agenda for the briefing with the military.
- When did they start?
- A few minutes ago, in the Oval Office.
- I'll play catch-up.
- (phone rings)
Tom Lennox.
Who?
All right, put him through.
The Russians are blaming us for allowing
the theft, and are preparing to retaliate.
Our efforts to reacquire
the component have failed,
so we have no choice
but to defend ourselves,
and to make provisions for the escalation of
this conflict beyond the Central Asian theatre.
(door opens)
- Excuse me, Mr Vice President.
- Glad you could make it.
General Crane was about to run
some response scenarios.
Before we do that, sir, I need
a moment alone with you and Karen.
Excuse us, ladies and gentlemen.
Phillip Bauer calling for you
on a scrambled line.
- What does he want?
- Dunno. But he's in league with the Chinese.
- I think we need to hear him out.
- Put him on speaker.
- Mr Bauer.
- Thank you for taking my call.
- What's this about?
- I think you know what this is about.
Tell me anyway,
so there's no miscommunication.
I want my grandson.
And I want clear passage
to the country of my choice.
Give me that,
and I'll give you the FB-sub-circuit board.
You're working with the Chinese.
I was.
They had their chance, they blew it.
How do I know
you even have this component?
Serial number: 3-P-T-L-3.
Check it against any records you have.
- (Lennox) Yeah, there it is, sir.
- You realise what you're asking?
I'm offering you the opportunity of avoiding
a conflict this country does not want.
A war this country cannot afford.
Not after what's happened today.
I'll send my instructions
on an encrypted data stream.
- Mr Bauer?
- (hangs up)
Sir, you are not seriously considering this?
Phillip Bauer is a federal fugitive,
complicit in selling
nuclear weapons to terrorists.
- I know what crimes he's committed.
- Then how can you negotiate with him?
- Cos maybe we can't afford not to.
- You'd trade the life of an innocent boy?
It'd be the lives of a lot more men
if we go to war with Russia.
And you think Phillip Bauer
is somebody that we can trust?
The man is a sociopath!
Tom?
He is a sociopath. She's right about that.
But given the stakes,
this is a risk worth taking, sir.
None of this makes sense.
Suvarov wouldn't risk military engagement,
even for this piece of technology.
- Unless he's being squeezed.
- Who by? His cabinet?
No. The military.
Gredenko was not the only
anti-American general in the Soviet regime.
Yes, some of them are still in power,
and Suvarov does rely on them.
You think these generals are just
looking for an excuse to pull the trigger.
Certainly sounds plausible, sir.
Well, if that is the case,
then we have no choice.
We have to recover that stolen circuit board.
Get me CTU.
As soon as we get back to CTU, you and your
mother will be transported to a safe location.
- How long will we be there?
- Until we find your grandfather.
When you find him,
what are you gonna do to him?
Josh, I don't want you worrying about this.
He will never threaten you
or your mother again.
Agent Bauer. It's a call for you. It's urgent.
Get in the car. I'll be right there.
- You need to come with me.
- What do you mean?
Come now!
- Uncle Jack!
- Agent Doyle!
Orders, Jack. Go back to CTU.
The boy stays with me!
Get outta my way!
- (agent) Hold him back!
- What are you doing?
- Uncle Jack!
- Take him to CTU.
- (agent) Hold him back. Restrain him.
Josh!
(inaudible)
Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net