This is Air Force One,
declaring an emergency.
We're not gonna make it.
I have to put it down.
Chloe, what's happening?
-  Air Force One, you copy?
Chloe?
Air Force One is down.
This may be him.
It's the president.
He's still alive. I repeat, the president is alive.
Marwan has to be in a 50 mile radius...
- There's a higher priority than Marwan.
- What?
- Recovering the nuclear football.
Didn't it go with Air Force One?
The missile inflicted enough damage
that it left debris.
A lot was sucked out,
including the football.
That case contains the codes and locations
of our entire nuclear arsenal.
- What's the location of the football?
- 40 miles northeast of here, in the desert.
Air Support, the football is in the lead Jeep,
headed north. Take it out.
I've got the football.
Three hostiles down, one escaped.
I'm not positive, but I think it was Marwan.
There are pages missing.
Tell me the contents of the pages.
It's the section which contains
warhead locations and activation codes.
If they get ahold
of a warhead and a matching code,
we will not be able to stop them.
Mr Vice President, President Keeler is alive,
but he's in critical condition.
Sir, I recommend you invoke the 25th
Amendment and take control of things.
- You're worried about him.
- I am. He seems unsure of himself.
I solemnly swear that I will faithfully execute
the office of the president.
Preserve, protect and defend
the constitution of the United States.
Mr President.
I've just received a phone call from CTU.
Part of the nuclear football
has fallen into the hands of terrorists.
Vice President Logan has been sworn in.
He is now President of the United States.
His office called.
They want an update in 15 minutes.
We're working on several protocols.
What is he gonna want to focus on?
How a Stealth fighter was stolen
from one of our air bases.
More to the point, how it took down
Air Force One with one of our missiles.
- Is he briefed on Marwan?
He knows he's behind today,
but he's gonna want specifics on the football.
Where are we on that?
Jack's at the debris field.
- He's trying to reconstruct the stolen chapter.
- How?
He's working with Fred Laughton
from the DOD.
- He wrote it, he'll know what's missing.
Good.
- Who's going to run point on this update?
- You and Tony.
All right, we don't have a lot of time,
so fast-track this.
Double source all intel
through Homeland Security and CIA.
Skip the usual request procedures.
Tie in to their data directly.
- Yes?
-  I've got Bauer on the line.
Put him through.
Go ahead.
- Are you still in briefing?
- Yes, on speaker. What have you found?
Laughton and I finished a reconstruction.
We're getting that to you.
Jack, it's Bill Buchanan.
Summarise our exposure.
What information does Marwan
have in his possession?
The location of our domestic nuclear arsenal.
The inventory's in the thousands.
Many weapons are in transit
as part of standard operations.
Why can't DOD secure these weapons?
A number are between checkpoints. It'd take
over an hour to account for all of them.
Listen, we've gotta remember,
Marwan only needs one.
All right. We'll get on this.
Get back here as soon as you can
and help Audrey liaise with DOD.
We need to account for every single weapon.
I'm on my way.
The coordinates for the third one are:
Latitude 37 degrees, 14 minutes,
longitude, 115 degrees,
21 minutes.
There it is. Jefferson City, Iowa.
- When is the warhead due to arrive?
- 7am local time. Five hours from now.
That puts it somewhere 200 miles east.
It's still in Illinois.
We can intercept it anywhere
from this point to here.
All right. Let's put our people in place.
Warheads in transit because of shift-and-hide
operations pose the biggest problem.
We can verify military traffic in coastal areas
from here. Find what DOD has in the Midwest.
Yeah, that's already underway. Audrey
said she should have it in a few minutes.
Look, Tony...
- Am I interrupting something?
- No, Chloe. What is it?
- Are you logged on?
- Yeah.
Look. 15 minutes ago, the credit card of Eric
Murphy was used at Western Gas in Torrance.
- Who's Eric Murphy?
- His real name is Yosik Khatami.
- He's affiliated with Marwan.
- How do we know that?
Our watch list. We put out a net asking
for anybody connected to Habib Marwan.
- We didn't expect any hits so soon.
- Why was he so careless?
Maybe he wasn't. Maybe it's a decoy.
It wouldn't be much of a decoy
because we don't know where he is.
- This was a mistake.
- Did the gas station have a camera?
- Yes. He's driving a Lexus.
Are we on the satellite?
Yes, we're monitoring them now.
If this guy's still on the road, we'll find him.
- Who do we have in the area to run point?
- Curtis left Division. He's headed here.
Divert him. Have Field Ops meet him there.
All right.
- Audrey.
- It's me.
- Hey. Are you on your way back here?
- Yeah. How much weaponry's accounted for?
72 per cent. We have problems
getting confirmations from the Midwest.
- Why?
- There were convoys shipping weapons
to be dismantled
under the arms reduction treaty.
A lot were rerouted
after the bombing this morning.
Use local channels. Weapon transports
check in with regional substations.
- Just call them directly.
- All right. I'll do that.
How are you holding up?
I'm OK.
What have the doctors told you about Paul?
They're having a hard time
keeping him stable.
Just hang in there. He'll fight through it.
Yeah.
- Tell Michelle I'll be there in 20 minutes.
- All right, will do. Bye.
- Yes?
- Marwan, it's... it's me.
- Is everything all right?
- No.
No, it's not. I...
I made a stupid mistake.
- They're gonna find me.
- What happened?
I stopped to get gas. While I was driving
away, I realised I used the wrong credit card -
the one with the name Murphy.
The one you gave me.
I told you to get rid of that one.
I was in a hurry, Habib. I had to make
arrangements for delivery of the warhead.
When that gets flagged,
they'll search the highways.
- I know. I'm not on the highway any more.
- Where are you?
Inglewood. I'm on my way to Prado's now.
You're closer to the marina.
Go straight there, I'll have him meet you.
Prado will help you get out of the country.
Thank you, Habib. Thank you.
Mr President, it may be precipitous
moving to the bunker now.
Working from the Oval Office
might exhibit a greater sense of confidence
in our abilities to handle this crisis.
The purpose of the bunker
is to protect the president, is it not?
- Yes, sir.
- Well...
I feel it is always wiser
to take the prudent course.
Will I be able to function at 100 per cent here?
- Absolutely, Mr President.
- What protection does this bunker afford?
Total.
You're 200 feet below the surface.
If the White House suffers a direct hit,
everyone would be safe,
as would communication infrastructure
to the rest of the country.
Let's hope that's not needed.
Yes?
- Mr Buchanan is on the line. He's asked...
Mr President,
Bill Buchanan from CTU is on the line.
Hello, Bill. What do you have for me?
I'm here with Michelle Dessler,
director of CTU Los Angeles,
and Tony Almeida, heading tactical.
Let's get started.
Have all of our armaments
referenced in the red chapter been secured?
Not completely, Mr President,
but we're working with DOD on it.
- What else?
- The man who choreographed today's events,
Habib Marwan, is at large. Most likely,
he is in possession of the red chapter.
- What are we doing?
We picked up a thread.
We have a location where one of Marwan's
associates was detected 20 minutes ago.
That sounds promising. What else?
We're sifting through intel, hoping
to put together a pursuit scenario soon.
So you're pretty confident you'll be able
to catch this terrorist, this Habib Marwan,
- before he strikes again?
-  It's not an exact science, sir.
All we can do is maximise
the probability for success.
- There are no guarantees.
- Of course, I understand that.
We need to get control of the situation.
I can't govern from here indefinitely,
but I'm not going until it's safe.
Sir.
Their time is better spent
working up what they have.
I recommend we let them get back to it.
OK, Bill.
Call us when you have
something more concrete.
Yes, sir.
All right. Let's get back to work.
Wait a second. Does anybody else
feel uneasy about what we just heard here?
In what way?
Logan's supposed to be the man who speaks
to this country and exudes confidence,
not fear.
Air Force One was just attacked,
Keeler's in critical condition.
- Logan was just sworn in. Give him time.
- We don't have time.
We've got Khatami, heading toward the coast.
We have him on satellite.
Link this up to Curtis.
I want him running point.
Tell Curtis to remain discreet. I wanna know
what Khatami's doing before we take him.
Michelle.
I was out of line a couple of hours ago
about you and Bill.
It's your life,
and I've got no right to judge you.
I appreciate that.
Whatever tension there is between us,
I want to apologise for my part in it.
I'd like it if we could just let it go
so we could do our jobs.
Leave the past in the past, and move on.
Sounds good.
All right.
- Thank you.
- Yes, sir.
Curtis is about to arrive at the marina.
- Set up a satellite, also an audio link.
- I'll take care of it.
Thanks.
- You want me to run point?
No, Bill and I will do that,
but I want you in on this.
- To do what?
- I'd like your tactical input.
Fine. I'll have Edgar transfer
everything over to the situation room.
Edgar.
I get the feeling Tony's not entirely
comfortable with the configuration today.
We haven't seen each other for a long time.
It's uncomfortable.
The difference is you seem to be able
to stay on point. I'm not so sure about him.
I am. He'll be fine.
- He's alone.
- What's he doing?
Looks like a meet. He's waiting for someone.
- Is the marine unit in place?
- They're behind the jetty.
The man he's meeting's just arrived.
He's walking towards him.
- Is it Marwan?
- I can't tell.
Remember, Curtis, we need them both alive.
I copy.
All right, teams, I'll close up for the pier.
Keep them contained, but do not shoot to kill.
Repeat, do not shoot to kill.
Dammit! Teams, respond. Who is that?
This is McKellan.
It looks like a private patrol.
All right, hold your positions.
Yosik.
Prado. You're late.
I've been standing here waiting for you.
I'm here now. Let's go.
- Come on. What are we waiting for?
- Wait.
- What's the matter?
- Someone's here.
It's Miller. U-base is clear.
It's OK. It's just harbour security.
No, something's wrong. They're onto us.
Yosik, now!
The man he's meeting is not Marwan.
- Is anybody else there besides them?
- No, unless someone's on the boat.
Marine units, move into position.
All teams, move in.
- We're OK. We should just get out of here.
- There was a police officer there.
I told you, that's harbour security.
They stop by all the time.
Who the hell is that?
This is CTU.
We have you completely surrounded.
-  Yes. Where are you?
- They found us. They're gonna get us.
Yosik, you can't let that happen.
You cannot allow yourself to be captured.
I understand.
Also you have to kill Prado.
He knows too much.
I'll do what's necessary.
Yosik! Yosik!
Shots fired! Shots fired! Move in.
Come out with your hands up.
You're surrounded. There's no escape.
Coming out!
Drop the gun!
Put the gun down!
Step off the boat. Get off the boat.
There's a man inside.
I shot him. He was gonna kill me.
He was trying to steal my boat.
It was self-defence.
Put your hands on your head.
- Who are you? Who are you?
- Oh, Jesus.
My name's Joe Prado.
I'm innocent. I have nothing to hide.
Where's Yosik?
- He's dead. His phone was lying next to him.
- Get him out of here.
- Let's go.
- Secure the boat.
Yes, sir.
Yosik's dead. We have the man he was
meeting. He says his name is Joe Prado.
- Bring him in.
- Will do.
We recovered Yosik's cellphone.
I'll report to you en route.
Good work, Curtis. We're standing by.
Go ahead.
What do you want to do?
Control the situation.
Make sure Prado doesn't talk
to the authorities. He can hurt us.
- How do we get to him?
- We can't. Not directly.
-  Hello.
- This is Marwan.
- Yes, Marwan?
- Can you reach Amnesty Global at this hour?
- What do you need?
- An attorney.
Tell them that an innocent man
is being held without charges
and is about to be tortured
at CTU Los Angeles.
By God's grace, President Keeler survived.
But more than 75 others did not.
I share in your grief and anger
over this tragedy.
My family and I feel no differently
than every one of you.
We are shocked, saddened,
and maybe a little afraid.
These terrorists have displayed once again
their indifference toward human life.
They will pay for what they have done.
- Bill, excuse me.
- However, we must endure...
- There's a convoy missing.
- What?
It was headed from Illinois to Iowa.
It disappeared inside the border.
Disappeared?
- They were due to call in. They didn't.
I tried on comm sat, there was no reply.
- Satellite?
Nothing.
- What was on the trucks?
- A nuclear warhead.
Our faith and our resolve will prevail.
... the files I sent. Have Prado's
information for me as soon as I get back.
OK, we've got the prints.
I'll run them through our databases.
Thanks.
What do we know about the prisoner?
Just the name he gave - Joe Prado.
Curtis uploaded his prints.
I'm running through them.
Prep Holding
so Curtis can begin interrogation.
I want this man broken in minutes, not hours.
Clear all directories.
Put all resources into finding this warhead.
Mike, I wish I'd known about this sooner too.
Look, I'm not pointing fingers here.
I'm on your side.
But the president is not going to be happy
that his statement can be invalidated.
I don't know what to tell you. We're
putting everything into finding this warhead.
All right. Let me get back to you.
Move!
Inside. Let's go. Move. Move, move!
Get in, get in.
We have it. We're heading out now.
Sir.
General Thomas told me
we're missing a warhead.
- I just heard some details from Buchanan.
- When did this happen?
- It disappeared between 1:45am and 2:15.
- And none of our satellites picked this up?
It was mountain terrain at night.
People are analysing the imagery,
but it's going to be hard to find.
What will we do if we don't find Marwan?
Our people are doing everything to contain
him. It's going to be difficult for him to leave.
It's difficult to shoot Air Force One with
our own Stealth fighter, but he managed that.
Who knows what they're planning?
I'm sure he's gonna come after me next.
There's no indication that that's his plan.
You don't know that. We don't have
enough information to know what his plan is.
Head of Secret Service
is on his way over now.
He has a revised plan,
and I'm certain it will ease your mind
about your safety.
That's the bastard from the marina,
helping the terrorists.
I guess.
Sir, holding room B is ready.
I'd like to get him in a room for a few minutes.
What?
He'd talk to me in about two seconds.
Oh, you wanna hurt him to get revenge
for your mother dying. I can understand that.
...images processed immediately.
Take him to Holding.
- Did Edgar run the prints?
- Name checks out. Joe Prado, ex-marine.
No criminal record. But over
the last five years, no record of employment.
- Which means he's a criminal or a mercenary.
- Right.
- I'll find out if he knows about the warhead.
- All right.
Tony.
- What have you got?
I found the convoy. I just got off
with Iowa Highway Patrol.
Military transport was ambushed.
Everyone's dead.
- What about the warhead?
- Gone.
Find out what they'd need to transport it.
Tell law enforcement to put up perimeters.
Check airstrips or clearings
where they might put a chopper.
Yeah.
Remember he's an ex-marine.
He won't cave easily.
I need to establish that even though we're in a
government building, I'll go as far as it takes.
- How are you gonna start?
- I'll use Richards.
OK.
I told you I'm not talking to you, pal.
I haven't been charged,
I haven't done anything wrong.
I killed in self-defence.
He was stealing my boat.
We both know that's a lie. So let's not waste
each other's time. What do you say, Joe?
- I'm not saying anything to you.
- Highly unlikely.
What the hell is this?
- Yes?
-  Where's Curtis?
- He's just about to start with Prado.
- Tell him to stop.
- What?
- That's an order. Come to the floor, now.
- It was self-defence. You can't do this.
-  Curtis.
- What?
- Buchanan wants to see us before you start.
Wait till I get back.
- What's this about?
- I don't know.
We have a problem.
This is David Weiss from Amnesty Global.
I have a court order protecting the rights
of Joseph Prado whom you have in custody.
This US marshal is here to assure
I'm taken to the prisoner immediately.
- Ridiculous.
- That's your opinion.
But Mr Prado's rights will not be violated.
Take me to him now.
- We have no choice, Curtis.
- A warhead's missing. This is our only lead.
I'll get into this with the Justice Department.
In the meantime, do what he says.
When can I expect his call?
It's extremely important.
I understand that, but I need to talk
to the judge. Please have him call me back.
- Mr Buchanan.
- Do you have those hourlies for me?
- No, I don't. But I'm here on another matter.
- What?
I heard Prado's interrogation is on hold. Why?
You have a job to do.
Please get back to it.
I know I'm not supposed to interfere, but
considering what I've been through today -
my mother dying because of these terrorists -
I wanna know why we're letting
some lawyer protect Prado.
We're gonna fix it,
but it's gonna take some time.
- That's time we don't have.
- Edgar, stop.
I'm trying to cut you some slack,
but get back to your job.
You need to put all that other stuff
on hold for a while, please.
Yes, sir.
Buchanan. Yes, I'll hold for the judge.
- You're supposed to be doing the hourlies.
- I don't know why everybody's telling me.
I have a photographic memory.
How could I forget?
You tell me, like, every other day.
I don't like what's happening - some
PC lawyer's holding us up from our job.
Your job is to do the hourlies.
You're holding yourself up.
- Chloe.
- Have you heard about the warhead?
Yeah. FBI link up
with Iowa Sheriff's Department?
- Yes.
- OK, good. Who's questioning the prisoner?
- Prado, the guy Curtis brought in?
- Yeah.
- No one.
- What are you talking about?
An attorney came in with an order saying
we weren't allowed to be alone with Prado.
Buchanan's on the phone
with the judge who signed the order.
I'll be right back. I don't believe this.
I disagree. This does not fall outside
the boundary of the Patriot Act.
- Thanks.
- What's going on?
You've got a key witness.
We should be pressing this guy.
Judge Norton won't budge.
We have to take it to an appellate judge.
- Does he know what the stakes are?
- He does, but Prado's got no record.
What about the fact he was meeting
a terrorist in the middle of the night?
Circumstantial.
We need to interrogate this prisoner.
I don't care about the order.
I agree, but his attorney's with him,
and a marshal protecting his rights.
- Where's his attorney?
- Holding, with Prado. Don't make it worse.
I just want to talk to him.
- How much longer do I have to stay?
- I'm trying to get you out.
My office is filing a complaint.
They have nothing on me.
I was alone on my boat.
I don't even know this man
that they were going after.
Come in with me now.
- Who are you?
- Bauer, Department of Defence. And you are?
David Weiss, Amnesty Global.
- Why is the suspect not in restraints?
- Amnesty's order supersedes our authority.
My client is cooperating.
He's not trying to go anywhere.
He wants to be treated like any US citizen.
Your client aided and abetted
the people who attacked the president.
- You don't know that.
- As a matter of fact, we do.
Then charge him.
May I speak with you privately?
Get the door.
You and I know your client isn't clean, and
that he conspired to steal a nuclear warhead.
All my client wants is due process.
Mr Weiss, these people
are not gonna stop attacking us today
until millions and millions
of Americans are dead.
I don't wanna bypass the constitution,
but they're extraordinary circumstances.
The constitution was born out of
extraordinary circumstances, Mr Bauer.
This plays out by the book.
Not in a back room with a rubber hose.
I hope you can live with that.
- Sir, can I help you?
- No, it's all right.
- How'd you get here so fast?
What?
- Who asked you to represent Mr Prado?
- I don't have to give you that information.
From his arrest,
did the suspect have time to call a lawyer?
No.
Marwan called Amnesty Global.
This is his play.
That means Prado knows something
Marwan doesn't want us to hear.
- We still can't get around that court order.
- We need to call the president now.
We cannot have leaks
regarding this missing warhead.
I've contacted General Wilson in Iowa.
He's sealing off the roads
while we clean up the ambushed convoy.
What about those Highway officers
who discovered it?
Wilson's brought them in
and is explaining the situation.
The good news is this is happening in the
middle of the night. The country's still asleep.
Yes?
CTU Los Angeles is on the line
for President Logan. They say it's urgent.
Thank you, gentlemen. That'll be all.
Walt.
Stay.
Put him through.
-  Go ahead.
- This is Bill Buchanan. I'm with Jack Bauer.
- Yes. What do you have for me?
In the process of trying to track down this
warhead, we've brought in a prime suspect.
- What have you learned?
- Well, that's the problem. Our hands are tied.
Amnesty Global has interceded on his behalf.
- Interceded? On what grounds?
- He's a US citizen with no previous record.
- Why is he a suspect?
- We found him with Yosik Khatami,
a man linked to today's events.
It doesn't violate any law
to question a suspect.
Mr President, if I may?
Go ahead, Mike.
- Jack, it's Mike Novick.
- Hi, Mike.
Am I correct in assuming
this suspect is unlikely to respond
to the kind of Q and A
his lawyer would permit?
Correct. If we want information, we're gonna
have to do it behind closed doors.
- Torture him?
- I'm talking about what is necessary
to stop this warhead being used against us.
Give us a moment, Bill.
Mike, what do you think?
I think we need to do whatever it takes
to find Marwan.
Walt?
Weigh in.
- Well, this makes me nervous.
- Why?
Should this man be innocent,
as he claims he is,
your first act as president
is to sanction his torture.
That'll forever haunt your presidency.
All right, gentlemen.
Here's what I'll agree to.
I'll call a session with members of the
Justice Department, and we'll discuss this.
I'll have an answer in 20 minutes.
- This thing could be over in 20 minutes.
- That's as far as I'm willing to go right now.
With all due respect, sir,
please let us do our jobs.
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
- I'll have Curtis start the interrogation.
- We can't afford to be wasting time.
You heard. He won't let us touch this guy.
The president's not here. You are.
If I authorise this, they'll know.
We'll all be out.
What if I find a way
that wouldn't implicate anyone but me?
- I'm not gonna authorise that, Jack.
- You don't have to.
- What do you mean?
- Accept my resignation.
- And if I do that, what then?
- Release the suspect.
- Release him?
- We don't question him, we don't charge him.
He won't need a lawyer or a marshal.
You're gonna take him on as a private citizen?
-  Yes.
- How far away are you?
32 miles.
When you get there,
you'll meet with Morrison.
- Is he going to configure the detonation?
- Yes.
I've given him the codes.
OK.
You have to follow the plan exactly, Sabir.
We cannot give them time
to start an evacuation.
- Yes, Marwan. I understand.
- No delays.
It will be done.
- Hey. When did you get back?
- A few minutes ago. Thanks.
- I could use your help on the DOD interface.
- I can't help you now. Sorry.
- What are you doing?
- I'll tell you when I get back.
Jack?
- Jack?
- Audrey, please.
What are you trying to pull? You wanna
torture me, now you're throwing me out.
- Right.
- They tried to fight the order and couldn't.
No, that's not what this is.
They're doing something.
- Don't be so paranoid. We're not interested.
- I want protection when I get out.
- The marshal can escort you back...
- No! You know what - change of plan.
I don't wanna leave here until I know I'm safe.
If you don't leave, I'll have to arrest you for
trespassing in a secure government building.
And once that happens,
not even your attorney can protect you.
Correct me if I'm wrong, David.
He's right.
- What's going on?
- He's been released.
- Why?
- I don't know. It came from Buchanan.
- Why are you letting him go?
- Not now, please.
- He's with the people that killed my mother.
- Not now.
- Cheer up. You're a free man.
Yeah, right.
- The marshal's gonna take you home.
- No! I can't go home.
I gotta go somewhere public.
Fine, tell him where you wanna go.
Don't let anyone know you're there.
Here's my card. You call me
if anyone from CTU tries to bother you.
Yeah, OK.
You're gonna be fine.
Make a sound and I will blow your brains
all over the windshield.
Handcuff your left arm to the dashboard, now.
Now we're gonna talk.
Now, you and I both know your heart
isn't in this. You just wanted the money.
I don't want you. All I want is Marwan.
Marwan? I don't know
what you're talking about.
Yeah. Well, I'm running out of time here,
so why don't we just cut to the chase?
What?
- Where's Marwan?
- I don't know!
Where is Marwan?
- Where's Marwan?
- I don't know! I swear I don't know.
OK, OK, OK. Marwan's... Marwan's
gonna be at a place called The Hub tonight.
- Where is it?
- It's... It's just...
- Just east of downtown. East of downtown.
This will help you with the pain.
Visiontext Subtitles: Jo Clarke
ENGLISH SDH