[Jack Bauer]
Previously on 24.
TheJustice Department is investigating
theJonas Hodges car bombing.
I changed my mind.
I didn't transfer the funds.
Why would he go ahead
and kill Hodges if he wasn't paid?
Because it's what you wanted. Am I right?
Jack, I unlocked Tony's location data.
[Jack]
Okay, we've got him.
Where's the canister?
I am not gonna stop
until you tell me where it is.
- Jack.
- It's all right. It's all right.
- You need to give yourself a shot.
- I already did, 20 minutes ago.
- It's not working.
- You heading home?
- Yeah.
- Us too.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- This is Bauer.
- I'm sending a link to your phone.
It's something I think you should see.
Your daughter's in the company
of our operatives.
Put this call on your earpiece
and keep the line open.
I'm gonna be listening to everything you say.
You will help Tony Almeida escape,
or my people will murder your daughter.
[Jack Bauer] The following takes place
between 6:;00 a.m. And 7:;00 a.m.
Okay. Thank you.
The Deputy Attorney General
is ready for you, ma'am.
TelePresence call is initiated.
Network is secure. Go ahead.
Good morning, Ms. Taylor. Thank you for
giving up your time for this investigation.
Of course.
Mrs. Rollins, Mr. Hock
are from theJustice Department.
They'll be conducting your interview.
Let the record show that this is to be
the testimony of Olivia Taylor...
acting White House chief of staff...
regarding the homicide
of federal witness Jonas Hodges.
Let it also show that I am present to ensure
that strict protocols be followed...
for Ms. Taylor's protection.
- Why would I need protecting?
- Uh, poor choice of words.
I merely meant that your questioning
is just a formality.
We have to go through everyone
who had knowledge of Hodges's
whereabouts until the bombing.
I see.
Mrs. Rollins,
you have the floor. Let's begin.
[Chattering]
I wanted Olivia in this briefiing.
Where is she?
I'm sorry, ma'am, but she's tied up
with the Deputy A.G. And investigators...
Iooking into the Hodges murder.
- Have they made any progress
on who leaked Hodges's location?
- Not yet.
But they agree that the list of people
who knew Hodges was alive and at F.B.I. Is short.
The leak had to come from inside.
- Good morning, everyone.
- Good morning, Madam President.
- Madam President.
- Please take your seats.
I realize that we are all
in dire need of sleep...
but I felt that it was vital...
to bring you all up to speed on the events
of the past few hours...
and a greater crisis we face
on the horizon.
Less than 30 minutes ago,
the F.B.I. Managed to recover...
the last canister of the bioweapon.
But I'm afraid that the danger
is far from over.
Before his death, Jonas Hodges told us...
that there were other parties involved with him
in the creation of this bioweapon-
a highly secret and extremely powerful group
of private military fiirms...
collaborating to undermine
the government of this country.
Excuse me, Madam President...
but which military fiirms
are we talking about?
We don't know, Admiral.
Hodges gave us no names
or idea of which companies are involved...
but whoever they are, they represent
a very real and ongoing threat.
Now, we don't have much
actionable intelligence at this point.
However, the F.B.I. Has apprehended
former C.T.U. Operative Tony Almeida.
He is a key fiigure in this plot...
someone we hope will be able
to help us uncover who these people are.
Agent Walker, this is air support Bravo 3.
- We're in position. Your convoy's in sight.
- Roger that, Bravo 3.
Metro will be controlling traffiic and setting up
a secure corridor through downtown.
We'll be bringing Almeida in to headquarters
through the west entrance.
[Cara On Earpiece]
It's almost time, Mr. Bauer.
The convoy you're traveling with
is about to get off on the l-70.
You'll need to break off
before you reach the downtown exit...
or you'll lose your chance
to facilitate an escape for Tony.
For your daughter's sake...
you don't want that to happen.
Now listen carefully.
You'll need to commandeer the van...
and peel onto the Taft Street exit
in about four miles.
I'll direct you further
once you've managed this.
Remember, my operatives
are with your daughter.
In fact, I'm looking at her right now,
so don't try to be a hero.
[Woman On P.A., Indistinct]
Something wrong?
It's starting to look like the flight
is gonna be full. And I'm on standby.
Oh, no, you're gonna get on. There have to be
some people that are too spooked to fly...
after those planes went down yesterday.
Bob, did you have to bring that up?
I'm just saying! Look, I think it makes us safer.
They're gonna take extra precautions.
Excuse me. Are those yours?
- Yeah, that's right.
- Would you mind, so my mother
could sit down, please?
Oh. Sure.
[Grunts]
- Oh! You're bleeding.
- What?
- You have a scratch on your neck.
- Honey!
That must have happened when the door
hit you getting out of the cab.
Oh, well, y- I'll just go to the newsstand
and see if they have some Band-Aids.
[Cell Phone Ringing]
- What is it?
- I'm getting worried.
It's only a matter of time
before that F.B.I. Agent's body's discovered...
and I think Bauer's daughter
is getting suspicious.
Look, I gave Bauer a short window
to deliver Tony to me.
It won't be long.
Just stand by until you hear from me.
And what if Kim Bauer
makes us before then?
You can't allow yourselves to be taken.
Do what you have to do.
Agent Walker, let me see your comm unit.
I want to adjust its frequency.
It's interrupting mine. Thanks.
- Don't move. Don't move!
- Jack.
[Jack]
Just keep driving and no one gets hurt.
Both of you, I want you
to slowly draw your weapons...
- put them on the floor and slide them to me.
- Jack-
Do it!
Don't make this harder than it already is.
Give me your weapon, or I will kill him.
Come on, Jack.
You're not gonna kill anyone.
- [Groans]
- Give me your weapon! Now!
Driver, I want you to handcuff yourself to
the steering wheel. Over and under. Do it now.
You're gonna exit the freeway when I tell you.
Until then, I want you to maintain speed.
- Now!
- [Tires Squealing]
Agent Walker, what's happening?
Agent Walker!
[Bravo 3] Comm, the prisoner transport
has split from the convoy.
Renee, it's Janis. Do you read me? Renee!
[Janis] Are you reading me?
Agent Walker, what's your 20?
Agent Walker, please respond.
- Jack, why?
- They've got my daughter.
That's not possible. I deployed Agent Franks
to watch over her like you asked.
Agent Franks is dead. The people that are working
with Tony have operatives with Kim right now.
- Jack.
- They've threatened to kill her
if I don't break him out.
- Jack, that's enough!
- You son of a bitch.
- Okay. We're on Taft. What now?
- You'll see the entrance to
the Connecticut Avenue tunnel.
- Take the north lane.
- Continue down this street.
Go towards the tunnel, north.
- Aerial Bravo 3, do you still have a visual?
- Affirmative.
The follow vehicles in the convoy...
are getting off at the next exit
and will be doubling back.
I've got prisoner transport on satellite.
They're heading west on Hudson.
Wait. They're pulling into
the Connecticut Avenue tunnel.
I'm losing visual.
Repeat: ; I am losing visual.
- Pull up the transponder locators.
- Yep.
Okay, we're in the tunnel.
[Cara] You'll see me parked in
the emergency lane about a quarter mile in.
I want you to pull behind that S.U.V.
[Engine Shuts Off]
Jack, please. I understand your reasons,
but you can't do this.
No, what I can't do is risk Kim's life.
UncuffTony.
[Handcuffs Clicking]
Give me the keys.
You cuff her. I'll take him.
[Handcuffs Clicking]
They have a camera on Kim.
I don't trust Tony to let her go.
Please, I am begging you,
do whatever you have to to save her. Please.
Jack.
The gun.
Cuff yourself.
Come on.
What are you bringing Bauer for?
Tony, I've done everything you've asked.
Just let Kim go.
- Let her go!
- Get in the car.
So what are you doing, Tony?
We don't need a hostage, okay, especially not him.
Shoot him already, and let's get out of here.
You're not seeing the big picture, Cara.
Your people are gonna be able...
to launch their biological attacks
just as they originally planned.
How? We lost the canister.
We don't have the pathogen anymore.
We haveJack.
The pathogen's in his blood.
It's in his organs.
We'll be able to harvest
everything we need from his body.
Why do you think I had you
put those operatives on Kim Bauer?
Your people are still gonna need proof
thatJack's viable.
Have one of your biochemists
meet us at the complex.
[Engine Starts]
[Beeping]
Let's begin with the confiidential document
on the left hand side of the packet.
Take a moment to look that over.
- Thank you again for coming.
- You can thank me, Agent Pierce...
by telling me what this is all about.
All right, sir,
but we don't have much time.
- You implied it had something
to do with Olivia Taylor.
- Yes, sir.
A few hours ago, Jonas Hodges
was killed outside F.B.I. Headquarters.
My God.
Now, authorities believe he was murdered
to keep him from implicating others...
who were involved
in the bioweapon attacks...
but I suspect
there may be another scenario...
and I have reason to believe
that Ms. Taylor might be involved.
That is an outrageous accusation,
Agent Pierce.
Olivia is capable of many things...
but I can't believe
committing murder is one of them.
Mr. Kanin, please just hear me out.
After the president agreed
to a witness protection deal for Hodges...
Ms. Taylor made a comment to me...
about wanting to see Hodges dead.
He was responsible for her brother's death.
She was venting.
I thought so too...
until she met in her offiice with an old colleague
of hers, a man named Martin Collier.
- I know Collier.
- Then you know the sort of man he is.
I do, but none of this
constitutes proof of complicity.
No, sir. That's why I need you to access
the digital recording system-
to see if their conversation was recorded.
Agent, you're asking me to break into an offiice
that's no longer mine...
and access classifiied recordings
of the acting chief of staff.
Mr. Kanin, if my suspicions
prove correct...
you, of all people, understand how grave
these consequences would be.
Sir, Ms. Taylor's behavior over the past
several hours has been erratic at best.
Now, she's with theJustice Department
investigators now, and we don't have much time.
Sir, I need you...
to decide if you're gonna help me.
If you could just again review
the records on the screen below, Ms. Taylor...
I want to confiirm that during the timeline
in question you had no outside contact...
other than what's reflected in the phone
and Internet logs you uploaded to us.
For the third time, that's correct.
We're just trying to be thorough, ma'am.
I think we've taken up enough
of your valuable time, Ms. Taylor.
Thank you for, uh, indulging us.
You're welcome. Good luck
with the rest of the investigation.
[Door Opens]
[Agent]
She's coming.
Sir.
She's on her way.
Ms. Taylor, I tried to get word to you
but was told you were not to be disturbed.
Word to me about what?
- Let me explain.
- [Kanin] Good morning, Olivia.
Ethan.
What are you doing here?
I'd forgotten some fiiles when
I cleared out my offiice, so...
Secret Service was kind enough
to admit me so I could retrieve them.
May I see them?
Nothing terribly important.
But I like to fully archive my memos
for, uh, posterity.
You understand.
So you have what you came for.
Um, I think so.
Well, then if you'll excuse me-
Of course.
Agent Pierce.
Stay a moment, please.
- What was he doing here?
- Ma'am?
Kanin. Did you observe him
while he was in my offiice?
Is something wrong, ma'am?
Yes. Yes, something is wrong.
No one, and I mean no one
is to be allowed in my offiice without-
Ms. Taylor, could I get someone
on staff to help you with that?
- Ms. Taylor-
- Security?
This is Olivia Taylor.
Ethan Kanin is on his way out of the
White House. I want him taken into custody.
Detain him until I arrive.
Ma'am, what's happened?
He stole my property, Aaron.
[Agent]
Sir.
Mr. Kanin! Mr. Kanin!
- Yes?
- We have orders to detain you, sir.
Orders from whom?
From the acting chief of staff, sir.
Please come with us.
Sir.
[Sirens Wailing]
Command, this is Walker.
Janis, do you read me?
- I'm here. Are you all right?
- Yeah.
- What is happening?
- Jack commandeered the transport.
He was forced into helping Tony escape.
Renee, it's Chloe.
What do you mean, "forced'"?
The group Almeida's working for threatened
to kill Kim Bauer if he didn't cooperate.
They have Kim?
According toJack, they have operatives
with her at the airport...
but I don't think she's aware of that.
- Do you want me to contact airport P. D?
- No.
We can't move on these people
until we know who they are.
Chloe, I need you to patch me in directly
to Kim's departure gate.
- She's at Gate 7.
- I'm on it.
- I'll brief the White House
and let them know what's happened.
- I'll call when I'm on my way.
I have a priority one emergency call from F.B.I.
Please connect me with an agent at Gate 7.
[Woman On P.A.] Attention, passengers
for Flight 147, nonstop to Los Angeles.
Maintenance crews have fiinished
preparing the aircraft...
and we should be ready to begin boarding
in approximately 10 minutes.
Thank you again for your patience.
Would the following standby ticket holders
please report to the ticket agent counter-
Marissa Boily, Kim Bauer,
Robert Leighton.
- Well, looks like I got on the flight.
- Told you you would.
[Man On P.A.] Passengers on Flight 678
and pending for Indianapolis...
we do apologize
for the delay at this time.
- [Man On P.A. Continues, Indistinct]
- [Whispering]
- Kim Bauer?
- Yeah.
- I'll take you over here.
- Okay.
Phone call for you.
Hello?
Kim, this is Renee Walker. Listen carefully.
Try not to react and do not look around.
You're in danger. You're being watched
by operatives sent by Tony Almeida.
Tony? I don't understand.
He's involved with the people
responsible for the attacks.
We had him in custody,
but he used you as leverage...
to force your father to break him out.
I don't believe that Tony
would do something like that.
He's on the run, Kim. He's taken your father
hostage. You've got to trust me on this.
I'm on my way with a team to you now, but we
have to I.D. The people who are watching you.
They're our only lead
to fiinding your father and Tony.
There was a man
that was staring at me earlier...
but I haven't seen him in a while.
- Describe him.
- He was Hispanic.
Medium build. He had short brown hair.
He was wearing a suit.
That was Agent Franks.
Your father had me deploy him to the airport...
to make sure you got on the plane safely.
He was killed by the people
following you. Listen, Kim.
Whoever these operatives are,
they're in close proximity to you.
Your father told me they sent him
a live feed to prove they had you in their sights.
Have you noticed anyone
with a camera or cell phone?
- Or a laptop?
- What?
There's a couple that I've been talking to.
They're sitting right next to me.
The man has an open laptop
right in front of me.
- Can you give me a description?
- Yeah. He's got long hair, he's tall-
- Kim? Kim, what's wrong?
- Oh, well, I appreciate that. Okay. Thank you.
Please let baggage claim know that
I will be much more careful next time.
Kim?
- Chloe, do you read me?
- I'm here.
The operatives may be moving on Kim. Alert
airport police. Have them lock down the terminal.
Tell airport security to maintain patrols.
Do nothing to arouse suspicion.
Okay.
Okay. Bye.
We saw you were on the phone. We thought
there might be a problem. You need some help?
No. There's no problem.
I left my electric toothbrush on in my luggage.
So the airline called
and said they broke my lock.
- Nice. You get your boarding pass?
- Oh, yeah. It's right here.
There was a little security problem
with her luggage.
[Kim]
Guess they can never be too careful.
- You okay?
- Yeah. Yeah, I'm fiine.
This is the fiirst time
that I've been apart from my little girl.
I'm just a little anxious
to get back to see her.
- Would you like to see a picture of her?
- Sure.
Got one in here.
Here it is.
Yeah.
Where is... Here. Yeah.
- Her name's Teri.
- She's adorable.
Thank you.
Look at this. So cute.
That's my husband, actually.
This is-Aww.
[Giggles]
Take her.
[Screaming]
- Let me go!
- [Gunshots Continue]
Code two! Code two!
Suspects are armed!
Get down!
[Screams]
Walker.
It's Kim Bauer. Security's down.
Where are the airport police?
They're mobilizing to you now.
What about the operatives?
The woman is dead.
The man is getting away.
Kim, we need him to fiind your father.
- What direction was he headed?
- [Phone Beeping]
- Agent Walker!
- [Beeping Continues]
- Damn it!
- Kim? Kim!
Let's go! Let's go!
[Screaming, Chattering Continues]
[Beeping]
Olivia.
I always liked that about you, Ethan.
Even when I was a little girl, you always
stood up when I came into the room.
Old habits die hard.
You removed something from my offiice.
- I want it back.
- I told you before, you're welcome to them.
- You know damn well
I'm not talking about those fiiles.
- Do I?
Ethan, I found the digital recorder.
Now give me what you took...
or I'll order the security offiicers
outside this door to strip-search you.
All right. I do have a recording.
It's a personal account of my last days
in service to this administration...
and I think I'm entitled to it.
No one is entitled to take sensitive
material out of the White House.
Oh...
now it's national security
you're worried about.
As a matter of fact, yes.
Well, I still have my clearances.
Why don't we listen
to the recording together?
You're in no position
to dictate terms, Ethan.
You're in violation
of at least 10 federal laws.
What are you so afraid of, Olivia?
What's on there that's so incriminating?
I'm not the one facing incrimination.
You are.
But give me the recording right now...
and I'll see to it no charges are fiiled.
Last chance, Ethan.
Search him for a data card.
I'm being held without cause.
I demand to speak to President Taylor.
It was the president
who ordered his detention.
If that's true,
I want to hear it from her directly.
Well, this is a criminal matter now.
Considering her personal relationship
with Mr. Kanin...
the president doesn't deem it appropriate
to intrude on the investigation.
Please stand up, Mr. Kanin.
Arms up.
You're making a terrible mistake.
Ms. Taylor is grossly
overstepping her authority.
Thank you, Agent.
- Process him out.
- Come with me, Mr. Kanin.
[Door Opens, Closes]
I don't think you understand
the seriousness of what you're doing.
[Door Opens]
I don't think you do.
Agent Hobson.
I can take him the rest of the way.
Fine.
She's defiinitely hiding something,
Agent Pierce.
Lucky for us,
I'm a paranoid son of a bitch.
May I ask
what was on the other data card?
Nothing. It's blank.
I can try to get you into the communications
offiice so you can listen to that.
Too risky. And unnecessary. I have
a companion device to the recorder in my car.
Well, it sounds like you were,
uh, expecting this.
One has to be prepared
when you're dealing with Olivia.
I'll let you know what I fiind.
[Grunting]
What are you doing?
[Shouts]
We're gonna use you to
reconstitute the bioweapon, Jack.
Put him on the table, face down.
How long till we know?
- It depends.
- On what?
On the levels of pathogen
in his spinal fluid.
- Give me a time frame.
- Fifteen minutes.
Good. Get started.
Tony. Tony!
- To-
- We've gotta give him something
to control the seizure.
I need him completely immobilized.
There we go.
I'll contact the group
as soon as we know if Bauer's viable.
- Yeah. Look, I need to talk to you fiirst.
- What is it?
I want a larger role in the organization,
and I think this is a good time to make my case.
Tony, we've gone over this before. Okay?
It's not how it works.
You don't ask in.
- You're invited in.
- All right, then get me an invitation.
Look, after what I've done today,
I think I've earned it.
You have been resourceful, it's true.
- Still-
- Look.
I know you talk to the top guy.
All's I'm asking is that you get us
in the same room together. I'll sell myself.
- I don't think that would be the right approach.
- Why not?
Because he's careful to a fault, Tony...
and he's very protective of his anonymity.
I can appreciate that.
But the bottom line is,
without me this operation never happens.
Now, you have influence over him.
He trusts you. You can convince him.
I've seen you do it before.
- This is different.
- That's right.
It is different.
This time it's for me.
I'm ready to extract the spinal fluid.
- Hold his head still.
- All right.
[Screaming]
[Beeping]
- He knows, Martin. I'm telling you.
- No, Olivia, he doesn't.
Worst case, he has a suspicion.
He never actually had the time
to listen to the recording, did he?
- No.
- Okay.
- And he never will, because
you destroyed the data card, right?
- Of course.
Then we're fiine, all right, so long as you
keep thinking clearly and don't panic.
You're forgetting,
I ended this man's career, Martin.
He won't let me off the hook. Ever.
You're the president's
daughter, okay? Trust me.
No one will come after you without
hard evidence, least of all Ethan Kanin.
- Olivia.
- I've gotta go.
President's been looking for you.
She needs you in the Oval Offiice.
- What's going on?
- A situation unfolding at the airport
involving Tony Almeida.
- We're about to be briefed,
and she wants you in on it.
- Okay.
Everything all right?
Yes. Fine.
[Chattering]
[Woman]
We need help over here!
Stand back.
- Did you see which way he went?
- It was chaos.
There were people running everywhere-
[Groans]
- Janis, it's Renee.
- Go ahead.
The male operative remains at large.
Kim Bauer is missing.
Either she went after him or she's a hostage.
Issue a priority alert across all channels.
[Gasps]
[Chattering]
- Yep, that's it.
- We got it. We're on our way back up.
Offiicer, my name is Kim Bauer.
I followed the man that shot up the terminal.
You need to contact
Special Agent Renee Walker with the F.B.I.
[Engine Starts]
Kim Bauer.
- Kim, it's Renee. Go ahead.
- I've got him. He's in the south parking garage.
- Are you in visual contact?
- No. He's on one of the upper levels.
I'm at the exit.
- Copy that. We're coming towards you.
- Hurry!
[Gunshots]
[Yells]
[Gasps]
Hang on. Help is on the way.
Oh, God.
[Screaming, Grunting]
No!
[Both Screaming]
- Move! Move! Move!
- [Kim Screaming]
[Offiicer Shouting]
Go! Go! Go!
- [Shouting Continues]
- Kim!
You're hurt. Let me see your arm.
No, listen to me, Renee. That laptop
has the camera they were using to track me.
With a D-11 inverse router...
we may be able to backtrace the signal
to the people that have my father.
I worked at C.T.U. Systems analyst.
Is there anyone back at your offiice
that can help us with this?
- Yeah. I've got Chloe O'Brian standing by.
- Get her on the phone.
[Beeping]
[Alarm Chirps]
[Engine Starts]
[Audio Fast-forwarding]
[Collier] Once this happens,
once it goes through, you can never go back.
You will live with it
for the rest of your life.
[Olivia] I don't need a lecture
on conscience from you, of all people.
I have thought this through.
What I can't live with is that monster
getting away with this.
He has to pay for what he did.
The virus load is even higher
than we hoped for.
Ten-plus in spinal fluid alone.
Not enough to reconstitute
the pathogen, of course.
We'll still need his organs for that.
He doesn't look too good.
How much longer does he have?
Couple of hours, give or take.
And what happens if he dies
before we extract the pathogen?
Obviously, it's optimal
to keep the host alive...
but the pathogen can survive up to two hours
after death, sometimes even longer.
In fact, the only sure way to destroy it...
is by exposure to extreme temperatures
above 500 degrees Celsius.
Make sure you put that in your report.
I have. And I've already
uploaded it to your computer.
Good. Get him ready to move.
Get the stretcher.
Bauer is viable,
but you'll need to secure a facility.
That won't be a problem as long as you're
absolutely certain that we can accomplish this.
We've already done the hard part, Alan.
And from what I understand,
with the proper equipment...
the actual extraction and bioengineering
is fairly straightforward.
Okay, Cara.
I'll contact the others. Good work.
They should know they have
Almeida to thank for this.
- He's the one who realized Bauer
was a possible source.
- Relay my gratitude.
I think you should consider
going farther than that.
"Farther"? What did you have in mind?
Tony believes in what we're doing.
He wants to play a larger role.
That sounds premature to me.
The thing is, Alan,
if we don't make a signifiicant gesture...
I'm afraid we may lose him.
I don't even know this man, Cara.
Then you should get to know him.
Are you suggesting I meet with him?
Look, all I'm saying is that he would be
a very useful voice in the mix.
His fiield experience fiills a knowledge gap
in regards to our logistics and planning.
Coming from you,
that's a hell of a recommendation.
There's no one better, Alan.
And it's not as if you haven't vetted
every other member of the group.
Maybe it is time that he and I met.
I could be there, where you are,
in the next half hour.
You're coming here?
I think it would be a good idea
if I supervised Bauer's transfer myself...
Make the others feel at ease,
don't you think?
But, Cara,
I'll look Almeida in the eye...
and if for any reason
I don't like what I see-
You understand.
I can't let him walk
out of that meeting alive.
I understand.
He wants to meet you.
He'll be here in a little while.
Thank you.
It's up to you now.
Wheel the gurney closer.
Get that.
[Grunting, Yelling]
[Neck Snaps]
[Groaning, Panting]
[Alarm Blaring]
Son of a bitch.
He's gone! Come on!
[Alarm Continues]
He's too weak to have gotten very far.
Cover the north exit. I'll go this way.
[Beeping]
[Crickets Chirping]