... ::: www.SubCentral.de ::: ...
proudly presents:
24 - Season 7
Episode 13
Mr. Burnett you are a traitor
and a terrorist.
Where's the target?
Where's the target?!
Take Mr. Bauer away.
He's under arrest.
Have you learned anything
else about the attack?
Renee Walker followed
a lead on her own.
Got a visual on a heavily
armed commando unit
lead by Juma himself.
Bill Buchanan.
Renee Walker says the target
is the White House.
Condition red.
Secure the president.
There's no safe path out.
Weeed to secure her in
the first floor lockdown.
Hostage rescue teams
are moving into place.
They'll be prepared
to storm the building
as soon as
the order's given.
Mr. Vice President,
terrorists are in control
of the White House.
Until you can provide me
more intel
on what's going on in there,
you are instructed to refrain
from launching any action.
President Taylor is
locked in the safe room.
What is it I can do for you?
I need you to find me
another way in.
Well, I'm looking
at the White House manifest,
and according to this,
Olivia Taylor
is presently in the building
with you.
You find Olivia Taylor,
and you'll get the president
to open that door.
President Taylor...
God, no.
... if you don't open the door,
I'm gonna cut out
your daughter's eyes
one by one.
Open the door.
Madam President ...
No, open the door.
Open the door!
I can't do that.
I can't!
Do you have children, Jack?
I have a daughter.
Could you do
what you're asking me to do?
Just stand by
and watch her butchered?
No, ma'am, but I am not the
President of the United States.
Well, I am the president,
and I am ordering you
to open that door.
All right, General,
you've got me now.
There's no reason
to hold anyone else.
Let them go.
Now, what we do know
is that the president
was in the building
when the attack took place,
and she may have
been taken hostage
along with numerous other
White House personnel.
Vice President Hayworth
was not in the building,
and we're told he was moved
to a secure location.
The FBI has cordoned off
a nine-block perimeter...
Mr. Vice President,
that was Agent Moss.
What does he have to say?
He's still requesting that you
authorize a rescue operation.
Does he have any more intel
about what the hell's
going on in there?
No, sir. He deployed two units
with deep-band parabolics,
but all they were able
to get w static.
They think Juma's using some
kind of jamming equipment.
They've also got spotters
at every possible angle
around the building,
but they haven't
been able to see inside.
we still don't know
whether Juma has the president,
or whether the president
is locked inside the safe room?
No, sir, we don't.
I will not authorize
any action
until I know
the status of the president.
Relay that to Agent Moss.
Yes, sir.
Mom, I know
that I hurt you.
I'm so sorry for cutting
you out of my life.
It's okay...
No, it isn't.
You were right to fire me
off the campaign.
I felt so betrayed,
I turned my back on you.
Olivia, don't
worry about it.
It all seems
so stupid now.
I hope you can forgive me.
Darling, I forgave
you a long time ago.
Livy, you have
to listen to me.
We really are going
to be okay.
Just keep your eyes
open and be ready.
Abo.
No, no.
Get up.
Leave her alone!
Get away from her!
Get back!
I said leave her alone!
Please!
Olivia, it's okay, darling.
It's okay!
Bill, we need to
try to save
the president.
How?
In the lockdown room,
there were five canisters of CH-4.
Before we surrendered ourselves
over to Juma, I opened the valves.
Within the next few minutes,
that room is going to be
saturated with natural gas.
It's going to take
one spark to set it off.
I think the explosion
is going to be large enough
to take out most of Juma's men.
That's when you
can make your move
How do we set it off?
I'll me a run
for the lockdown room.
Try and draw their fire.
All we need is one stray bullet.
That's a suicide play, Jack.
We don't have a choice.
Just make sure you can
get to the president
and get her
out of here.
She knows about the
plan; she will be ready.
What are you planning?
Are you going to do something?
When it happens,
you'll know about it, Senator.
Damn it, if you're
planning something,
I want to know what it is.
Senator, shut up.
Read this statement.
It is a confession
of your crimes
against my country.
The atrocities that
you have committed
will now be seen
by the whole world.
I'll read your statement,
General,
but I need you to release
the other hostages.
You got what you came for.
You have the President
of the United States.
As a sign of good faith...
I will release one
of the hostages.
You...
Stand up.
Do you want me to release any more hostages,
President Taylor?
You son of a bitch.
You will read this statement
or I will do the same thing
to everyone here...
starting with
your daughter.
General, the uplink is complete.
All right.
The world is waiting,
Madam President.
"This is the president
of the United States."
"Six hours ago,
I ordered our armed forces"
"to invade Sangala without
warning and without provocation."
"This attack was a cminal act
motivated solely"
"by America's desire"
"to exert its power
and influence."
Tell me you're
shutting this down.
We can't, sir.
It's a live feed straight
to the Internet.
I don't care.
Shut it down.
It's going out
on multiple servers, sir.
It would take hours
just to trace them.
This is Derek Watts.
Hold on.
Sir, it's Agent Moss
on teleconference.
Put him on.
Sir, are you getting this?
Yes. So is the rest
of the damn world.
Mr. Vice President,
I believe Juma came here
to humiliate the president
and stage a public execution.
We have a rescue operation
in place.
All we need is
your authorization.
You don't know what Juma's
intentions are.
This could be a prelude
to a set of demands.
There are no demands here, sir.
This is about revenge.
Juma knows he'll never get out
of the White House alive.
You're speculating,
Agent Moss.
My advisorare telling me
the most prudent course
of action
is to try to initiate
communication with Juma.
We've been trying to do that.
He hasn't responded.
Sir, Juma has no desire
to negotiate anything.
Hes going to kill
the president.
Sir, we have a tactical plan
in place.
It's a two-pronged assault,
and we're confident that
it stands a good chance
of catching Juma off guard,
but we're losing time.
We have to initiate now.
I can not authorize any action
at might result
in the president's death.
Keep trying to open dialogue
with Juma.
Hold your position
till you're told otherwise.
I will keep this feed open.
"General Juma has demonstrated"
"that even a tyrant state
like the U.S..."
Be ready.
Jack, listen to me.
Juma's not solely
coordinating this attack.
What do you mean?
I heard him talking
on his sat phone.
He's coordinating with someone
on the outside.
They were giving him
real-time intel.
You think it's someone
in the White House?
I don't know.
But even if we take Juma down,
the president may
still be in danger.
You're the only one I know
who can do this, Jack.
Find out
who Juma's working with.
Agent Moss, a device
has been detonated
in the West Wing.
Mr. Vice President, there's been
an explosion at the White House.
An explosion?
Yes, sir.
The president's Internet
feed has gone dark.
We saw that. What's happening?
I don't know, sir,
but we're going in
under my authority. Let's go.
That is not your decision.
All teams, Attack Plan Delta.
Agent Moss, you're under orders!
Agent Moss!
Code Green.
Go, go, go, go!
Pierce, get to the president!
Madam President, are you okay?
Mm-hmm.
We need  get out of here right now.
Both of you, come with me.
Let's go. This way.
Madam President, get down.
Stay low till I know we're clear.
Ngozi...
kill the hostages.
The president is mine!
Udo...
Udo?
No, no, no, no!
Don't move!
Don't you move!
Clear.
We're clear!
Secret Service!
I have the president!
Aaron Pierce, Secret Service.
Let's go, ma'am.
Madam President, this way!
We have the president.
The president is secure!
Repeat: We have
the president.
This way, ma'am.
Renee! We gotta get
the president out of here now!
This way, ma'am.
It's all right, darling.
It's gonna be all right.
Move! Move! Move!
This way. This way.
Madam President...
we're still sweeping
the West Wing.
but we do believe all the
hostiles have been accounted for.
Now you and your daughter
will stay here until we
finish securing the building.
I understand.
Now once we get the all clear,
we're going to move you
to Andrews Air Force Base.
No, I'm staying right here.
Ma'am, it's for
your own safety.
Do what's necessary to make sure,
this building is safe
because I'm not going anywhere.
The American people need to know
that the president
is in the White House.
Yes, Madam President.
How many people did we lose?
It's too early to tell.
Medical teams are on their way
to treat the wounded.
We're going to set up
a triage unit in the East Wing.
All right.
I'd like to speak
to the vice president
as soon as possible.
Yes, ma'am.
And I need to know
how my husband's doing.
Would you please contact
Dr. Lee Schulman
at West Arlington Hospital?
Yes, Madam President.
Thank you.
How's Agent Pierce?
They said he's gonna be okay.
What about you?
I'm not sure.
I still can't believe
this happened.
I thought
they were gonna kill all of us.
I was so scared.
It's over...
and we're safe...
thanks to a lot
of brave people.
Excuse me, Madam President,
the vice president
is on a secure line.
I'll be right there.
Did you mean
what you said ...
about putting
the past behind us?
Of course I meant it.
I don't ever want
to lose you again.
You won't.
The president's safe, Jack.
She's in the residence.
She's secure.
I'm so sorry, Jack.
I know that he was your friend.
It was supposed to be me.
I was supposed
to set off the explosion
so that he could
secure the president.
He died protecting his country.
Yeah.
This isn't over yet.
Agent Moss...
Juma and his men were
not working alone.
What are you
talking about?
When I was in the lockdown
with the president,
Bill said he heard Juma
talking on a sat phone.
Said he was getting
real-time intel
from someone on the ouide.
Who?
I don't know.
The point is, I don't think
this threat is over,
and I don't think
the president is safe.
You sure Buchanan
heard this right?
He wouldn't have told me unless he was sure.
And right now the only lead
we've got is Ryan Burnett.
He knew about
the attack
on the White House,
and chances are,
he's gonna know who Juma
was talking to.
All right, all right,
I'll talk to him.
No, the president already
offered him immunity.
He turned it down.
He's not gonna
tell you anything,
but he will talk to me.
Why is that, Jack,
'cause you tortured him?
I don't need to touch him.
I just need him to think
I'm there to finish
what I started.
And I promise you
he will tell us
everything we need to know.
Larry, please,
the last thing Bill asked for
before he died
was for me to follow this through.
I owe him that.
Look, I give
you my word.
I will not
touch Burnett.
Jack, look, I understand
about your friend,
I do, but I got standing
orders from the president
to take you into custody.
I gotta get you
back to FBI,
but I promise you
I'll look into this, all right?
Agent Powell,
handcuff Mr. Bauer.
Take him down
to Staging Area B.
Sir, put your hands
on top of your head.
Larry...
If you're gonna tell me
he's right about this
I don't want to hear it.
Yes, that's the problem.
You're not listening to what he's saying.
When are you gonna
stop defending this guy?
I'm not defending him,
I'm defending a good idea.
I just said I will look into this!
Now do your job:
Finish locking down
the building.
Agent Reynolds.
I need to speak with
the president. It's urgent.
She's in a secure location.
You'll need to go
through Ethan Kanin.
Where is he?
He just arrived.
He's on his way
to see the president.
Thanks.
The president's in the
residence with her daughter.
They've both been
checked over
and they're in good condition.
Thank God.
I want a conference
with the SECNAV
and the Joint Chiefs
as soon as possible.
We're routing all White House
communications to the residence,
and we're setting up
a temporary command post.
Good.
Mr. Kanin,
I need to speak with you.
I'm on my way
to see the president.
Yes, I know, sir,
but it's extremely urgent.
It'll only take
a few moments.
All right.
What is it, Agent Walker?
Some new intel has just
come to our attention
and we need to act
on it immediately.
I tried to reach the president,
but I couldn't get through.
I'm listening.
Sir, the threat to the president may not be over.
We've reason to believe
that General Juma
was not acting alone.
Before Bill Buchanan died,
he saw General Juma communicating
with someone on a sat phone.
At this point, we can confirm
that FBI ages entered
the White House moments ago,
and there were reports
of sustained gunfire.
It appears that authorits
are now in control of the West Wing,
and we are expecting word
from our FBI source
of the status of the hostages.
While there has been
no official comment...
So what have we got?
The president's alive.
Are you sure?
We've been monitoring
interagency servers.
Word just went out.
Juma's dead, Taylor survived.
What happened do you think?
We don't know any details yet,
but we'll keep monitorg.
Well... you gotta admire
the damn bitch.
She doesn't give up easily.
I'm sorry, sir.
We, uh,
just didn't have enough control
over the situation.
Greg, you look tense.
Do me a favor.
Have a drink, relax.
NEWSMAN:
"Our FBI source speculated"
"that there were as many as 20
terrorists, all heavily armed..."
Juma held up his part
of the bargain.
We're getting what we wanted.
As far as I'm concerned,
everything's still on track.
"The shocking events of this day..."
Where are the weapons now?
A shipment should  ready
for pickup
in the next couple of hours.
Good.
Get Chapman on the phone.
I want to nail down
some targets.
Sir, the chopper
you requested is on its way.
It'll be here in ten minutes.
You'll be escorting Mr. Bauer back to FBI.
Hold him in the command center.
Yes, sir.
This is Larry Moss.
This is Ethan Kanin.
I understand
you're taking Jack Bauer back
to FBI?
Yes, sir.
He's gonna be debriefed
and remanded
into federal custody.
I want you
to put that on hold.
Sir?
I just spoke
with Agent Walker.
She told me Juma may have
been working with someone
on the outside,
and that there may be
an ongoing threat
to the president.
Yes, that's true.
I want you to send Jack Bauer
to question Ryan Burnett.
Agent Moss?
Sir, I think
that's a mistake.
Yes, Agent Walker shared
your concerns with me,
and I've given this
some thought.
If Burnett does know
who Juma was working with,
Bauer's approach may be our best
chance to get that information.
With respect, sir,
Bauer almost killed this man.
I was there, Agent Moss,
but this will be
a controlled interrogation.
We're gonna play
on Burnett's fears.
Bauer's presence alone
should be enough
to intimidate him into talking.
Sir, Bauer is a wild card.
We have no idea what he'll do
when he gets in that room
with Burnett.
I realize there's a risk.
That's why you're going to
do this under my authority
and my authority alone.
You're not taking this
to the president?
No.
If something does go wrong,
I want to make sure
the president is protected.
With respect, sir, I think you're not
telling the president
'cause you know
she'd never allow this.
You've made your objections
clear, Agent Moss.
I'm not going
to debate this with you.
I want you to take Bauer
to question Burnett.
That's a direct order.
Do you understand?
I understand.
And I'm counting on you
to supervise every second
of that interrogation.
I'll expect a full report
as soon as you're done.
Yes, sir.
I want to speak personally
to the families of everyone
we lost tonight, so...
keep me informed
as they're notified.
Absolutely,
Madam President.
And the minute
Angela Nelson
gets here,
send her straight up to me.
We need to start working
on the speech to the country.
Of course,
Madam President.
Patrick,
you have just
been through
a terrible ordeal.
Are you sure you're okay?
I'll be fine.
It helps to focus on work.
I understand.
Thank you, Patrick.
Thank God you're all right.
How you feeling?
Like I just woke up
from a nhtmare.
It was unbelievable,
Ethan.
I can't even imagine it.
How's Olivia?
She's shaken up,
but she's going to be okay.
I'm glad to hear it.
We lost some good people
tonight, Ethan.
We're going to need
all the help we can get.
I'm thinking
about bringing Olivia on
as a special advisor.
Madam President,
I can understand your
not wanting to be separated
from your daughter
after what's happened.
Especially after
what's happened,
we need people
who can do the job.
I'm not disputing
Olivia's competence,
we need people
but she's also a political liability
Nobody's forgotten what
she did during the campaign,
leaking damaging
personal information
about your opponent
to the press.
Olivia knows
what she did was wrong.
She almost cost you
the election.
She's changed.
We talked about it, Ethan,
and she is accepting
full responsibility.
She has learned
from her mistakes.
I'm willing
to put the past behind us
so we can move ahead.
I still think it's a mistake.
I don't care what you think!
I am so sorry, Ethan.
You know I don't mean that.
But I've made up my mind.
I want Olivia
to join my administration.
And I want it to come from you.
Me?
Your offering her this position
would be a good way
to extend an olive branch.
I need the two of you
to make peace.
All right, Madam President.
I'll talk to her.
Thank you, Ethan.
I understand Agent Walker
was trying to reach me.
That's right,
but I spoke to her.
What did she want?
Just some procedural matters,
Madam President.
I took care of it.
Larry, you wanted
to see me?
I just got off the phone
with Ethan Kanin.
Look, I didn't want
to go behind your back,
but you didn't
leave me any choice.
I didn't leave you a...?
How about you choose
to follow orders?
I'm sorry, Larry.
No. I don't think you are.
Larry, I've seen Jack
do some terrible things today.
Things that
I still can't justify.
But he has been right every time.
And you know what?
I can't help but think
that maybe if we had just
stayed out of his way,
none of this
would have happened.
Look, I am sorry
that I went behind your back,
but I... I promise you
this play with Burnett
will go down
just the way Jack says.
If you think
you're going with Bauer,
you are out of your mind.
You may have gotten
a White House order, but I'm
still running this operation.
I'll take Bauer to see Burnett.
You're going back to FBI.
I want you to clean out your office
and hand in your badge.
I'm suspending you indefinitely.
Okay. I know that you're upset
Larry, but this isn't over.
You're going to need me.
What I need are people
that I can trust.
I thought that was you.
Look, you may think
you got what you wanted,
getting Renee
to go behind my back,
but Ethan Kanin ordered me
to let you question Burnett.
I'm going to be watching you
every second you're in there.
You do one thing I don't like,
you're finished.
You understand me?
Understood.
You should leave Renee
out of this.
She was just doing
what she thought was right.
Yeah? Well,
she may lose her job over it.
She's the best agent you've got.
She circumvented my authority.
I can't just ignore that.
I've known this woman
for nine years,
and I've never seen her do
the kind of things she's done
in the last nine hours.
We've narrowed the list down
to 12 targets
along the eastern seaboard.
They're all within
300 kilometers of the base.
How many people?
10,000 to 15,000
in each target zone.
And our kill ratio
would be what?
Well, we've chosen these areas
for maximum population density,
so the ratio could
be as high as 80%.
Let's hope
we never have to find out.
Get these coordinates down
to the boys in Tac-Ops.
Have them start
programming them in.
Yes, sir.
We just intercepted
a flash memo from the FBI.
Jack Bauer is on his way
to Kennedy Memorial Hospital
to question Burnett.
Bauer was arrested.
How is this possible?
There was an executive order
from the White House
giving Bauer access to Burnett.
Bauer will finish
what he started.
Burnett will
tell him everything.
No, he won't, sir.
I have already sent
somebody to the hospital
to deal with Burnett.
He can take care of Bauer
at the same time.
Who did you send?
Quinn.
Oh. Quinn's good.
Bauer's good, too.
Agent Moss, we've locked
down the entire floor.
We equipped
Burnett's room
with two cameras and
audio surveillance.
Where is he?
Down the hall.
It's going to be a moment.
Doctor has to
revive him.
Why? What happened?
He was given a heavy sedative.
He was in pretty bad shape
when he got here.
Dr. Wyndam, Special Agent
Larry Moss, Jack Bauer.
I understand you're here
to interrogate my patient.
That's right.
Well, he's still
recovering from his last
interrogation, so if you're here
to brutalize him again,
I won't be party to it.
Doctor, your patient
was involved in a terrorist
attack against the White House
in an effort to kill the
President of the United States,
and I believe
the people he's working with
want to try it again,
so if you've got a problem...
We won't harm him,
Doctor.
This will be a controlled
interrogation. Please,
we need your cooperation.
It's going to take him a couple
of minutes to come out of it.
Who are you?
Shh. I'm a friend.
What's your name?
Robert.
Robert?
Yeah.
You're recovering
from heart surgery?
Yeah.
Do you have a wife, Robert?
No. She passed away.
Children?
Grandchildren?
No.
What about this man?
Does he have family?
Yeah.
Lots of grandkids.
Make a hell of a noise
when they visit.
How's your arm?
I should be back on my feet in a couple of hours.
And you, ma'am?
Oh, it's nothing a little
aspirin won't take care of.
I want to thank you
for what you did.
You took a bullet for me.
You saved my life.
There is no need
to thank me, ma'am.
Right, you were just
doing your job.
Only in this case,
it wasn't really your job
since you retired
four years ago.
Yes, ma'am, that's true.
Do you mind
if I ask you why?
Did it have to do
with Martha Logan?
Martha and I were... close.
It must have been hard for you--
what happened to her.
I'd prefer not to talk about it.
I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
I hope you won't be a stranger,
Agent Pierce.
Thank you.
And, uh...
it's Aaron.
Okay, Aaron.
You get some rest.
I'd like to head back
to the residence now
if that's okay?
Olivia...
I was just coming
to see you.
I'm glad you're all right.
Thank you.
you have a moment to talk?
Sure.
The blunt fact
of the matter is...
this administration has just
suffered some terrible losses,
and we need help.
The president and I would like
you to consider coming on board
as special advisor
to the president.
I, uh...
I have to say
I'm a little surprised.
Surprised?
Oh, that you'd sign off on this.
You mother said she's ready
to put the past behind her...
and so am I.
I overstepped my bounds during the campaign,
and I was wrong.
I'm glad you see it that way.
But it's not the past
that concerns me, Ethan.
It's what's happening right now,
and what's been happening ever
since my mother took office.
Excuse me?
Do you think any of this
would have happened
if my mother had a chief advisor
who knew what the hell was
going on in her administration?
What are you talking about?
Our government was corrupted
on every level,
and it all happened
right under your nose.
Even you have to admit,
it's an unconscionable
failure on your part.
Frankly, I'm surprised
you haven't tendered
your resignation.
You have no right to speak
to me that way.
You don't know what
you're talking about.
You don't have the facts.
I intend to get the facts.
I'm going to
find out exactly
who failed my mother,
and I am going to make sure that
that person never is
in a position to do it again.
Excuse me.
Okay, let's go.
I'll be watching.
You lay one finger
on him, it's over.
Right.
He's coming around.
Good.
Wake up.
Remember me?
Oh, my God.
What the hell are
you doing here?
I've just come
from the White House.
Juma's attack failed.
He's dead,
and so are his men.
A lot of innocent people
died today.
Good people.
Including a friend
of mine-- Bill Buchanan.
You might have met him.
You stay the hell away from me.
And I want to talk
to a lawyer right now.
Do you hear me?
I want to talk to a lawyer!
Somebody get me
the hell out of here!
You're not
going anywhere.
It's just you and me, pal.
Did you really think
you were going
to get away with it?
Somebody please,
help me!
You're wasting your breath.
They're not coming for you.
Please don't hurt me.
I'll tell you anything you want.
Do you hear that--
I'm ready to talk.
I'll tell you anything
you want to know!
Just get him out of here!
I'm ready to talk!
They're done talking to you.
That's why they sent me.
Please, you can't do this!
You have no right!
This isn't legal!
What happened?
I don't know.
Looks like we lost
the sound feed.
Give me a second.
There are no laws
in here, Mr. Burnett.
You aided
and abeted terrorists,
who then tried to kill the President of the United States.
You have no right...
Now you have
to answer for that.
The rules don't apply
to you anymore.
No, please, please, you
can't let him touch me!
Please, you can't let him do this...!
Shut up!
It could be a glitch
in the trunk line.
Damn it,
fix the thing!
I'm trying, sir.
Bauer?
He jammed the
electronic bolt.
Is there another way in?
No.
Jack! Jack!
Damn it, Bauer, open the door!
Have security
lock down the hospital.
I want a high-priority APB
issued for Jack Bauer.
All agencies.
It's done.
Good. Thank you.
Burnett's dead.
And Bauer?
They'll think he killed Burnett.
So, nobody will know
that we were involved.
Good.
Yeah.
Now we're having some fun.
Agent Moss.
Larry, it's Jack.
Listen to me.
Where are you?
I didn't kill Burnett. I'm being set up.
Set up?
A man released some kind of
nerve agent into the room.
It immobilized me.
He came through the ceiling
and killed Burnett.
I swear to you, I'm not lying.
I watched him do it.
Get back in here,
we'll work this out.
I can't, you know that.
You can if you're innocent.
Look, there is a reason why they
wanted me framed and didn't kill me.
They're trying to keep you
distracted by dealing with me
so they can finish
what they started.
Don't let them
get away with this.
This threat is not over.
Jack...
Jack?!
Damn it!
... ::: www.SubCentral.de ::: ...