I've been told a cruise missile was launched
containing a nuclear warhead.
That's correct.
What about Marwan? You think he'll break?
That won't be easy, sir. He's planned and
organised everything that's happened today.
How do I fight terrorists
while provoking a nuclear superpower?
We marched on Chinese soil,
we kidnapped one of their nationals, and
in the process the Chinese consul was killed.
The murder of our consul on Chinese soil
could be construed as an act of war.
I assume you know this man.
Howard Bern, one of your field agents.
Camera at the consulate picked up your face.
- I was wearing my mask.
- Trust me, I saw the freeze-frame. It was you.
I'm sorry, Jack.
You gotta go.
There's a chopper waiting for you.
It doesn't matter where you take me.
What I want is already happening.
Go!
Notify the perimeter
we no longer have Marwan in custody.
Richard Heller called Marwan a week ago.
They're bringing him to CTU.
This is a sketch of the guy
Richard Heller described.
He and the girl are our only leads
to finding Marwan.
One of us is gonna get caught
to save the other?
It's gonna be you.
Tony, wait.
I can't spend another day without you.
I'm ready to leave here.
I'm ready to go with you.
Be careful.
Tony, this is Jack.
- Has anybody reported outside movement?
- No. Why?
The man is dead.
The girl is no longer in the apartment.
Tony, do you copy?
Castle, why is Almeida not on com?
All teams, this is Bauer. Castle is down.
Almeida is missing and possibly a hostage.
-  Have you apprehended her?
- No, we do not have her in custody.
She's hiding here in the apartment complex.
She killed Castle and I believe
she's taken Almeida as a hostage.
- Is there any way she slipped the perimeter?
- No.
There's over 600 apartments.
We have to search them room by room.
- Listen, we need more personnel here.
- We're running low on manpower.
There's a missile in the air
carrying a nuclear warhead.
This is our best shot at taking it out
before it hits.
The White House is searching for the missile.
We're stretched thin.
We'll have LAPD send more men. We'll send
Curtis and another tac team to the location.
OK. We've initiated a search starting with
the buildings nearest the perimeter,
working our way in,
but we need LAPD here now.
Keep us posted. Contact Division.
See if they can spare more men.
I'll call our liaison at LAPD.
We've almost completed our satellite pass
over the radius of the missile.
- And no sign of it yet?
- No, not so far.
What do you think our chances are of locating
the missile with subsequent passes?
They're not very good.
This missile's an S-class.
It uses elements of Stealth technology.
It was designed to evade detection.
I know, but it will still have a heat signature.
Yes, but the lower the missile flies
to the ground, the harder it is to pick up.
How much longer
until you've completed the pass?
Uh, less than 20 minutes.
- Get back to me when you have the results.
- All right.
- We need every agent there.
-  They're not cleared for field work.
Bump up their security level on a provisional
basis. Call me back with the exact number.
All right. Coordinate that with Edgar Stiles
here at com. Thanks, Rick.
- What did LAPD say?
- They're keeping units in reserve...
- They're sending more patrolmen to Jack?
- They're sending nine over there now and...
Nine? That's not nearly enough.
- We'll have to reassign our people there.
- I'm taking care of that.
When? We need people there now.
This woman has to be captured.
Michelle.
Everyone understands what's at stake here.
We're gonna do our best to find this woman,
but we have to remain calm,
or everything will spiral out of control.
You're right. I'm not being objective.
I'll admit it. I'm worried about
what this woman might do to Tony,
but I will not lose sight of the big picture.
The big picture is that
we have to apprehend this hostile alive.
Nothing else matters.
- What is it, Marwan?
- You're late. You were supposed to check in.
I know. There was a hitch.
- Nothing serious. Um, I am gonna be there.
- What kind of hitch?
There was a problem in the apartment
and I'm dealing with it.
I'm leaving in one hour.
I'm not waiting for you.
I know, and I'm gonna be there.
Well, we don't have much time.
They're very close to finding us and that
would be very, very bad for both of us.
So tell me. Two years ago you put Michelle
Dessler's life ahead of national security.
You let a suspect escape
and you committed treason.
Is she gonna do the same for you?
- Mike, it's Audrey Raines.
- Yes, Audrey. What have you got?
The satellite pass is complete. We could not
detect the missile with thermal imaging.
There's just too much radiant heat
from ground sources.
Ms Raines, this is President Palmer.
Is there a chance another satellite pass
will find the missile?
Well, the more data we have,
Mr President, the better,
but a more intensive pass
will take two to three hours.
And we expect the missile
to find its target before then.
Yes, sir, we do.
All right. Make sure FBI's on a real-time link
with all local emergency channels.
I'll get that done right now.
I also want you to compile disaster scenarios
for the urban centres
within range of the missile.
Sir, that's 20 of the largest cities
in this country.
I'm aware of that. I want death rates,
fallout patterns, emergency response
predictions for all of them.
- Yes, sir. I'll take care of that right now.
- Thank you, Ms Raines.
Assign teams sections of the grid. We do not
want people bumping into each other.
If the subject is spotted, what's the protocol?
We maximise for capture.
There can be no lag time.
You wanna evaluate the formation?
She's got Tony hostage.
We proceed as if there is no hostage.
There is only one operational objective -
to capture this woman.
Make sure that's the profile you send out
to all the teams. Understand?
Yes.
Dessler.
Why don't you go somewhere private
so we can talk?
- Who is this?
- I'm sending you the answer.
Tony.
Now do you know who this is?
And don't bother trying to triangulate the call.
- It's scrambled.
- Please, don't hurt him.
He's OK for now, but he won't be
unless you do everything that I say, Michelle.
- I understand.
- I need your help getting outta here.
- Wh-what kind of help?
- You're hesitating.
I'm not. I'm not.
I just need to know what you want me to do.
Your men are between me and my exit.
I need to know what their search patterns are
and how many men there are.
- OK. OK. I'll find out.
- You'll tell me right now.
- I have to talk to my tactical teams.
- Oh, Michelle, you're stalling.
How many men are there, total?
Upwards of 30, not including LAPD,
and reinforcements are on the way.
You will need to remove your men
from the northeast driveway of the complex.
I- I don't know if I can do that.
You will redeploy your men
by the time I call you back,
or Tony dies.
- When are you calling back?
- Soon. Get moving, Michelle.
Oh, she still loves you.
The question is how much.
- Edgar Stiles.
- Send the deployment group to my screen.
- It's updating. You want the last version?
-  Just send it.
- Are reinforcements there?
- Some are on site now.
Some will be there in 15 minutes. You want
me to send the upgraded grid when it's in?
Ms Dessler?
Yes.
Yes, do that.
No. No, we can't eliminate the Midwest or
any region within the missile's flying range.
All areas of the country are vulnerable?
Yes, that's what I'm trying to tell you.
This warhead could hit anywhere.
We're putting together the projected
casualty numbers. They're gonna be high.
Yeah.
- Where are we on the apartments search?
- Nothing so far.
- LAPD there yet?
- They're on their way.
I'll be at com.
I can't do this.
Can't do what?
I can't sacrifice the lives of all those people
if this warhead goes off.
- She called me.
- Who? Who called you?
The hostile who has Tony.
- When? What did she say?
- A couple of minutes ago.
She said to redeploy our men
so she can get away...
or Tony dies.
-  Yes, sir?
- Patch me through to Jack Bauer.
Take your team.
Start working the second floor, building 11.
-  Jack, you read me?
- I copy.
We've got something.
The suspect contacted Michelle.
She confirms she's holding Tony hostage.
She's trying to use him as leverage against
Michelle to open an escape route.
- Is Michelle there?
- I'm right here, Jack.
Do we have any idea where she is?
She wants me to clear the northeast driveway.
She's going to call to confirm I did it.
- When?
- I don't know. It could be any second.
I want you to make her believe
that you're still cooperating with her.
I need you to draw her into the open.
I promise you that we will do
everything we can for Tony.
OK.
Stay ready for her call.
I'll pull all our units out of the northeast
driveway, put them in concealed positions.
She might change her mind at the last minute
and try another escape route.
We'll be ready for that, but I want her
to believe Michelle's complying.
Once she's 50 yards outside of the complex
and can't re-enter, our teams will converge.
- Let me know when your men can redeploy.
- Copy that.
- Are you gonna be all right?
- Yeah.
- I was gonna do what she wanted.
- Michelle.
I didn't call you right away. All I could
think of at first was saving Tony's life.
It's OK. It's done.
Los Angeles Police Department.
Open up!
Yes, sir.
All designated teams, prepare to move into
secondary positions on my command. Curtis.
- What should I do?
- Some residents aren't cooperating.
Have LAPD units arrest anybody
that's giving us a problem.
Why don't we pull some of the resources
off the search?
We'd have a better chance
of finding the hostile.
The hostile will look for any sign
that Michelle's betrayed her.
We have to act as if we have
no idea they've been in contact.
- Understood.
- Once you're done with LAPD, I need you.
You got it.
- Bill, this is Jack. Do you copy?
- Yeah.
We're ready to go here.
Any new communication from the hostile?
No, Michelle's still waiting for her call.
Have you been able to make any ID on scene?
Forensics tried to pull prints,
but came up with nothing.
Same result here.
No match on the voiceprint.
She's managed to stay completely
out of the radar.
We're gonna have to hope she slips up and
makes a mistake, otherwise we're in trouble.
- Proceed when ready. We're standing by.
- Copy that.
All northeast driveway teams,
move into secondary positions. We're a go.
- Hi. What are you doing here?
- Hey.
You're supposed to stay in your apartment.
There's some crazy person loose.
- Yeah, I know. I know. Hey, where's Joss?
- He just got up.
Can you just get him?
I need to talk to him. Something happened.
Joss!
- What's going on?
- Nothing, just weird stuff.
- What?
- Nothing.
- Why don't you just tell me?
- No, it's cool.
- Hey, what's going on?
- Hey, man, how are you?
Not a sound.
I just got off a very disturbing phone call
from the Chinese foreign secretary.
They're pressing us on the consulate attack?
It's much worse than that, David.
The fallout from that attack
you authorised is escalating.
They're determined to pin this on us.
If they confirm this is one of our men, I don't
have to tell you how disastrous it would be.
No, sir, you don't.
This is not conclusive enough for the Chinese
to turn this into an international incident.
- If they find corroborating evidence?
- CTU is preventing that from happening,
including getting this agent out of sight
until it blows over.
I gave you the authority to make the decision,
but you never should have
ordered that assault.
If we hadn't carried out the raid,
we'd be nowhere in stopping the missile.
And where are we, David?
Is there some progress I don't know about?
CTU is closing in
on one of Marwan's associates.
If they apprehend her in time, they feel
they can use her to find Marwan.
Do you know how speculative that sounds?
My God, we're never gonna find it in time!
Don't say that!
We will. You must believe that
if you're going to lead today.
How? Every second brings that missile
closer to its target,
which, for all we know, is us.
We are not sitting on our hands, Mr President.
We are using every resource at our disposal
to find this missile.
We will prevent the warhead from going off.
I wish I was as confident as you are.
You need to be.
Remain presidential.
Demand nothing less than success
from your people and you will get it.
All right.
- What do I tell the Chinese foreign secretary?
- You don't.
Let Mike handle this. He'll tell them
unless they have proof of our involvement,
you don't wanna hear from them today.
-  Mr Buchanan, Agent Bern on six.
- Send it to my cellphone.
Yes, sir.
Buchanan.
It's Agent Bern, sir. I got a message
to call you as soon as I landed.
- Are we on a secure line?
- Yes, sir, it's an encrypted cell.
The Chinese are pressing the case that we're
involved in the assault on their consulate.
Have they found evidence
beyond the video of me?
No, and we have to make sure they don't.
I want you to start fabricating an alibi
with CTU in San Diego.
Make it look like you worked there
during the assault.
Our transport's arriving right now, sir.
I'll get right on it.
The alibi has to withstand careful scrutiny.
San Diego phone logs, rosters
and mainframe records all have to back it up.
- It'll be airtight, sir.
- It has to be.
Sir, about my family, do you think there's any
chance the Chinese will try to get to them?
They can't. We've already contacted your wife
and we've moved her and your kids to a hotel.
- I'll be in touch, Agent Bern.
- Thank you very much, sir.
Drive.
- What the hell is this?
- I think you already know what this is.
CTU sent a team into our consulate
just a few hours ago.
You were on the team
and our consul general was killed.
You're gonna tell me who was responsible.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Really?
Then why were you being transported here
by helicopter from CTU Los Angeles?
- You don't know where I came from.
- Actually, I do.
Before entering CTU earlier tonight,
we turned our satellite on that location.
While I was questioning your superiors,
our satellite picked up someone
being taken away by helicopter.
So what? That wasn't me.
No, it was you!
The Chinese government insists
that someone take responsibility
for the death of our consul.
What does that mean, "take responsibility"?
Now, I believe
you were only following orders.
Tell us who gave you orders
and I'll let you go.
I'm not telling you anything.
I believe you're gonna change your mind.
- Yes?
-  Have you redeployed your men?
- Yes, I have.
- Bill, it's Jack. Uplink is on.
You sure they followed
your instructions?
-  I'm sure.
- It's starting to rain pretty hard.
Michelle...
do you love Tony?
- Yes, I love him.
- Good.
If I find out you're trying to play me,
the first thing I'll do is blow his brains out.
Don't think there's anything you can do
to stop it. There's not. You understand?
- OK. I understand.
- Good. Stay by the phone.
All com analysts, clone that call
and filter it through all our servers.
- Do you have multiple source?
- No, just one feed, low res.
I know the configuration, Edgar.
I need to know if we can multiplex.
- We need to pinpoint the source.
- I was gonna do that.
This is happening now.
I shouldn't have to walk you through this.
- Dammit!
- You don't have to. I'm setting it up now.
Go to Delta two, Edgar. It's all there.
I will not let this thing fall apart
because of technical incompetence.
All right. All our visible forces
have been pulled away from this street.
OK, good.
Jack.
We've got something.
Building three, west entrance.
Edgar, video feed.
- Yes.
OK, we're on our way.
- OK, it's them.
I've got a gun on Tony.
My finger's on the trigger.
If I move it, he'll die.
I told you, I moved my men.
She's completely in the open. She's running
a huge risk exposing herself like that.
So far, so good.
- She's crossing the street.
When she gets near the car, she can't
stay on top of him. That's our chance.
- She's moving towards the black jag.
- All teams, hold your position.
Here's the deal. Once we're in the car
and have cleared the area,
I'm gonna call you and I'm gonna tell you
where you can find Tony.
OK.
- All right, move. Everybody, move.
- Bill, not yet! All teams, stand down.
I see your men. You lied to me, you
bitch. You are not gonna take me alive, got it?
No! No!
Bill, they're gone. She blew herself up
in the car. She took Tony with her.
They're gone.
- Bill Buchanan requested a conference call.
- Yes, sir. We were waiting for you to begin.
- Bill, we're all here. Go ahead.
- I'm afraid that Marwan's associate,
the woman we hoped
would help us locate the missile,
has killed herself and one of our agents.
Oh, my God.
Bill, did she leave behind
any physical evidence that could help us?
It doesn't appear so.
So, what is CTU gonna do now
to find the missile?
Mr President, at this point,
CTU has no reasonable expectation of finding
the missile before it reaches its target.
This is it. It's going to happen.
What do we do?
At this point we have no choice
but to alert all state and federal agencies
and focus all our resources
on managing the aftermath.
But we don't even know the missile's target.
I know. We can assume it will be a major city,
but no matter what the target is,
there will be widespread panic
across this country.
We need to mobilise the army
and the National Guard in every state
and draw up a declaration of martial law.
Yes, we need to do that.
Bill.
All federal agencies need to prepare
for the aftermath of a nuclear attack.
CTU's priority should be
disaster management.
- Redeploy your people now.
- Understood.
Edgar Stiles.
Tell Jack the field operation is over. Have him
bring his people back here immediately.
Got it.
The worst disaster in this country's history
has taken place on my watch.
I gave you the responsibility to stop this.
You've failed me, David,
and you've failed your country.
I can't even imagine
what you must be feeling.
I know part of you is second-guessing
your decision...
but you couldn't place Tony's life
before the lives of
potentially millions of people.
You made exactly the decision Tony would
have wanted you to make. That's our job.
That's why we sign on.
We decided we were gonna leave this.
Go somewhere and start again.
- Michelle.
- I wanna get to work and find this missile.
- No, no. I want you to go home.
- I'll be OK, Bill.
It's not advice. It's an order.
- Buchanan.
- Sir, Jack said he's not pulling his men out.
- We have orders from the White House.
- Yeah, but he says he's not ready.
Put him on the videophone
in the situation room.
You lied to me, you bitch.
You are not gonna take me alive, got it?
Play it again.
Give me more volume on the phone.
- We need to redeploy.
- Do it!
Jack.
Tony's gone.
I'm sorry, Curtis.
Look, just play it again, please.
Yeah.
Jack, you've got a phone call.
- This is Bauer.
-  Jack, why haven't you redeployed?
- The operation's over.
- Because it doesn't make any sense.
Everything we know about this woman
tells us she's a professional, not a fanatic.
We had her cornered. Her next move was
to negotiate for her freedom, not kill herself.
In theory I agree with you,
but you saw what I saw.
All I saw were two darkened figures
concealed by an umbrella in an explosion,
and I saw that from half a block away.
Jack, you've got to focus now. Nobody here
is holding you responsible for Tony's death.
- Let this go.
- You're not listening. All I want...
We reviewed the tactical feed.
There's nothing to suggest we were deceived.
Look, I know Tony was your friend,
and you probably feel responsible
for getting him involved...
This is not about Tony! This is about her,
and until I can absolutely confirm she is dead,
I am maintaining this perimeter
and I am gonna continue this search.
I'm under orders from the White House.
You have ten minutes,
then I want you to move out.
- Can you enhance the image from here?
- Not in the field.
Then play it again.
-  Here's the deal.
- I still can't hear properly. Give me a headset.
... I'm gonna call you and I'm gonna tell you
where you can find Tony.
I see your men. You lied to me, you bitch.
You are not gonna take me alive, got it?
- Play back the last 15 seconds.
- What are you seeing?
It's not what I'm seeing.
Come on, play it back.
I see your men. You lied to me, you bitch.
It's pouring rain.
You see it bouncing off the car.
- You can't hear it on her side of the call.
- She was making that call from indoors.
She'd want a position
with a clean line of sight to the car.
That would put her in the building
the couple exited from. Get teams ready.
All teams, we're gonna converge
on building 11.
-  Converge on building 11.
-  Copy that.
Well, they're heading back in.
Looks like my neighbours died for nothing.
They know you're still in here.
Open up the palm of your hand.
Here are the keys.
Take off your cuffs.
Put these on. We're getting outta here.
OK, now cuff yourself back up.
Let's go.
We've got every way in and out covered
and men going room by room.
- We need to take her alive.
- Everyone's aware.
Agent Bauer.
We found fresh blood outside an apartment.
- Where?
- 208.
- Stand down until we get there.
- Copy that.
Curtis, take the door.
Curtis, she went this way.
Turn around.
Move.
Don't move! Drop the gun.
- It's over.
- Take one more step and I'll kill him.
Do it, Jack. Do what you have to do.
Shut up.
Do you really have what it takes to let me
kill him while you're looking him in the eye?
Yes.
I believe you.
So what's to stop me from shooting him?
You can't...
kill me,
can you?
You need me.
Tony.
Hostile is down. I repeat, the hostile is down.
Get a medic down here.
I want her conscious as soon as possible.
Look at me. Are you OK?
Are you OK?
Yeah.
- Get me that medic now!
He's on his way.
Does Michelle know I'm alive?
No, not yet. I'll call CTU on my cell
so you can talk to her privately.
Thanks.
- Buchanan.
- This is Jack.
Jack, have you redeployed back to CTU?
- No. We just apprehended the hostile.
- What?
She's unconscious but she's unharmed.
Tony's OK too.
Thank God. I'll alert the White House.
OK, good. Bill, Tony wants to talk to Michelle.
Can you put her on the line?
She's not here. I sent her home.
I'll find her and patch her through.
Thanks.
- Hello?
- Michelle, it's Bill.
Tony's alive.
- What?
- He wasn't in the car.
He's OK.
I'll let Tony explain to you.
Hold on for him.
Michelle, it's me.
Tony.
- Oh, my God.
- It's OK, sweetheart.
Oh, my God.
- What happened?
- She made somebody else wear my clothes.
She needed to keep me alive until she got out.
Jack figured it out.
He was able to save me.
- I don't know what to say.
- You don't have to say anything, sweetheart.
I'm coming to CTU right now.
I'll see you in a few minutes.
Michelle.
I love you.
I love you, Tony.
Get Palmer patched through.
We'll have to structure a deal.
- All right.
- She's conscious.
Pick her up.
Call the White House now.
Where is Marwan?
That's what I thought.
We're both professionals.
You know that I can force this information
outta you, but I'm running outta time.
We never get second chances in our work,
but I'll give you one.
I have the power to give you a deal
signed by the president
that grants you immunity
from past and present crimes.
In exchange, you can help me find Marwan
and stop this warhead from hitting its target.
Do you understand?
You are either gonna help me now,
or I will kill you.
Show me the deal.
You were part of the team
that mounted the assault on our consulate,
an operation that resulted
in the death of our consul.
Who lead the mission?
- Who was responsible?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
Please, Mr Bern, you're wasting time.
Give us a statement and we'll release you.
I'm telling the truth. You'll have to release me
when CTU realises what's happened to me.
Actually, Mr Bern, no one will ever know.
No one will ever tell them.
What are you talking about?
The China Queen container ship
is moored at the port of San Diego.
If you don't give us our statement,
we'll put you on board and you will arrive
in 18 days in the port of Guangzhou.
Then we will transport you 2800 miles
to the province of Xinjiang
where you will be remanded to the maximum
security labour camp on the Siberian border.
- You wouldn't do that.
- Why wouldn't we, Mr Bern? We want justice.
If you won't tell us who is ultimately
responsible for the situation at the consulate,
that leaves you.
Your wife and your two daughters
will not be notified.
The US government will not be notified.
Therefore, there will be no chance
for prisoner exchange.
There will be positively no chance of escape...
for the rest of your life.
Decide, Mr Bern.
The China Queen is on a tight schedule.
- I don't know.
- All we want is a name.
A recorded statement
naming the person responsible
for what happened at the consulate.
Then...
- Then what happens?
- You will walk out of that door.
No. I meant...
to him.
As I said,
all we want is justice.
His name...
is Jack Bauer.
Visiontext Subtitles: Margaret Burke
ENGLISH SDH