I'm reprogramming
the CTU key card right now.
Good. Couriers are delivering the canisters
to the targets. They'll be in place soon.
- When are you launching the attacks?
- After you're done at CTU.
When these terrorists attack,
you'll need to maintain order.
We should think of a pre-emptive declaration
of martial law in the greater Los Angeles area.
If CTU can't find this man Bierko,
we're gonna get hit.
Why didn't you just tell me you were alive?
If you knew I was alive
you would have been at risk. I had no choice.
I'm happy that you're alive. I am.
But I can't give you what you want right now.
Michelle's murder was part of a bigger plan
to supply terrorists with Sentox nerve gas.
- Who was behind it?
Christopher Henderson.
Whatever he's not telling us is important.
He can tolerate an inhuman amount of pain.
Thousands of lives are at stake. Tell me what
I need to know to stop this insanity. Please.
I'm sorry, Jack,
but I can't tell you what you wanna know.
This is Bauer.
We've been compromised. Someone used
a stolen key card to access CTU.
Freeze! Drop the gun.
Bill, it's Jack.
I think he tried to deploy nerve gas.
Code six! Everybody out! Go! Go!
Seal all the rooms.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Chloe.
Attention all CTU personnel.
This facility has been contaminated
with Sentox VX-1 nerve gas.
I repeat, this facility has been contaminated.
There are two safe zones. On the main floor,
in the situation room and Medical.
On the second floor,
the safe zones are the CTU director's office,
and holding room four.
These areas must remain sealed pending
the arrival of the Chemical Response Team.
If you are in any of these sealed areas,
do not attempt to leave
until the CRT clears the environment.
I'm on my way, but it could take 30 minutes
to gather all the CRT personnel you need.
I understand, Curtis, but we need CRT here
now. This is a high priority.
- Get here as fast as you can.
- Copy. I'll call in a few minutes with updates.
Excuse me.
- This is Bauer.
- Jack, it's Bill. I just talked to Curtis.
He's with the Chemical Response Team.
- They won't get here for at least 30 minutes.
- Why not?
Most were sent to Tyler Memorial. The rest
are en route to high probability targets.
We'll keep working.
Our networks are up, right?
The phones are working, computers are up.
I can coordinate with Division from here.
- What do you need?
- I need to know if Henderson's alive.
- Where is he?
- Agent Burke took him to the isolation clinic.
I don't know if they made it.
- You can tell if you pull up a grid.
- What about CTU's response plan?
Gas masks are in the armoury,
atropine's in storage.
Both areas are contaminated.
We can't get to them without being exposed.
Bill, I'm gonna have to get right back to you.
Chloe, I know how difficult this is,
but there's nothing we can do for him.
I need you to come back to work.
Tell me how to pull up a building grid.
I'll do it myself.
- Jack, we can try to pull it up.
- Get started.
Chloe, CTU is immobile right now.
Everything is going to go through Comm.
That's you. I need you back at work.
- Can't.
- Yes, you can.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can!
Mr. Bauer.
- What?
- I can help her.
I'm a clinical psychologist.
Thank you.
Chloe.
My name's Dr Landes.
He was a friend of yours. What was his name?
- Edgar.
I'd like you to turn away from Edgar
and focus on me, please.
Chloe,
you're in shock,
and I'd like to help you through it.
The only thing I'm gonna ask you to do
is sit in this chair and collect your breath.
Let's do that now.
Just collect your breath, just for a second.
He was such a good guy.
I just treated him like crap all day.
- This is my fault.
- Sir?
Someone stole my key card
and used it to get in the building.
It was missing, and I didn't say anything.
- Why not?
- I thought they stole my wallet for money.
How could you not report it?
I was embarrassed.
I didn't want anyone to know I got beat up.
So we're all gonna die
because you were embarrassed?
- What are you doing?
- I wanna know what's going on.
- No, I can't allow that.
- I won't sit in bed while CTU's under attack.
Fine.
- How long are we supposed to be like this?
- I haven't received any news.
Oh, my God.
Jack, we've got the building grid.
- Buchanan.
- It's Jack. The grid's up.
All right. Check the isolation zones
that have logged in. They'll have survivors.
Two zones have logged on in Medical.
- Try them. I'm gonna keep this line open.
- OK. Hold on.
- Clinic.
- Dr Besson, it's Jack Bauer.
What's going on?
A terrorist infiltrated CTU and deployed
Sentox through the ventilation system.
That's why we sealed off rooms. I need to
know if Burke got to Medical with Henderson.
- Yes, he did.
- Henderson's here right now?
- Tony, is that you?
- How long are we gonna be locked down?
Right now we're in stand-by. We're trying
to figure out how to clean out the air supply.
Doctor Besson?
Tony?
- Get a security feed.
- This program's not set up for that.
Try a redirect. Doctor Besson?
- What are you doing?
- Move aside.
All right, I've got video.
Oh, God. He's got a gun.
Patch me through to their intercom.
- Do it.
- We can hear them, but they can't hear us.
- Don't kill him. He's got information we need.
- He killed my wife!
- Tony, please, don't kill him.
- Move aside.
I don't want to shoot you, but I will. Move it!
You remember me?
My name is Tony Almeida.
You killed my wife,
Michelle Dessler, this morning.
He's gonna kill him. Hurry. Hurry!
She was my life, and you took her.
And now I'm gonna take yours.
- I got it.
- Tony, I've got you on the security feed.
- Stay out of this, Jack.
- Please, just listen to me.
You can't do this.
I know how you feel right now.
I lost Teri the exact same way,
to one of our own.
I know what it feels to be betrayed like this.
But, Tony, Henderson has information that
can save thousands and thousands of lives.
And I know that doesn't make you feel
better right now, but I know you, Tony.
I know you don't want
to make this situation any worse than it is.
Please.
Please just let us finish our interrogation.
Hurry up.
Agent Burke, please continue.
When Henderson starts talking,
focus on how to find the Sentox canisters
and how we can find Bierko.
Tell me where to find Bierko.
Where?
Nowhere.
What is your computer password?
No.
No password.
- Agent Burke, can we increase the dose?
- Not without killing him.
Take a break then start again.
Get back to me when you've got anything.
Yes, sir.
- How could CTU be hit?
- We're not sure, Mr. Vice President.
Are you telling me
they didn't have any safeguards?
They had partial containment,
but reports indicate
that 40% % of their personnel
have been taken out.
- You mean, they've been killed.
- I'm afraid so, sir.
CTU is protecting this city. Are you saying
they're no longer capable of doing that?
They've been seriously compromised, yes.
What are we going to do? We've got terrorists
with nerve gas out there. Who will stop them?
- I suggest an emergency restructuring.
- Meaning what?
The Chemical Response Team will go in,
neutralise the gas at CTU,
and I will take a team in there
and personally manage the operation.
- How soon can you do that?
- Within the hour.
- Fine. Do it.
- Yes, sir.
All right. We're operational.
It's not a complete disaster.
Mr. President, it is.
I can see no other option but to impose
martial law on the city of Los Angeles.
My advisors believe if the military takes over
and detains people, it could create mayhem.
It's only a matter of time before
more canisters are released in public places
and you will have mayhem,
except without soldiers to contain it.
What do I tell the public? We've got nerve gas
all over the city, but we don't know where?
You don't have to get into that.
Tie it to that earlier incident at the airport.
- I'm going to get resistance from all sides.
- That's true, sir.
We may have to swallow some saltwater,
but wouldn't it be worth it?
If we can keep the people off the streets,
safe from another public attack?
- I don't know, Hal.
- Sir, consider this.
If we clear the streets
of everybody except the military,
these terrorists won't be able to move
as freely as they are now.
We have to do whatever we can
to stop the people behind this.
CTU is no longer an obstacle,
at least for the time being.
Good. Have our men move from their
current positions and go to the new target.
How much of the nerve gas
will they release there?
All of it.
Excuse me.
- Chloe, are you ready to go back to work?
- What do you need?
You. We can't break Henderson. I need you
to try to decrypt the files from his computer.
I tried. It didn't work.
Maybe somebody else can do it.
Chloe, you're the only person
in the room qualified.
Chloe, please. Don't shut down on me now.
I'm upset about everything too, but you know
how it works. We do not quit until it's over.
You're not helping her.
You're just making things worse.
I am sure that you are qualified
to help someone through distress
over an extended period of time, but we
do not have an extended period of time.
If you don't mind stepping aside
so I can do my job, I'd appreciate it.
You don't have to be qualified to help people,
you just have to be there.
Like you were there for my daughter.
What does that mean?
You're 20 years older than she is.
I know what you're doing.
I've done nothing but try and help her. How
dare you accuse me of taking advantage?
You did.
Dad, you can be angry at me all you want.
But before I met Barry, I didn't want to live.
Do you understand that?
Fine, I'll get back to work.
If everyone could just relax.
Jack, we have a problem.
What?
Chloe, I just saw the alarm. What's going on?
Pressure indicators in contaminated zones
are showing traces of sublimated polymer.
- What does that mean?
- The nerve gas must be mixed with an acid.
The acid's breaking down
the seal between the rooms.
- How long till the seal fails completely?
- It's hard to say for sure.
- Give me an estimate.
- It's deteriorating quickly.
- 15 minutes, 20 at the most.
- And then what?
Gas permeates the seal and enters the room.
Then it's over.
Get me schematics on all the isolated zones.
Mr. Vice President, with all due respect,
I'm not trying to usurp your position.
I'm simply trying to serve the president
the best way I can.
Yes, sir.
What was that about?
I was trying to convince Gardner to let me
help him draft the president's statement.
Charles is letting Hal write his statement?
He's insisted.
And the president gave him the go-ahead.
That means Gardner's effectively
making policy. You gotta stop him.
I'm trying.
But you know the pressure he's under today.
He wants all the counsel he can get.
And Hal's only too eager to help out.
Of course he's eager.
He's got his eye on the Oval Office.
Anything he can do to speed up Charles's
downfall puts him closer to the presidency.
Martha,
you have to intervene.
Hal feeds the president ideas.
We saw it at the WTO. We saw it in Chicago.
When they work, Hal takes the credit for 'em.
When they don't, the president takes the hits.
- Have you reminded Charles of that?
- I can't.
Hal's the vice president.
I'm just the Chief of Staff.
You have influence
that supersedes any constitutional rank.
And now's the time to use it.
- I want to see the statement when it's issued.
- You will.
I checked the readings
from all uncontaminated zones.
The testing you've been doing
in your respective areas is consistent.
The Sentox gas released into the air duct
system contains a corrosive agent
that is eating away
at the barrier seals protecting safe zones.
I'm not gonna pull any punches.
CRT will not be here in time to help us.
At this point,
our only hope is to help ourselves.
We need to find a way to either neutralise
or flush the Sentox out of contaminated areas
before the barrier seals fail,
and the gas enters the safe zones.
I want all personnel working on this problem.
We don't have much time.
Do what you can.
We'll hope for the best.
Maybe we can do something.
Access the ventilation system.
Even if I could,
it doesn't mean we could do anything.
Just try.
Maybe it's not so bad.
Maybe the numbers are off.
They're not.
Even if the seals leak,
CRT could get here in time.
The only reason she's here
is because I asked her to stay.
If something happens to her,
it's going to be because of what I did.
There is no way you could know
that CTU was vulnerable.
Jack.
Have you got something?
If I slow the seals' breakdown,
I can flush the area using the air conditioning.
Do it.
- Something's wrong. It isn't responding.
- Why not?
It's being blocked
by some program I can't get to,
probably on a computer near holding four.
- Can you get me in there?
- This is a false wall. The air in there is clean.
- Can he get to the computer?
- Yes.
But after the safe zone,
he'll be in a contaminated area.
What? He can't go through
a contaminated area.
I can hold my breath. Sentox
won't be absorbed over that short a time.
- I'll be fine.
- You can't hold your breath that long.
I only have to get to the computer, disconnect
the program and get to the ventilated room.
Once I'm back,
how long will it take to clear the Sentox?
About 20 seconds,
based on the cubic footage.
- Jack, what if we can't ventilate that room?
- Chloe thinks we can. This is our only option.
- CRT is not gonna get here in time.
- The seals are now 80% % gone.
- What's the bottom line?
- We have less than 20 minutes.
We are on channel one. If you need
anyone else, we'll patch you through.
As soon as I go through,
you have to replace this behind me.
Jack, it's time. Go now.
Now.
Chloe, I just completed the airlock. I'm getting
ready to move into the ventilation room.
I'll tap my comm unit
when I'm back in the safe room.
All right. Jack, if that airlock leaks, we'll
all be dead within the next three minutes.
It's not gonna leak, Chloe.
OK.
- I'm going in.
- OK.
- The seal corrosion is now at 86%.
- Is there anything we can do here?
Just wait. There's nothing we can do
to get your dad out any faster.
- Don't talk down to me, Chloe.
- Listen, we're in a crisis situation here, OK?
Tempers are bound to flare.
Just everybody breathe.
What's with you and the breathing?
Is that your solution to everything?
- He's back in the room.
- It's too soon.
He couldn't have found the program
and disabled it yet.
He's got 15 more seconds
before the room clears.
- What's it mean that he's finished?
- I don't know.
- It could be good, right?
- It could be good or bad.
That's what "I don't know" means.
All right, the room is clear. Are you OK?
I couldn't get to it.
Chloe, you're right, I saw it.
There's a program running on the AC control,
but there's a security grate behind the vent.
- I don't see it on my system.
- Trust me, it's there.
I just found it. It was a security upgrade
in the last two years.
Somebody didn't file it properly
so I didn't see it.
Are there other vents into that wall?
- They've all been upgraded.
- There's gotta be a door. Where does it lead?
To a corridor above holding four.
None of us can get there.
- Who's in holding room four?
- Lynn McGill.
Are there any vented rooms
we can get him to?
No, Jack. There's nothing.
Patch me through to him.
- McGill here.
- Lynn, it's Jack.
We found a computer interrupt
in the AC control.
If we shut that down in the next few minutes,
we can stop the gas permeating safe zones.
Well, that's good news.
The problem is, you're the only person
close enough to get to it. Chloe?
It's above the room where you are now.
Take the stairs, go around the corner,
it's the room on your left.
OK. How are we gonna do this, Jack?
Lynn, the truth is if I could get there, I would
do this myself, but I'm not close enough.
No one still alive is.
You're the only person who can do this.
But you have to do it without protection.
- I see.
- No, you don't.
As soon as you open the door,
your room will become contaminated.
You can hold your breath long enough
to fix the problem, but we can't airlock you.
There are two of us in here, Jack.
Sir, this is Harry Swinton.
So you're saying that if he does this,
then we're both gonna die?
I'm so sorry.
We don't have a choice, Harry.
How do we know that you're not making this
up so you don't have to sacrifice yourself?
You don't. All I can ask you to do
is believe me. I'm telling you the truth.
That's easy for you to say, sir.
You're not about to die.
It's not easy for me to say.
Hold on.
We have to do this, Harry. We're gonna die
anyway. If we don't, so will everyone in CTU.
We have to do this.
OK, Jack. Go ahead.
Once you get into the ventilation room,
the computer will be on your right.
There's a program running
on the computer. You need to quit out of it.
Lynn, we don't have a lot of time.
I'll do it.
Chloe,
I'm sorry about how I acted earlier,
and about your friend that died.
OK.
- Thanks.
- I've been wanting to ask you something.
Did you have contact with my dad
while he was gone?
- I sent him information about once a month.
- What kind of information?
- A lot of different things.
- About me?
Actually, almost all of it was about you.
Your break-up with Chase, your depression.
- How did you get...
- I'm really good at getting information.
I don’t judge it, I just pass it on.
I'm sorry about you and Chase.
It must have been really painful.
Yeah. It was.
So you talked to him too?
- Chase? No.
- You know where he is?
- No, but I could find out if you want.
- No, no. It's all right.
Barry thinks I should let that go.
He's probably right.
Yeah, well, shrinks are always giving advice
that they probably don't follow themselves.
- How are you doing?
- I woke up with a guy I'll never see again.
And I just watched one of my best friends die
right in front of me, so I guess not that great.
Yeah.
Replace the panel. Pull up the security feed
from the observation room.
You be a good girl for Mommy, OK?
If she tells you you have to go to bed,
you have to go to bed.
- When are you coming home?
- I don't know, honey.
- If I fall asleep, will you wake me up?
- Of course I will.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
OK.
I'm going in now, Harry. Say goodbye.
- I love you.
- I love you too, Daddy.
Bye, baby girl.
Chloe, we're ready. I'm going in.
OK. Good luck. And thanks for doing this.
Yeah.
- He did it.
- Is the AC responding?
- Yes.
- How long before the Sentox is neutralised?
At least 15 minutes. But it should stop
eating away at the seals immediately.
Polymer count is down. It looks like
the seals will hold until all zones are clear.
Lynn, Harry, I don't know if you can still
hear me, but what you did was successful.
The seals are holding.
I will personally notify your families
and tell them of the sacrifice you made.
I'm so sorry.
I don't know what else to say.
Thank you.
I'm OK.
Pull up the security feed to Medical.
Can you hear me? What's your name?
No.
No name.
You're wasting your time.
It's Jack Bauer.
What have you got from Henderson?
Nothing. He's still not talking.
OK, keep working on him. As soon as
the barriers go up I'll get back to you.
Chloe, I don't think
we're gonna break Henderson.
All we're gonna get is from his computer.
Keep working on it.
- My team is gone. How am I gonna do that?
- Only work on his files.
Kim. As soon as the barriers go up, I want you
to go to Medical and let them check you out.
- No. When the barriers go up, I'm leaving.
- Please do this for me. We still need to talk.
There's nothing to talk about.
- Don't be in such a hurry to cut me off.
- You cut me off.
Listen to me, I'm not angry. I love you.
But there's nothing left to say,
except I don't want to be around you.
Every time I am,
something horrible happens. People die.
And I know that's not your fault,
but I can't be a part of it.
I don't want you to be a part of that.
All I want is for one day,
you and I just to be able
to spend time together.
Kim, I had to give you up once.
I'm not gonna let that happen again.
Dad...
I can't.
- Hi.
- Hey.
God, that was close.
You all right?
No.
"An emergency peacekeeping force. "
That was Hal's suggestion. I think it works.
Charles, aren't you afraid an edict of this kind
could do far more damage
than any chemical weapon ever could?
Martha, CTU has been attacked.
Our first line of defence is shut down.
People were killed because of this weapon.
That's just a prelude to what's gonna happen.
More nerve gas will be released.
I can guarantee it.
Look, if you or Mike
have any better ideas, please.
I would be glad to hear them.
- Mike, could we have a moment?
- Certainly.
What is it, Martha?
If you, Charles Logan,
really feel that martial law is your only option,
I will support you.
But what I will not do is stand by
and watch Hal Gardner use you
to promote his own agenda.
- Please, give me some credit.
- He has done it before.
He is not the president. You are.
I'm doing this
because it's the right thing to do.
I don't know
how much more of this I can take.
I really don't.
David's assassination,
the nerve gas, the murder of those hostages,
Walt Cummings' betrayal...
And you.
I almost lost you.
I didn't lose you, did I?
No, Charles.
You didn't lose me.
I'm still here.
- Yes.
- We're set in position.
Good.
The men are there. They need the schematics.
Who is it?
Just a client.
- Yes?
- Have you got it yet?
I told you I'd call you as soon as I have
everything. I'm still waiting on a few items.
I'm paying you a lot of money, Collette.
If you could've got the specs of a facility this
secure from someone else, you would have.
But you didn't. You called me,
and I'll have it for you in a few minutes.
- What's wrong?
- Nothing.
Difficult client.
I wish I knew exactly what it is you did.
I might be able to help.
You do help me.
Oh... I can't.
I have to go and finish something.
Finish this.
- How long until the air's safe?
- Momentarily.
All right, thank you very much.
Buchanan.
- Karen Hayes from Homeland Security.
- Karen.
I'm running a damage assessment.
I need your body count.
We don't have one yet. We'll know more
when CRT gets here and the barriers lift.
What's your best estimate?
I'm guessing we'll need at least 20 in Comm,
35 in Tactical and other departments.
I'm on my way over there with a core team.
We can make adjustments when I get there.
- You're coming here now?
- Yes.
- I see.
- I'll be there soon.
- How's your progress?
- Good. I've reformatted their main servers.
All tactical protocols
will have to go through me.
I may have to replace some personnel
with my people. Is that a problem?
Absolutely not. After what they've been
through, most won't be up to full capacity.
We need to identify these people quickly
and send them home.
Will I need approval from Bill Buchanan
to make a personnel change?
No, Bill won't be in charge when we get there.
I will.
For all intents and purposes,
CTU is no longer an operational entity.
It's a building with workers
who will report to us.
We're clear. I'm going back to Medical.
Kim.
- I have to finish this now.
- I know.
Goodbye, Dad.
Yeah.
Goodbye.
Excuse me, Jack.
I just wanted to say thank you
for saving our lives.
We definitely couldn't have
gotten through this without you.
Take her outside of this city.
Don't make any stops. You understand?
- Looks like he's dead.
- No. His nervous system is shut down.
- Well, can you wake him up?
- No.
- Almeida.
- Tony, it's Jack. I'm on my way.
Yeah, Jack. Henderson's in a coma.
He's not coming out of it.
You've had your chance. He's mine now.
- Dammit, Tony, just wait until I get there.
- No. I'm done waiting.
Don't do this. It won't bring back Michelle.
No. But I'll feel better.
Trust me, you won't.
You're probably right. I'll let you know.
Tony!
Tony! Dammit.
What'd Jack say?
He's on his way here.
We'll figure out what to do when he gets here.
There's nothing to figure out.
This guy's cooked.
Tony! Tony!
I... couldn't do it.
It's all right. It's all right.
Come on. Come on.
Stay with me. Stay with me.
I need help! Somebody help!
No, no. No. Hang on.
Hang on.
She's gone, Jack.