Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net
- I need Karen Hayes to go away.
- I understand, sir.
I need the president
to sign off on my proposals.
She has gone from
being an irritant to an obstacle.
I wanna talk about your husband's
incompetence and your covering it up.
I did nothing illegal or incorrect.
Your resignation within the hour.
Mr President, I am tendering my resignation.
Is there anything I can do
to change your mind?
No, sir. There is not.
Walid has earned their trust. These men know
something about the bombs that we don't.
These guys aren't connected to anyone.
They're not terrorists.
I'm getting Walid the hell out of there.
You spied on us?
You're worse than they are!
Son of a bitch!
A nuclear bomb just went off,
like, 25 miles from here.
When I'm done with this deal,
I may just buy you a small country.
- Have you found an engineer?
- I told you I would. Now I will.
It's just taking longer.
Start talking, Gray.
I made a mess. Dad's trying to clean it up.
(Jack) What happened?
I hired McCarthy to oversee the job.
The nukes the terrorists are in possession of,
including the one detonated in Valencia,
were supplied by McCarthy
and stolen from you?
Yes.
- Heading to McCarthy's office in Simi Valley.
- Teams are standing by.
Stop. He's my son.
- What are you doing here, Jack?
- I know you're covering up. Gray told me.
McCarthy's not here.
Hey! What are you doing? Put the gun down.
- You work for me.
- No, Dad, he doesn't.
You don't think I'd let you loose
without keeping an eye on you?
This is insane.
I am at the edge of the safe zone
and behind me is the nuclear blast.
Emergency teams are overwhelmed
by the number of injured
in what President Palmer has confirmed
was a tactical nuclear weapon
detonated two hours ago in this Valencia
neighbourhood north of Los Angeles.
More than 12,000 people are estimated
to have perished in the blast.
LAPD is spread thin
but, on an encouraging note,
we've heard that they are...
I just heard about Karen's resignation.
I'm sorry for the loss.
Are you really sorry? Because your worry
seems somewhat hollow to me.
Karen and I have butted heads
the last few weeks.
Nevertheless, I respected her as an adversary.
She never gave me a reason
why she resigned,
but there was something
she wasn't telling me.
This may have something to do with it.
This is the executive order
I presented this morning.
Karen found out I was going
to resubmit it to you.
So she quit?
That makes absolutely no sense to me, Tom.
She's never been afraid of a fight.
Maybe she finally realised
her arguments are invalid
and that this is the only possible response
to the danger we're facing.
Why would I sign off on something
I rejected six hours ago?
Because six hours ago
we didn't know Fayed had nukes.
Even so, you're talking about
suspending habeas corpus,
expanding the length and broadening
the criteria for those detention centres.
Those actions would constitute
an abuse of executive power.
Those actions will
degrade Fayed's network,
limiting his ability to make use
of these remaining nuclear weapons.
Sir, Fayed's sole intention here
is the destruction of our country,
its infrastructure,
social order, entire way of life.
He has the will and means
to make good on that threat.
Have you stopped to think that
I would be forcing the people who elected me
to give up their rights
that define the essence of this country?
Sir, if one more nuke goes off, it will have
been Fayed who has redefined our country.
Pass this out to the cabinet.
We'll convene in 30 minutes.
You're doing the right thing, Mr President.
Reed.
Call the cabinet in for a session.
- We are ramping up.
- Is the president signing off on this?
He wouldn't convene the cabinet
unless he was. Good work, Reed.
- I'm just doing what needs to be done.
- Getting rid of Karen was unpleasant
but she left us no choice.
(phone rings)
- Hayes.
- Sorry I'm late with the briefing.
We're tracking Fayed through McCarthy.
- Bill. I've just had to resign.
- Resign? What are you taking about?
I can't get into it now, but I've asked to be
reassigned to CTU as an on-site liaison.
Karen, you can't leave the president today.
Bill, do you think that I would do this
if I had any other choice?
- Lennox had something to do with this.
- I cannot talk about this right now.
I will see you in a few hours, OK?
Karen...
(phone rings)
- Mr Buchanan?
- What is it, Chloe?
- Jack's not answering his cell phone.
- Try his backup teams.
I tried. They're not answering either.
Maybe he had them all go dark.
He wouldn't do that without telling us first.
Send in a support unit.
- Fine.
- And keep trying Jack.
All right.
- Where do you want us to meet?
- I'll be here an hour dumping hard drives.
- We'll meet you back at the house.
- Make sure it goes according to plan.
- Don't worry.
- It's my job to worry.
(Phillip) It was all for you, Jack.
Everything I worked for, everything I built.
It was all for you.
After you left, I tried to convince myself that
Graem was capable of heading the family,
protecting the company.
I guess on some level
I always knew the truth about him.
I just wasn't willing to admit it to myself.
I don't know what you want me to say.
I want you to understand.
After you left, Graem was all I had.
He pushed you away, didn't he?
I'm really sorry.
Get out. Come on.
Don't do this, Irv.
Whatever Graem's paying you, I'll double it.
Just keep it moving.
Get down on your knees, both of you.
No. You son of a bitch,
at least have the guts to look me in the eye.
I needed to question him.
They were gonna kill us, Jack!
Search his pockets for the keys.
Dammit!
- (phone rings)
- Buchanan.
- Bill, it's Jack.
- We couldn't reach you. Are you all right?
- I'm fine but the backup team has been killed.
- Have you found McCarthy?
- I know how to get to him.
- How?
- My brother.
- You said your brother wasn't involved.
- He lied to me. He didn't tell us everything.
- Based on what?
He tried to have me and my dad killed. I need
you to set up a perimeter around his house.
- I'll send a field team right away.
- Have them do an immediate recon.
I want Burke standing by
with an interrogation kit.
- Jack.
- What?
McCarthy is our only lead to Fayed. We need
to find Fayed before he arms the nukes.
I'll get back to you as soon as I make contact
with the field teams. We need to go.
Rita?
- Where do you think you're going?
- There's a candy machine in the lobby.
- We'll be leaving soon.
- You said that an hour ago.
Sit down, Rita.
(Fayed) Yes?
Good news. I've found someone
to program the trigger codes for your bombs.
- Who?
- I just sent you his profile.
Employment record, education, the whole CV.
You should have it on your screen.
I'm looking at it now. He seems qualified.
He'll get the job done, but he won't work
willingly. He'll need to be coerced.
- OK. When will you have him?
- Within the hour.
Call me when you do.
- Mr Buchanan, you need to listen to this.
- What?
NSA intercepted a stream of chatter.
Part of it's an audio recording.
They've identified one of the voices
as belonging to Fayed.
(McCarthy) I've found someone
to program the trigger codes on your bombs.
- (Fayed) Who?
- I just sent you his profile.
Employment record, education, the whole CV.
It should be on your screen.
(Fayed) I'm looking at it now.
He seems qualified.
(McCarthy) He'll get the job done, but he won't
work willingly. He'll need to be coerced.
- (Fayed) OK. When will you have him?
- Within the hour.
The second voice matches the sample
from McCarthy's voicemail.
They lost Numair in the explosion, so
McCarthy found someone to arm the nukes.
Have audio forensics scan for background
artefacts that could give us a location.
- Yes, sir.
- I got Morris working on something.
We also found an image file inside the data
stream. It might be a photo of the engineer.
- This it?
- It got all corrupted during the intercept.
I'm writing a salvage utility.
(Buchanan) Recovering this may be
our only way to stop those nukes.
- Give me an estimate.
- Could be ten minutes, could be an hour.
All teams confirm.
Who's the agent in charge?
- My name is Jack Bauer.
- Mr Bauer, I'm Al Turner. I'll be on point.
- Are your men in position?
- We've sealed off one block
and recon has confirmed
your brother's inside.
His wife and son are in there as well.
Use nonlethal force.
We need to take my brother alive.
- Understood. Attention...
- Let me go in with you.
No. You wait here.
I need to question Graem alone.
What are you gonna do to him?
Whatever it takes to find out what he knows.
I'm not stupid. I know something is wrong.
- Everything's fine.
- You're a lousy liar. You always have been.
- Why don't you make some coffee?
- Make your own coffee!
Will you two stop fighting?
All you guys ever do is fight.
I'm sorry, honey.
We're just all a little tense today.
What's going on?
Nothing. Nothing. Why don't...
why don't we leave your father alone?
He needs to work.
Put the weapon down! Drop the gun!
- What the hell is this, Jack?
- Put it down!
Do it.
Get on the floor. Get on the floor!
- Take it easy!
- Take him into the next room.
Have Burke prep him for questioning.
I want every drive in this house uploaded
and sent over to CTU.
Pick him up. Go. Go!
- What are you doing to my dad?
- I'll explain as soon as I can.
Please, just take a seat. Please, come on.
Let go of me!
Stop looking at me like this has
something to do with us. It doesn't.
- Gray tried to have me and our father killed.
- Why? Why would he try and kill you?
The nuclear bomb that was detonated today
was acquired from the family's company.
Gray's been trying to cover it up.
I'm sorry, Marilyn. I understand
how difficult this must be for you to believe.
It's not.
I may not know the details of what he's done
but I know what he's capable of.
There are four more other bombs out there.
Is there anything that you can tell me?
- Like what?
- Did Gray talk about a man named McCarthy?
- No.
- Are you sure?
He hasn't confided in me in years.
He probably never did.
Marilyn, thousands of lives are at stake.
Please, just think.
I wish I knew something, I wish I did,
but I don't know anything.
Josh doesn't know anything
and he doesn't need to know.
- I'll do everything I can to protect him.
- No!
No, I've seen what happens
when you try and protect people.
I just wanna get my son
and I wanna get outta here!
- Marilyn!
- Sir.
We found two computers.
He was trying to erase files.
- We're sending what's left over to CTU.
- OK, good.
My sister-in-law and my nephew don't need
to stay here. Have them transported to CTU.
Yes, sir.
Ms Bauer, we're taking you
and your son back to CTU.
- Josh?
- Grandpa.
- Are you OK?
- Not really.
Wait in the car, baby.
Jack told me what Graem did,
what he was involved with.
Is it true?
- It's complicated.
- But it's true.
You make sure he keeps Josh out of this.
I panicked, Jack. That's all there is to it.
You panicked?
That's your excuse? You panicked?!
You tried to kill me and our father.
I was backed into a corner.
I was protecting my ass.
You knew about a tactical nuclear weapon
on American soil.
You were responsible
for the death of thousands.
You think I wanted that bomb to go off?
I think you knew more about McCarthy
than you told me.
- How do I find him?
- I don't have a clue.
- How do I find him?!
- I just told you, I don't know.
There are four more bombs out there.
This isn't ajoke, Gray.
- Tell me now, how do I find McCarthy?
- I've told you everything I know, Jack.
Perspiration and temperature patterns
indicate deception, especially his last reply.
Set up the interrogation package.
- You don't wanna make me do this, Gray.
- We grew up together, Jack.
In all those years I could never make you
do anything you didn't wanna do.
- I need to talk to you.
- What is it?
- It's Morris's brother.
- Timothy?
He's on his way to Horizon Regional Hospital.
On-site paramedics confirmed
he has severe radiation exposure.
It says he's in critical condition.
- I'll tell him.
- Chloe.
- I think we should hold off.
- Why?
Morris is our best hope for restoring that file.
If we drop this on him now,
he might shut down.
- It's his brother. We can't keep it a secret.
- I understand this might sound insensitive,
but put aside your personal feelings
for Morris and consider what's at stake.
- We need him to finish that salvage utility.
- I know Morris. He can handle it.
I hope so.
- Morris.
- Yes, darling?
I have some bad news.
It's about Timothy.
He's been taken to the hospital. I'm sorry.
This can't be right. It says he was pulled from
his car by rescue workers north of Valencia.
Could you connect me with Horizon Regional
Hospital? What was he doing in Valencia?
- I'm sorry. All circuits are busy.
- I realise the lines are busy.
This is CTU.
I need an emergency breakthrough.
I can't help you at this time, sir. I'm sorry.
- I have to go out there.
- Morris, hey.
I know it's hard.
We are in the middle of a crisis.
We need to find the engineer
before Fayed does. You can't leave.
You can't expect me to sit there while my
little brother is dying in a hospital. I'm sorry.
Morris, listen.
12,000 people are dead. If Fayed finds
an engineer, it'll be many, many more.
Four bombs is about a million people.
Think about this.
- You can finish writing the program.
- Yes, I can, but you started already.
It'll take me half an hour
to figure out what you've done.
You need to stay here and do yourjob.
Please.
OK.
Thanks.
- Buchanan.
- Did Chloe pull anything off the hard drives?
She came up empty, but the NSA picked up
a conversation between McCarthy and Fayed.
McCarthy's found another engineer
to arm the four remaining nukes.
- He's delivering him within the hour.
- The nukes will be operational in 45 minutes?
I'll get back to you.
CTU confirmed that McCarthy is looking for
an engineer for Fayed. They'll arm the nukes.
- You're wasting time talking to me.
- (Jack) You're holding something back.
(Graem) I told you everything I know.
That's hyoscine pentothal. It's a
neuroinflammatory designed to induce pain.
All you have to do to stop me from using it
is tell me how to find McCarthy.
Your guess is as good as mine.
Two ccs.
(moans)
- Come on, come on.
- (screams)
I can take this to seven ccs.
You will experience pain I can't even describe.
At eight ccs I run the risk
of inducing a heart attack.
Gray, make no mistake about it,
I will go there if I have to.
Please, just tell me what I need to know.
- Please. I don't wanna hurt you.
- Oh, you sure about that, Jack?
Please, Gray, just tell me what I need to know.
How do I find McCarthy?!
Do it. Two ccs.
(screams)
Breathe. Just breathe. Just breathe.
- Please, just tell me what I need to know.
- (moans)
How do I find McCarthy?!
Damn you. Damn you. Four ccs.
That's eight ccs total.
His vitals are spiking across the line.
- Four ccs!
- Jack, don't!
The machine knows you're lying!
I know you're lying! Tell me the truth!
Tell me the truth!
(screams)
This has nothing to do with McCarthy.
- It has to do with Palmer.
- David Palmer?
Yeah.
I gave the order for his assassination,
and Agent Tony Almeida
and Agent Michelle Dessler, your co-workers.
They're all dead because of me.
I arranged everything.
I set the timetable.
I- I paid off the killers.
I even lured you out of hiding to take the fall.
Today wasn't the first time
I've tried to have you killed, Jack.
Why?
Because I love my country!
And in the real world, sometimes that means
you have to do things, terrible things,
even unforgivable things,
for the sake of your country.
But you know all about that,
don't you, brother?
We're the same.
I mean, look at me. We're the same!
We are not the same!
You want me to kill you?
- Do it!
- I'm gonna do it my way. Four more ccs.
- I can't do that.
- Pick up the syringe. Do it! Now!
- Son of a bitch!
- Get me somebody in here now!
Do you wanna die?
Drop your weapon!
Drop it!
You're gonna die.
Shut down the IV. Shut it down.
I'm here, baby.
I'm ashamed.
What do you mean, you're ashamed?
For spying on those men.
I thought I was doing the right thing,
but I was wrong.
You did the only thing that you could do,
OK? And that was the right thing.
Look, you're the bravest,
most principled man I've ever known.
(phone rings)
You get some rest, OK?
Hello?
Sandra, it's Wayne.
I just heard what happened to Walid.
I am so sorry. Is he gonna be all right?
Yeah, I think so.
What they told me is confusing.
They said Walid was working undercover
to expose some plot?
There was no plot. The men weren't part of
any conspiracy. They were just bystanders.
They told me these men had information
about the nuclear weapons.
One of the men pulled it from the internet.
Sandra, they should've reported that.
They were afraid they were gonna get
into more trouble than they're already in.
Most of these men were pulled
from theirjobs and their homes
on trumped-up immigration charges,
and now they're facing deportation.
Wayne, you are detaining
without due process
the people whose help
you need the most.
How do you expect for them to help
if they don't have any legal protection?
Wayne,
I'm scared.
I know.
Everything's gonna be all right.
- What's the status?
- I ran the program but this is all we got.
- I still don't have a clear image.
- What are you doing?
I'm downloading an application from
a hacker's site. It might kick-start things.
- It could corrupt the file.
- I know these guys.
They write really good code,
when they're not serving time.
Unbelievable.
That's what Graem was holding back?
He was responsible for Palmer's
assassination. He directed the conspiracy.
He was trying to protect the company.
He's trying to do that now.
- Incredible.
- I wish it got us closer to the nukes.
He doesn't know where McCarthy is.
Were you able to pick up anything on chatter?
- Maybe an image of McCarthy's engineer.
- How long till you know?
The file's corrupted.
Morris is working on it now.
As soon as my brother is ready,
I want him sent back to CTU.
I've redirected a chopper
to Jackson Middle School.
Thanks, Bill.
Dad, Graem made his own choices
after you let him start running the company.
You can't make yourself responsible for that.
It's not fair.
I'll tell you what isn't fair.
You deserved a better family, Jack.
Not this.
Not us.
I can just imagine what you must be feeling.
All that time we lost.
What I wouldn't give to have some of it back.
Me too.
Your brother's been stabilised.
He'll be ready to move in ten minutes.
Thank you.
Dad, I want you to go back to CTU.
OK.
I need a few minutes.
Of course.
They're sending a chopper for me.
I have to go.
- There.
- What?
- The plug-in's working.
- How long is it gonna take?
You'll have a photo of the engineer
in two minutes. Just don't touch anything.
I have got to find out
what's happening to my brother. Save it.
Thanks for trying to help.
- I'm leaving. Watch my station, OK?
- Call me when you find out about Timothy.
I will.
Congratulations, Tom,
it's an excellent plan.
Thank you very much, Mr Vice President.
It's about time someone in this administration
stood up to these people.
To be honest, I didn't think this president
had the stomach for the cure.
I think we're about ready for kickoff here, sir.
I'll put you on speakerphone.
- Is the vice president with us?
- I'm here, Mr President.
I'm assuming everyone here
has read Executive Order 1066.
Tom first proposed his plan to me
very early this morning, and I rejected it.
Sacrificing the rights and freedoms
guaranteed by the Constitution
seemed like... like too steep a price,
even for the promise of security.
But then Fayed murdered 12,000
innocent Americans with a nuclear weapon.
I felt compelled to revisit my earlier position.
After careful reconsideration
I remain convinced that my initial response
was in fact the right one -
that implementing this plan
would be a terrible mistake.
Now, I cannot and I will not
endorse these actions.
Some of you seem to feel
that the Constitution is somehow valid
only during times of peace,
but not during wartime.
That is not what the founders intended.
With your indulgence, sir, George
Washington's enemies wore bright red coats
and marched in a straight line.
The founders could never have conceived
of a stateless enemy hiding among us
that targets not our soldiers
but our civilisation.
Your plan would only hinder the efforts
of law enforcement to stop Fayed.
(Lennox) How does my plan
hinder law enforcement, sir?
By marginalising and thereby radicalising the
very people whose help they need to enlist.
The American Muslim community is our
best line of defence against these terrorists.
But we Americans need to demonstrate
that we are governed by the rule of law
and never, never by the politics of fear.
- Mr President?
- Yes, Noah?
Before you make unilateral decisions,
maybe you should hear
some other people's thoughts.
I'm sorry, Noah.
The discussion on this matter
is over.
- This better work.
- (Buchanan) Jack's on his way.
I want Holding A and B prepped
for interrogation
and put together a clearance package for him,
no restrictions.
- Do you have it yet?
- (Chloe) A few more seconds.
As soon as we ID the engineer, post it on the
interagency subnet. We need all eyes on this.
- Yes, sir.
- Oh, my God.
It's Morris. His clearance level,
personal history, everything.
- (Buchanan) Where is he?
- On his way to the hospital.
We got a call that his brother
was hurt in the blast. He just left.
This is Buchanan.
Has Morris O'Brian left the parking lot?
- (man) He just drove out, sir.
- Dammit.
Milo, contact LAPD.
Put an APB out on his car.
Chloe, see if you can raise him
on his cell phone.
- Bauer.
- We just ID'd the engineer. It's Morris O'Brian.
- Morris?
- Yes.
The file we intercepted was Morris's photo
and CV. McCarthy was sending it to Fayed.
- There is no doubt.
- Fine, put him under a protective watch.
We can't. He's gone. He got a call
claiming his brother was in the hospital.
We're trying to raise him on his cell.
Morris, hold on! He's on line one.
- We got him, Jack.
- Patch me through.
Morris, it's Bill Buchanan with Jack Bauer.
Where are you?
- On my way to the hospital.
- Come back to CTU immediately.
- I can't do that.
- This is Jack.
There is nothing wrong with your brother.
It's a setup.
- The engineer McCarthy's looking for is you.
- Me?
It was your photo
McCarthy was sending to Fayed.
- (Jack) You need to turn the car around now.
- Uh, OK. OK.
- (gunshots)
- Morris!
- Get out of the car.
- What do you want?
Don't talk, move! Come on. Let's go.
- They got him.
- Sounds like a transfer to another vehicle.
Chloe, bring up a satellite feed,
five-mile radius of CTU. Hurry, hurry!
Drive.
- (phone rings)
- Yes?
- (McCarthy) We're on our way.
- How soon?
- 15 minutes.
- We'll be waiting.
- With my money.
- You'll get paid when I have what I want.
Let me be clear. I'm just delivering him.
You'll have to make him cooperate.
He'll cooperate.
Agent Burke.
I'd like to speak with my son.
All right. Five minutes.
(Phillip) Thanks.
How am I doing?
You're doing great.
Everyone thinks Jack is so tough.
And maybe he is.
But so am I.
It's nice to know that I can take
anything he can dish out.
- You told him about Palmer.
- I had to make him think I cracked.
But I kept you out of it.
It's gonna get a lot worse. He's not finished.
He knows you didn't tell him everything.
Yeah, and I won't. You know I won't, Dad.
They'll take you to CTU. They'll do things
there that will make this seem like a cakewalk.
Like I said,
I can take it.
I'd like to believe that.
Problem is, I have to be sure.
Well, you can be.
I'll hold my mud, Dad.
Everything's going exactly according to plan.
Jack bought the ruse.
Oh, I know. I'm sure we convinced him that
you were gonna have me killed as well.
Yeah. That makes me the bad guy
and you the good guy.
I take the rap, do some time.
You escape free, get me out when you can.
Meanwhile, the company lives on.
Dad, stick to the plan.
That's what you've always said, right?
Make a plan and stick to it.
Sometimes you have to make adjustments.
I would never betray you, Dad.
I love you.
I love you, too, Graem.
You've been a good boy.
You've done everything I asked.
Only this time
I asked too much.
I'm sorry.
Dad...
(coughs)
(muffled screaming)
My son's had a seizure!
Get in here now! Hurry up!
What happened? Is he gonna make it?
I don't know. Please give us the room
so we can work. Get CTU medical now!
My God. If you people killed my son,
I swear,
you're gonna regret it for the rest of your life.
Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net