We know you printed a document
before the EMP detonated. Where is it?
You decide when the pain stops.
Drop your gun or I'll kill him.
Paul, where's the data printout?
I hid it.
- Is this it?
- Yeah. It's in code.
I couldn't make any sense out of it.
We need to get it back to CTU.
I appreciate you carrying the ball
until Michelle got here.
Why don't you
bring everyone up to speed?
The man responsible
for planning today's attacks, Habib Marwan,
has been a long-term employee
of McLennan-Forster.
Jack and Paul Raines
went to inspect his computer files.
As they were doing so,
an EMP bomb was detonated,
wiping out the company's database.
We have to assume
whoever detonated the EMP
wants Jack and Paul eliminated.
- Why are we going here?
- Weapons and ammunition.
Get out of here!
The next one won't miss.
I'm a federal agent. Look, we need your help.
Who's after you?
It has to do with the terrorist attacks.
I have evidence
that I need to get to the authorities.
If you're fighting the people who
caused today's bloodshed, we'll help you.
It's time.
- Jack!
- I'm here.
- You safe?
- Yeah.
I need you to get this to CTU.
It needs to get decoded immediately.
Jack, look out!
Paul? Paul! Get me a medic.
It's time for you to go.
Are you ready?
Yes, of course.
Proceed as planned. The President
of the United States is on a tight schedule.
We can't be late.
He's bleeding out. Tell 'em
we need two litres of A-positive haemo.
Roger that.
Come on, Paul.
Stay with us. We're almost there.
- Hello.
- Audrey, it's me.
Oh, Jack. Thank God you're all right.
Audrey, I need you to listen to me.
Paul's been shot.
Audrey?
How bad is it?
The medics are working on him.
We'll be there in a few minutes.
Jack, how did this happen?
One of the gunmen tried to shoot me.
Paul pushed me out of the way.
He saved my life.
Audrey?
I'm here. I just...
- Jack, I don't know what to say.
- You don't have to say anything.
Surgeons are standing by.
We're gonna do everything that we have to.
- You understand that?
- Yeah, I understand.
I'm sorry.
I gotta go.
- See you in a minute.
- Yeah. OK.
Mr President, all the evidence we've gathered
confirms that this one man, Habib Marwan,
is responsible for everything
that's happened today.
The train derailment, my abduction,
the sabotage of our nuclear power plants.
Does evidence suggest
he is planning more attacks?
I'm afraid so. NSA is reporting a spike in
chatter. They're sifting through the intel now,
trying to determine
potential targets and time frames.
- Trying is not good enough.
The chopper is about to land.
We need to pre-empt further attacks.
I understand, sir. Our best chance
of doing that is by capturing Marwan.
- How close are you?
- Jack Bauer recovered a document
we believe contains contact data
on Marwan's network.
CTU is using it to track Marwan.
- And if that fails?
- We just have to hope that it doesn't.
Jim,
today's events are continuing
to generate an unprecedented level of fear.
I'm not sure the social and civil fabric
of this country can withstand another attack.
- We need to make provisions.
- Provisions?
The civil unrest that I believe is inevitable
in the event of another strike.
Are you saying
we should impose martial law?
General Wakefield will meet with you
in LA to discuss our options.
- When?
- Now. His plane landed.
He'll be calling you
to confirm a secure location.
- And, Jim, keep this between us.
- Of course, Mr President.
He's still falling.
He's losing pressure. I need ten
cc's of adrenaline, no compression. Let's go.
Paul. Paul, can you hear me?
- Paul.
- We gotta get him to surgery now.
- Let's go.
I'm sorry.
Please tell me he's not gonna die.
Come here.
Please.
Jack, tell me.
We don't know. We just don't know.
- Jack, are you OK?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- We pulled a name off the list you sent us.
- Who is it?
Someone on our watch list.
We had no idea he was with Marwan.
Come on inside. We'll talk you through it.
You need to stay out here
while your husband's prepped for surgery.
Please, can I just talk to him for a second?
Paul, hey. Hey, it's Audrey.
Listen to me.
I just want you to know
that I'm here, OK? I'm here.
We need to prep him now.
- I will be here when you get out of surgery.
Paul?
Get him prepped and ready.
Joseph Fayed, professor
at Green University, chemical engineering.
Came to the US in 1985.
We're sending in a tactical team
to pick him up.
- That's a mistake.
- Why?
Marwan's vetted his inner circle carefully.
That man'll die before he says anything.
You're probably right, Jack,
but what can we do besides arrest Fayed?
Send someone in undercover.
They might lead you to Marwan.
We don't have time to put
one of our people undercover.
I'm not talking about one of our people.
Dina Araz.
We've granted her son immunity.
We have nothing left to offer her.
Maybe not. I'll talk to her
while you mobilise a tactical team.
If I can't get her to cooperate, send them in.
It's simple - we either find Marwan, or we will
not be able to stop what he's planning next.
Meet them at the hotel, Old River Road,
half a kilometre from the base.
- When?
- Leave now.
I'll need his flight package,
including clearance and identification codes.
You'll have whatever you need.
Is that all you've got?
- For now it is.
- Come on, I haven't seen you in two weeks.
Yeah, I've gotta get to the base.
I'm flying tonight.
Damn. I'm gonna be late as it is.
- Oh, look at me. I'm all wrinkled.
- I wouldn't worry about that.
Hello.
I need to talk to John.
- It's for you.
- What?
It's your wife.
But it's your cellphone.
Laurie.
They say they'll kill the children
unless you do what they want.
- What's going on, Laurie? Who's there?
- I don't know.
Listen to me, Laurie.
Whoever's there, you put them on the phone.
Please don't let them hurt the children.
Laurie.
Laurie, put...
Put your clothes on, John.
Curtis is prepping the tactical teams, which
means you have five minutes to do this.
Do you recognise this man?
- No.
- He's connected to Marwan.
I don't know him.
I already told the other agent.
Marwan doesn't permit
communication between cells.
His name is Joseph Fayed.
He's a professor at Green University.
You know more about him than I do.
He's also our only way to reach Marwan.
We can't do that without your help.
Why should I help you?
I've already gotten
all I'm going to get for cooperating.
That's not necessarily true.
I know you love your son.
You've already shown me that today.
But unless you help us get to Fayed,
that'll be the last time you see him
for the rest of your life.
- Dessler.
-  The teams are in place.
All right. Have them stand by.
Tactical teams are ready.
They can be at Fayed's house in ten minutes.
Let's give him another minute.
I'm offering you freedom. You and Behrooz
will go into a witness protection programme.
You'll be given new names,
identities, everything.
This is what you told me you wanted.
I'm offering you a life with your son.
Right now, the only question is
which life do you want?
We're out of time.
What do you need me to do?
I need you to go to Fayed, and tell him
that you need to speak to Marwan.
He won't let me through his front door,
let alone get near Marwan.
He will when you tell him
that you've got a hostage that can help him.
A hostage? Who?
Me.
So what's this all about? What are you doing?
- I'm delivering you to someone.
- Who?
- I don't know.
- You don't know who you work for?
- I work for myself.
- Somebody's paying you.
I don't ask them who they are,
and they don't tell me. That's how I stay alive.
All right. It's time.
If you don't cooperate, your family will die.
Do you understand?
It's all there. Get out of here.
Get your things. We've got a plane to catch.
Increased chatter indicates
Marwan is planning another strike.
It is imperative we locate him
before he triggers this.
We are mounting an undercover operation
to lead us to him through this man.
Joseph Fayed.
We've struck a deal with Dina Araz to
work undercover for us and approach Fayed.
- Marwan knows we have Araz in custody.
- We will use that to our advantage.
- Jack will run us through the cover story.
- The cover story goes as follows.
An hour ago, I was transporting Araz
to the federal detention centre.
My vehicle was attacked by members
of a terrorist cell run by Navi Araz
at the intersection of Sepulveda and National.
I managed to kill all of the attackers,
but during the engagement
Dina Araz secured one of the weapons
and took me hostage.
She'll take me to Fayed.
He'll take me to Marwan.
- Marwan takes the bait, we track you to him.
- Yeah.
They're gonna search both Jack and Dina,
which makes surveillance a problem.
We'll handle this passively. We'll use
satellite parabolics and laser aggregators.
You think Dina Araz'll be able
to play this convincingly?
She's lived in the United States
for five years while part of a terrorist cell.
Yes. She's an expert at deception.
As long as she doesn't deceive us.
This is our best
and only chance at finding Marwan.
No matter how well we fabricate this story,
Jack will be in extreme, immediate danger.
We have to be able to move in at the first sign
of trouble. There is zero tolerance for error.
- Thank you.
- Good luck, everyone.
Curtis, the detainees from McLennan-Forster
have been taken to Division.
- Run the interrogation.
- You got it.
Thank you.
Edgar, I want you to call LAPD and Caltrans.
Their logs need to reflect
that the ambush took place.
I need an exact time window.
He just finished telling us. An hour ago.
- I didn't know if there was an update.
- No, you weren't paying attention.
We can't afford for you
to lose focus at a time like this.
I'm sick of people saying
I don't know what I'm doing.
Especially people who
don't really work here.
Is there a problem with Edgar?
His mother was caught in a contamination
zone at San Gabriel. She took her own life.
Up till now he's been handling it well.
It might be catching up with him.
Do you think he can run
the comm part of this operation?
Based on what just happened? No.
I didn't see Chloe on the active roster.
- Yeah, well, Driscoll forced her to resign.
- Why?
Apparently, Chloe went against
Driscoll's orders, sided with Jack.
Turns out Jack was right.
Thank you.
Hello.
- Chloe. Michelle Dessler.
- Are you calling me from Division?
I'm back at CTU. Secretary Heller
asked me to take Erin Driscoll's place.
She got fired? That's too bad.
Tell Edgar to upgrade
the pattern-recognition software.
- He gets overwhelmed.
- I'll make sure he takes care of that.
- Thanks.
- Listen, Chloe,
you're better at what you do
than anyone I've worked with.
I need you here.
Thank you for saying that,
but I've had enough for today.
Chloe, this would be for Jack,
not just for CTU.
- What are you talking about?
- He's about to go into a high-risk operation.
We need to mount massive
surveillance in little time.
I'm not confident
that Edgar can do this on his own.
- Well, there's nothing I can do about that.
- Chloe,
I just need a few hours of your time,
and then you can move on.
I just wanna do everything I can
to ensure Jack's safety.
Fine. But it's just for today.
- Thank you, Chloe.
- You're welcome.
Set cars up at the ambush site
in case Marwan wants to verify.
Use dead bodies of terrorists
from Heller's rescue.
The follow team will stay as close as they
can, but you're flying without a net here.
If a hostile decides
to take you out without warning,
- there's nothing we can do.
- I know.
Audrey's still at the clinic.
There's time if you wanna say goodbye.
She's got a lot on her mind right now.
Jack, she should know
what you're about to do.
She's been through enough today.
Look over the time line.
We'll talk through the details.
I'm not doing anything until I see my son.
- We don't have time for that right now.
- Seeing my son is non-negotiable.
Tony.
Learn every aspect of the cover story.
Your life depends on it.
Don't worry about me.
You can see your son,
but only for a minute. That's all. Let's go.
Mom.
They wouldn't tell me where you were
or if I'd see you again.
We are going to be together.
What? They wouldn't let you come with me.
Everything has changed.
I agreed to do something for them,
and they'll let me go with you.
- What do they want you to do?
- Help them find Marwan.
- It's too dangerous.
- Oh, I can handle Marwan.
- Please, Mom, no.
- Don't worry. I'll be fine.
Please, Mom.
Mrs Araz, it's time.
- Is field surveillance in place?
- We have audio.
We should be able to hear inside the house.
That's assuming they get that far.
- OK. Thank you.
- Yeah.
Come on. Come on.
- Why aren't you going through?
Use a Danziger filter.
You can download it internally
if you know what you're doing. You're in.
- Why are you here?
- Michelle asked me to help.
- I'll cover your overflow.
- I can handle my assignment.
You can't, otherwise
Michelle wouldn't have called me in.
Edgar, I meant to tell you
before Chloe got here.
I can do my job. I don't need any help.
I'm not saying you can't,
but I'm not taking chances.
- I know we got off to a rocky start, but...
- Edgar, this isn't a debate. It's an order.
Brief Chloe so she can
run satellite with you.
Jack's approaching
the staging area now.
- Baron.
- Dessler. We're set on our end.
Teams are in place. Go in at your discretion.
Roger that. We'll leave this line open.
We are going in alone?
Our agents are conducting audio surveillance.
- What does that mean?
- Acknowledge that you can hear me.
Copy that.
- What are you doing?
- I have to make it look like I was injured.
Take my gun.
This has to look as convincing
as possible. Take my gun.
You must know that I want to kill you.
Yes, but you won't because of Behrooz.
Let's go.
- They're going in.
We're standing by.
- What if Fayed doesn't believe us?
- Then we're both dead.
... people were evacuating
the San Gabriel Island area.
As you can see here
from footage that was shot earlier...
... people tried to evacuate.
- Who is it?
- Joseph, it's Dina Araz.
- Who?
- Dina Araz. I'm a friend.
My husband is Navi. He's been killed.
I don't know what you're talking about.
- I need to speak to Marwan.
- I don't know any Marwan.
- Yes, you do.
- Go away before I call the police.
You won't call the police,
and we both know why.
- What do you want?
- I have a hostage.
Someone Marwan will want.
His name is Jack Bauer, he's a CTU agent.
Now, please let me in
before someone sees me.
Close the door.
Put your gun over there. Do it.
- How did you find me?
- My husband told me.
- I don't know your husband.
- He knew you.
- Tell me what happened.
- My husband was killed, and I was arrested.
They were transporting me to CTU.
I heard an explosion,
and the van we were driving crashed.
It was our people.
They came to rescue me.
Everyone fell, except Bauer and me. He was
wounded, and I managed to get his gun.
-  Where?
- The intersection of Sepulveda and National.
Half a mile from here.
Don't move.
What is it?
- This is Fayed.
A woman named Dina Araz came to me.
- How did she find you?
- She claims her husband told her.
- What does she want?
- She has a hostage.
- A CTU agent named Jack Bauer.
- Jack Bauer?
- Can you break into the other side?
- No, the signal's scrambled.
Our people ambushed a vehicle
at the intersection of Sepulveda and National.
Everyone was killed,
but she escaped with Bauer.
What do you want me to do?
Bring them to me.
I will call you back in five minutes
with the details. Be ready.
- Do you understand?
- Yes.
I understand.
Marwan wants to see him.
- Baron, it's a go.
- I heard.
Set a follow grid.
We'll coordinate from our end.
- Evening, sir.
- Evening.
Pop the trunk for me, sir.
Since when are you searching
officers' cars at the gate?
Elevated threat level.
- OK. You're good to go, sir.
- Thank you.
- I'm on base.
-  Proceed as planned.
- Let me talk to my family.
- Open the trunk.
- Let me talk to my wife.
- I said open the trunk.
Please. Let me talk to my family.
Your family is dead. And so are you.
Mrs Raines.
Your husband sustained bullet wounds
to his chest and abdomen.
We extracted one bullet,
but I called a neurosurgeon in from Cedars
- to help extract the second bullet.
- Why a neurosurgeon?
Well, the bullet is lodged
against his T5 vertebra,
and we want to avoid
any further spinal trauma.
I can't believe this is happening.
- I'll let you know as soon as I get any news.
Thank you.
Dad...
I don't think I realised
how much I care for Paul until now.
I know this is terrible timing, but
the president has called and I have to leave.
You'll be able to reach me on my number.
The doctors will keep me up to speed here.
OK.
I love you, Audrey.
And I'm proud to be your dad.
I love you, too.
Be careful.
- Where are you taking me?
- Shut up.
How far are we going?
It won't be long.
You look nervous.
What do you expect?
I wouldn't have contacted you
if I felt I had a choice.
And as a result, I have no choice.
We do whatever we have to for the cause.
So what's the problem?
There is no problem.
They're turning off Olympic.
Moving to the next subchannel.
He's turning onto a side street.
- Collier Avenue. Hold that distance.
- Understood.
He's heading towards the Broad Street tunnel.
He's slowing down. Baron, drop back.
- We can't have him spot the tail.
- We're backing off.
- He's turning into the tunnel.
- Maintain your distance.
He's too far ahead.
We won't be able to hear what's going on.
The tunnel is 400 yards long.
They'll be out of view for 20 seconds.
Pull in front of this truck.
- What's going on?
Get out of the car.
What are you doing?
- From Marwan.
- Yes.
This is taking too long.
- They're outta the tunnel.
- Do you have a visual?
That's it. We got him up ahead.
- Fayed's turning onto Napier.
- Napier loops back around to Olympic.
He just spent the last five minutes
driving in a circle.
Maybe he's trying to detect surveillance.
- Chloe, can you switch to infrared?
- Hold on.
- There's only one person in the car.
- They made a switch in the tunnel.
The covert part of the operation is over.
All teams, move in on the target car.
Alpha team, cut him off at the bridge.
Establish a perimeter.
Stop and search all vehicles.
- Anything on satellite?
- Nothing around the immediate area.
- Can you go back into archives?
- It'll take a few minutes.
- Do it.
- Baron, what's your status?
We're closing in now.
We got him
surrounded on the bridge. I'll take the lead.
- Passenger side.
- On the left.
Flank him.
- Get out of the car, and put your hands up.
Out of the car!
Bomb! Bomb! Bomb!
Oh, my God.
Marwan set us up.
- Almeida.
- This is Alden. Baron's dead.
So is Fayed. Is there any sign of Jack?
- No. Any other hostiles in the area?
- No, the area looks secure.
OK. I'll get you another backup team
as soon as I can.
- I have the archive satellite footage.
- Play it back.
OK. During the time Fayed's car
is in the tunnel, three vehicles exit.
- Check the van.
- Can you get me a licence number on that?
Not from the satellite. I'll check the traffic
cameras. Get me the Caltrans interface.
We have a socket open. Logging in.
Done.
OK, there's a camera
at the entrance to the tunnel.
Looking for the right frame.
Got it.
Send this out to all field teams.
I want support setting up the grid.
I'm on it.
We have an ID on a vehicle.
White Chevy van, late '90s,
licence plate - Charlie Victor Alpha 322.
Get up.
You've caused me a lot of trouble.
Sorry for your loss, Dina.
Navi was a great man.
I hope my men weren't too rough with you.
It was necessary,
in case you were under surveillance.
I understand.
But we weren't followed. I was careful.
- You're a good liar, Dina.
- What?
Fayed martyred himself.
The men who were following you are dead.
- What men?
- Enough with the lies.
Marwan, please believe me.
I did not betray you.
Prove it to me.
Kill him.
Just what I thought.
Get him out of here.
Visiontext Subtitles: Joanna Wilkinson
ENGLISH SDH