You're not my son.
Why? Because I don't
want to kill innocent people?
Because you're weak,
and you stand for nothing!
Is there a problem, Navi?
Government agents arrested Dina
and surrounded the building.
How much more time
do you need to melt down the plants?
One hour, maybe two.
I don't want to have to kill you, but I will.
I have the suspect in custody.
I need assistance.
I need you to take Dina and her son
back to CTU and head the interrogation.
They'd never let me set foot in CTU,
even if I wanted to.
I can get you reinstated. But I need
to know now, is that what you want?
- I'm sure you're aware of my history here.
- Not an issue.
Jack Bauer and Secretary Heller
both vouch for you. That's enough for me.
Did he work directly for the terrorists?
- I told you, I don't know.
- I need names who can get us to the override.
This place may not be as empty as it seems.
- What? You think this is some kind of trap?
- Yes. I do.
I didn't give them anything. I...
What does CTU know about the override?
Audrey, it's me.
Hey. Did you find anything?
The company that owns the building...
Galaxy Financial. Ever heard of them?
- No. Should I have?
- Your husband's the chief financial officer.
What's really going on?
What? Are you spying on me?
- Are you doing something to spy on?
- What is that supposed to mean?
- Take your hands off of her!
- You set me up!
Put your hands on your head now.
- What do you want?
- I want answers.
You should leave the room
while I question your husband.
Wait outside with the backup team.
- What are you gonna do to him?
- Whatever I have to.
I'm staying.
Fine.
Look at me, Paul.
- Look at me.
- I've got nothing to say to you.
This is what you need to know, Paul.
Five power plants are ready to melt down.
All I care about is making sure
that doesn't happen.
Your name is on a lease on a building in
Chatsworth that was used to plan the attack.
That makes you a prime suspect.
I'm gonna treat you like one. Understand?
My name is on at least 50 different leases.
I own ten corporations. I don't know
about some building in Chatsworth.
I don't believe you.
The lease was notarised.
There's documentation of your ID.
CTU verified your signature.
Paul, you need to start talking to me now.
I've got nothing to say to you.
Jack...
Paul wouldn't betray this country.
Paul is a prime suspect
and he's not cooperating,
and I don't have time
to do this any other way.
I need to know for sure.
Paul...
This is the last chance to talk to me
before I have to hurt you.
Tell me about 24878 Alvert Street in
Chatsworth. Why is your name on the lease?
- Jack...
- Audrey, don't interfere!
If you need to step outside of this room, do it.
Why is your name on the lease?
You're bluffing.
If you've got information, Paul, I need it now.
Come on, Paul, just tell me.
What's your connection with the terrorists?
Jack...
Please don't.
All right, wait, wait.
I don't know the specific building
you're talking about. I can find out.
How?
My corporate records are on my laptop. If that
address is under my name, then it'll come up.
- Maybe there's someone else involved.
- What's your user-ID number?
L- i-it'll be much quicker if I just do it.
Please.
You want me to believe you're not involved
with this? You better show me who is.
Sorry I had to call you here, Marwan,
but I had no choice.
CTU is trying to disable the override
using a Drinfeld module.
They've already shut down over 90 reactors.
We always knew they'd stop some of them.
The important thing
is that one reactor has melted down.
As long as the override has control
of the other five, I can do the rest from here.
Everything is ready for you upstairs.
- Will anyone in the office be suspicious?
- I reported a system failure.
If anyone asks, tell them you're from IT
restoring my hard drive.
My desk is in the last row,
three from the end, C86.
The override is well-disguised
inside the desk. Here is the key.
- Good.
- How long will you need?
45 minutes to melt down the remaining ones.
I am here if you need anything.
- Where's the CTU agent?
- Forbes is questioning him now.
He's out. He's not gonna tell us anything.
- What does Marwan want us to do with him?
- Finish him off, then get rid of the body.
Take care of it.
He came with a woman and two agents.
- Where are their bodies?
- They're already in the van.
- Here. Here it is. Galaxy Financial Services.
- What kind of a company is it?
It's a failing payroll service
I was about to dissolve,
and someone made an offer
to buy 51 per cent of the shares.
7-800 grand, something like that.
- Here. Harris Barnes, director.
- Who is Harris Barnes?
- I... don't remember.
- What do you mean, you don't remember?
I'm involved with over 30 companies.
I don't deal directly with them.
- How did your name get on the lease?
- I don't know.
You're saying you entered a deal
worth hundreds of thousands of dollars
with someone you'd never met?
- My attorney handles most...
- I don't believe you.
Jack, it's possible. Paul has put together
a lot of deals through his attorneys.
This is Sarah.
- It's me. I need you to run a name for me.
- Go ahead.
Harris Barnes, a director of a California
S corporation, Galaxy Financial Services.
What am I looking for?
Where he lives, businesses,
anything that could connect him to terrorists.
- All right. Give me a minute.
- I'll be here.
She's calling me right back. Excuse me.
Audrey, your boyfriend
is just a thug with a badge.
Why is your name on that lease?
Unbelievable.
An hour ago I was sitting here feeling sorry
for myself that you didn't want me back.
And now you think I'm a terrorist.
You think I was involved
with the kidnapping?
I don't know what to believe any more.
Yeah?
I ran down the name Harris Barnes.
A lot of data came up, but it was inconsistent.
I went into the IRS records and he didn't
appear on their logs until two years ago.
So it's an alias.
It's a washed ID with a valid social
security number and credit card history.
Interpol traced the name and listed
foreign nationals who have used it.
- Who used it most recently?
- A man named Habib Marwan.
We need to find him.
- I think we have.
- What do you mean?
He used the name Harris Barnes
to lease office space in LA.
It turns out the same address was given to us
an hour ago by Marianne Taylor.
- She and Curtis are there now.
- What's the address?
The 29th floor of the Rockland building.
I'm on my way.
When Curtis calls, patch him through.
You got it. You think Marwan's there?
Right now it's our only lead.
If he is, that's where the override is.
I'll get back to you.
I want you to tell me who's still out there.
I want the name of anyone who can help find
that override to stop the plants melting down.
My husband kept all this from me.
I only helped.
Yeah, that's a bunch of crap!
Now, we know you were
just as involved as your husband.
We're aware that the only reason
you're helping us is because of your son,
but believe me, it's not too late for us
to change our minds about how we treat him.
There are a few men
whose names I heard Navi mention.
They might know what you want...
but I don't know how to find them.
All right.
Why don't you start
by writing their names down?
As far as we can tell, this Habib
Marwan's been controlling the override.
- Jack's on his way there now?
- Yes.
Curtis and his team are already there.
We haven't been able to reach him or his
team members. He's not answering his cell.
- How far is Jack?
- About 15 minutes out.
Keep trying Curtis. Tell him Jack's
on the way. We have to coordinate them.
OK.
Tony, ask her about a man
named Habib Marwan.
Who's Habib Marwan?
I heard Navi speak of him a few times.
He's an engineer.
Beyond that, I don't know.
-  Ms Driscoll?
- Yes?
This is Nurse Carlson in the clinic.
There's a problem with your daughter.
I think you should get down here
as soon as you can.
- I'll be right there.
- Thank you.
It's the agent's phone.
What should we do with it?
Nothing. Let them wonder where he is.
By the time they realise what's happened,
it will be too late.
Find out if Adam and Jason have disposed
of the body. They should be back.
All right.
The radiation cloud- tell us more about that.
The government confirmed...
How is the evacuation moving?
It's moving slowly...
- Yeah?
- Ali, Adam and Jason are dead.
- Did the agent escape?
- No. The door is armed.
He's still on this floor.
- Find him.
- Yeah.
- Yes?
- The CTU agent is loose on this floor.
- How did he escape?
- He killed two of our men.
- Does he know the override is here?
- I don't think so. We have the exits covered.
Disconnect all the hard lines.
He can't contact CTU.
I will.
Maya...
- No, no, you can't keep me here!
- Maya...
- No!
- We want to help you feel better.
- I'll feel better when you get out of my face!
- Maya!
- What took you so long?
- I thought she took a sedative.
- She's fighting it.
- Give me a few minutes.
- Sure. Ruth...
Honey, I brought you here so you could
be near me. Isn't that what you wanted?
I want for us to go home.
Maya, we will, honey,
but we can't just yet. Honey.
I don't like these people here.
Maya, Maya.
That's not gonna make you feel better.
You're wrong. I do feel better.
- Sweetheart, I need you to...
- Go! Get out!
You're such an important person. Why don't
you take care of your important business?
- Oh, Maya.
- Doctor!
Doctor! Doctor!
Yes, Maya?
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry I was misbehaving,
but I promise to be good
if you'll just get that out of here.
I'm going.
Bye.
- I'll be in my office if you need me.
- All right.
Come on, Maya.
Curtis isn't answering his phone?
Right. It rang before I got his message.
If he had turned it off
it would go to voice mail.
- Where are the field teams?
- Castle's team will be there in two minutes.
I can have them set up a staging area
and stand by for your command.
- What's the probability that Marwan's there?
- We don't know yet.
Where are they staging?
In a parking lot in northwest
Wilshire and Grand, one block away.
OK.
- Have your people found Marwan yet?
- No.
Audrey, I would never be involved in anything
that could bring you harm.
Of all the people he could have approached
he chose you. It's a hell of a coincidence.
It might not be a coincidence. Maybe they
wanted him for more than the corporate shell.
He chose Paul because he was my husband?
That would put them close to your father.
So this Marwan used me
to get to Audrey's father?
It's a possibility.
I had no idea where Audrey
or her father would be today.
The information couldn't have come from me.
They used your relationship
with her father for something.
Maybe to plan something for the future,
a contingency plan.
I've been careless.
I am so sorry.
All right, so far every name Dina has given us
has checked out as a mid-level cell member.
But Marwan, who she claims to have never
met, is connected to everyone on this list.
It looks like all roads lead to him.
This must be his operation, which means she
definitely knows more than she's telling us.
- What do you want to do to make her talk?
- I just need you to give me a little bit of rope.
Do it.
Why don't you tell me about Habib Marwan?
- I already told you.
- No.
- You told me you never met him.
- I haven't.
Danny, could you come in here, please?
I'm gonna need all video and audio
monitoring in this room disconnected.
Thank you.
I'm not a stupid woman.
- What are you trying to prove with this?
- I'm not trying to prove anything.
I just don't want
what I'm about to say to be recorded.
I don't believe you.
Open the door!
Everybody out! Get out now!
Everyone, Erin.
Unless you tell me the whole truth,
that deal you made to save your son is over
and he goes to prison.
You can't do that.
The president signed an agreement.
If that gets in the way of protecting this
country, you think he'll stand behind it?
He's gonna tear it up and your son
goes to prison for the rest of his life.
And I know a little something about prison.
Based on the conditions of his confinement,
I give Behrooz three months
before he commits suicide.
And by the way,
I'm gonna make it my personal mission
to make sure you never hear word one
about what happens to him, ever.
Wait.
Habib Marwan is the man
our cell reported to in the United States.
You said your cell.
How many other cells reported to him?
- I don't know.
- But there are others?
- Yes.
- How many?
I told you, I don't know.
The cells are not in contact with one another.
Marwan thought it was safer that way.
What about the override?
Is it in his possession right now?
- Definitely.
- Why definitely?
Your programmers are trying to interfere
with the meltdown sequence.
Marwan is the only one
capable of stopping them.
- He's controlling it directly?
- Exactly.
Where? Where?
Somewhere in downtown.
The Rockland building?
Yes.
- Sarah Gavin.
- Get me Jack Bauer on the phone.
You got it.
Place her back in holding.
Dina just confirmed. Marwan's got
the override. He's at the Rockland building.
Everyone, listen up.
The address where Curtis is and where Jack
is heading is the location of the override.
I want every station to focus on this location.
I want field teams ready.
Rework your assault tactics on the building
factoring in this new information.
-  Let me speak to Tony.
- Hold on a second. Tony, I've got Jack.
- Jack.
- Yeah?
Marwan has the override.
He's at the address you're headed to.
- What about Curtis?
- No, we haven't been able to reach him yet.
- Have you changed the assault profiles?
- We're working on it.
Marwan can't know we're coming
or he'll take off.
Also, we have about 20 minutes
before the plants melt down.
Tell Castle to prep for a low-profile assault.
I'm on my way.
Copy that. Get me Castle.
Ali.
Go.
- Have you found him?
- It was not necessary for you to come down.
- Not necessary?
- We will find him.
If I'm captured, it'll end all we've worked for.
He can't get far.
Don't tell me that.
He's killed two of our men.
What is it, Forbes?
- Tell me you've got him.
- No, I'm sorry. He may have gotten away.
How is that possible?
Ali says the floor is locked off.
I know, we're still searching,
but we've got to deal with ventilation,
air ducts, ceiling space...
I don't care how you get him,
as long as he's contained.
I need 30 minutes.
Can you make that happen?
I can make it happen.
30 minutes.
Who's Marwan?
Who is he? Does he have the override?
Does he have the override?
- Yes.
- Where is he?
Where is he?
One flight up.
I don't have access to the floor.
- CTU, Sarah Gavin.
- Sarah, it's Curtis. Where's Driscoll?
- Where have you been?
- I'm still in the Rockland building. Listen.
Marianne's dead.
I'm sure our backup teams are dead too.
- The override is here.
- Jack's on his way to you now.
- Jack.
- I need you to put together a security detail.
I'll take care of it.
I want you to stay here until I get back.
- Are you going in?
- Yeah.
Just a second.
- This is Bauer.
- Jack, it's Manning.
- Where are you?
- 29th floor. Where are you?
At the staging area a block away.
Have you secured the override?
No, but it's here.
A man named Marwan is in control.
I know, CTU got a profile.
What's your mobility?
Limited. They're looking for me.
I took an access card off them.
- How do we meet?
- Take the main elevator.
- There's only one guard. I'll take care of him.
- I'm on my way.
They've got Marwan boxed in.
Send your team. Reinforce the perimeter.
I want men on the first floor
in case this thing goes hot.
I'll be right back.
Go! Go!
That was our field agent from the Rockland
building. Your daughter's with him.
- I don't want her anywhere near harm's way.
- She won't be, sir.
- Are we closing in on the override?
We hope so.
- We believe we've found where it is.
- Which is where?
In an office in LA.
We think the terrorists are either associated
with a tenant or they've created a corporation.
- How is CTU proceeding?
- We have teams converging.
Once we find the override we have to use it
to reprogram the reactors manually.
- Will there be enough time?
- Our people will be ready once we find it.
All right. I don't have to remind
both of you of the consequences if we fail.
Everyone here
understands what's at stake, sir.
Ms Driscoll,
Dr Sanford's on line two.
Excuse me, sir.
I'll meet you on the floor.
Yes, Doctor?
- Sorry to bother you. Maya's acting out again.
- What is she doing?
She's being abusive to my staff,
she's broken a few things.
If she doesn't settle I'll have to move her
to a private hospital. We can't handle her.
All right, don't do anything.
I'll be right there.
- Sarah.
- Excuse me.
- Is Edgar still on line with NRC?
- Yes.
- Find any other ways to stop the meltdowns?
- Not without the override.
- What's happening at the Rockland building?
- Castle's teams are on the perimeter.
- What about Curtis?
- He's about to meet up with Jack inside.
- Where are you working?
- Station three.
I'll be there in a few minutes.
Call me if Jack or Curtis get the override.
OK.
- You're a cruel person, do you know that?
- Maya, please!
This is a restricted area.
You must stay in bed.
Stay in bed? What am I? A baby?
Maya!
- What do you want, Mother?
- Don't!
Please don't
treat these people disrespectfully.
Please don't tell me what to do!
I'll stop telling you what to do
when you stop behaving like a child.
- What?
- You heard me.
There are other people in this world
besides you and they have problems too.
Now, are you gonna get a grip on yourself,
or do I have to call security to restrain you?
- You're pathetic, you know that?
- I will not allow you to talk to me like this.
- I will not!
- What are you gonna do about it?
I...
I just want to get out of here, Mommy.
And I will take you home.
But I have something I have to finish first.
No.
OK?
Yeah.
Are we clear?
Good.
That's my girl.
We got a man down. Take the wall.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
I overheard a phone conversation.
We have less than 15 minutes.
- How many are still alive?
- At least four.
- Have your men secure the floor. Which way?
- This way.
- What about backup?
- No. We can't let Marwan know we're coming.
- What's upstairs?
- IDS Data Systems.
Marwan's cell must have inserted a sleeper.
And used their servers
to download the virus to the plants.
- By piggybacking on IDS hardware.
- Yeah.
- Take the door.
- All right.
Clear.
Step away from the door, ma'am.
I need you to exit the building.
It's an emergency.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Let's go.
- Did we get a description on him?
- No.
He could be anyone.
What's up? What's going on?
Hold it!
- Yes?
- Marwan, it's Ali. We've been discovered!
Ali?
- Make sure all the exits are covered.
- Roger that.
Last man down.
Curtis!
Stay down!
Stay down! Get down! Get out of the way!
Stay where you are! Stay down!
- I got this exit!
- You got him?
No!
- Jack, I have the override!
- Secure it!
Call CTU now! Now!
I got him!
- Driscoll.
- Erin, I have the override. Put Edgar on.
Edgar! Line one. Curtis has the override.
- Edgar Stiles. Is the override logged in?
- Yes.
Send it to channel 11.
- I can't.
- What do you mean?
- The fields are write protected.
- That can't be.
If you're plugged in
you should be able to do what you want.
It's locked. What do you want me to do?
- The clinic called.
- Tell them to wait.
- They said it was...
- Tell them!
If you're gonna do something, do it now.
Marwan must have modified
the override to do this.
The NRC screen shows
the meltdown is beginning.
- Edgar, do something.
- There must be a hot key.
There's a lot of keys.
I can't just try random combinations.
Press the function keys.
The status window will light up
when you get to an active one.
- F5.
- Good. Hold it down and press escape.
- Nothing.
- Try F5, shift, escape.
- OK, it's responding.
- Good. Send it to channel 11. Hurry up.
Edgar, now they have three plants
in meltdown initiation.
- Did you get it?
- I hope so.
It's starting to respond.
Yes! Yes!
The temperature is dropping
in all remaining power plants.
Good work.
- Congratulations, Edgar.
Yeah! Whoo! Congratulations.
- Great work, Erin.
- Thank you, sir.
Excuse me.
Maya?
Where is she?
Maya!
Oh! Oh!
Oh, baby!
Oh!
It's over, sir.
We've stopped the meltdown.
Congratulations, Mr President.
Well done.
This is Bauer. We've got a man down.
Marwan is in the northwest stairwell headed
to ground level. Does anybody read me?
Jack, it's Castle. I'll get a man up there.
Son of a bitch! All CTU agents,
Marwan is impersonating a CTU officer.
I repeat, the suspect
is impersonating a CTU officer.
Solarz, do you read me?
Visiontext Subtitles: Sarah Johnston
ENGLISH SDH