I'm on the phone with a man who claims
to be James Nathanson, Cummings' contact.
He says he has information,
but he will only talk to you.
- What do you want with me?
- The terrorists are trying to kill me.
What makes you think I won't kill you?
Because you want to stop the Sentox gas
being released on American soil. So do I.
Nathanson, stay down!
Stay down!
What's on the chip?
Please! What's on the chip?
O'Brian.
I have a ThumbDrive
that will help find the Sentox.
The decryption kicked out
a company called Omicron.
Pull up their roster.
See if Christopher Henderson is on the list.
Senior vice president
of research and development.
- Send me the decrypted files over to my PDA.
- That's gonna be hard to do.
You're up to something. I won't stand for it.
- This was an attempt to circumvent me.
- We are on the same side.
If your father wasn't secretary of defense,
I'd have you thrown out.
I don't have that problem with you.
I spent a year securing a weapon
that would bring Moscow to its knees
and you waste it.
We were betrayed, Bierko.
Someone must pay.
I agree.
This is President Logan. What is it you want?
I want the route of Suvarov's motorcade.
If you refuse to cooperate, I will have
no choice but to release all the Sentox gas.
- He wants to assassinate Suvarov.
- Don't negotiate with them.
Isn't that the point of the treaty you signed?
Mr. President,
I'm glad we have this opportunity
to thank you and Mrs. Logan
for your hospitality.
The motorcade will take
service roads to the 118.
- Mrs. Logan.
- Aaron. I've decided to drive to the airport.
- I'll ride up front.
- No, that's not necessary.
Yes, it is.
The world has become, quote,
"safer and more secure from terrorist attack".
President Suvarov and his wife
will be flying back to Moscow in a few hours.
- Yes.
- Where is the motorcade?
- Getting on the 118.
- How long till they reach the ambush point?
- About 40 minutes.
- Good. We'll be waiting.
Get everything ready.
Mr. President, I asked Secret Service
to send their threat assessment
for President Suvarov's route.
The most vulnerable point is here
at the downtown corridor.
This is the most likely point of attack
if an ambush were to occur.
It's going to happen, Mike.
We gave the terrorists Suvarov's route.
I need to come up with a public response
to convince the world that Suvarov's death
only underscores the importance of this
antiterrorism treaty that we just signed.
I'll begin working on a statement, sir.
Yes.
Thank you. I'll let the president know.
What? What is it, Mike? What's going on?
Who was that?
Agent Pierce.
- I don't know how to tell you this, sir.
- Just tell me.
- . Logan is with the Suvarovs.
- What are you talking about?
Sir, she got into their limousine.
Oh, my God!
Didn't the Secret Service stop her?
There was no reason to.
The motorcade is under Secret Service escort.
As far as they're concerned,
she's not in any danger.
She wants me to call back the motorcade.
She's trying to save them.
- Should I alert them?
- Yes!
No, stop. Wait.
If we warn them,
the terrorists are going to set off the gas.
Where are they now?
They're still on the 118.
Get my wife on the phone.
My aunt visited Los Angeles in the 1950s.
She told me this area was filled
with orange groves, but I haven't seen any.
I suppose it's all been built over, no?
Martha?
Yes, I was just trying to remember. I think
your aunt's memory is better than mine.
I visited when I was a child,
but I don't recall the orange groves.
- Yeah, this is Pierce.
- Let me speak to my wife.
Mrs. Logan,
it's the president for you on line one.
Thank you, Aaron.
- Hello, Charles.
- Listen to me carefully. I want you...
Yes, I think they had a wonderful visit.
Anya would very much like us to come
to Moscow. Wouldn't that be lovely?
I want you to tell the Suvarovs
that I need you back here.
- I'll have one of the cars bring you back.
- I don't think so.
Tell them now, while I'm on the phone.
Martha, I know that you want me
to call the motorcade back,
but the terrorists were very specific.
If I don't allow them to attack the motorcade,
they'll release canisters of nerve gas
in multiple locations.
I guess we'll just have to
figure something out before that happens.
We're trying!
We're trying, but we haven't found them yet.
You need to get out of the car.
OK, I should go now,
but call me if there's any change of plans.
- Dammit, Martha!
- OK, bye-bye. I'll talk to you soon.
- She won't get out of the limousine.
- My God!
We gotta do something,
get her out of the car.
I could have one of the trail cars stop and
force her out, say that I need her back here.
You could, but if Martha is desperate
to save the Suvarovs,
she might feel that the only remaining option
is to tell them the truth.
Then Suvarov would know
that I gave him up for assassination.
Sir, do you want me
to recall the motorcade or not?
Meet me in the server room in a few minutes.
- Am I in trouble?
- No, there's something we need to discuss.
- OK.
- And, Edgar?
Don't tell anyone where you're going.
This stays between us.
Sure.
- What did Audrey Raines want?
- She was going over some DOD protocols.
- Thought you were monitoring chatter.
- We are.
- Why isn't it on my screen, Carrie?
- I thought you wanted to save time.
I do. It saves me time
by not having to clean up more mistakes.
Mirror everything until we've secured
this nerve gas. Clear?
Yes, sir.
The ThumbDrive data Jack sent checks out as
authentic. It's time stamped by DOD and CIA.
So Omicron International
did make Sentox for the military.
Yeah, and some terrorists found out about it.
Or worse, they were in contact with Omicron.
- Who is this Henderson?
- Henderson, senior vice president of R & D.
Jack said he knew him.
- Is he connected with the Sentox?
- It just said he was a senior VP.
All right.
- Yeah.
- We've authenticated the data.
Omicron made the Sentox for the military.
OK. I need you to work something up that
gets me in without them knowing I'm CTU.
Do you think it's necessary?
Yeah. There's someone
I don't want to see me coming.
Christopher Henderson?
- Yeah.
- Who is he?
- Someone I used to work for.
- Where?
- CTU. He was the man who recruited me.
- You never mentioned him.
I know. Things ended badly between us.
What happened?
I was part of an investigation
that implicated him
in the sale of classified intelligence
to defence contractors.
We never had enough evidence to indict him,
but he lost his job, his command.
Even as he was walking out the door,
he maintained his innocence.
He never forgave me for being part of it.
- Are you convinced he did it?
- I was at the time.
Chloe can't find a connection
between the Sentox and him.
Trust me, if Omicron was making Sentox
legally or illegally, Henderson knew about it.
- Get back to me when you've got my cover.
- All right, I'm on it.
- What are you doing here?
- Same thing you are.
- Thank you for coming.
- Look, I don't have a lot of time.
We don't have a single lead on this gas.
- That's not true. Jack is following a lead.
- How do you know?
- I just spoke with him.
- Lynn issued an arrest warrant.
That's why we wanted to talk to you.
Lynn is losing it.
He went after Jack,
then he took Buchanan out of play.
- Lynn is incapable of leading us through this.
- You're working behind his back?
We're afraid if we bring him in,
he might derail the only good lead we have.
We have to help Jack locate the nerve gas
before it's too late.
- What do you want from me?
- Cover for Chloe until Jack reports back.
- Please?
- OK.
Thank you.
OK, fine. Yeah.
That was Secret Service. The motorcade
continues to the airport without incident.
There won't be any warning. When these
people attack, they will be fast and merciless.
You can count on that.
I have to talk to this man.
- Maybe I can convince him to hold off.
- Hold off?
Until Martha gets out.
She wasn't supposed to be part of this.
- I don't think that would change his plans.
- He has to know that my wife's in the car.
- I can't lose her, Mike.
- The only way to keep Martha safe
is for me to call Secret Service
and tell them to turn the motorcade around.
What about CTU? Do they have
any active leads on the nerve gas?
As of five minutes ago, they don't.
Nothing that would help.
What am I missing? There's gotta be
some way out that I'm not seeing.
You're not missing anything.
Any action we take to save Martha
would also save the Suvarovs,
and if that happens,
the terrorists will release the gas.
Unfortunately, it's that simple.
Then there's nothing more we can do, Mike.
Unless I warn them...
Martha's going to die with the Suvarovs.
Aaron, have there been any changes?
Excuse me? Changes to what, Mrs. Logan?
I was wondering
if there'd been changes to our route.
We haven't gotten
any revised instructions, ma'am.
Thank you.
- Are you sure you're all right?
- Yes, yes.
I just wanted to make sure
we don't run into any heavy traffic.
Understood. Those protocols
should be coming over shortly.
- Who were you on the phone with?
- Homeland Security.
I gave you orders
to have all systems mirrored to mine.
- I've been doing that.
- Yet somehow you have time to chat.
They needed updated code sets.
It'll just take a minute.
No, it won't.
Stiles, finish her task. Carrie, you're done.
- What do you mean, "done"?
- Fired. You don't work here any more.
- It's not her fault. She...
- One more word, you walk with her.
What's it gonna be?
- Where's Agent O'Brian?
- She had to step away for a minute.
- Where?
- I don't know.
OK, I'm through the gate.
I'm pulling into a parking space now.
- How's my cover?
- I'm still trying to get your credentials in.
- You can't get in without them.
- What's wrong?
Omicron's systems don't refresh enough.
We need to push this page in manually.
OK, I'm in. You're going in
under the name of John Barrie, B-a-r-r-i-e.
- You're with a company called Eclipse LLC.
- John Barrie, Eclipse LLC. I got it.
- Hold on. She hasn't planted it yet.
- Chloe, what are you doing in here?
- I asked her to help.
- She doesn't work for you, she works for me.
But I don't,
and DOD has assignment priority over CTU.
We're in the middle of an investigation.
You can’t just take her away from me.
I'm not. We needed a system patch on the
server. Chloe's the only one who could fix it.
Then you come and you ask me.
Everything in this office runs through me.
Lynn, we are all trying to do the same thing.
- Can we please just get past this?
- Yeah, I'm past it. I want Chloe back.
OK, I'm finished here.
Sorry, Mr. McGill. It won't happen again.
Good afternoon. I'm John Barrie with Eclipse.
I've got a 4:30 with R & D.
Thumbprint, please.
- Go on in.
- Thank you.
Kick the Macavoy meeting to next week
on Thursday, but keep everything else.
- What about your trip to Washington?
- OK.
I gotta talk to Kagen tomorrow.
I'll get back to you.
- Can I help you, sir?
- Sorry. I was looking for the men's room.
Over there. Second door.
Thank you.
Audrey Raines.
I need you to lose a secretary.
Her name is Joanna Tandy.
All right. I'll take care of it.
- Henderson's office.
- Ms Tandy?
- Yes.
- Jane Espenson from accounting.
We need you to check some of these invoices.
- What invoices?
- It's difficult to explain over the phone.
Would you mind popping down for a minute?
- Fine.
- Thank you.
There's a problem in accounting.
I'll be right back.
Yeah, OK.
Jack. Jack.
Just for the record,
I never believed you were dead.
What are you doing here?
Earlier this morning, terrorists gained control
of a large quantity of Sentox.
Omicron made it.
I pulled up the executive list, you were on it.
Sure, I work here. Omicron had the contract.
We manufactured the stuff.
But every gram of it went to the DOD.
It's all accounted for.
That can't be true. We have confirmation
the terrorists are in control of 19 canisters.
Are you accusing me
of being in bed with terrorists?
- I'm following the leads.
- The leads are wrong.
DOD destroyed the entire stockpile.
Sentox was responsible for the death of the
people in the mall less than two hours ago.
- The news said it was chlorine gas.
- That was a story to stop widespread panic.
Come on, Christopher.
You know how this works.
The terrorists have threatened
to release the rest of the gas.
Good God.
Whoever's implicating me in this
knows my history with CTU.
I mean, I'm an easy target.
This is not a coincidence.
Look, Jack. I know the deal between us, but I
swear to you, I've got nothing to do with this.
- I can't afford to take your word on this.
- You'll have to take my word.
11 people died. Hundreds of thousands
of others will if they release the Sentox.
You're not hearing me, Jack.
I had nothing to do with this.
Then prove it to me.
I need access
to Omicron's Sentox programme.
I'm doing it now. The entire operation
was run from a bunker across the campus.
Let me see the bunker.
Let's go.
Chatter analysis came in.
They decoded some words and phrases.
- What were they saying?
- It's too scrambled.
But number strings keep coming up -
5, 110, 10.
- Freeways?
- The routes Suvarov's taking to the airport.
The only other phrase I could decode
refers to the downtown corridor.
How long ago did this chatter start?
About 30 minutes ago.
Come on.
- Have we expanded the search?
- I've got air surveillance east of Glendale.
- North?
- Edwards Air Force Base is giving support.
We're still at a dead end on finding new leads.
Excuse me, there might be an attack
on President Suvarov's motorcade.
- What?
- Edgar monitored some chatter from NSA.
Why are you analysing chatter
unrelated to the gas?
- It came through on one of my filters.
- We found something.
Don't you want to alert Secret Service?
He is on his way to the airport.
Based on an unsubstantiated theory
from two analysts?
I've been embarrassed enough for one day.
Can we at least devote some resources
to try to confirm this?
I'm sorry. Maybe I wasn't clear.
No. Now go downstairs and focus on
what you're supposed to be doing.
I don't think it would be a bad idea
to pass along the intel.
Well, I do.
I don't want to hear another word about it.
- Yes.
- Our men are in place. How far out are they?
They will be there in less than 20 minutes.
Are you sure no one's gonna interfere?
I don't think so. Logan knows
the consequences if that happens.
But be alert. Make sure they haven't
placed any of their people near you.
- If police show up, we'll deal with them.
- Good.
I'll call you when it's over.
Let's go. Let's go.
Keep them armed. If things
don't go as planned, I'll use them here.
- I'm busy.
- I looked at this chatter report.
I think that we need to let
Secret Service know of the threat.
I'm not gonna repeat my orders
to every person.
My people are not gonna chase that white
elephant. They're trying to locate Sentox gas.
Has it occurred to you that if this is real,
then it's likely the terrorists who have
the Sentox are the ones planning this attack?
This is an unverified threat. If you want
to hand it off to NSA, be my guest.
NSA can't recall the motorcade
without a time-consuming approval process.
Good! That process
helps eliminate false threats.
- Look, we don't have that time.
- Ms Raines! Ms Raines.
This office has made enough mistakes
and I intend to stop it.
Now let my people focus on their work
or I will have you escorted out of here.
Thank you.
Secret Service won't act on this
unless Lynn verifies it.
- He's never gonna back you up.
- Yes, he is.
I need you to hack into Lynn's account. I'll
forge a message to look like it came from him.
- That's illegal.
- Fine.
Put a blanket on my subnet
to make it look like I'm doing something else.
- We could all end up in jail.
- Think about it for a second.
The Russian president, his wife, about 35
Secret Service, all dead in a few minutes.
All right.
For the record, this is not a good idea.
All right. I'll compose the message. As soon
as you have the forged verification, call me.
Curtis, excuse me.
We need to talk.
- What is it?
- We've got a problem with Lynn.
Yeah, he's not listening to anybody.
- It's gonna cost lives.
- Give him time. He'll come around.
Curtis, we don't have time.
We've got to get Bill back here.
- That won't happen.
- We need to make it happen.
What are you suggesting?
- Section 1-12.
- On what grounds?
Lynn is mentally incapable of running CTU.
I may not agree with his choices, but going
from there to mentally unfit, that's a stretch.
No, it's not, and you know it.
You've seen him.
With Bill in custody,
you're the only one that can invoke it.
- Look, I don't know, Audrey.
- Yes, you do.
Curtis, CTU is barely functional.
You are the one that can turn it around.
Even if I agreed, section 1-12 requires
documentation, testimony, groundwork.
The record of what is going on right now
is documentation enough.
Curtis, please.
Think about it.
- I will.
- Good. Thank you.
Mr. President.
Come in, Mike.
The motorcade is only 15 minutes away
from the airport.
Yeah.
My father told me that life was about problem
solving, that every problem had a solution.
You tell me where the solution is on this one.
I don't have an answer, Mr. President.
But if you want
the Suvarov motorcade to turn back,
I need to do it now.
We know the terrorists are willing
to kill civilians. And the low...
the low end of the casualty range
on this one is 100,000 lives.
Yes, sir.
I decided before that I couldn't risk all those
lives to save one man, the Russian president.
I can't risk those lives now.
Even to save my own wife.
Damn you, Martha.
Putting me in this position.
You brought it on yourself.
Mike.
Pray with me, Mike.
Mr. President, with all due respect,
this is a personal matter.
- I don't...
- Please, Mike.
- How much longer until we can send this?
- A couple minutes. I'm almost in.
- We don't have a couple minutes.
- I'm almost there.
- Oh, no! Lynn cut us off.
- What do I do?
I think it's too late to do anything.
Did you think I wouldn't notice you
accessing my comm?
- Listen. We need to talk.
- Shut up. They're against CTU, against me.
What is this?
- We were warning Secret Service of an attack.
Take Mr. Stiles and Ms O'Brian.
Put 'em in Holding.
And then escort Audrey Raines out of CTU.
I can't do that.
Yes, you can. It's a direct order. Do it.
You forced them to work covertly.
You're not behaving rationally, Lynn.
You and you, take them all into custody,
including Mr. Manning.
If you try to carry that out,
I will draw my weapon.
- If he draws his weapon, shoot him.
- This is out of control. Don't make it worse.
Why are you hesitating?
I gave you an order. Now do it!
- What should I do, Mr. Manning?
- What?
I'm relieving you of your command
under the incapacity clause of section 1-12.
- You will do no such thing.
- Take him away.
You can't do that.
He can't do this. Don't touch me.
This is an unjustified usurpation of authority.
You hear me? We're in the middle of a crisis.
There are gonna be repercussions. Everyone
involved with this is gonna face prosecution.
- Security office.
- This is Manning. Release Bill Buchanan.
Inform Division he's been reinstated
as director of CTU under section 1-12.
Right away, sir.
Everyone, get back to your stations.
Fill me in.
Chloe and Edgar detected chatter
indicating an attack on Suvarov's motorcade.
- How'd they get the route?
- We don't know.
The likely point of intercept is downtown.
- Is Secret Service notified?
- Lynn refused.
- Notify Secret Service now.
- I need to override the firewall Lynn put up.
- Here.
- I need Carrie. He fired her.
Have security reinstate her. Edgar.
Pull up satellite on all possible
intercept points and call the president.
- Where are we on the location of the gas?
- No substantial progress.
- What about the lead Jack was following?
- He traced the gas to Omicron International.
- Is that where Jack is?
- Yes.
Mr. Buchanan, the president's on the line.
We have intelligence
that indicates President Suvarov's motorcade
may be attacked in the next few minutes.
- Is that so?
- Yes, sir. We are notifying Secret Service.
What we can tell you
is that if the attack happens,
it will occur in or around the downtown area.
The motorcade is approaching
that area now, sir.
Mr. President?
Bill, Mike Novick.
The president is at a loss for words.
His wife is in the Suvarovs' limousine.
Thank you. You've done a good job.
- What do we do?
- There's nothing we can do, sir.
CTU is informing Secret Service.
They will no doubt take defensive measures,
which makes the attack
substantially less likely to succeed.
- Red Protocol. Turn back.
- Protocol red! Protocol red!
Hold on tight. We're turning around.
We just received intelligence about a threat.
They're turning around.
We're under attack. We need backup now!
That's a missile fire.
The motorcade's been hit.
Aaron.
Aaron. Oh, God!
No!
Let's go! Let's go!
Are you OK?
- Novick.
- The motorcade's been attacked.
- How badly?
- Bad. We sustained major casualties.
- What about Mrs. Logan?
- They're shaken, but alive. Tell the president.
I will. Thank you.
Your wife survived the attack.
CTU intervened in time.
Thank God.
What about the Suvarovs?
They were shaken up, but they'll be OK.
He's going to think I tipped off CTU.
It won't matter to him
that I tried to keep my end of the bargain.
I agree.
We need to prepare ourselves
for the terrorists' retaliation.
All the work on the Sentox project
was run out of here.
- How restricted was access?
- Extremely.
For security reasons, each contract was run
out of its own separate, dedicated bunker.
Each bunker is completely sealed.
Nothing gets in and nothing gets out.
This is gonna take some time.
I've gotta merge some files,
find out who worked on this.
You're senior VP. You don't know?
Give me a break. 8,000 people work for this
company. I gotta run a sort. It'll take a minute.
So who's the honcho over at CTU now?
- Bill Buchanan.
- Buchanan?
What a stiff. No wonder
everything's going to hell over there.
You get rid of everybody who can do the job.
- You made your own bed.
- You accused the wrong man.
- I just showed them what I found.
- I was framed.
- By who?
- Nina Myers, George Mason, who knows?
But I tell you, the one thing that just
hangs on me, the one thing that just hurts me
is that you didn't believe me.
You made it impossible to believe you.
How could I possibly defend you?
You couldn't even defend yourself.
No one gave me the chance.
OK, we've got something here.
Lead scientist, head of project Sentox,
- Allen Burkett, PhD.
- I'm gonna need to speak to him.
You're gonna have a problem. Died in
a helicopter crash in Geneva two years ago.
Let's see what else we've got.
This is bizarre.
Two other scientists on the Sentox project,
one drowned on a diving trip in the Bahamas,
the other burned to death in a car accident
two weeks later. What the hell is going on?
CTU's gonna have to break it down.
How do I upload files ready to transfer?
We need IT. They're next door.
I'm gonna get somebody to help us.
I'll let CTU know
that we're sending the files over.
Hello?
Dammit!
Oh, my God!
How could I be so stupid?
- Yes?
- Yeah, it's me.
I listened to everything Bauer had to say. CTU
does not have enough information to hurt us.
What about Bauer?
Well, in about one minute, he'll be dead.
Agh!
Argh!
Look, tell the media
we don't know how the terrorists found out
about the Suvarovs' route.
We're looking into it now.
Mike, I've been thinking that, diplomatically,
we should play up the fact
Martha was in the vehicle.
- Why is that, sir?
- It'll get rid of suspicion we might've been...
There he is.
- Hello.
- We had an understanding.
I had nothing to do with this. Believe me.
It was your job to make sure
no one interfered with the attack.
It happened outside of my authority.
I told no one.
If Russia isn't going to pay
with the life of its president,
then its new ally, the United States,
will pay with the lives of its citizens.
Mr. President,
this is our final conversation. Goodbye.
No! Wait!