- Any problems getting the canisters out?
- No. They were exactly where you said.
The Russians will learn the
consequences of occupying our homeland
when we turn Moscow into a graveyard.
Erwich has just cleared airport security.
- And the authorities don't know anything?
- Not yet.
The only thing left to take care of is Bauer.
- You paged me?
- I need you to do something.
- We've our hands full searching for the gas.
- Bauer is a priority.
I just signed a treaty.
Now I find the terrorists are still out there.
With nerve gas.
You people have to listen to me.
I had a document.
It was hidden in my blouse.
It's gone. Someone stole it from me.
This is what she was like before Vermont.
- Are you suggesting that I readmit her?
- Consider the option, for her sake.
My wife is gone.
- We have a priority alert.
You've been burrowing into classified
CTU protocols without authorisation.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Stop. You logged onto the subsystem.
Someone knew that Jack was alive.
It's critical to our investigation
that we find out who that was.
Did you let that man into CTU? This man is
a professional assassin. He killed Dr Paulson.
Who told you to let that man into CTU?
The White House.
Mr. Cummings.
Palmer was murdered because he was about
to expose Cummings' link to the terrorists.
When Cummings failed
to frame me for it, he tried to kill me.
Jack, we don't have proof.
We can prove Cummings used Spenser
to get Jack's assassin in.
Spenser's word isn't enough to build a case.
You don't have time. You want the gas,
Cummings is your connection.
Cummings is the president's chief advisor.
How do we get to him?
I secretly meet Mike Novick. Enlist his help.
How do we know Novick's not in this?
Because I know him. He'll listen to me.
The president will listen to him.
With Novick, we can isolate Cummings.
Jack, much as I appreciate this,
you don't work here any more.
That's exactly the reason
why I should do this.
If it backfires, there'll be no fallout on you.
- I think it's worth a try.
- I agree.
It's your call.
All right, Jack.
But this is about finding the nerve gas,
not getting revenge for David Palmer.
Understood.
Work out your protocols with Ms Raines.
We'll look through Cummings' background.
I'm gonna need to set up a secure channel
for you to contact us on.
OK.
Can you bring up a satellite photo
of the compound?
Jack, I'm sorry
if I'm being a little distant. I just...
It's taking me a little while
to get used to you being alive.
I understand.
I'll call Novick.
Jack.
When Cummings finds out that you're
still alive, he's gonna come after you again.
Yeah.
- Yes?
- Is Bauer dead?
I haven't received confirmation yet.
Your man should have taken care of it.
Perhaps he had to alter his strike window.
Has the nerve gas reached the port?
Not yet. But it should be arriving any minute.
Good.
I have to go. I'm late for a briefing.
You have the shipping documents in order?
The canisters will arrive in port in eight days.
Ground transportation to your base camp
will take another day.
- Do you need help getting them to the target?
- No.
I've arranged transport to Moscow.
- Would you put this on now?
- Have they found my wife yet?
No. Secret Service is confident
she's still on the grounds.
If they're so damn confident,
why can't anyone find her?
I'm sure it's just a matter of time,
Mr. President.
- Sorry I'm late.
- I was just setting up the video.
This was made by terrorists to document
the effects of exposure to nerve gas.
It was recovered from a training camp
two years ago.
Disorientation occurs
moments after exposure.
Now the video jumps forward. No more
than a couple of minutes, we estimate.
Within that time, there's permanent damage
to the central nervous system.
Violent seizures take over,
bronchial membranes blister, peel away.
- Death occurs within...
- Stop.
Now, according to DOD,
the Sentox-6 nerve gas stolen from the airport
is far more lethal
than the gas we just saw used.
If released in a town or city, for example,
the cloud will remain lethal for much longer.
Are we any closer to finding the canisters?
There haven't been
any reports of progress, sir.
Excuse me, Mr. President.
I need to return a call to the State Department.
Do you have those updates, Walt?
Yes, here's one from CTU.
Also one from Homeland Security.
- This is Bauer.
- Jack. Mike Novick.
It's good to hear your voice.
Yours too, Mike.
So sorry about David Palmer.
I know how much he meant to you.
Yeah.
What's going on?
I have a lead on the stolen nerve gas.
Isn't CTU coordinating the search?
This is something
I need to bring directly to you.
- I don't understand.
- I can't talk about it on the phone, Mike.
We need to meet. No one can know about this,
not even the president.
I'm not comfortable
with all this secrecy, Jack.
You need to give me
some idea of what this is about.
It concerns Walt Cummings.
Ah.
There's an area a few hundred yards
outside the southwest gate,
at the far side of the property
from the main house.
Thanks, Mike. I'll see you in 15 minutes.
- Jack.
- Hey.
- They say we can leave soon.
- I know. I heard.
Well, what about you?
Are you coming home with us?
No, I need to stay here.
CTU still needs my help.
I'd like to speak with your mom
for a moment. All right?
- Yeah, of course.
- Take him downstairs. She'll be there soon.
You're not coming back to us, are you?
No.
I never thought
I was gonna be back here at CTU.
I would never have gotten you involved
in all of this, I promise you.
It's the woman who interviewed me, isn't it?
Audrey Raines?
You were involved with her.
I could tell
by the way you looked at each other.
I was with her before I had to disappear.
Are you still in love with her?
Yes.
Does she still love you?
I don't know.
Mr. Bauer?
Your transportation's standing by.
I'll be right there.
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Yeah.
Thank you.
I'm not comfortable
with all this secrecy, Jack.
You need to give me
some idea what this is about.
It concerns Walt Cummings.
There's an area a few hundred yards
outside the southwest gate,
at the far side of the property
from the main house.
- Your man didn't do his job.
- Don't put that on me.
You were supposed
to have Bauer killed hours ago.
I'm not gonna warn you again.
Pull yourself together.
You heard the call, didn't you? Bauer's
coming here to expose my role in all this.
- You're assuming he knows it all.
- It's obvious he knows enough.
Now what the hell am I supposed to do?
At this point,
there's only one thing you can do.
Mrs. Logan. Please come out of there.
Mrs. Logan.
Aaron, don't let them take me.
You've got to listen to me.
- They're just trying to help you.
- No. No, they're trying to set me up.
They're trying to make it look like
I had a breakdown so they can cart me off.
- Ma'am, they're...
- Aaron.
It's someone in my husband's administration.
They're trying to shut me up
because I know the truth.
- What truth?
- David Palmer.
I know...
- Don't let them take me, Aaron. Please.
- We have our orders, Mrs. Logan. I'm sorry.
Aaron?
Please?
Aaron.
Audrey. Did you check with the airports?
- Yes. They've all been alerted.
- And CHP?
Trucks are being checked at all interstates.
Make sure the gas isn't mentioned.
The White House was clear.
I know. The bulletin only describes the
canisters. No mention of chemical weapons.
The last thing we need is for the public
to find out that nerve gas is out there.
Schaeffer.
What are you doing in there?
Making sure the canisters
were secured properly.
Don't want 'em knocking around on the ship.
My men secured the canisters according to
my instructions. You needn't be concerned.
All right. Here are the customs documents
you need when the shipment arrives,
along with the remote trigger, and the arming
codes. I'll take the rest of my payment now.
Our arrangement was you get your final
instalment when the ship left port.
That won't be a problem.
They're loading in less than an hour.
Then you won't have long to wait.
Fine.
I'll be right there.
- Ms Raines?
- Yes?
- We've been released.
- Oh, good.
- Can I ask you something?
- Of course.
Do you still have feelings for Jack?
- I'm sorry, that's personal.
- I know.
But he's been living with my son and me
for the last six months.
We started to become a family.
And I care about him.
Do you know he still loves you?
If you don't love him, let him go.
- Bauer.
- Jack, it's Audrey.
What's going on?
Jack...
What?
Audrey, what?
When this is over, are you coming back?
I don't know.
Are you going back to Diane?
No. I-I don't know what I'm doing yet.
I haven't had any time to think about it.
- Is it true, what she said?
- What'd she say?
That you still love me.
I never stopped loving you.
Not for one second.
Then don't go away again, Jack. Please.
- It's more complicated than that.
- I know.
It's time.
- I've gotta go.
- Jack...
- I have to go.
- Yeah, I know. I know. OK. Bye.
No, no. Keep me outta this.
The last thing I want to do is comment
to the press about the roadblocks going up.
And we can't have any leaks about
the nerve gas. It would just cause a panic.
Come in.
- Pardon me, we've found Mrs. Logan.
- Is she all right?
She's fine, sir.
She was hiding in the stables.
The stables.
What the hell did she think she was doing?
Mr. President.
I feel awkward mentioning this, but...
Mrs. Logan said some things.
- About David Palmer?
- Yes, sir.
I've heard her conspiracy theories, Aaron.
I've heard them all.
But thank you for your concern, Aaron.
They found my wife.
Good.
Mr. President.
We need to talk.
What is it, Walt?
I was hoping to spare you from this,
but I'm afraid Jack Bauer's forcing my hand.
He's on his way here
to meet with Mike Novick.
Bauer? Why?
To accuse me of helping the terrorists
acquire the nerve gas.
That's ridiculous.
No, sir.
It's the truth.
What did you say?
Through a proxy, I leaked information to the
terrorists about where the gas was hidden.
This gas was never
gonna pose a threat to American lives...
Never pose a threat?
People died in the airport.
Hostages were killed.
- We had hoped to limit the collateral damage.
- What are you thinking?
This is an unspeakable crime.
Walt.
- You have to answer for this.
- Mr. President.
It's in your best interest to hear me out
before you make that phone call.
What do you mean, "my best interest"?
The gas is being smuggled out of the country
by separatists who think they're
going to use it against the Russians.
However, that nerve gas
will never reach Russian soil.
And you know this how?
We control the remote detonators
on those canisters.
As soon as they reach the terrorist base,
we'll trigger the canisters and release the gas.
What happened today
was just to kill terrorists?
No, the goal is to produce a smoking gun.
Proof of the existence of
weapons of mass destruction in central Asia.
- This is unbelievable.
- No. It's necessary.
It will give us a pretext to increase
our military presence there,
guaranteeing the flow of oil
for the next generation.
How dare you?
How dare you act without my consent?
How dare you put this administration,
this entire country, in jeopardy?
- You're a traitor.
- No.
No, Mr. President, I am a patriot!
Doing what needs to be done for the
continued safety and wellbeing of this nation.
My God.
You gave the order
to have David Palmer killed.
That was an unfortunate,
but necessary, intervention.
- He found out too much. We had...
- Walt.
You're rationalising murder.
The murder of a president.
Contact these people,
recover the gas before it leaves the country.
- I'm afraid I can't do that.
- Why not?
I don't know where the gas is.
The man I have working inside has gone dark.
He's unreachable.
Now, you let things play out as they are.
Otherwise, your administration
will be implicated,
and your presidency will be destroyed.
It's your choice, Mr. President.
Jack.
Thanks for seeing me like this, Mike.
What is it?
- Did you tell anyone we were meeting?
- Of course not.
Son of a bitch. Who did you tell?
- Who did you tell?
- I didn't tell anybody, Jack.
Jack Bauer. Stay right where you are.
- Put down your weapon.
- Tell your men to stand down!
- Sir, we can't do that.
- He's here at my request.
We have orders to use force if necessary.
- Orders? From who?
- The president of the United States.
Get on your knees.
Affirmative, sir. Bauer was
apprehended with no resistance on his part.
- We're transporting him back to the retreat.
- Thanks.
Novick and Bauer
have been taken into custody.
- So we're just gonna lock Mike Novick up?
- For the time being.
What good will it do?
Eventually, he's gonna talk to the press.
- What can he say? He doesn't know anything.
- You told me he talked to Jack Bauer.
We stopped Bauer
before he could give Mike any details.
What's he gonna think? We're detaining him.
Bauer was about to divulge secrets
that Mike's not authorised to hear.
That's why Mike's being detained.
What about Bauer? He must have talked to
people at CTU and told them what he knows.
As soon as this nerve gas leaves US soil,
it's gonna be very difficult to prove that
either of us is connected to this in any way.
Are you sure these detonators will work?
The gas will be released
before it can be used against the Russians?
Yes.
Right now, all you need to do is authorise me
to terminate CTU's involvement in this matter.
Tell them we've got the situation
under control and that we'll deal with Bauer.
Who, after all, is not
officially affiliated with them any longer.
All right.
Good.
- Yes?
- Mr. President, Mrs. Logan for you.
- Not now.
- Yes, sir.
Dunley.
What is Jack Bauer doing here, why is
he under arrest, and why wasn't I told?
- Orders of the president.
- Directly?
No, they came
through Walt Cummings' office.
OK. Thank you.
We're no longer on the search for the
canisters. We've been ordered off by Division.
Why?
The White House wants to use their people.
- That doesn't make sense. We'll waste hours.
- I know. The president's not taking my calls.
- What about Mike Novick?
- Unreachable. Jack's cell goes to voicemail.
- Something's wrong.
- I know. But I don't know what we can do.
- I do.
- What?
- Disregard the order.
- We won't disregard a presidential order.
If we don't, we won't find this nerve gas.
Sending Jack to Mike Novick
as a private citizen is one thing.
But I'm not about to disobey
a direct order from the White House.
That's because you don't have
the experience to know any better.
Mr. Buchanan,
would you step outside for a moment?
- I can't have you talking like that.
- Sorry.
- Are we clear about who's in charge?
- My advice stands.
If this orderjeopardises our chances
of finding that gas, you must ignore it.
At least until we can
bring our case to the White House.
- You need to make decisions faster.
- Bill.
One more thing that comes with experience.
If we don't do everything in our power to
stop these terrorists, we're not doing our job.
- OK. Disregard the order.
- Thank you.
Is there anything else
you'd like me to pack for you?
Maybe a few of your nicer dresses?
I'm being confined
to a psychiatric ward, Evelyn.
I don't think
there are gonna be any black-tie events.
Sorry.
How'd this happen?
What's that, Mrs. Logan?
Charles and me.
I was his confidante.
All his years in Congress, my opinion
was the one that mattered most to him.
Now I'm...
less than an afterthought.
I'm sure the president
would be here if he could.
He's the president
of the United States, Evelyn.
He can do whatever he wants.
If he wanted to be here, he would be.
Mr. Bauer. You're being moved,
per the president's orders.
- Where?
- To a class three detention facility.
On what charges?
I was invited here by Mike Novick.
Those are my orders, sir.
You're Pierce, right? Aaron Pierce.
You served under David Palmer.
- Yes, I did.
- I need to speak with you for a moment.
- That's not possible.
- It concerns David Palmer's killer.
All right.
Palmer was assassinated
because he was on the verge of discovering
the terrorists that attacked us today were
helped by someone in the administration.
- Who?
- Walt Cummings.
- Why would he be involved with terrorists?
- I couldn't tell you.
But the terrorists are in possession
of a weaponised nerve gas
and Walt Cummings may be the last chance
we have to stop them in time.
Walt Cummings ordered
the assassination of David Palmer.
I know that's hard to believe,
but I can prove it. It's true.
Actually, it's not that hard to believe.
The first lady also thinks
someone in the administration was involved.
Your primary responsibility as lead agent is
to protect the president of the United States.
Someone in his administration
is undermining him.
That is equivalent to a coup d'état.
Agent Pierce, please. Please. I need your help.
- Bauer's escaped.
- When? I didn't get a code alert.
My comm's down. Call it in,
have agents cover the west gate.
- What about you?
- I'll take your post. Go.
Yes, sir.
That was NSA. CTU hasn't transferred
the search operation to their jurisdiction.
- What's the problem?
- I don't know.
Call Lynn McGill, make sure we're in charge.
He's going to ask why CTU's been pulled off
the search and I don't know what to tell him.
You don't have to tell him anything.
You're the president.
Agent Pierce, we're in the middle
of a meeting, if you don't mind.
Mr. President, my name is Jack Bauer.
I'm sorry to confront you like this.
But your chief of staff is withholding
information vital to this nation's security.
Stop this!
I'm the president of the United States.
Get your hands off him.
- Do something.
- I am, Mr. President.
I'm upholding my oath to protect you.
That won't have any effect, sir.
I've overridden the distress line.
Mr. Cummings is guilty
of conspiring with terrorists.
He facilitated the theft of a military nerve gas
and is responsible for the death
of three people, including David Palmer.
- I know about that. There's an explanation.
- What do you mean, you know about that?
Please. I just found out a couple of minutes
ago. It's very complicated.
I don't know what he's told you,
but we need to find that gas,
immediately, before it's too late.
- It's already too late.
- What?
Apparently, it's on its way out of the country.
- Where is it?
- He told me he doesn't know.
- He's lying to you, sir.
- The man I had inside has gone dark.
I don't know.
I'm done talking with you, understand?
You've read my file.
First, I'm gonna take out your right eye.
Then your left. And then I'm gonna cut you.
I'll keep cutting
until I get the information that I need.
So, for the last time, where is the nerve gas?
I don't know.
Stop. Stop! Stop! I'll tell you. I'll tell you.
I'll tell you. It's on a freighter
leaving the port of Long Beach at 2:30.
- How is it concealed?
- In a container of medical supplies.
- Container number?
- I don't know.
- What's the number?
- I don't know! I'd tell you, I swear.
Mr. Bauer!
I don't know.
Mr. Buchanan,
I've got Jack Bauer on line three.
Jack, what's going on?
Bill, hold on.
I'm gonna put you on speakerphone.
Bill, I'm here with the president.
The gas is in Long Beach
in a container of medical supplies,
on a freighter bound for central Asia.
It's set to depart at 2:30pm.
- How solid is the intel?
- It's direct from Cummings.
We've been trying to reach you about an order
we received changing our jurisdiction.
Disregard the order.
You want CTU to maintain
operational control of the retrieval?
Yes. Absolutely.
- I'm alerting CBP.
- Get hazmat teams to set up a perimeter.
Have medical teams standing by
in case the gas is released.
Good work, Jack.
Are you heading back to CTU?
I don't know yet.
We'll let you know
when we have more on the container.
Copy that.
Mr. President, Agent Pierce and I
are prepared to hand ourselves over
to the authorities now.
Aaron.
Yes, Mr. President?
Take back your shield
and get Walt Cummings out of my sight.
Yes, sir.
He told me it was too late, and I believed him.
You need to understand.
I trusted Walt Cummings.
But he lied to me. I was coerced.
There is one more thing
that we need to discuss.
- What is that, sir?
- You.
The fact that you're alive
presents problems for both of us.
Yes, Mr. President.
I accomplished what I set out to do,
which was to identify and locate
David Palmer's killer.
I would like to stay on
until the nerve gas is retrieved,
but after that I give you my word
I will simply disappear again.
All right. I think that would be best,
for the good of the country.
Yes, sir.
Thank you, Mr. Bauer.
Thank you, Mr. President.
Excuse me.
I'll see you soon.
Hold on.
- What's happening?
- Marty.
- Charles.
Come on, get out of the car. Come here.
What?
You were right. There was a conspiracy.
David was trying to warn you, and me.
- I should have listened to you.
- I-I...
You... You believe me now?
It was Walt Cummings.
He lied to me.
He convinced me you were out of control.
- Walt?
- Yeah.
Sending you back
to the clinic in Vermont was his idea.
- And you went along with it.
- I'm sorry, Marty.
Sending me away without a word.
Like I was some nuisance to be gotten rid of.
Excuse me. You wanted to know
when a link with CTU was established.
Yes. Um...
Thank you, Wendy. See that
the first lady's bags get back to her room.
Of course.
I've gotta go.
Chloe, do we have
confirmation on the intel?
There's only one ship scheduled
to leave Long Beach at 2:30.
It's a freighter heading for Asia
leaving from pier F.
We don't have any CTU teams in the vicinity,
but we've got a Customs and Border
Protection task force onsite.
Make sure they understand
the nerve gas is in 20 unmarked canisters
in a shipment of medical supplies.
They know that. But there's about a thousand
containers, and we don't know which one.
Container 539-146, box 7.
I hacked into the ship's manifest. It's the
only container stocking medical supplies.
- Make sure the strike force units have that.
- Right.
The White House is requesting a live feed.
We'll have Chloe patch 'em in
once the tac teams reach the staging area.
That's him.
Ivan Erwich. He's a
chemical engineer, trained at St Petersburg.
Joined a separatist movement six years ago.
Do you have any clearer images,
any file photos?
No. Which is why we need you to ID him
when the strike force has a visual.
OK. Just make sure that CBP knows
we need to take Erwich alive.
They know. Stand by.
- What's the situation?
- Strike team is in place, Mr. President.
We're just waiting
for the video feed to come up.
Feed's up.
CTU, we have located
the target container. No hostiles present.
You have a green light.
Remember, do not discharge your weapons
unless absolutely necessary.
If a bullet breaches a canister,
we'll have massive casualties.
Copy that.
Masks on.
Go!
Go, go, go.
Don't move. Put your hands in the air now.
He's dead. Open 'em up.
Open 'em up. Open 'em all up.
Moving on, moving on.
Come on, get it open.
Open it, come on, move it. Open it.
Open it. Come on, come on.
What have we got?
What have we got? Nothing?
There are no gas canisters here, CTU.
Repeat, the nerve gas is not here.
- Get Walt Cummings in here now.
- Yes, sir.
Dammit!
The nerve gas isn't there.
- It has to be.
- Where are the canisters?
I don't know. I-I've told you everything.
They have to be there.
Oh, God.
- What is it?
- That's Schaeffer, the man we had inside.
They must have found out
we've reprogrammed the detonators.
It's his cellphone, sir.
- Who's calling you?
- That's Schaeffer's number.
- Bill?
- Yeah?
- I want you to monitor and record this call.
- We're on it.
Answer it now.
Yes?
We know
you've altered the arming codes.
- Who is this?
- I think you know my name.
As I now know yours.
Your man Schaeffer confessed everything.
Is President Logan with you?
The president had nothing to do with this.
Nor did anyone else in the government.
- I was acting alone.
- You expect me to believe that?
It's the truth. Erwich, listen.
We can negotiate something.
I don't negotiate with my enemies.
I eliminate them.
Your country
is about to pay a very steep price.