- Excuse me, Miss Driscoll.
- What is it, Chloe?
Intelligence indicated the possibility
of an attack at eight this morning.
A Turkish national on the FBI watch list,
Tomas Sherek, was last seen in the city.
It's Tomas.
- Did Dar get the briefcase?
- Yes. He's on his way to you now.
So far, everything is on schedule.
The briefcase is on its way. When it gets here,
you'll take it to the warehouse.
What we will accomplish today
will change the world.
We're fortunate that our family
has been chosen to do this.
I found something on the Net
I think you should know about.
I think someone's positioning code
for a major Internet attack.
The thing is, not all
the code remarks are in English.
- What language were they in?
- Arabic or Turkish, maybe.
What did you find?
- It was my friend, not me.
- What's his name?
Andrew Paige.
- Is it gonna be uncomfortable?
- What?
Going back to CTU. Seeing Driscoll again.
- I don't blame her for her decision.
- She forced you out of CTU.
I could have joined other agencies
if I still wanted to do field work. But I didn't.
- I know this guy.
- Fortunately for you, Jack,
it's our problem, not yours.
Erin, listen to me. This doesn't make sense.
He wouldn't risk exposing himself here in the
US for a train bombing. It's not big enough.
We'll consider that when we interrogate him.
I am not messing with you. You are gonna
tell me. What is happening at eight o'clock?
- Jack!
- What is your primary objective?
Secretary of Defense!
Heller.
Did it ever occur to you
that these people are using you?
Don't you realise they're letting you speak
for one reason? Because you are my son!
Audrey, it's Jack. Are you still at Richard's?
Get your father out of there now!
Your father is the real target.
Oh, my God.
Jack!
Audrey?
Audrey!
Richard Heller?
They took my father and my sister.
Come on!
It's been over five minutes.
You need to widen your perimeter.
You're not listening to me. I'm not interested
in local law enforcement. Get Secret Service.
- Good. Get back to me.
Everyone.
Everyone, please listen up.
Secretary of Defense Heller
was abducted a few minutes ago,
along with his senior policy analyst,
Audrey Raines.
He was at his son Richard's house
when he was taken.
LAPD is bringing Richard in for questioning.
This is a top-priority situation.
I want all interagency protocols
activated immediately.
Move off that page.
Link up to the Secret Service channel.
- It's not that simple. We're locked out.
- Why?
- They're sequestering the cabinet.
- Driscoll wants the protocols activated.
- What do you want me to do?
- Break through those channels. Hack in.
Chloe, move everything from the bombing
to the secondary server.
- I did that already.
- Then sync up the kidnapping and bombing.
I did that too, but I haven't opened a pipe to
the Army Criminal Investigation Division yet.
- Do it.
- On my way to.
I'm looking at it. They widened the perimeter.
Any ID on transportation?
-  I'm working on it...
- I'm gonna have to get back to you.
- I need to speak to you.
- You're done here. I'm detaining you.
Erin, listen! Heller is my responsibility. I need
you to reinstate me on a provisional basis
- until I get him back.
- You don't give me orders, Jack.
I'm detaining you until an investigator
can take your statement.
I'll recommend you're arrested for torturing
a suspect and rendering him useless.
You were getting nowhere.
Because of me, Sherek told you all he knows.
You'd better hope so.
Would you please escort Mr Bauer
to a vacant office until Division gets here?
I'm fine. You're making a mistake.
Excuse me. President Keeler.
- What about him?
- He wants to talk to you.
All right.
- This is Erin Driscoll.
-  Please hold for the president.
Tell me about the attack on the secretary.
We know that he was taken
approximately ten minutes ago.
- You had any contact from the kidnappers?
- No, sir. We have not.
How is it that Secret Service
wasn't able to protect him?
I understand that
he broke his schedule to visit his son.
Somehow, the kidnappers
had access to that information.
We're looking into that now.
All right. We're going to go
to an elevated level of security.
- Take the appropriate measures.
- I understand.
- Get them back, Erin.
- We're doing everything we can, sir.
- Hello.
- Mom?
- Hi, sweetie. I didn't...
- Mom, listen.
- Get out of the house now.
- What are you talking about?
Someone's looking for me
and they might come for you next.
- What kind of trouble are you in?
- I don't know. I found something on the Net.
- Now these people are after me.
- Andrew, you are being paranoid.
Mom, they killed Melanie.
They killed everybody in the office.
- What?
- They shot 'em. Mom, I'm really scared.
Oh, my God. I'm gonna call the police.
Just get outta there! Get to one of your
friends' houses and stay there! Go! Go now!
Andrew!
- I said Driscoll wanted me to question you.
- What's going on? What are you doing?
I'll probably get in trouble, but I don't care.
- I may have a way to find Heller.
- Why are you telling me?
I don't think Driscoll's handling this
the right way and I don't trust her, I trust you.
Sit down.
A friend of mine called about 40 minutes ago,
someone I went to school with.
- He wouldn't call me unless it was serious.
- What is it?
He noticed computer code
planted on the Internet.
- How is that connected to Heller?
- It originated in Turkey, like everything else,
- Sherek, the train bombing.
- Where is your friend now?
You can see them taking Secretary
Heller's son away from the scene now.
That's being done for his own protection,
according to police sources.
Those same sources tell us that at least
five Secret Service agents were shot...
- Hello.
-  Andrew, it's me.
- What did you do, Chloe? Who did you tell?
- What do you mean?
Everyone's dead. They're dead.
Now they're trying to kill me.
- Talk to me. Who's dead? What happened?
- Everyone's dead. They're dead.
After I called you, I went back to my office.
There was a guy there torturing Melanie.
He wanted to know
who hacked into their system.
And then he shot her.
Oh, my God.
- Who shot her?
- Who's this?
Jack Bauer.
I work for Secretary of Defense Heller.
- Andrew, we need your help.
- What?
Heller was kidnapped
less than half an hour ago.
I believe the same people
that kidnapped him are chasing you now.
- I don't know anything.
- Son, you've been targeted for a reason.
You know more than you think.
- What do I do?
- Where are you?
I'm at Union Station. I'm getting outta town.
No. You stay put. The best thing
you can do right now is let me bring you in.
- Chloe, what should I do?
- You can trust Jack.
OK.
I'll be next to track three
at the bottom of the ramp.
Andrew, what are you wearing?
Blue jeans, brown jacket and a black bag.
OK, you stay put.
I'll be there in about 30 minutes.
OK.
This is all my fault. I shouldn't have let
Driscoll talk me in to handing it to the FBI.
- She did what?
- She told me to give it to the FBI.
-  Yes.
- I found out who stumbled onto our server.
- Is he with you now?
- No. I'll have him shortly.
- Find out who he's talked to.
- Of course.
- And then kill him.
- Yeah.
- Is everything in there?
- Yes.
- Where's Behrooz?
- Upstairs, checking traffic on line.
It's almost time for him to go.
Are you sure you don't want me
to take the briefcase to Omar?
The plan is in place. I don't want to deviate.
Why?
This is the key
to everything we're doing today.
It's a lot to entrust to a teenager.
I told you. Our whereabouts
have to be accounted for today.
Besides, it's because he's a teenager
that he won't arouse suspicion.
You're right.
Don't worry, Dina.
We prepared well for today.
The train. The kidnapping.
It's all gone as expected.
I spoke with Omar. He's happy.
And he knows Behrooz is the one
who will deliver the device?
Yes, he knows.
Behrooz will be fine.
We're looking to find a connection between
the bombing and Heller's abduction. Sarah.
NTSB has given us a full passenger list.
We're processing those names now.
What about Heller's son? Is it possible
he had something to do with this?
We're not counting anything out.
He's being brought here for questioning now.
Erin, I need to speak with you.
Privately, please.
- You're testing me, Jack.
- Erin, please.
Curtis will hand out assignment protocols.
I want status reports every 15 minutes.
I have information you ignored that seems to
be connected to the bombing and kidnapping.
- What information?
- A computer programmer, Andrew Paige,
accidentally came across
a possible Internet strike.
- I know. It was passed on to the FBI.
- Yes. Against CTU protocol.
You abandoned an active investigation
during a terrorist strike.
I got confirmation from the LAPD
that Andrew Paige's co-workers
were all found dead less than 20 minutes ago.
I'll coordinate with FBI
and we'll investigate that.
No, you won't. I talked to the kid.
I'm the only one who knows where he is.
You want that kid picked up,
you're gonna have to reinstate me.
- I'm having you locked up for impeding me.
- You do that and I'll tell the president
that you had Sherek in custody over half
an hour before Heller was even kidnapped,
and you couldn't break him, I did.
Are you threatening me, Jack?
I am asking you to let me
help rescue Secretary Heller.
This is how it's gonna work.
I'll reinstate your commission
on a temporary basis until Heller is safe.
You will not make any unilateral decisions.
You will work as an auxiliary agent
under the authority of Ronnie Lobell.
And then I'll hand you over to Division.
- What are they gonna do?
- I don't know,
but if they wanted me dead,
they would have killed me at Richard's house.
Richard. God.
He was still in the house.
I don't think they went in there.
Listen to me, Audy.
No matter what happens to me,
they have no reason to hurt you.
- They don't need a reason.
- And I don't want you to give 'em one.
Do what they say.
Whatever happens to me, don't provoke them.
If they threaten me, if they hurt me,
even if they kill me...
do what they say.
I only asked for Heller.
I didn't want to kill her
without your permission.
- Dad!
- Leave her alone! Don't you touch her!
- So help me God, I will kill you!
- Dad!
- Son of a bitch! I'll kill you!
- Omar! Yes or no?
Do not do this! Leave her alone.
Not yet.
We may be able to use her.
Take them away.
Dad. Dad.
I'm going with Ronnie to pick up Andrew.
- Has Driscoll cleared you?
- Yeah.
That's unlike her. I hope you didn't
tell her I gave you the information.
I didn't. Have we heard anything from
any agents that survived the kidnapping?
- There's one. He's in surgery.
- Any other witnesses?
The son, Richard.
They're bringing him in now.
Get back to me as soon as you've got
anything on Heller or Audrey.
Sure. Bad luck about Audrey being there
when her dad got kidnapped.
Yeah.
I'm going to my car to get my things.
OK, so let me understand this.
Bauer illegally shoots a suspect
and you let him back in the field?
He'll only give us the location
if I let him work it.
- He can't hold back information, Erin.
- We don't have time to interrogate him.
It's a simple job.
You pick up the subject and bring him in.
Bauer has not been in the field for
a year and a half. That has consequences...
Which is why I need you to keep him
on a tight leash. It's not optional, it's an order.
Fine.
I'm ready to go.
This is a simple task, Behrooz. But these
are the ones where mistakes can be made.
Drive carefully. If there is anyone
in the area who looks suspicious,
drive away and call us. Understood?
Yes.
- Hello.
- Mrs Araz, this is Debbie.
Yes, Debbie, what can I do for you?
- Can I please talk to Behrooz?
- Let me see if he's here. Hold on.
- What does she want?
- I don't know.
Debbie?
I've left messages on your cellphone.
Why haven't you called?
- I'm sorry, I've been busy.
- Doing what?
Working for my father.
I don't believe you. If you're seeing someone
else, at least have the decency to tell me.
I'm not seeing anyone else.
- Then why are you avoiding me?
- I'm not.
- This isn't the right time to do this.
- That's what I mean. You're still avoiding me.
I'm not.
Then why can't we talk now?
Because I can't.
- I've gotta go.
- Behrooz!
Behrooz.
That's not the right way
to deal with this situation.
This girl needs to know it's over
and that there will be no more phone calls.
I'll take care of it later.
I don't wanna be late getting this to Omar.
- You sent Jack Bauer out in the field?
- He'll be with Ronnie.
- Yeah, but why?
- He knows our procedures.
And he may have information about Heller.
What is it, Chloe?
Curtis, you wanted to know when Richard
Heller arrived. He's on his way to Holding.
Thanks. Do you want me
to choreograph the jurisdictions?
No, I'll do it. Find out what the son knows.
Chloe, I'd like to talk to you.
Has it occurred to you
that we might be farther along
if you trusted me
half as much as you trust Jack Bauer?
Miss Driscoll, I'm not in the mood to play
the scared student at the principal's office.
I came to you with information
that my friend Andrew gave to me
and you chose to not respond to it.
When you came to me with the information,
we were looking for Sherek, were we not?
- Yes.
- Wasn't he our most important lead then?
- I guess.
- Then my question to you is...
once we had Sherek in custody, if you felt
that your Internet lead was still valuable,
why didn't you reprise it?
You're right.
I felt more comfortable going to Jack.
Well, at least that's honest.
You can go back to work now.
Check that, please.
For the record, I think Driscoll
made a mistake letting you come.
- All right.
- And just so we're clear, I give the orders.
I'm fine with that. What happened
earlier in Holding with Sherek,
I had intel and had no time
to do it another way. I'm sorry.
Apology accepted. But if you try to exceed
my authority again, I will stop you cold.
Fine. Have Marcy isolate all the death threats
Heller's received over the last six months.
I want phone calls, emails, snail mail,
everything sent over to CTU for analysis.
Well, for the time being,
I'm working with them.
Yeah. OK, good, thanks.
- Has Heller had a lot of death threats lately?
- No more than anyone else in the cabinet.
So what's it like working in DC?
For the most part, we solve problems
in theory that'll never come into play.
- Then why do it?
- I've got my reasons.
Hey, man. I'm just trying
to make some conversation.
I read your file. It must have really
burned you up when Driscoll fired you.
She did me a favour.
I wanted to get my life back.
I wouldn't have been able to
if I was still doing field work.
How's the master plan going?
Do you have a life yet?
Yeah.
Yeah, I got a life.
We'll be fine, Audy.
We're still on US soil.
That's not gonna help us
if this is some sort of suicide mission.
You said Jack tried to warn you
before they grabbed us.
Yeah. That's right.
That means he must have a reliable source,
which means our chances are good.
Audy, sit down.
I am your father.
Do you trust me?
- Of course I do.
- Then listen.
You cannot allow a negative thought
to enter your head now.
They will find us.
We will be rescued. Say it.
- Please, Dad, don't.
- We will be rescued. Say it, Audy.
- We will be rescued.
Take off your clothes.
You first.
OK.
Go to hell.
Stop it. Dad.
-  Who is it?
- It's Behrooz.
Behrooz.
Good job, Behrooz.
- Debbie, what are you doing here?
- I followed you.
- Why?
- Cos I didn't believe you.
I thought you were seeing someone else.
Look around. Does it look
like I'm seeing anybody else?
You shouldn't be here. I'm working for my
father. He doesn't like me socialising at work.
OK. I get it.
That doesn't explain
why you stopped calling me.
It's my parents.
They've got a problem
with me seeing someone that's...
Not Muslim?
Yeah.
- And that's it? Whatever they say, you do?
- No.
Then what's going on between us?
Do you wanna be with me or not?
- I do, but...
- But what?
Debbie, I wanna straighten things out,
but I can't do it now.
We'll get together later.
Debbie, please.
- Is everything ready for Richard Heller?
- Just about. They're starting to hook him up.
Then let's do it.
Does Driscoll know you're subjecting
Heller's son to a lie detector?
- Yeah.
- Is he a suspect?
Not exactly, but he's on very poor terms with
his father. I wouldn't wanna rule anything out.
- You want to be in the room on this?
- No, I'll observe through the one-way.
- What are you doing? What are you doing?
- We wanna make sure you're telling the truth.
Why would I lie to you? My father
and my sister have just been kidnapped.
Please sit back, Richard,
or I'll have to sedate you.
You can't do this to me.
My father is the secretary of defense.
I understand.
But according to my information,
you were about to unleash personal attacks
on your father at a rally at Lockheed.
Are you insane? This is America.
I can say what I want in public.
- How dare you treat me like a criminal.
- I'm not.
You wanna be constructive?
Find my father and my sister.
- We intend to.
- By treating me like I'm guilty of something!
Richard, right now, you are the only witness
to your father and your sister's kidnapping.
- We need your help.
- Then get these things off of me
and start talking to me
like a normal human being.
- You don't have anything to hide, do you?
- No.
How's the polygraph?
100 per cent.
Father.
How did everything go?
It went fine.
Omar said one of his men saw you
with someone outside the compound.
- A young woman.
- I was going to tell you.
Who was it?
- Debbie.
- Where is she now?
- She didn't see anything.
- She saw you at the compound. It's enough.
We've spent years planning for this,
waiting for this day to come.
Now it's here
and you've compromised everything.
She didn't see anything.
I made sure of it.
We'll see how much she knows.
Call her and tell her to come here.
- Please don't do this. It's not necessary.
- I decide what's necessary, not you.
- What are you going to do to her?
- Since when do you question me?
How long have we lived in this country,
preparing for this day?
How long?
Four years.
Almost five.
That's how much time can be erased
by a simple mistake.
Call her. Now!
Yes, sir.
- Tim Felson. MTA.
- Ronnie Lobell. CTU.
Head of field ops. Where's track three?
- East entrance. My guys can lock it down.
- We don't wanna draw attention to anything.
The platform's just at the end of this hall.
- Hello.
-  Andrew, it's me.
- Where are they?
- On site. They'll be there any minute.
All right. Tell 'em to hurry up.
It doesn't work that way. Stay where you are
and I'll talk to you when they bring you in.
- Andrew.
- Yeah. Are you Jack Bauer?
- Yes. Come on. Let's go.
- Where are we going?
I'll explain later. It's not safe here. Let's go.
Just around the corner.
- You sure he said the bottom of the ramp?
- Yeah.
- Hello.
- Andrew.
- Who's this?
- It's Jack Bauer. Where are you?
Andrew?
I can't really... talk.
- Let's go.
- Andrew.
Andrew. Son of a bitch.
They got to him before we did.
- How did they know where he would be?
- I don't know.
- Who are you?
- I'll kill you if you don't follow my orders.
Felson, come on. Alert your MTAs. Tell 'em
we've got a Caucasian male, early 20s,
wearing a brown jacket,
being taken from here against his will.
Tell your men not to engage the target.
I want a visual and a location. That's it. Now.
Where are you taking me?
- This is Marx. I see the target.
- What's your 20?
I'm on the train platform. Target is on the
easternmost periphery. Second-level parking.
Open the door.
- They're in a dark blue Lexus.
- What's the fastest way?
- Out the back.
- Tell your men to stay out of sight.
Stay on the guy,
but make sure he doesn't see you.
Lay down.
There he is. You get the gate.
I'll get the kid out of the car.
- Wait.
- Wait for what?
- This isn't the right play.
- What?
- If we follow him, he may lead us to Heller.
- Or maybe he won't, but he'll kill the kid.
Right now, this hostile's
our best chance to find Secretary Heller.
- We'll break him back at CTU.
- You don't know if you can break him in time.
This is not a field ops call, Jack.
We need authorisation.
I can't take the chance
of Driscoll resisting me.
- I told you not to go against me, Jack.
- Ronnie, please.
You get up.
Interlace your hands behind your head.
- You're making a mistake.
- Shut up.
Gate four, he's leaving the parking lot.
What do you want me to do?
This is Lobell. I'm moving in now. Let the
front car go ahead and lock in the hostile.
Ronnie.
Ronnie, where you been hit?
Can you move?
Ronnie.
Give me the keys to the cuffs.
Please, Ronnie. He's our only lead.
We gotta stop him.
Come on.
Dammit!
So tell me what happened, Richard.
My father and I were talking
and...
- my sister came in with a phone call for him.
- He was in the room on the call?
- No. He and Audrey went outside.
- All right. Go on.
Then I heard an explosion, looked out
the window and saw 'em being grabbed.
And they didn't come in and get you?
I know you told me not to interrupt,
but we need you.
- What's going on?
- A webcast is on servers all over the place.
- A webcast of what?
- Secretary of Defense Heller.
The terrorists are broadcasting this
all over the Internet.
Call Curtis.
Curtis, we need you on the floor.
There you are, you son of a bitch.
We speak for the men, women and
children who have had no voice until now.
Who have been victimised by the genocidal
policies of the US that Heller has advanced.
But the time has come
for the victims to demand justice.
Edgar, isolate Secretary Heller.
Our soldiers have taken
the terrorist James Heller into custody.
In three hours, Heller will be tried
for war crimes against humanity.
If he is proven guilty, he will be executed
in accordance with our laws.
Because we have nothing to hide, the world
will have full access to these proceedings.
Visiontext Subtitles: Simon Campbell
ENGLISH SDH