... ::: www.SubCentral.de ::: ...
&
-= ydy.com =-
proudly present
24 - Season 7
Episode 16
Previously on 24 ...
No!
Sir, it's Senator Mayer.
He's dead.
Are you telling me
that Jack Bauer just killed
a United States Senator?
How could you have let
this happen?!
Mr. Kanin, you are not going
to lay this one at my feet.
What is it, Ethan, what's wrong?
Madam President,
I'm afraid I have no choice
but to resign
as your chief of staff.
You're taking this too far.
Where's Jack?
We don't have him.
The man
who framed Jack
for Burnett's murder was
John Quinn,
a Starkwood contractor.
Jack went to Mayer
to get the evidence
to prove it.
Starkwood was involved
with everything
that's happened today.
They were the ones
that helped Juma and his men
bring down the planes and attack
the White House.
In exchange,
they were allowed to develop
and manufacture a WMD
in Sangala.
The text message I got
off their agent's cell phone
said "Port of Alexandria,
lot "C," 10:15 p.m."
Code red, code red!
Engage, engage.
Get that truck out of here now!
Tony!
The truck--
I'm going after it!
Cover me now!
I'm in possession
of a biological weapon
interdicted
at the Port of Alexandria.
What's your status?
Package is secure;
we're inbound.
What about Bauer?
He's at the scene, sir,
but he sought cover nearby.
We have to assume that
he contacted the authorities,
so we'd better be
on an accelerated timetable.
Get over here.
Starkwood reacquired
the bioweapon.
They airlifted the freight
right out of here.
They were headed due west
from my current position.
Jack, I can't assault
a private compound
unless I have proof
that a weapon exists.
Okay, where is the CDC?
They're scrambling a team
right now.
Send them to me.
You'll have
all the proof you need.
Jack, what happened?
I was exposed.
The following takes place
between 11:00 P.M. and 12:00 A.M.
We're ready for you, sir,
come with me.
Mr. Bauer.
Dr. Macer, CDC.
We need you to
get undressed.
You're the one
that talked to Agent Moss?
He brought me up to speed,
said you had some information
about the bioweapon.
All I know is that it was
developed in Sangala,
and according to rumors
from the village
that it was tested on,
all the victims suffered
from dementia and paralysis.
Check neurological
vectors and pathogens.
How much was released?
I'm not exactly sure.
The weapon was stored
in a pressurized canister.
It was breached
for maybe two minutes
before I could seal it off.
This is not
a reaction.
I've had
these scars.
This is a full
spectrum antibiotic.
It should counteract
a wide range of
known pathogens.
Step inside, sir.
Raise your arms and
close your eyes.
Janis, where are we?
Metro closed down a six-mile
stretch of Highway 236.
The CDC first responders
are on-site. What the hell's
going on?
One of the bioweapon canisters
was breached.
Jack may have been exposed.
Oh, my God.
Starkwood took the canisters.
They're probably flying it
back to their main compound
in Virginia, along
with Tony Almeida.
- Almeida?
- Yeah, he was working with Jack.
We think he might have been
taken captive.
Hang on one second. I
need you to put together
a briefing packet
on Starkwood.
I want every division
caught up to speed
on what we might
be dealing with.
You planning to
move on Starkwood?
That place is enormous;
it's practically
a military base.
We're not going to do anything
till we have concrete evidence
on the bioweapon from CDC.
Then I'll inform
the president.
She'll decide
how to proceed.
Almeida's not going
to talk.
He's not the type;
he's the brave type.
Know the psychology
of your subject.
That's in our manual.
Here we go.
Mr. Hodges,
we isolated
the damaged canister.
We got lucky.
They know we
have the weapons.
That's not so lucky.
How fast can you
have them ready?
It's going to take me
at least two hours.
Too long, Tom.
Sir, we don't know
what the government knows.
They're coming,
and they'll be coming
with everything they've got,
and the only thing
that's going to stop them
is getting these weapons ready
to deploy.
Yes, sir, I'll do my best.
I know you will.
Okay, let's go!
What does
the FBI know?
I'm not going to
ask you again.
(coughing)
Okay.
You're a good man, Tony.
I know your profile.
You've had some
hard breaks.
I don't want to see you hurt,
so you just tell me
what the FBI knows
about what we're
doing here,
and I can't say you'll
walk away smiling--
that would be
unrealistic--
but you'll be alive.
You hear me?
But I don't know
anything, Mr. Hodges.
I'm giving you
a way out, Tony.
Sir,
may I speak to you for a moment?
Not now, Greg.
Please, sir,
just for a moment.
What is it?
This was supposed to
be a covert operation.
That is not
the case
anymore.
The government knows
that we have these weapons,
and they're not just going
to sit on that information.
What are you suggesting, Greg?
Maybe we should destroy
the evidence
while we still have
some time.
I can't believe
that I'm hearing
this from you.
I'm just trying
to help, sir.
I care about this company
as much as you do.
Oh, I doubt that.
We've invested a lot
of blood and treasure
to get these weapons, and I'm
not going to give them up.
Think about what
you're risking, sir--
everything,
everything you've built.
You say you're
trying to help.
You know what I think?
I think you're worried
about your own ass.
Get him out of here and
do what you have to do.
Think about what I said,
young man.
You're a little nervous,
Greg.
Well, I've got a news flash:
we're all nervous.
Keep your doubts to yourself.
I'm not going to tell you again.
We're going to need to take
more blood and saliva samples,
and I'd like to collect
a spinal fluid specimen.
Until we know
what we're dealing with,
we need to keep you
under quarantine.
How long is it gonna be
till you know
whether or not
I've been infected?
We should have the
preliminary results
in the next
15 minutes.
Okay.
Dr. Macer,
we've detected
trace amounts of an
airborne pathogen.
It's concentrated
near the truck.
We're also picking it up in
the surrounding environments
at much lower
concentrations.
Can you identify it?
No, but we're analyzing
a sample now.
These levels shouldn't present
any danger
to the nearby population,
but I still want
atmospheric monitors set up.
It's a good thing you sealed
off the canister, Mr. Bauer.
You saved a
lot of lives.
You're going to have
to transport me back to FBI.
I'm still material evidence
in an ongoing terrorist threat.
Those were
our orders.
We can run our
tests from there.
Okay.
Bob Justman's been
associate counsel
for the past three years.
He and Ethan worked
very closely together.
He is certainly qualified
to be chief of staff.
But...
After what's happened today,
I think you should be looking
outside your administration.
An insider has a leg up.
Chief of staff has a
steep learning curve.
I think you're underestimating
the value
of a fresh perspective.
You have
someone in mind.
I do.
Rick Berman.
Would Rick even consider leaving
the private sector?
Well, he's made his fortune.
I think he'd jump at the
chance to serve his country.
Let's sit down with him.
Great.
But keep Bob on the list.
I still have a good feeling
about him.
I'll start to set up
meetings tomorrow.
Livy, it could take weeks
to find Ethan's replacement.
In the meantime,
I'm going to need
a provisional chief of staff.
I'd like that to be you.
Um...
Madam President?
Yes?
Tim Woods is here to see you.
Just give me a minute,
please, and then
send him in.
Livy, I need someone
I can trust.
Especially after everything
that's happened today.
You're not going to say "no"
to your mother, are you?
Of course not.
Good.
Madam President,
I have Larry Moss
at FBI calling for you.
What's this about?
I don't know the specifics,
but he says it involves
an imminent homeland threat.
Put him through.
It's all right, Tim.
I've made Olivia
Acting Chief of Staff.
Agent Moss,
you're on with the president.
Madam President, we have
a situation developing.
First of all, you need
to know that Jack Bauer
did not kill Ryan Burnett
nor Senator Blaine Mayer.
He was framed
for their murders.
I knew it.
Who framed him?
Our operational theory
is that he was set up
by Starkwood.
I don't understand.
Why would Starkwood frame Jack?
To cover up the fact that
they helped Juma stage
the terrorist attacks today.
What?
Ma'am, we have evidence
that Starkwood provided Juma
with technological
support and intelligence.
And in return, Juma allowed
Starkwood to use Sangala
as a base to operate
without having
to worry about any oversight.
A base for what?
To manufacture
weapons of mass destruction.
Specifically,
biological weapons.
What kind of bioweapons
are you talking about?
We're not sure,
but it could be
some kind of neurological
pathogen.
CDC has obtained a sample
and they're analyzing it now.
Agent Moss, you said there
was an imminent threat.
Yes, a large shipment
of bioweapons
was delivered
to Starkwood.
We believe they're
in possession of them now.
Are you saying these weapons
are on U.S. soil?
We suspect they're
at the Starkwood
headquarters
in Virginia.
You're not suggesting
that Starkwood
intends to use those weapons
to attack this country?
We don't know,
but, given their actions today,
we need to move
on Starkwood immediately.
Madam President?
Assemble the Cabinet
and the Joint Chiefs.
Yes, ma'am.
Jack was right about Starkwood.
You found evidence that
they've been supporting Juma.
Yeah.
Did you find out why?
I mean, what could Starkwood
possibly get from Juma?
The infrastructure to develop
and test biological weapons.
We think they're
holding them somewhere
on the Starkwood compound.
Okay, where's Jack?
He's on his way over here.
What, Larry?
He managed to secure
the weapons, but then, uh,
Starkwood got them back.
And when that
happened, um...
Jack was exposed.
He may have
been infected.
He's being placed
under quarantine.
Listen, he's on his way here
and we need to find out
everything that he learned
about these weapons.
And I think you should be
the one who debriefs him.
And I owe you
an apology.
I was wrong not to trust you,
and I-I let my prejudice
about Bauer get in the way.
But...
Renee, you should've
kept me in the loop.
You should've
trusted me.
I know.
I should have.
When are we moving
on Starkwood?
Aaron?
I'll check in
with you guys later, okay?
Thank you.
May I speak with
you for a moment?
Of course.
I heard you finished
your debrief and were
on your way out.
Yes, ma'am.
Well, I need you to stay.
Ma'am?
I've been appointed
Acting Chief of Staff.
Secret Service is going
to assign an agent
to handle my
security detail.
I'd like that to be you.
Well, I'm truly flattered,
ma'am,
but as you know,
I'm retired.
I can have you reinstated.
There are plenty
of fine agents
on the roster.
But I don't want them.
I want you.
I can't go into
the details now,
but the threat to this
country isn't over.
We're in the middle
of a crisis,
and I need people
around me I can trust.
I trust you, Aaron.
I can't say that
about a lot of people.
I'm running into a meeting
with the president.
I'll assume your
answer is "yes."
Gentlemen, ladies,
please take your seats.
Now, those of you who
haven't had a chance
to finish your briefing packets,
please keep reading.
As we've all
just learned,
this day is not over.
Our national security is
still being threatened,
and we are here
to consider our options.
Mr. Woods.
Your briefing materials
include FBI intelligence
about a cache
of biological weapons on
Starkwood's main compound
in Northern Virginia.
This is a recent satellite
view of the compound.
Over three square miles,
259 structures--
the weapons
could be hidden
anywhere on
the facility.
What kind of bioweapons
are we talking about?
This is Ben Landry,
he's director of CDC.
He's here to answer any
questions you may have
in regards to the pathogen.
Ben.
I've just received
a preliminary report
from our agents
in the field.
They've identified
the pathogen as a prion variant
indigenous to the East Congo.
It's a form
of Creutzfeldt-Jakob disease.
It attacks the brain
and the nervous system,
causes dementia,
physical deterioration,
ultimately death.
Standard CJD kills
within several months,
but this strain
kills more quickly.
How long?
A day, maybe two.
There's no treatment
for this disease.
There's no cure.
If dispersed
over a populated area,
the results would be
catastrophic.
But it goes
without saying
we cannot allow
a private military force,
these killers, to possess
weapons of mass destruction.
We need to find these weapons,
and arrest those bastards
in Starkwood
who are responsible
for bringing them here.
Madam President.
Given the size of the compound,
it would take
a considerable force
to locate these weapons.
Not to mention the fact
that there are 1,500
highly-trained mercenaries
on that base.
God forbid
they decide to resist.
We could have a small war
in our own backyard.
I share those concerns,
Madam President.
We also have to consider
the possibility
that Starkwood might use
these biological weapons
against our own forces.
What about an air strike?
A facility that large would
require multiple bombing runs.
We'd be looking
at massive casualties
on the Starkwood base,
with no guarantee
of destroying the bioweapons.
For all we know,
they've been
buried underground
or in fortified facilities.
There's also a risk that
hitting these weapons
with insufficient force
could release the bio-agent
into the atmosphere.
We can't just
ignore the law here.
All these scenarios
would be in violation
of the Posse
Comitatus Act.
I mean, we can't deploy
military personnel
in a law enforcement
capacity.
Not without
congressional approval.
What I'm hearing
is that there are
no good options.
I don't accept that.
Until we find
a way to contain this threat,
we are risking another attack
on this country.
And that is an option
I won't consider.
Mr. Hodges
wants to know
if you've given
any thought to his offer.
Why this loyalty to a government
that screwed you over?
I don't get it.
Just tell us
what the FBI knows
and you can walk.
For the record,
I bet Mr. Hodges a pair
of Redskins tickets
you wouldn't talk.
Looks like I'm going
to be sitting
on the 50 yard line.
Hey.
Hey, what
the hell is going on?
I need your help.
My help?
We need to stop this.
It's gone too far.
Look, I'm not going anywhere
until you tell me
why you're doing this.
I'm not spending
the rest of my life
in prison because Jonas Hodges
has lost his mind.
You know where the weapons are?
Yes.
Then you better
tell me right now.
I want immunity.
Look, I can't promise you
anything.
We can call the FBI
and negotiate a deal,
immunity in exchange
for your help
in recovering the weapons,
that's the best I can do.
I can set up a secure
landline in my office.
Good, let's go.
We're pulling up to FBI.
We have to put you
in an isolation suit
to transfer you to
the quarantine area.
I understand.
How are you feeling?
No different.
We have the results
of Mr. Bauer's blood work.
Thank you.
Open it.
Excuse me.
Larry wanted me
to tell you,
that CDC arrived
with Jack Bauer.
I'll meet them down in quarantine.
He's not in quarantine.
I don't understand.
That's all I know.
They just cleared security.
He's on his way up.
Jack, are you okay?
My blood work came
back positive.
I'm infected.
Mr. Bauer, there's a room
for you to change in.
Thank you.
It's fine.
But he's not in quarantine.
We've learned the disease
isn't contagious.
It was engineered that way
to prevent blowback
on the people deploying it.
Okay,
but there has to be something
that you can do
to help him.
There's no cure.
But he's patient zero.
Whatever we learn
from the pathogen
will come from the tests
we still need to run.
Excuse me.
This is Macer.
He's stable for
the moment.
Yeah?
Jack, um...
I don't know what to say.
Then tell me that Agent Moss
followed up on Starkwood.
Sorry.
Larry debriefed the White House
and we're waiting
on the president
to decide on a course of action.
Good.
Any word on Tony?
Sorry, we don't know
anything yet.
I need to debrief you
on the canisters that you saw.
You okay with that?
Yeah.
I read the statement
from the Port
Authority cop.
He said that
you risked the mission
to save his life.
You did the right thing.
Thanks.
Uh, it's the lab.
It's probably
Hodges.
We should talk to him.
Put it on speaker.
Seaton.
Where the hell have you been?
I've been trying
to reach you.
I was, uh, checking
on Almeida.
Did Stokes get him to talk?
He's still working
on that, sir.
I told him to put
Almeida down
if he didn't
start talking.
I think we should give him
a few more minutes, sir.
We're busting our asses to
get these weapons ready
before the government
makes their move,
I want all hands on deck.
We'll be there soon, sir.
See that you are, Greg.
Call FBI.
I need to set up
the secure landline.
Make sure nobody's listening.
All right, well, do it.
I never thought Jonas
would take it this far.
I mean, the man's a patriot.
He founded Starkwood to protect
this country.
Yeah, well,
why is he attacking it?
It's complicated.
I don't understand
it myself.
I should've done more
to stop this.
I should've
called FBI months ago.
Well, you're doing
the right thing now.
I've pulled together everything
we have on Starkwood.
Structural specs,
aerial maps,
topography,
company roster,
the whole works.
All right.
Upload it onto
the interagency servers.
Let's get everybody
on the same page.
That's good work, Janis.
Renee...
I heard about Jack.
I'm sorry.
I'm still debriefing him
but I brought a full
description of
the canisters.
All right.
All right, get this out
to the field agents.
How's he doing?
Hard to tell.
Larry, so many people
have died today.
We cannot let their deaths be
for nothing.
We won't.
Larry.
I've got Tony Almeida
on the phone.
Almeida?
He says he's calling
from inside Starkwood.
Put him through.
Go ahead, Tony.
Who am I talking to?
It's Larry Moss.
What's going on?
I'm on the Starkwood compound.
I was being held by a man
named Jonas Hodges,
but I was released
by one of his executives.
A man named Greg Seaton.
Now he wants
to cut a deal.
He wants immunity.
What's he offering
in return?
He knows where the weapons
are being held.
All right, Tony, I got to run
this by the president.
Wait, Larry.
Do you know
what happened to Jack?
He's here.
He's in medical.
Was he hit?
No.
One of the canisters
was breached.
He's been infected.
Tony, I got to call
the White House. Stand by.
Janis, set up a secure
connection in the conference
room with Almeida and the White
House for this signature.
And get me the president
on the phone.
What is this?
Footage recovered from Sangala.
It was smuggled out
of the remains
of a biological weapons lab
about 45 minutes ago.
It's a confirmation that
Juma was experimenting
with biological weapons
on the local population.
These poor people
were suffering
from the effects of the
weaponized prion variant.
And that's what
we allowed Starkwood
to bring into this country.
We didn't allow this.
Starkwood is a monster
we created, Olivia.
We have been feeding it
for years.
We gave them military contracts.
We relied
on their paid mercenaries
instead of our own soldiers,
outsourced intelligence
gathering operations.
My God, we even passed a law
so that they could build
a military base
13 miles
from the nation's capitol.
You fought against all that.
You've been trying
to limit Starkwood's power
ever since you took office.
I didn't do enough...
fast enough.
And now it may be too late.
Madam President, Tim Woods
and Admiral Smith
are here to see you.
Send them in.
Madam President, Larry Moss
at FBI is calling in.
He says it's urgent.
Put him through.
Agent Moss,
the president's here. Go ahead.
Madam President,
we've been contacted
by someone inside
Starkwood.
Ma'am, it's Tony Almeida.
Almeida?
He's been working with Jack
Bauer to recover these weapons.
He was taken captive
but then released
by someone on the inside.
His name is Greg Seaton.
He's part of Jonas
Hodges' inner circle.
Ma'am, he says
he's willing to tell us
where the weapons are
in exchange for immunity.
Now, I've already started
mobilizing
for a targeted raid.
We can catch 'em by surprise
and lock down
these weapons.
But I'm going to
need you to sign
an immunity agreement
for this man.
How confident
are you of Seaton's intel?
We believe it's genuine, ma'am.
Madam President,
we may not get a chance
like this again.
Admiral Smith?
I concur,
but I would suggest
we supplement the FBI
with a seal squad.
They're ready to move
on my order.
The attorney general
will raise hell
about us involving the military
in this operation.
We'll deal with him later.
Agent Moss, you have
my direct authorization
to move on Starkwood.
How soon can you be ready?
We've already drafted
an executive pardon,
and set it up via WebEx.
You'll be able to give a secure digital
signature and we're good to go.
We have the document set up
at your assistant's computer.
Agent Moss,
the president
is prepared to sign.
Go ahead, ma'am.
All right,
it's done.
Tony, did you get
the signature?
Yeah, we're good.
When can you be
at Starkwood?
We can be there
in ten minutes.
Agent Moss, thank you.
And good luck.
Thank you, ma'am.
Let's go.
Madam President, we may have
just caught a lucky break.
Until this plays out,
I want everyone to keep looking
for other options.
All right, Mr. Seaton.
Go ahead.
The weapons are
in a warehouse
on the northeast quadrant
of the compound.
32, 44.23 north...
117, 10.42 west.
Mr. Seaton, it would help
to have someone on the ground
doing recon.
Can you get Tony
to that warehouse?
I think so.
See if you can get ahold
of a hand radio.
We'll be on 480 kilohertz.
All right, we'll be there.
If we land here, we'll be within
50 yards of the warehouse.
Yeah, support
teams here
and here.
Shore us up.
Coordinate
with the navy.
Get moving.
I'll meet you upstairs.
Let's move!
You're mobilizing.
What's going on?
We got a call
from Tony.
He's working with an informant
inside Starkwood.
We got a location
on the weapon,
we're getting ready
to stage
a raid on the compound.
I want to go.
I can understand why,
but I'm sorry.
I can't allow it.
Larry, I can help you with this.
I'm the only one who's
seen the canisters,
I know exactly what
we're looking for.
I read your debrief.
You gave us all the
details we need.
Larry, please, I've earned this.
Jack, I know
what you've done today,
the sacrifice you've made.
Uh, under any
other circumstances,
I'd want you out there
with us, but you're sick,
and we have no idea
when you're going to
start showing symptoms.
I cannot risk
that happening
out in the field.
I need my best men
for this operation.
I hope you can understand that.
You're right.
Yeah.
I always knew eventually
we'd agree on something.
I'm so sorry, Jack.
Mr. Seaton?
Murphy, I need
to check the personnel that...
That's it.
The weapons are
inside there.
How many men inside?
Hodges, munitions team,
security.
I'm guessing a
dozen or more.
Wolves are at the door, Tommy.
How much longer?
We're still an hour away
from being armed, sir.
We just intercepted
a government transmission.
FBI is on the way.
Sir, we haven't even run
the sequence checks yet.
Let's do it!
Oh, damn it.
What's our ETA?
Two minutes, sir.
Tony, it's Larry Moss.
Are you in position?
Affirmative.
We're about 50 yards
north of the warehouse.
What can you tell me?
Got two entrances,
north and south.
Heavy steel doors.
Two guards armed
with automatic weapons.
Seaton says there's probably
about a dozen inside.
We have to assume
they're armed, as well.
All right.
We're almost there.
I'm gonna need your eyes
on the ground in case
there's any resistance.
Copy that.
Aerial One to home base.
Target has been confirmed.
We are go
for Tac plan Alpha.
Copy that, Aerial One.
All feeds are live.
We're monitoring your approach.
Sir, we're being signaled
by Starkwood's air tower.
Let me talk to them.
You're on.
This is Special Agent
Larry Moss from FBI.
We have an executive order
from the president
of the United States
to search one of your buildings.
FBI? I'll need
to get authorization
from my superior.
We have sent you
a digital copy
of the executive order.
Check your wireless frequency.
That is all
the authorization
you will need.
Make no attempt to interfere,
or you will be arrested.
Do you understand?
Understood, FBI.
Take us in.
Aerial One to home base.
We're good to go.
Copy that, Aerial One.
Looks like
you have got a clean approach.
No hostiles in sight.
You all right?
We have a medic.
I'm fine.
Seaton, I need you
to stay behind us.
Let's go.
Stand down!
You were told to stand down!
Lower your weapons
and get on the ground now!
Lock them down!
It's locked, sir.
Blow it.
Blasting!
Three. Two. One!
Go. Go!
Where are the weapons?
I don't know.
What do you mean,
you don't know?
Almeida was threatening
to kill me.
I told him
what he wanted to hear.
You lying son of a
bitch! You came to me!
Now, where are
the weapons?!
Where are the damn weapons?!
Tell him to take his hands off of me.
Tony? Tony! I need you
to stand down now!
You're not getting away
with this.
Secure him!
He's lying, Larry.
He played me.
Yeah, I know.
It looks that way.
Well, what do you know?
Little old Seaton
bought us some time.
They're on the other
side of the compound.
We just have
to keep them there.
There's nothing here, sir.
Renee, the warehouse is empty.
Tony's informant
sent us to the wrong location.
This whole thing
was a diversion.
They couldn't have
gotten them out that fast.
The weapons are
there somewhere.
Larry, the weapons have to be
inside of Starkwood.
Tell them to
keep looking.
Stand by.
All right, everyone
outside now.
All right, listen up.
We're going
to do a point-by-point
search of this entire compound.
Good.
I want four teams sweeping
every structure
on this property.
Jack.
Hold your fire!
Hold your fire.
Stay in position.
Tell Larry to have
his men stand down.
Are you kidding me? They just
drew on federal forces.
If you don't want to lose
your men, you'll get them
to stand down now. Now!
Hold your fire!
That's far enough.
We cooperated
with your demand
to search this building.
Now, we're asking you to leave.
There are biological
weapons on this facility.
We're not going anywhere
without them.
Now, tell your men
to stand down.
Those charges are absurd,
and we're not going to
let you keep searching.
You're on private property,
and we're prepared
to defend it if necessary.
You are threatening
federal agents.
Stand down! Now!
We're protecting our rights
against a hostile
government that's using
false charges to
try to shut us down.
Now, we don't want
any bloodshed.
But if you try
to advance any farther,
you will be fired upon.
... ::: www.SubCentral.de ::: ...
-= ydy.com =-