Previously on "24":
Welcome to the first of three debates
between President David Palmer
and Senator John Keeler.
We've just learned that the woman with whom
the president is involved, Dr Anne Packard,
is being accused of helping to fabricate
the results of a clinical drug trial.
Did the president know of these
accusations and choose to ignore them?
Kim, your dad's trying to break out Salazar.
- When did you last hear from him?
- About a half hour ago.
He asked me to issue a transfer order
for Ramón Salazar.
- And you did it.
- Yeah. He said Salazar needed to be moved.
- You're telling me this isn't true?
- Kim, I'm sorry. Your dad lied to you.
- What's gonna happen to him?
- Best way out of this is to find Kyle Singer.
Then your dad will give up Salazar.
Kyle, what are you doing?
There's no way out of here.
If I die, the virus is dying with me.
Kyle!
I got it. A patrol car found
the truck Kyle Singer was in.
Pipe this in to the teams on standby.
Assume everyone on site is contagious
and use level one CDC protocol.
If you wanna get out of this,
you're gonna have to trust me.
- Chase!
- What are you doing, Jack?
I gotta get Salazar in the air in 60 seconds
or 100,000 people will die. You choose.
This is Warden Mitchell. I want all teams
to stand down. I repeat, stand down.
Congratulations. Now you are an even
bigger enemy to your country than I am.
The following takes place
between 6pm and 7pm.
Have we enough fuel to get to Mexico?
- We're not going to Mexico.
- What? Why not?
If we try, they'll just force us down.
You're gonna have to trust me.
- Field Ops. O'Brian.
- Chloe, it's Chase.
Jack disarmed his locator,
but the military have him on radar.
They're feeding us the stream
now, Chase. I'm sending it to you.
He just banked.
He's heading west towards downtown.
Downtown? He knows they can't
shoot him down over a populated area.
Try to override his disabled comms
using an emergency frequency.
We have to get through
to let him know we found Kyle Singer.
On it.
Major Blanchard, this is Chappelle.
What's the status of your pursuit craft?
I have two helicopters that have
just taken off from down here.
- How quickly will they intercept?
- Bauer's no longer headed south toward us.
- Where's he headed?
- He's headed toward the city.
At his current speed,
it'll take us ten minutes to get within range.
You got to force him down.
Even shoot him down, if it comes to that.
We can't do that over the city
without serious collateral damage.
Then do it before he gets to the city.
If he lands, he'll be difficult to catch.
- Yes, sir.
- Keep this line open.
Michelle, I'm taking over for Tony. Division
wants a senior officer in charge of CTU.
Give me an update.
We're trying to contact the chopper.
Now the virus is contained,
we need to let Jack know
the attempted escape of Salazar is pointless.
Send the department heads to the conference
area. I want everyone on the same page.
- What about C-band?
- It's a SWAT chopper, they wouldn't use it.
Adam, tie up whatever you're doing. We have
a briefing in the conference area in two.
Kim?
- Over here.
- What do you need?
Anchor these lists for Chloe while she tries
to find an admitting channel for the chopper.
I'm on it.
I'm sorry I lost it in your dad's office.
It's OK. Did you tell Michelle
about the drugs you found in there?
- Yeah.
- What are they gonna do?
I don't know. Everything came in right
after that, so no one's had time to process.
- Sending you over the first two groups.
- Sure.
We'll attempt to communicate with Jack,
to resolve this peacefully.
But if we can't, I need everyone
absolutely clear on this.
Salazar's terrorist connections are a threat
to this country. We cannot let him leave.
Now that we've got Singer, should it come
to it, both Salazar and Bauer are expendable.
Can't we focus on options
to bring down the chopper without force?
Jack's not giving us any options.
He's on a suicide mission either way.
Once he hands Ramón off to Hector,
they'll have no use for him. They'll kill him.
I just got off the phone with Major Blanchard.
He has pursuit craft tracking Jack.
However, if they're not able to catch him
by the time he reaches metro airspace,
then we have a whole new set of problems.
We need to coordinate
with local authorities now.
- Dammit!
- Hector, relax.
- Why can't I reach Gael?
- Maybe he can't get away.
I need to know what's going on
with Ramón now.
The government is probably
releasing him. It's just taking time.
They're not releasing him.
- I didn't want to tell you.
- Tell me what?
The plan has changed. Jack Bauer
is the one who is going to deliver Ramón.
Jack Bauer? What is that, a joke?
- No.
- How is that possible?
Ramón would never accept help
from the man who put him in prison.
Oh, no. He is accepting his help.
Bauer is now a criminal
in his own country for doing this.
Hector, what's going on? How could you let
Bauer come to us? That's too dangerous.
- Don't worry about it, Claudia.
- No, I am worried!
Look what he's already done to us.
It's some kind of trick.
Don't worry about Jack Bauer.
I have plans for him.
Yes?
I don't have a lot of time.
We're in the middle of this.
Is Ramón alive?
Yes. He and Bauer
have escaped in a helicopter.
- Have they contacted our pilot?
- No. They're being pursued.
Everything will be decided
in the next few minutes.
Hey.
What did Chappelle say in the briefing?
He said a lot of stuff.
Are they gonna try
and shoot down my father?
If they have to. But if they can contact him it
won't come to that. Chloe, where are you at?
No progress on the hailing frequency.
We can't get through to Jack.
I've some new ones to try. Use a tree search.
We've got to get through to that chopper.
- Kim?
- Yeah?
- I need to speak to you.
- Sure.
Ryan and I feel you shouldn't be here until
the situation with your father is resolved.
- I'm qualified to handle the work.
- Your qualifications aren't at issue.
- Your emotions are.
- I can control my emotions.
My father's doing this to stop the virus. If he
knows we have Singer, he'll return Salazar.
I know, but we can't reach your father.
Not yet, but Chloe and Adam are
getting there. And I can help them.
I'm a resource, Michelle. Don't do this.
OK, go back and help Adam.
If we have to fire on that chopper,
I want her out of here.
- What's going on?
- It's military.
- How can you tell?
- Their formation and speed.
- They'll be on us in three to four minutes.
- And then what?
I assume they've got orders
to shoot us out of the sky.
- Chappelle.
- I just called CTU.
- They said you authorized the use of force.
- That's right, Chase, I did.
Does President Palmer
know about this?
Palmer? First of all,
he's in the middle of a national debate.
And I don't need his realized. Bauer
helped Ramón Salazar break out of prison.
To stop Salazar's people releasing this virus.
I don't care. Look, this is my jurisdiction.
All I'm saying is that getting Palmer's
realized might be the smart play here.
Think about it. Bauer has
a personal relationship with the president.
He's saved his life more than once, and
Palmer has interceded on his behalf before.
Our mandate does not bend to
accommodate personal relationships.
You're right. After you shoot Jack down, you
can personally explain that to the president.
Chappelle.
Our aircraft are about to make contact
with Bauer. We can be ready to fire...
Do not fire. Repeat, do not fire
until you hear back from me.
The president has spoken of his support
for the American worker,
but I'm sure these words sound hollow
to Armando Rodriguez of Galveston,
to Shawnda Brown of Biloxi,
to Kendall Taylor of Tampa,
and to 100,000 of their fellow workers
who have lost their jobs
because of trade agreements
signed by President David Palmer.
It's my belief that opportunities were missed.
- Wayne Palmer.
- Mr Palmer, Ryan Chappelle calling.
Mr Chappelle,
what's the latest on the bio threat?
Kyle Singer, who we believe to be
the only carrier of the virus, is in custody.
So there's no risk
of this virus being released?
- That's what I'm saying.
- Oh, thank God.
- Yes. We still have the Bauer situation.
- What's the status?
Bauer has taken Salazar
from the prison in a helicopter.
We have him in our sights
but can't communicate.
- What are you planning on doing?
- We can't allow Salazar to leave the country.
I'm afraid our only alternative
is to shoot him down.
Mr Chappelle, my brother
is not gonna like that.
That's why I'm calling. I don't wanna fire
on Bauer without the president's permission.
The president is in the middle of a televised
debate right now. This is gonna have to wait.
In a few minutes, their helicopter
is going to be over downtown LA.
We'll be unable to shoot it down without
risking significant civilian casualties.
- Let me get back to you, Ryan.
- Soon, Mr Palmer.
Otherwise Bauer will land that chopper and
disappear with Salazar into the population.
Yeah.
Economic experts predict that those
jobs will be regained and more will be created.
-  Senator Keeler.
-  Whose economic experts?
The administration's? I, for one,
cannot accept the blurred numbers
projected by the so-called economic experts
of this administration. Those are the people...
David, it's me.
The bio threat's been eliminated.
We have Kyle Singer in custody.
However, Jack Bauer doesn't know this.
He's facilitated Salazar's escape and they're
in a chopper on the outskirts of the city.
Listen to me carefully, David.
It may be necessary to shoot him down.
I would like to hear the
president's answer to that question.
Are you prepared to authorize this?
Mr President, your response?
Come on, David. What do you wanna do?
I think the entire American
workforce would like to hear his answer.
-  Mr President?
- My fellow Americans,
I have been informed of a national emergency
that requires my immediate attention.
Therefore I must withdraw from this debate.
Excuse me.
- Now what is this?
-  This is, to say the least, unusual.
No one here is sure what this emergency is...
I need this room clear.
Get these people out of here!
Hey!
Where are you guys taking me?
Where are you taking me?
Why won't you talk to me?
Hey! Hey!
Help!
Hey, where you going?
Where you going?
Hey!
What's goin' on?
- Talk to me, please!
- I'm Dr Duncan. I need you to calm down.
- Where's my girlfriend? Where's Linda?
- We have her in another part of the facility.
- Is she OK?
- Yes, she's fine.
There's an incubation period of 14 hours.
With this virus, if you haven't become
symptomatic, you haven't transmitted it.
But what about my parents?
Are they going to be OK too?
Yeah, they're on their way.
What happens when I do become...
symptomatic?
It's like that Ebola thing, isn't it?
It's gonna eat me alive.
We'll keep you as comfortable as possible.
Alpha One,
Zebra One. We have visual.
They've locked onto our heat signature.
- Why aren't they firing?
- I don't know.
Chloe, come on,
give me the hailing frequency.
I can't make the servers go any faster, OK?
We've locked onto the chopper.
It is not yet over a populated zone.
- I need an answer.
- How much time do we have, precisely?
Before collateral damage becomes an issue,
just over four minutes.
Stay on course, Major. I'm waiting
to hear back from the president.
We still haven't gotten any indication
as to the nature of this national emergency.
Senator Keeler's staff is questioning
whether or not this emergency actually exists.
If this indeed is
a national emergency of any sort,
something to challenge the nation
at this critical time,
it would be an odd thing, but nonetheless
something that should be taken seriously.
And so tonight everyone on both sides
of the aisle is beginning to tread lightly...
- Could you give us a moment, please?
- ... veracity to the president's claim.
Any speculation
as to what the emergency might be?
The auditorium was a buzz
with speculation of all sorts...
David, I'm sorry,
but we don't have a lot of time.
So what do you want to do
about shooting down this chopper?
- I can't order them to kill Bauer.
- You can't let Salazar go either.
Is it Salazar you're worried about?
Or are you worried
Bauer will talk about our arrangement?
It's a fair question. To be blunt, yeah,
I am worried about that. Even if you're not.
But you still have to think about
national security, David.
Salazar not only runs a drug cartel,
he's connected to terrorist organizations.
And he has proven he has the infrastructure
to launch a biological attack on our soil.
We can't allow him to do that again.
Jack Bauer sacrificed everything
to prevent that attack.
Jack Bauer volunteered.
Jack Bauer knew the risks.
David, you have got to make this decision
as if it wasn't Jack Bauer on that helicopter.
You have to do what's right
for this country, David.
Listen, this is your call.
But you gotta make it now.
Get me Chappelle.
We have just over one minute...
Hold on, Major.
- Ryan Chappelle.
- This is President Palmer.
Can't you force down that chopper
without firing?
Bauer won't communicate with us.
He's forcing our hand.
- How much time do we have?
- In 60 seconds he'll be out of reach.
Sir?
- You have my realized to fire.
- Yes, sir.
- Major, shoot him down.
Alpha One to Zebra One and Zebra Two.
You have a go. I repeat, you have a go.
Roger that. Preparing to launch.
- Dammit, what's happening?
- They gave the order.
No. Please.
He's diving. I don't have a shot.
He's changing course.
Get under him.
Do you have a shot?
Negative. He knows we're
on him, and he's maneuvering away.
-  Rockets engaged.
- You're clear for shot.
-  Target locked. I'm taking the shot.
-  Hold fire. Stand by.
Alpha One, he's reached downtown corridor.
Should we still fire?
No. Stand down.
I repeat, do not fire. Do not fire.
Roger that,
Alpha One. Standing down.
We're going in.
All right. Everyone, fall back to B protocols.
Have all units on the ground prepared.
Wherever Bauer lands,
I want to be on top of him.
I'm coming up behind.
Stay with him. He's heading to the southeast.
He's dogging.
Dessler.
- What's going on?
- They're not firing. Jack's over the city.
- Can you get him on the hailing frequency?
- Chloe's getting close.
- OK, he's putting it down. I've gotta go.
- Whoa, whoa. Get me to Chloe.
Yeah?
Chloe? Chloe?
- Any second now, Chase.
- I need to get through to him before he lands.
I've got it, Chase.
Patching you through. You're in. Go.
Jack? We found Kyle Singer.
I repeat, we found Kyle Singer. The virus is
contained. There's no need for you to do this.
Area four, full quarantine.
Mr and Mrs Singer, I'm Dr Duncan.
- Hi.
- Hello.
One more second.
That's good. Get these.
... but our options
for treatment are limited.
I don't understand. If he's not sick yet,
why isn't there any way to treat him?
Once someone's exposed and is incubating
the virus, there's nothing we can do.
- Well, how long does he have?
- The lab tests haven't come back yet...
Please, just give me some idea.
Hours, not days.
I'm sorry.
- Can we see him?
- Of course.
- Come on, hon.
- No, I can't. I can't!
Hey, Helen, he needs to know
that we're not angry with him.
OK?
Almost done.
Kyle, your parents would like
to speak with you.
They can hear you through the intercom.
Take your time. I'll be just outside.
- Baby.
- The Doctor told us everything.
But maybe they're wrong.
Maybe it isn't as bad as they think.
They're not wrong.
- I deserve what I'm getting.
- Don't say that.
All you deserved was a father
who could do better for you,
so you wouldn't have to get money
and bring it home because I couldn't.
No.
I'm sorry. Kyle, I'm so sorry.
I love you.
You've always taken care of me.
Now, I never...
Now, I never told you this,
but you made me feel safe.
Even now,
you make me feel safe.
You did the best you could, Dad.
- I don't wanna die.
- No, no.
- Edmunds, CTU. Anybody seen 'em?
- They ran into the station five minutes ago.
- How many trains have left?
- Two. One stopped ten blocks east.
Officers are searching that area.
We stopped the other train here.
- Jack won't let himself get trapped on a train.
- You think he's still in the tunnel?
- CTU. Bauer.
- Kim.
- I need MTA schematics of Pershing Square.
- What's going on?
Your dad got out of the chopper.
He and Salazar are on the run.
I've got the schematics.
How many tunnel emergency exits
are there between here and Grant?
- Kim?
- I'm looking.
Come on, let's go!
There's one. In the alley just off
Sixth Street. Southwest corner.
- How far is that from here?
- One block.
- All one-ways. You're better off on foot.
- I'll get back to you.
Hey, are we coordinating
with you guys or not?
- I just spoke to Chase at the metro station.
- What did he want?
- Plans of the subways.
- Copy them to our other agents.
- I did.
- Good.
They know not to use lethal force, right?
Mandate's the same.
Stop Salazar by any means necessary.
But now that they're on the ground, they can
probably do that without harming your father.
Right.
- Dessler.
- Michelle, it's Chase.
Jack got out through a maintenance access
off Mission.
Redeploy all your people here.
Seal off a ten-block radius.
I'm on it.
Come on, get in.
The exit of the president did come
at a critical time in the debate,
and even pundits on both sides of the aisle
are speculating that it is odd to say the least...
Yeah, I will. I'll tell him. Thanks.
That was CTU.
They still haven't found Bauer or Salazar.
LAPD's placing a net around the area
where the chopper landed.
Hopefully they'll be picked up
without incident.
Yeah. Yeah, it's probably
more likely that Bauer slipped through.
David, listen. You're gonna have to stop
thinking about his welfare for the moment.
Bauer breaking Salazar out of prison
has already leaked to the press.
You're gonna have to explain to them
that's why you ended this debate.
And then explicitly denounce what Bauer did.
So Jack puts his life on the line to stop
the virus, and we hang him out to dry.
David, we cannot allow anyone to know
that we sanctioned what he did.
That would do irreparable damage
to you, to the office...
Now, you know what I'm saying is true.
I'm sorry. You're gonna have to let him go.
- Who are you calling?
- Your pilot.
Your brother gave the FBI
contact instructions in his last call.
He's got a plane circling,
waiting to pick you up.
So CTU knows about the plane?
Won't that be a problem?
Not for long.
- Yes?
- This is Jack Bauer. I've got Salazar.
I'm on a secure cell. 7-1-1-star-6-5-5-9.
Reconfigure your frequency and call me back.
- If I get confirmation.
- That's right.
- Is this the real thing?
- Yes. He's got Salazar. Call him back.
- And we're buffered from CTU?
- It's handled.
- Yeah?
-  Where are you?
2700 block of Figueroa.
We're headed south.
The closest safe airstrip is Santa Margarita.
Do you know where that is?
Yeah, I can get there in about ten minutes.
You really are the best, Jack.
When you were down there with us,
I had no idea you were an agent.
We accepted you. You didn't
have to put the needle in your arm.
You did that for other reasons.
Same reason as all junkies. To kill the pain.
What's your pain, Jack?
What does the needle make go away, huh?
- Tell Division to move their men.
-  Same place?
- Yeah, we need everyone downtown.
-  Dr Linzer on line three.
-  it'll take a few minutes.
- Yeah, call me back with confirmation.
- Yeah, Doctor?
- Well, your husband's out of surgery.
- How is he?
- There was no nerve damage.
The injury was entirely vascular.
- And that's what we were hoping for, right?
- Yes, he should recover fully.
Oh, thank God.
He's going into post-op now,
so he should be awake in the next hour or so.
I'll be there. Thank you.
Thank you, Doctor.
Thanks.
That was the hospital.
Tony's gonna be OK.
- That's good news.
- Thank you, Ryan.
Have you heard back from INS?
Yeah, we sent out an alert,
and we're covered from Baja to New Mexico.
How about local airfields?
We're trying to stop everything
but we're bogged down with the FAA.
Have Gael run a pattern analysis on local
air traffic. We may come up with an anomaly.
That's a good idea.
- Kaufman.
- Adam, where's Gael?
Um, Tech One. Kim and I
are just about to head down there.
- Do you need me to tell him something?
- Just send him to my office.
- OK, I'll let him know.
- Thanks.
Once you get back in the air, I'll be offline.
Increment your frequency every 15 minutes.
- I'll pick you up on 22-7.
-  Roger that.
I'll get back to you.
Everything on the system
hasn't been updated since 11am.
- That's where you should start.
-  Got it.
Gael? Michelle needs to see you in her office.
OK.
- You can use this station.
- What's she doing?
Updating the logs.
We got behind when everything hit the fan.
I can do that a lot faster than she can.
No, Michelle needs to see you now.
- OK, you're all set.
- Great.
- See you in a bit.
- Yup.
Sir?
- Can you give me a moment?
- Yeah.
I want these two paragraphs inverted. And
have the secretary meet me in the morning.
- All right?
- Yes, sir.
Is everything OK?
We had to make some fast choices,
and I couldn't do that while I was on stage.
Yes, everything's OK now.
Are you sure?
- This is just damage control.
- David, I'm sorry.
I still can't believe Keeler would
repeat those lies in a national debate.
You don't have to apologize for anything.
We didn't sink to their level.
And in the long run, it's gonna pay off.
- I hope you're right.
- But I'm more concerned about you.
You've only been brought into this
because of me.
- I'm fine.
- Yes, you are.
David, Jerry scheduled a press conference.
They're expecting a statement this evening.
- Fine.
- Good.
- We need a response to Keeler's accusation.
- What did the quick polls tell us?
We got hit hard. Voters who were on the fence
may have just fallen into Keeler's camp.
Once they find out Ted was lying...
And how are they supposed to do that, Anne?
It's he-said-she-said.
This is politics. It's not medicine.
Do me a favor and stay out of it.
- "Stay out of it"? I am it.
- That's enough.
Be patient. Anne's not going anywhere,
and we're not changing our strategy.
- David, we need to talk...
- Right now, it's "Mr President".
Yes sir, Mr President.
I may not agree with his bedside
manner, but I think he's right.
- You don't need this right now.
- What are you saying?
We should put our relationship on hold
until after the election.
First of all, that won't resolve anything.
And second of all, I need you.
Then I'm right here.
That's my lady.
-  And the third series?
-  Yeah, he'll be isolated.
Wait a minute.
How can that be?
- Have we checked these results?
- Three times.
- You're sure?
- Very sure.
OK. Thanks.
Yeah, get me Chappelle at CTU.
Put him through to my cell.
What's going on?
There's no trace of the virus in your blood.
What?
We reran the tests several times and had them
double-checked at another lab. You're clean.
My God!
- Duncan.
- Nicole. Chappelle.
- Kyle Singer's tests came back negative.
- How is that possible?
It's only possible if he was never infected.
You're telling me this whole
virus scare was a bluff?
I don't know if I'd say that.
That dead body this morning was infected.
Then why wouldn't they have infected
the boy? What the hell is going on here?
I don't know. You tell me.
- What the hell's going on?
- You didn't think I'd let you just leave?
- Get him out.
- Ramón!
What the hell is going on? Ramón!
- Thanks for the ride, Jack.
- Ramón!
Hector said to bring him back. Alive.
Fine. Let's go.
Adam!
Adam, there's something seriously wrong...
I just remembered.
I forgot to close that file.