There's a convoy missing.
It was headed from Illinois to Iowa.
It disappeared inside the border.
- Disappeared?
- They were due to call in. They didn't.
I tried on comm stat. There was no reply.
- What was on the trucks?
- A nuclear warhead.
- They found us.
- Where are you?
It's over. They're gonna get us.
You have to kill Prado.
He knows too much.
Drop the gun.
Put the gun down!
- Who are you?
- My name's Joe Prado. I'm innocent.
Mr Prado's rights will not be violated.
Take me to him now.
- We have no choice, Curtis.
- A warhead's missing. This is our only lead.
What's going on? You've got a key witness.
We should be pressing this guy.
It's Mike Novick.
If we want information, we're gonna
have to do it behind closed doors.
- Torture him?
- I'm talking about what is necessary
to stop this warhead being used against us.
All right, gentlemen.
I'll have an answer in 20 minutes.
This thing could be over in 20 minutes.
What if I find a way
that wouldn't implicate anyone else but me?
I'm not gonna authorise that.
- You don't have to.
- What do you mean?
- Accept my resignation.
- And if I do that, what then?
- Release the suspect.
- Now you're throwing me out.
- Right.
Make a sound and I will blow your brains
all over the windshield.
- Where is he?
- I don't know!
Where is Marwan?
OK. OK. OK. Marwan's... Marwan's
gonna be at a place called The Hub tonight.
- Where is it?
- It's... It's just...
- Just east of downtown.
This will help you with the pain.
-  Yes, sir?
- The White House.
- President Logan?
- No, Mike Novick.
One moment, please.
- We're still trying to locate Mr Novick.
- Call me when you've got him on the line.
What happened?
- Prado talked.
- Who did this?
- Audrey...
- I represent DOD.
I have a right to know, Bill.
Did Jack do this?
Yes, he did.
It was the only way to get him
to give up Marwan's location.
President Logan gave Jack
the authority to use force?
No, Audrey. The president didn't.
Where's Jack now?
He's prepping a team to apprehend Marwan.
Curtis.
- You want to utilise LAPD?
- They'll lock down a ten-block perimeter.
Marwan's people are coming and going.
If we lock down, we give them a heads-up.
All right. We'll stay invisible.
Excuse me for one second.
What is it?
The clinic are treating Prado
for multiple injuries.
Audrey, what do you expect me to do?
Marwan has a nuclear warhead.
- He'll use it unless we find him first.
- I understand the situation.
Then you know what I did was necessary.
At least now we know where he is.
Logan gave you an order
not to use extreme interrogation methods
without his authorisation.
- Jack, you are acting against the president.
- I know.
- Jack, we're set.
- I'll be right there.
- All right, everyone. Let's move out.
- Look, I've gotta go.
Jack, you can't keep walking outside the line
and not expect consequences.
Trust me, no one understands
the consequences better than me. No one.
Jack...
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, I'm fine. Why?
- Just asking.
- I'm sorry. I'm fine.
Look, for whatever it's worth,
you did the right thing with Prado.
Thanks.
Authorising the torture of a foreign national
is one thing, but torturing a US citizen...
- I can't...
- Sir.
This man, Prado, has information
on the whereabouts of a nuclear warhead.
- We don't know that for sure.
- No, sir, we don't,
because you're not letting
CTU do what they need to do.
I wanna wait till the attorney general
gets back to me with an opinion.
Mr President, we are running out of time.
Walt, you were the first one
to raise an objection to this.
- What do you think now?
- I think you need to make a decision, sir.
And sooner rather than later.
Mr Novick, Buchanan's on the phone from
CTU. He's called twice. He says it's urgent.
- I'll be right there.
- Yes, sir.
What should I tell him?
- Mr President...
- Don't press me for an answer I can't give yet!
I need more time.
Sorry about the delay. The president
is working through his decision.
The president won't have
to make that call.
- What do you mean?
- Prado gave up Marwan's location.
I thought Prado claimed
he didn't know anything.
He did.
- He changed his mind.
- You mean Bauer physically coerced him.
Tell me what happened, chapter and verse.
Bauer got the information we needed. I think
it's best if I insulate you from the details.
The president gave explicit orders.
You should have restrained Bauer.
With all due respect, restraint is
a luxury we can't afford right now.
What do I to tell the president?
Convince him to sign off on the extreme
interrogation, and we'll cheat the timeline.
I made the mistake of deceiving one
president. I won't make that mistake twice.
Even though we both know Bauer was right?
Mike.
Someone out there
has one of our nuclear warheads.
- May I speak off the record?
- Go ahead.
I'm worried about President Logan.
Worried? Why?
His behaviour over the last few hours.
I'm concerned about his ability
to lead us through this crisis.
I understand.
- Yes?
-  Where are you?
At the location.
We arrived with the package.
- Has Sabir done the compatibility check?
- Not yet.
Call me as soon as he's finished, then I'll have
the next payment wired to your account.
- Is it compatible?
- I'll need to reconfigure the mechanism.
Is it compatible?
Yes.
- How long will that take?
- An hour, maybe less.
Then you should start.
- Girlfriend.
- She'll leave a message.
She's already left three messages.
I don't want her calling around for me.
Take the call, but hurry up.
- Nabila?
-  Where are you?
- It's the middle of the night.
- I asked you where you are.
- At the hotel.
- Stop lying to me. I called.
You never checked in.
Tell me what you're doing.
Nabila, I can't talk about this now. Get some
sleep and I'll explain everything tomorrow.
After you've had time
to come up with another lie?
I found something on your computer, Sabir.
A bookmark. Do you have something
to do with what's been happening today?
- How can you ask that?
- Are you working with these terrorists?
Of course not!
You know I'm not a violent man.
- I know your politics.
- Nabila, enough! Stop talking nonsense.
- Is it nonsense?
- Like I said, I'll explain things tomorrow.
Sabir, listen to me.
She's fine. Don't worry.
I want schematics on the nightclub,
options for a staging area, and traffic control.
- Thank you.
- Bill. How could you let Jack torture Prado?
Audrey, it had to be done.
Logan made it clear
he didn't want Prado's rights violated.
He did make it clear, and he was wrong.
We can't break protocol because we think
it's right and expect to get away with it.
Normally, I'd agree, but here I'd rather
ask for forgiveness than permission.
- What kind of answer is that?
- The answer is, it worked.
We got Marwan's location.
Audrey.
With all due respect,
this is not Washington, DC.
Policy and politics do not always work
on the front line, where we are today.
Yes, well, Charles Logan is a politician,
and he is not gonna give you forgiveness.
I hope this does not come back
to haunt you or Jack.
If what we did gets us to Marwan,
we'll live with it.
What is it?
CTU located Marwan.
They sent a tactical team to grab him.
That's good news.
But I'm curious
how they obtained Marwan's location.
Did they use force?
Yes, sir, I believe force was used.
I'm sure I don't need to remind you
this is an extremely time-sensitive situation.
Who's responsible, Mike?
I'm asking you a question, Mike.
Who did this?
Jack Bauer.
I'm the President of the United States. I can't
allow this insubordination to go unanswered,
especially at a time of crisis!
I want Bauer arrested.
I agree that should happen, sir. But I think we
should wait until we have Marwan in custody.
No.
- I want him arrested now.
- Sir, Bauer is heading the field operation.
Bauer is not the only man who can do the job!
Put someone else in charge!
Mr President...
- Get me Secret Service.
-  Yes, Mr President.
- Has Jack set the robotic camera?
We're still a few minutes out.
We're set to receive. Thanks, Curtis.
Get this to Audrey Raines
and have her stream it to DOD.
- Buchanan.
- Bill, it's Mike Novick.
I just got out of a room with President Logan.
He knows how we got
the information from Prado.
- How did he find that out?
- He's not a stupid man, Bill.
- I'm not gonna lie to him.
- You have to convince him to leave it alone.
- I tried. He's not going to leave it alone.
- Tomorrow he can bring charges against me.
I have to get back to the business
of finding Marwan.
- It's not tomorrow and it's not you.
- What does that mean?
- He wants Jack Bauer arrested.
- Arrested?
Mike!
Jack is heading up the team
that's bringing in Marwan.
We're aware of that. Logan's adamant.
He wants this dealt with immediately.
Anything less he will take as
a personal repudiation of his presidency.
What's more important? His feelings
or capturing the man
responsible for today's events?
I hear what you're saying, Bill,
but Logan's already called the Secret Service.
They're on their way
to take Jack into custody.
I suggest you warn him immediately.
Before moving,
we need confirmation Marwan's inside.
- I'll send in the remote camera.
- All right.
- What's your point of entry?
- Ventilation shaft.
Chloe, can you get the schematics for the AC
configuration? Send it over to my PDA.
I'm on it, Jack.
I'll send it to you as soon as I can.
OK, the camera's working.
O'Brian.
We got an LA woman
reporting suspicious activities.
First tier wants it kicked up to you.
- Cross-referenced an ID match?
- She seems to be who she says she is.
Send her information to my screen.
Put her through.
- Here you go.
- This is Chloe O'Brian. How can I help you?
I was just telling the man on the phone I'm
not sure who exactly I should be talking to.
I'm an analyst at CTU Los Angeles.
Why don't you start at the beginning?
- I'm calling about my boyfriend.
- What's his name?
Please understand I'm not sure
if this means anything.
You were about to tell me his name?
Sabir Ardakani.
We've been going out since grad school.
- Uh, can you spell that?
- Ardakani. A-r-d-a-k-a-n-i.
- Where'd you go to grad school?
- Berkeley Tech.
We were both studying engineering.
He's been travelling a lot lately.
Business trips, he said.
I'm not sure why I looked - probably
because of everything that's gone on today -
but I found something on his computer.
Tell me.
I think Sabir may have become involved
with radical groups.
- You mean terrorists?
- Yes.
- Where's Sabir now?
- He said he was going to Arizona,
but the hotel has no record of him.
When you looked through his files,
tell me what you found.
Most of his files were encrypted,
but there was one document
that's a schematic for a microchip,
a type I've never seen before.
-  Jack, do you copy?
- Yeah.
- Buchanan wants to talk to you.
- Now?
He says it's urgent.
Fine.
-  Go ahead, Bill.
- Jack, we got a problem.
- Secret Service is on their way to arrest you.
- What are you talking about?
Logan knows we violated
his order about Prado.
We can't interrupt this mission.
You gotta stall them.
I've been on the phone for the last ten
minutes. There's nothing I can do from here.
You have to get Marwan
before Secret Service gets there.
- Curtis, did you copy that?
- Yeah. I'll run interference.
Give me a couple of minutes.
I'll be ready to transmit.
Jack, we're ready.
Excuse me, Marwan.
I just talked to Abad in New York.
As soon as you're done, I'll upload the tape.
Good. I want this delivered to television
stations by dawn on the east coast.
It won't be a problem.
- Do you wanna cover your face?
- No.
I want the American people
to know who did this.
Ready.
People of America,
you wake up today to a different world.
One of your own nuclear weapons
has been used against you.
It'll be days and weeks before you can
measure the damage we've caused,
but as you count your dead,
remember why this has happened to you.
You have no understanding for the causes
of the people you strike down
or the nations you conquer.
You choose to meddle
in their affairs without respect.
You follow your government unquestioning
toward your own slaughter.
Today you pay the price for that ignorance.
The camera is in the vent.
I've got a visual on the main room.
Approximately 50 civilians.
Marwan won't be here.
He's gonna want to stay out of sight.
Hold on, I've got a possible sentry.
A second possible sentry at the window
looking at the street.
- Hey, Michelle, can you get a frame grab?
- We're working on an ID.
I'm sending a freeze-frame
to the facial recognition software.
We have a match.
He's a known associate of Marwan.
That confirms it's a legitimate address.
But not that Marwan is there. We can't risk
exposing ourselves till we know he's in there.
Castle.
Secret Service
is approaching your position.
Jack, Secret Service has arrived.
- Did Marwan's people see them approach?
- No, they came out through the rear alley.
Moving over to the next room.
Unless you renounce your policies
of imperialism and interventionist activities,
this attack will be followed by another,
and another after that.
I got a visual on people,
what looks like a storage unit.
- How many?
-  Five.
But they're talking to someone else
out of my sightline.
All right, copy.
Stand by, Jack. What's going on?
Secret Service. I'm Agent Moorefield.
This is Agent Wells.
We know this is a highly irregular situation.
We have orders to take Bauer into custody.
Curtis, let me talk to them.
- Go ahead, Jack.
- This is Jack Bauer.
We are trying to confirm
Habib Marwan is in this building.
He is the terrorist who has a nuclear warhead.
I cannot impress upon you
how sensitive this mission is.
The president was specific.
We need to pull you off this now.
I am in a concealed position.
You pull me out now,
you put this whole operation in jeopardy.
As soon as this is over I give you my word,
I will go with you.
I'm sorry. If you don't come out,
we'll have to come in and get you.
Secret Service Command has confirmed
the order. There's nothing I can do about it.
We don't have a choice.
We're gonna need to replace you.
Jack, this is Castle. I'm heading out to you.
-  Approach the south of the building.
Got it.
- We're on the move.
- All right. Careful.
Marwan, the police are here.
Yasir saw an officer outside.
Start packing.
Hold on. I got a visual on Marwan. I have
a visual on Marwan. He is in the building.
- They know we're here. Move on the building.
- Our cover's blown. Everyone, go, go, go, go!
Get down! Everybody, get down!
Get down now! Get down!
Outta the way!
- Freeze!
I got him, Jack.
Marwan's men have escaped
through a hole in the wall.
Set up a two-mile perimeter.
Cover all utility access points.
Bomb! Bomb!
Jack, what happened? Curtis!
Curtis!
Jack, are you OK?
- Yeah. Check out the men.
Michelle, it's Jack. We can't pursue.
They blew the tunnel up behind them.
It's completely blocked.
Have LAPD tighten up the perimeter. Get
'em to tell us what this tunnel feeds into now.
Jack.
Agent Bauer.
Agent Moorefield, Secret Service.
I'm sorry, but I'm here to take you into
custody. Hand over your weapon, please.
- You blew this mission.
- I'm sorry, sir. I'm just following orders.
Has anyone asked President Logan
what the hell he was thinking?
Curtis, we still have to focus on finding
Marwan. We pulled up city records.
The building is directly adjacent
to a sewer line.
- How many ingress points are there?
- 30.
- Marwan's probably passed our perimeters.
- We have to keep looking.
LAPD and FBI will set down a grid there.
Coordinate your men with them.
We found a video tape on a man we shot.
We should be able to recover
most of what's on it.
Have one of your men come back with it.
Edgar's repositioned the satellite.
- We'll let you know if we find anything.
- You got it.
How did Marwan get past your men?
- They had to move in before they were ready.
- Why?
Secret Service showed up to take Bauer,
which compromised one of our positions.
I didn't mean...
That's not what I meant to have happen.
With respect, sir,
your orders were explicit.
What other search protocols are you running?
None. We're essentially without a lead.
Bill, give us a few minutes.
We'll get right back to you.
Standing by.
This is not my fault.
None of this would have happened
if Jack Bauer hadn't disobeyed my orders!
I'm sorry, sir, but if you're asking me
to agree with that assessment, I can't.
If it wasn't for Jack,
we wouldn't have located Marwan.
CTU is waiting for us
to call them back with a directive.
What would you like me to tell them,
Mr President?
I have no idea.
And that's the problem, isn't it?
It is my fault we lost him.
This man, Marwan, has a nuclear warhead
and I allowed him to escape.
- Mr President...
- Stop.
I don't even know
if I deserve to be called that.
Whatever I call you won't change the fact
you are President of the United States.
I shouldn't be.
- For the good of this country, I should resign.
- That's not an option, sir.
Not without destroying the public's
confidence, which is already at its limits.
Three presidents in as many hours
would be devastating.
Then what should I do, Mike?
Tell me what to do.
There's someone who can
advise you better than I can.
You should consider bringing him in here
to help you through this.
Who?
Keeler is in critical condition
after Air Force One crashed a few hours ago.
A White House spokesperson reports
the president was taken to a military hospital
following the crash.
Sir, there's a secure call
coming through for you.
Thank you, Alex.
- Hello?
-  Mr President.
- Mike?
- Yes, sir.
I'm sorry to disturb you so late.
No, I've been up all night following the news.
This is a tragic day for our country.
Yes.
May I ask when you received
your last intelligence briefing?
- Three hours ago. Why?
- The terrorist behind today's events,
Habib Marwan,
has taken possession of a nuclear warhead.
Oh, my God.
How?
Well, he recovered the football
from the wreckage of Air Force One
and he used it to track and steal a warhead.
- President Logan feels he needs help.
- What kind of help?
- Substantial.
- I'm not sure what you're asking me to do.
President Logan is requesting you run
the effort to recover the stolen weapon
and be in place to make
whatever decisions need to be made.
A crisis is looming.
Hard choices may need to be made.
And by the president's own admission,
he feels he may not be up to the task.
This country is very possibly about to face
the worst terrorist act in its history.
We need your leadership.
Before I do anything, I wanna speak
to President Logan face to face.
Fair enough. I'll notify your Secret Service
detail to bring you to the White House.
All right, Mike.
Thank you, Mr President.
Secret Service rescinded the order.
Yeah, they're releasing Jack now.
All right.
Yeah.
Please step out of the car, Agent Bauer.
What's going on?
President Logan realised this was a mistake.
You're free to go.
I am genuinely sorry about all this.
Doesn't really help us with our situation,
does it? We had Marwan. Any sign of him?
We have people all over the tunnels.
So far, nothing.
- We had him. Dammit, we had him!
- They're not finished searching the tunnels.
If you haven't found him yet, you're not
going to. Too many ways in and out.
CTU have any new leads
on Marwan or the warhead?
- No.
- Great.
Load everybody up.
We're going back to CTU now.
All right, everyone, let's go!
- Edgar.
- I'm busy.
Release your system.
It's the only one with the random sequencer.
- You'll have to wait.
- Someone called a lead in.
I need to pursue this.
I have agents out there looking for Marwan.
I need to reconfigure the perimeter.
You don't need your system to do that.
They can just use the profiles on their panels.
Things are changing every minute.
They're field agents.
They don't need you to coddle them.
You know, that's a pretty rude attitude.
- I need your system.
- No.
- Tony.
- What?
A woman thinks her boyfriend may have
something to do with today's attacks.
- Did you verify it?
- No. I need to use Edgar's system.
- Why?
- Her evidence involves data
that she got from her boyfriend's computer.
It's in preparatory format.
- What's Edgar doing?
- Moving agents Jack and Curtis don't need.
- Edgar!
- Yeah?
- Let Chloe into your system.
- What about tactical? I got guys out there.
Marwan's long gone.
Most of those agents you can call back in.
Excuse me.
All right.
Yes?
This is Morrison. Is there a problem?
- CTU found the club.
- How'd they know you were there?
Must have been Prado.
Has the warhead been reconfigured?
Yes.
Then our timetable remains unchanged.
Marwan.
- We may have a potential security breach.
- Who?
The technician, Sabir.
His girlfriend's getting suspicious.
- But it's being taken care of?
- Of course. It's being handled.
Let me know when it's done.
- Tony.
- Yeah?
The woman who was suspicious
about her boyfriend panned out.
- What'd you find?
- She sent us a schematic of a microchip.
It's used exclusively
in legacy nuclear warheads.
Including the one Marwan has control of?
Yes. This is the design of the chip that
controls the trigger on the stolen warhead.
What do we know about the boyfriend?
His name's Sabir Ardakani. According
to his girlfriend, he's become radicalised.
I want his ID on an all-agency
distribution list, highest priority.
She thinks he's out of state.
He's probably somewhere
in the Iowa region with the warhead.
- Is this woman who gave you the tip local?
- Yes.
The rest of the files on his hard drive
are locked. We're gonna need a specialist.
We're gonna need to send a team
over there as soon as possible.
- All right. Chloe, I want you over there.
- What?
- Take a team with you. Let's go.
- I'm not a field agent. I don't do that.
Chloe.
We need a specialist. You're the only one
who can get those files off that hard drive.
I wanna know what Ardakani is doing
and where he is.
Chloe, I'm giving you an order. Go.
Edgar, it's Chloe. Does my panel have
a live link to the tactical network?
- Not yet.
- What are you waiting for?
- We don't do that until the agent's on site.
- I'm not an agent.
I know that,
but you're attached to a mobile unit.
I'm doing things by the book
like you always tell me to.
I'm just not comfortable out here. I wanna
make sure you have everything covered.
- You have your live link. What else?
- Trunk my audio in with Bergin and White.
I wanna make sure I can monitor
a two-way between them and CTU.
Done.
OK. I can't think of anything else right now,
but if I do, I'm gonna call you,
and I really hope you don't give me
so much resistance next time.
Chloe, I know you're scared, and I'll make
sure everything is covered on this end.
Why did they ask me to do this?
I really hate it.
While you were prepping,
I asked Buchanan if I can go instead of you.
He wouldn't let me.
He said you were the best analyst we have.
He's right.
I know. I'll call you
if I can think of anything else.
OK.
Hi. I'm Agent O'Brian. These are Agents
Bergin and White. You're Nabila Argamila?
- Where's the computer?
- Please come in.
Did Mr Ardakani keep records
other than on his computer?
- There are some papers in the bedroom.
- This is the computer?
Yes, but like I told you,
the rest of his files are encrypted.
- Are you sure?
- Yes. I ran a check to confirm.
I have a doctorate in computer sciences.
OK, let's see. You're right.
They used Bloawish algorit
- How can you tell?
- By the tab on the file headers.
- Can you decrypt it?
- CTU has a proprietary algorit
It shouldn't take long. We'll start by trying to
hack the password. Let's start with the basics.
Write down nicknames, pets,
anything he might have used.
OK.
- What was that?
- I don't know.
Go! Go!
In here!
Your men are dead. Open the door!
God. Don't you have a gun?
- I work with computers.
Open the door!
- Stiles.
- It's Chloe. We're being shot at!
- Where are you?
Open the door!
- Las Vilas. We need help.
OK, all right.
- Jack, Chloe's under fire.
- What's her location?
- 1482 Franklin, Las Vilas.
- How far out are the closest tac teams?
- I'm on it.
- Chloe, it's Jack. What's your situation?
- Barricaded in the laundry room.
- Who are you with?
Our informant. Bergin and White were here.
Bergin's down. I don't know where White is.
- I'll call you back.
- Chloe, don't hang up the phone.
Get her back on the line now.
Hurry.
This is Jack Bauer.
I need an LAPD response at 1482 Franklin.
We have two agents down, one under fire.
Where are the tac teams?
About 15 minutes.
- It's too long.
We open the door... We open...
Where are the keys?
- Jack, it's her!
- Put her on speaker.
-  How far away is help?
- At least ten minutes.
- Ten minutes is too long!
- Just try to stay calm.
Tell me where you are now.
- He's shooting at us! The glass is bulletproof.
- Tell me where you are.
In the CTU car.
He's shooting at us from outside.
I don't have the keys. Can I hot-wire this?
No, it's secure. There should be
weapons stored inside the vehicle.
There's a rifle in the back.
It's locked. I need the combination.
I'm on it.
He's going.
- Where's he going?
- Wait. I think he's leaving.
Have we got the combination?
- Not yet.
He's gonna ram us!
What's taking so long, Jack?
Got it. It's 3-1-4-3.
-  Did you get that?
- 3-1...
What's going on here?
What are you doing?
Go! Get out! Get out! Get out!
Visiontext Subtitles: Margaret Burke
ENGLISH SDH