Alan Milliken is dead.
All signs point to a heart attack.
What happened, Sherry?
I went to the house to speak to Julia.
There was an argument
and he had a heart attack.
- I need you to tell me what happened.
- I tried to give him his medication.
- What do you mean, you tried?
- Sherry stopped me.
We believe Amador
is in possession of the Cordilla virus.
He is either headed to LA or is here already.
Our only lead is Nina Myers.
She thinks Amador is meeting with
a man by the name of Marcus Alvers.
- What about Nina?
- She's out of the picture.
I hope so. She can point to both of us.
I'll give you an update on Nina.
Richards is working on her.
-  I think that's a mistake.
- Why?
I don't think anybody should be in there
that hasn't worked with her.
All he does is inflict pain.
There's no way for her to manipulate him.
Nina, I don't think
you've met Darren Richards.
- How much more do you want to endure?
- I think this is about it.
-  Damn! She hit an artery.
-  Call Medical!
Take her now!
- Nina tried to commit suicide.
- Where is she?
In the clinic being operated on.
Dammit.
- Drop the gun. Put your hands on your head.
- You won't kill me.
Nina. Dammit.
You don't have any more
useful information, do you?
I do.
No, you don't.
Tony.
- What happened?
- Nina Myers is dead.
- How?
- Jack shot her.
Chappelle's on his way
to talk to him right now.
Was it... justified?
Jack wouldn't risk this operation
just to get vengeance.
Are you sure about that?
This is the gun I used.
Send it over to ballistics for a match.
Secure this area till Forensics gets here.
And pull the surveillance footage off of there.
- Jack. Can I have a word?
- Just give me a minute.
- No, Jack. Now.
- Look, it's OK. I'm all right. Go.
I'll be right back.
- What happened?
- Nina tried to escape.
I know that. How did she get shot?
She pulled her gun.
I pulled mine in self-defence.
- Just like that?
- Just like that.
Nina was our best chance for this virus.
She was a material witness
in an ongoing investigation.
I know exactly what she was, Ryan.
- Division'll want me to certify this shooting.
- Then do it.
- Come with me and look at security playback.
- Fine.
- Kim, you all right?
- Yeah, I'm OK.
I got here as soon as I heard.
I've got to go with Chappelle.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
- I'll stay with her, Jack.
- It's OK. I'm fine.
- She tried to kill me.
- It's over, OK? Your father stopped her.
- Yeah, except I don't know what happened.
- What do you mean?
He told me to leave the room
and I heard shots.
Kim.
You're safe, OK? And that's all that matters.
I don't know. Ever since she killed my mother
I've been wanting Nina dead,
and now that she is,
it's not gonna bring my mother back.
And I just didn't think
I was gonna feel this way.
How do you feel?
I'm not sure.
It's OK.
Come on.
He's here.
We were getting worried.
We have a job to do.
You've got plenty of time.
-  I'm curious.
- About what?
Why you chose such a limited target.
Why not the airport or sports arena? If the
objective was to inflict maximum casualties...
That's not the objective.
Not yet.
Then why are you doing this?
To send a message.
Most of you know, but for those who don't,
Jack killed Nina
while she was trying to escape custody.
- Division specified we use nonlethal force.
- It's over, Chloe. She's dead.
So how will we find the virus?
Nina was our only connection to Alvers.
Not necessarily. We were on to Alvers
because he was Amador's contact in LA.
- The search order for Amador is still active.
- Technically, but we've exhausted all leads.
Then run 'em again and widen the parameters.
Cross-refer transactions, itineraries, aliases.
We're still assuming
Amador's in LA with the virus.
That's right, and the Russians have just sent
us some intel that supports that assumption.
It's a detonating device, part of the Soviet's
biowarfare arsenal till late 1980s.
It disperses pathogens
throughout the atmosphere.
Three weeks ago, a dozen
were stolen from the Ukraine.
We believe Alvers and Amador are arming
these devices with vials of the virus,
which means we all have to work fast.
So let's get going.
Place the vial here. To actually arm
the device, flip switches one and two.
Then wait ten seconds and flip
the third switch, which activates the timer.
When the timer goes off...
- What's the dispersal radius?
- Hundred meters.
The dispersal rate increases geometrically
depending on wind and weather.
- Better than I thought.
- I made some modifications.
So, Michael...
tell me how it went down in Mexico.
You didn't think I would find out.
I didn't think you needed to know,
as long as you got what you wanted.
You were stupid enough to believe
Bauer had turned against CTU,
now you've got every agency
in the country after you?
- Bauer's story checked out.
- Don't presume to tell me about Jack Bauer.
What you did in Mexico was stupid, greedy
and it may have cost me my advantage.
Alvers and I still expect to be paid.
The authorization code is 7QV78.
- This is only half.
- The balance on confirmation on the hotel.
- The deal was we get paid in full.
- The deal changed when you went to Mexico.
Now, after you've hit the hotel,
you'll get the rest of your money.
Fine.
Adam.
Gotta comb through these.
If it isn't important, I don't have time.
- I think I have a thread on Amador.
- What are you talking about?
A gold certificate account
registered to an alias.
It's a Zurich bank,
but was activated locally.
- When?
- Just a few minutes ago.
- Kim. I need a backtrace.
- What's going on?
- A bank that may be talking to Amador.
- What's the sequencing program?
Beta One.
- If this is real, how long to tag the location?
- Five minutes. Ten, tops.
- She was down when you shot her.
- She was going for her gun.
- That's what you keep telling me.
- It's the truth.
You knew where the camera was. You stood
in front of it to obscure any visual record.
- Ryan, she was going for her gun.
- I wish I could believe that, but I don't.
For God's sake,
there's something called due process.
It's why we've got judges and juries and laws.
Don't you dare tell me about the law.
Nina killed my wife and they let her go.
And she would have killed my daughter
if I hadn't gotten there when I did.
Using drugs to maintain your cover
is one thing, I looked the other way,
but I've got to answer to my bosses about
the questionable death of a key witness.
- Sir.
- We're in the middle of something.
- I assume finding the virus is a priority.
- What do you got?
We may have Amador. A Zurich account
registered to an alias was accessed locally.
- We'll have an origin soon.
- Field teams.
- Tony's on it.
- Jack. This isn't resolved yet.
- We have a live lead.
- What do I tell Division?
That I let you stay on active duty
while still under investigation?
- It's my ass on the line.
- I've been working with Jack all day.
He's operating at a higher level
than anybody else, including me.
- I didn't ask your opinion.
- I'm giving it.
Excuse me?
Sir, if this lead turns out to be real,
we need Jack on-site.
And, believe me, you will want him there.
They'll crucify me
if I let you back out in the field.
Would you give me a minute?
This is your call, Ryan.
I understand the position you're in,
but I give you my word, I can do my job.
Thank you.
Listen, Julia, I thought I was clear.
You can't be contacting me today.
I'm scared, Wayne.
They've already started to question Beatriz
and I'm next. I don't know what to say.
- Where's your lawyer?
- He's not here yet.
OK, first of all, you're innocent.
Remember that, all right?
I'm not innocent. I let Sherry convince me
not to give Alan his medication.
- I could have saved his life.
- You don't know that.
What about Sherry?
Has she said anything to the president?
No. No. And she won't.
She told him it was an accident.
Now, whether he believes her or not
is another matter. I just...
- Wayne?
- Yeah?
Wayne?
Yeah, Bill. The president just walked in,
so I'll have to get back to you.
- I'm so scared.
- I understand. Just... remember what I said.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- Well, what did Bill have to say?
- Uh, he found out that Alan died.
- That didn't take long.
- Yeah.
He wants us to know that we have his support
on the healthcare bill.
That's good.
Have you spoken to Julia yet?
No.
Maybe you should call her.
Get her side of the story.
David, I think we should stay
as far away from this as possible.
You don't believe Sherry,
that it was an accident.
I don't know what to believe.
All I know is what it will look like.
You call in Sherry to deal with Milliken
and a few hours later he winds up dead.
Let's go.
Dad. Just heard back from Division.
They'll have a man on the inside.
His name is Jim Wong.
- Here's an update on your strike team.
- Thanks.
You OK?
Yeah, I'm OK. Did Chappelle question you
about shooting Nina?
Yeah.
And?
I told him I wasn't sorry Nina was dead,
or that I shot her.
She posed an immediate threat to you,
to me, and to thousands of innocent people.
You had to do it, didn't you?
Yeah.
Come here.
- We gotta go.
- OK.
Wayne.
- What's going on?
- You tell me.
- Look, it's late and I'm a little too tired for...
- Sherry, I know about Alan Milliken.
Yes. It's awful.
But I already told David what happened.
Except you left out the part about preventing
Julia from giving Alan his medication.
You stood there and you watched a man die.
- You would've done the same thing.
- I never would've been there in the first place!
David asked me to help clean up your mess.
What did you think he expected me to do?
What he expected was for you
to get Alan off his back, but not like this.
Complex problems sometimes
have the simplest solutions.
For God's sakes.
You're upset. That's understandable.
But what is done is done.
This is insane, Sherry. You are insane.
We can control the situation, Wayne.
We just need to be on the same page.
- I'm sorry, but David will have to handle this.
- David can't know.
For his own protection. If he doesn't
know anything, he's got nothing to deny.
- Sherry, we can't cover this thing up.
- We can and we will.
That's why you're talking to me not David,
because you understand what has to happen.
Yeah, you've got it all figured out, don't you?
Wayne.
What did you say to Julia?
Not to talk to anyone
until she spoke to a lawyer.
Good.
And, as long as she keeps her mouth shut,
we'll be fine.
Mrs Milliken?
I'm Detective Norris.
I'm sorry for your loss.
Thank you.
I know this is a... difficult time for you,
but I'd like to ask you a few questions.
Unless that's a problem.
No, no. It's just that my lawyer wanted me
to wait for him before I talked to anyone.
Really?
Did he say why?
- You know lawyers.
- Unfortunately, I do.
But these questions don't require counsel,
they're pretty straightforward.
According to the officers, you told them you
were asleep when the body was discovered.
Yes.
Alan and I have had
separate bedrooms since the stroke.
You didn't hear anything
until the housekeeper woke you?
That's right.
Because, you see, she says she heard a car
starting up and leaving the driveway.
- Our driveway?
- That's what woke her up.
She got to the window in time to see
a light-colored car driving away.
She thought it was a Mercedes.
I didn't hear anything so I... I wouldn't know.
Do you have any friends
who drive a light-colored Mercedes?
Detective, half of the people we know own
a Mercedes. And we know a lot of people.
Are you aware that the security cameras
in your surveillance system are shut down?
According to the time code,
it appears they were shut down
about an hour before your husband's death.
Beatriz arms the system before she goes
to sleep. So maybe you should ask her.
My partner did.
She doesn't know anything about it.
Neither do I.
- Are you sure about that?
- Yes.
You don't sound very sure.
Detective Norris,
exactly what are you implying here?
My husband was a very sick man.
He died because he was sick.
That's... probably true.
But it's beginning to look
like he might have had some help.
I'm sending grid coordinates,
so open a data pipe.
- Tony. How close are you?
- A few minutes.
Whoever accessed the account was within
this grid. We'll guide the field units as we go.
- Did you get the coordinates?
- Yeah.
You're too far north, adjust toward Broadway.
OK. Go right on College.
I won't have an address for a few minutes.
I'll call.
All right.
Look, I appreciate
what you said to Chappelle earlier.
- Wouldn't have said it if I didn't mean it.
- Still...
Finding the virus is all that matters right now.
Everything else can wait.
Are you going to wait
to tell Kim about your daughter?
- No. We talked about it.
- How'd she take it?
- She's handling it fine.
- Handling it fine?
It's between Kim and me.
If you don't mind, I'd like to keep it that way.
- Yes, I mind. She's my daughter.
- She's a grown woman.
We care about each other.
We should stay focused
on what we're going to do.
-  Where are you?
- I'm here.
- How long will it take?
- About 25 minutes.
- Hurry.
- I will.
- Get it done so we can get our money.
- It's gotta be done right.
I don't want to be in any of the body bags
they'll be carrying out of here.
- Hello?
-  Is this Sherry Palmer?
Yes. Uh, who is this?
I'm Detective Michael Norris of the LAPD.
I'm sorry to bother you at this time of night.
Uh, Detective Norris, uh...
how did you get this number?
It was given to me
by a woman named Julia Milliken.
- Do you know her?
- Yes, I-I do.
Were you with her tonight?
- Tonight? No, I wasn't.
- She says you were.
- Well, she's lying. I've been here all night.
- And where's "here"?
"Here"'s in the District Offices
with my ex-husband, President Palmer.
He asked for my help on
a political matter and...
I'm sorry, Detective,
do you mind telling me what this is about?
Mrs Milliken's husband died
about an hour and a half ago.
Oh, I'm so sorry.
She claims that you and she caused his death
by withholding his medication.
Well, that's preposterous. I haven't seen
Mr Milliken or his wife in over three years.
And you say that you were with
the president since... what time?
Since about ten o'clock.
That's over five hours ago.
And if we were to contact President Palmer,
he'd be able to confirm that?
I'm sure he will.
Thank you, Mrs Palmer. We'll be in touch.
Wayne?
Outbreak scenarios from
the National Health Services.
A little light reading.
They're sending a liaison
to answer any questions you may have.
No doubt I'll have many.
Anything else?
No.
Wayne.
I'm your brother. I think I know
when there's something on your mind.
No. I just want to make sure you're OK.
I'll let you know when this is all over.
- David?
- Yeah?
The reason I joined your administration
was because I thought I'd be an asset.
The last thing I ever wanted
was to be a thorn in your side.
You are an asset.
There's a lot of smart people
you could've hired.
But none that I trust as much as you.
Wayne Palmer.
It's Tony. We have a lead. Jack is on his way
with the team. I'll have someone update...
I want you to stay on the line with me. I want
to be apprised of everything as it happens.
CTU may have located the virus.
Jack Bauer's leading the operation.
- What about this area?
- Lieutenant Wong's heading that way now.
- Jack.
- Bill.
This is my partner, Chase Edmunds.
Have you got a man on the inside?
He's been through about half the rooms.
- Have you seen Alvers or Amador?
- Not yet.
Captain, north room is clear.
Moving down the main corridor.
I count 15 people.
I'm still not seeing either target.
Copy. There are three rooms
adjacent to the hall. They may be offices.
I'm checking it now.
Captain, I got an armed man outside
the door of the southernmost room.
Don't move.
He was looking in your room.
Lieutenant?
- Lieutenant Wong?
- Get your men in there now.
Team A, move on target.
Team B, maintain perimeter.
Get out of here.
Get down on the floor!
You're not going anywhere.
Let me see your hands.
Target's been neutralized.
All units sweep the building.
- Where's the virus, you son of a bitch?
- You're too late, Jack.
Chase!
Take him into another room.
We got work to do.
I don't want to be disturbed
by the SWAT guys.
Set him down there.
You betrayed me, Jack.
You were with CTU all along.
That's right, Amador. You betrayed me too.
I'm just better at it than you.
It won't matter in the long run.
You have no idea what you're up against.
Why don't you tell me?
He knows who you are, Jack.
What are you talking about?
Who knows who I am?
"Don't presume to tell me about Jack Bauer."
That's what he said.
You go up against him, you're a dead man.
All I want to know right now
is where the virus is.
I don't know. I've passed it off.
Look, you can do what you want to me.
I'm not going to tell you anything.
What are you afraid of?
Who are you afraid of?
We can protect you.
- Can you, Jack?
- Yes.
- And my family?
You couldn't even protect your own.
I'm going to ask you this one last time.
Where is the virus?
Go to hell.
Chase.
Where's the virus?
When he comes to, you do it again.
- This is Bauer.
- Jack, I'm transferring you to Tony.
I'll take it over here.
Jack, I'll put you on speaker. Ryan's with me.
- We've got Amador.
- What about the virus?
- We were late. He'd already passed it on.
- To who?
We haven't found out.
Amador's terrified and doesn't scare easily.
He did tell me one thing. Whoever's
behind this apparently knows me very well.
- That's not much to go on, even if it's true.
- Yeah, but we also can't ignore it.
Crosscheck everybody I've worked with over
the last five years on both sides of the law.
Check the names against
what we know about the virus.
-  We're on it.
- Bauer?
Yeah?
We found an incubator.
There's no contamination,
but we'll isolate it, run a few tests
and then send it back to NHS.
We found prints, hairs.
We'll send them to your lab for a workup.
- OK. Good work.
- Jack, what's going on?
They found the incubator. They'll run
some tests here, then send it over to NHS.
The other evidence is coming back to our lab.
- Agent Bauer?
- Yeah?
- We found Amador's laptop.
- Tony, hold on one second.
- Most of the files are heavily encrypted.
- Can you read any of it?
- Chandler Plaza Hotel.
- What about it?
His hard drive has the full architectural
schematic. Structural, plumbing, electrical.
When's the last time this file was accessed?
- Five hours ago.
- Tony, we've got a high-probability target.
- What?
- The Chandler Plaza Hotel on Wilshire.
Get me head of security at
Chandler Plaza Hotel. Should we evacuate?
We don't know if it's been released.
Evacuation could accelerate an outbreak.
We need to contain the building
without starting a panic.
I'll set up a soft perimeter, no police presence.
We'll send a team, run the operation on-site.
No one goes in or out of that building.
Do you understand me?
- Copy that.
- Good.
Dennis, call NHS. Have them send teams
to the hotel as soon as possible.
They have to operate
under the radar, all right?
Tony, I have the head of security
for the Chandler Plaza Hotel, Craig Phillips.
Mr Phillips, this is Tony Almeida, CTU.
- How can I help?
- There's a threat against your hotel.
As of now, it's important that you not allow
anybody in or out the structure.
I understand. What's the nature of the threat?
The release of an infectious substance
inside the hotel.
- The substance has already been released?
- It's possible. We don't know for sure.
- Who's responsible?
- You're probably looking for a Marcus Alvers.
His description's being sent to you.
I want your people to do a search of the hotel.
- Does that mean he's already in the hotel?
- We have to assume that's the case, yes.
- All right, I'll start a search.
- I'm bringing a CTU team. We'll call you.
- Right.
- Thanks.
What the hell is this?
Ryan assigned me to head the team
that's going to the hotel.
- Ryan...
- I don't want to hear it.
As the head of CTU you're obliged to stay
here at the center of information flow.
Michelle has more hours of
disaster control simulation than anyone else,
not to mention her practical experience
from the DC anthrax outbreak.
Michelle will lead. Gael will second.
You'll be in constant communication.
Pass on any guidance you can
based on intel that comes in.
They're waiting for me.
Michelle.
I don't care what Ryan says. I can get
somebody from Division to take your place.
No, he's right.
I should be the one to go.
All right, then, you let me know
the second you get your people set. All right?
We're a couple of minutes away
from the hotel. Where's NHS?
Getting ready. They'll be there in a while.
What does that mean?
Two minutes? Ten minutes?
- Probably closer to 20.
- We don't have that kind of time, Tony.
I understand, but you wait till they get there. I
don't want anyone going in without biosuits.
We can't wait too long.
If we have to go in and stop the virus...
Michelle, you wait. All right? That's an order.
Fine. Anything else?
No.
- What's wrong?
- Just stuff between Tony and me.
Sorry.
Things haven't been right
since he got back from the hospital.
The last couple of months,
Tony and I have been working pretty
closely together, planning this operation.
It's been eating away at him
that he wasn't able to talk to you about it.
I just want this day to end.
- Did you lock the garden doors?
- Yes, sir.
Mr Phillips? CTU has arrived.
They're outside the front door.
A maintenance man walked through.
I haven't seen him before.
- Turnover's pretty high in Engineering.
- Check it out anyway.
Yeah, sure thing.
Oh.
Phillips.
Mr Phillips, this is
Agent Michelle Dessler from CTU.
Have you circulated the Alvers photo yet?
So far nobody has seen him. We're halfway
through the common areas of the hotel.
After that, start on the guest rooms.
That'll take us some time
unless you can lend us some manpower.
We'll be coming in
as soon as the hazmat suits arrive.
My people don't have any hazmat suits.
I know that, Mr Phillips.
We'll bring some when we come in.
Yeah.
Michelle.
- I pulled this off the security camera.
- Alvers. How long ago was this?
- About half an hour ago.
- Has he come back out?
- Not as far as I can tell.
- Half an hour.
He may have already released the virus.
But if he hasn't, we may be able to stop him.
I can't order anyone in
because it's against protocol,
but Alvers is in there
and we might still have a chance to stop him.
- Did you find that man?
- No.
But Penzo saw someone heading
to the utility room. He's gonna check.
Where can we set up?
Use this area and this area here. I thought
you were gonna wait for those hazmat suits.
They'll let us know as soon as they get here.
This guy, we have an idea where he is.
Let me take you.
Why don't you tell me and I'll check it out.
- Hands in the air! I'm a federal agent!
- Lady! Lady, take it easy.
Slowly!
- Move where I can see you!
- I'm a maintenance man, for God's sake.
I adjusted the thermostat
in the laundry room.
Stop right there!
Put your hands on your head!
Wrap your right arm around the pipe.
Now cuff yourself.
Where's the virus?
If this virus gets out, you die,
just like everyone else.
It's in the central ventilation unit.
- Gael, can you hear me?
- I hear you.
- The virus is in the central ventilation unit.
- I'm on my way.
- Found it. It's in a vial.
- Stay clear, Gael.
NHS should be here any minute.
I'll send down a hazmat suit.
There may not be enough time for that.
The vial's inside a detonating device.
The timer's armed.
I've got to get to it, try to disarm it.