Previously on "24":
We've learned that the woman with whom
the president is involved, Dr Anne Packard,
is being accused of helping to fabricate
the results of a clinical drug trial.
Voters who were on the fence
may have just fallen into Keeler's camp.
Once they find out that Ted was lying...
And how do they do that?
It's he-said-she-said.
See, this is politics. It's not medicine.
So do me a favor and stay out of it.
- I'm taking over for Tony.
- We're trying to contact the chopper.
Now we have Singer
and the virus is contained,
we need to let Jack know the attempted
escape of Salazar is pointless.
Salazar's terrorist connections
are a threat to this country.
- Both Salazar and Bauer are expendable.
- What's going on?
Your dad got out of the chopper.
He and Salazar are on the run.
All that matters is telling him
the virus has been contained.
That way, he'll turn Salazar over.
Your brother gave the FBI
contact instructions in his last call.
He's got a plane circling,
waiting to pick you up.
You really are the best, Jack.
- What the hell is going on?
- You didn't think I'd let you just leave?
Ramón...
Adam!
There's something seriously wrong...
I just remembered,
I forgot to close that file.
The following takes place
between 7pm and 8pm.
- Let me go.
- You shouldn't have walked into this.
Calm down. I have to ask you
a few questions, OK?
This room is soundproofed,
so if you scream
it won't do anything but make me mad,
and you don't wanna do that.
So are we gonna be all right here?
- What are you doing to my father?
- I'll ask the questions.
You came in here to bring
the logs back up to date.
When do they expect you to finish?
- Don't make me ask you twice.
- I don't know. Ten minutes.
And after that, what are you working on?
Just utility work.
Good.
What do you think you're doing?
This isn't gonna work.
- Adam?
- Yeah?
Tony's out of surgery. I'm trying
to head over there in a few minutes.
- Who's gonna be in charge?
- Gael.
Unmount and transfer
all my directories to his system.
- Sure.
- Anything new on Jack?
Our last location on him was the
subway station, then Chase lost his trail.
- Have we contacted LAPD?
- They're all over it. So is the FBI.
I think we're going about this
the wrong way.
Jack broke Salazar out of jail
to stop the bio threat,
but now that we have Singer,
there is no threat.
If we saturate the media,
Jack will get the message.
The president does not want the
public to know about the bio threat.
We have to find Jack and Salazar ourselves.
Yeah.
- Dessler.
- Michelle, it's me.
Why aren't you
in the teleconference room?
Kim bumped into some embedded no-ops
in the log files. It'll take a few minutes.
She can handle that.
I'm heading to the hospital.
I need you up to speed
so you can take over for me.
- On my way.
- Thank you.
I'm watching you. So don't try anything.
All right?
Transfer all blue-alert key codes to Gael.
- Anything else?
- That's it. Thanks.
There is no longer an outbreak threat
for the city of Los Angeles.
Kyle Singer, who was being
held by Salazar's people,
was not carrying the Cordilla virus
and is perfectly healthy.
But we do know Salazar's
organization has the virus,
which means finding Ramón Salazar
is our top priority.
Thank you for joining us, Gael.
If you're taking over for Michelle,
be on time.
- Sorry.
- From this moment on,
we are focused on one thing only.
Finding Ramón Salazar.
Adam, where are we on that?
After Jack and Ramón ditched the chopper,
we lost their trail. They could still be in LA.
Not for long.
We suspect they're heading for Mexico.
We've contacted the Mexican government
and the Central American allies.
- They're monitoring all air corridors.
- What about Chase?
- I assume he's coming here.
- Don't assume anything.
Ramón, have a drink. You're a free man.
Thank you.
Ramón...
Hello, Jack.
The party's going well.
I wanted you to know.
I want you to know something else.
For some reason, Hector wants you alive.
Maybe he wants to kill you himself.
Or maybe he wants to watch me do it.
- I'm just not sure I can wait that long.
- Ramón, let's get back to the party.
Come on. The girls. Sandra is waiting.
- Yeah?
- This is Chappelle. What are you doing?
- Trying to find Jack.
- So's the rest of CTU.
- Well, I may have a thread.
- Tell me.
Jack and I back-pocketed
some of Hector Salazar's contacts.
We'll pass any information on
to another field team. I want you here.
As soon as Jack hands Ramón Salazar
to his brother, they'll kill him.
- Jack may already be dead.
- I won't stop until I know for sure.
- Chase, I want you back here now.
- Why?
Because I just found out
Jack's been using heroin.
And since you're his partner,
you must've known.
- I had no idea.
- I don't believe you.
I believe you've been covering for him.
All that matters is finding Jack,
and I can't do that from CTU.
If you even want a chance
of keeping your job,
you'll get back here now
and debrief me on Bauer.
- Do you understand?
- Yes, I understand.
Good.
- O'Brian.
- Is Kim up there?
- No.
- Are your logs lagging by six hours?
Let me check.
- Yep.
- Kim was taking care of that.
I don't know what Kim's doing.
I don't follow her schedule.
Gael, are you going back
to Tech One right now?
- No, not right now. Why?
- I need something from Kim. I'll get her.
- No, she's not there.
- Yeah, she is. She's backing up logs.
Chappelle asked her to take a mirror drive
to Network. She'll be back soon.
- What do you need?
- What do I need? I need to find Jack.
We're dead-ending. Kim's his daughter.
Maybe she can help us.
As soon as she gets back,
I'll send her over, OK?
Yeah. OK.
Gael, I had Adam transfer
all my directories over to your system.
- Thanks. Great.
- Hold on.
I wanna go over the dispatches from Division.
There are 17 units in the field,
five of them downtown.
- They're trying to find Jack.
- And the other 12?
Health Services, LAX... Hold on.
Let me pull up the rest for you.
This is the matrix I use to balance resources.
I'll transfer it to you.
- Is Tony out of surgery?
- Yeah.
- Is he gonna be OK?
- Hope so.
- Dessler.
- Is Gael with you?
- Yeah. Why?
- I can't get into Tech One. It's the code.
Did you change the code to Tech One?
- No. Why?
- Adam can't get in.
- What does he need?
- What do you need, Adam?
- I'm looking for Kim. She was in there.
- Did you call her?
Something's wrong with the phone.
Can you override the door? It's tweaked.
Yeah, sure.
- What are you doing?
- Overriding the access code.
OK, I'm resetting it to 1-2-3-4.
It'll take 15 seconds to sync, though.
Thanks.
I'm sending everything related
to the virus to volume A.
Where do you want the Salazar file?
Kim?
Oh, my God. Kim!
- Kim?
- Adam, it was Gael.
Section five is clear.
I have a visual on the subject.
Section five.
Block him off on the other side!
Get down here! Come on!
I'm on it. I'm heading
down the stairwell now.
Section seven.
I'm locking down the corridor.
I do not have a visual on the subject.
Repeat, I do not have a visual. Please advise.
We need backup!
Section seven!
Put it down! Put it down!
Don't do it. Put it down now.
Gael!
- Don't get in my way!
- External security is in position.
You're not going anywhere.
You take one step outside,
you know exactly what will happen.
Yeah, OK, I will.
Thanks.
What did they say?
They haven't found Jack.
They're not sure if he's in the city.
He's not in the city.
His plan was to take Ramón Salazar
back to his brother to prevent the outbreak.
That's what he's gonna do,
even if it costs him his life.
That's probably true, but there's
nothing we can do about that now.
Our intelligence and military services
are working overtime on that front, so...
let them do their job.
We, unfortunately,
have other fires to put out.
Anne?
- I'm sorry about Ted and the debate.
- I don't wanna hear it. It's not your fault.
I told you to stand up to him,
but maybe I was wrong.
- Maybe you should've just paid him off.
- You were not wrong.
Mr President?
We have a lot of work to do.
I still can't believe Gael could be
a traitor. Has he said anything?
We haven't gone in yet.
We're sweating him first.
Listen, Ryan, Tony's out of surgery.
I wanna be there when he wakes up.
And I need you here.
We just uncovered a mole. We don't know
how badly we've been compromised.
But you're handling that. Anything
that spills over, you can give to Chloe.
- Chloe's a pain in the ass.
- She can do it. At least until I get back.
Fine. If you think you're dispensable.
I just wanna be with my husband.
All right.
Thank you.
All right, let's do this.
You had us, Gael.
Now we have you.
You workin' alone, or does Salazar
have other moles inside?
You know Johnson.
You know what Johnson does.
Sooner or later, you're going
to tell me what you know.
The only question is how hard
you wanna make this on yourself.
Kim says you were monitoring
the plane that had Jack Bauer on it.
- Is that true?
- I have nothing to say.
If it's the last thing you ever do, you're
going to tell me where that plane is landing.
What is it, Ramón? Don't you like the girls?
Tell me again why Hector wants Bauer alive.
- I don't know. He didn't say. But I...
- "But"?
But nothing. Every time Bauer
takes a breath is an insult to me.
I went to prison because of his betrayal.
I know, Ramón, and I'm sure
that Hector feels the same way.
- Then he won't mind.
- Ramón, no!
Are you giving me an order, Tomás?
Ramón, I work for you and your brother.
I love and respect both of you.
Hector instructed me to keep Bauer
alive until the plane lands.
And I'm instructing you to sit down.
Honor the one wish of your brother,
who arranged for your escape today.
In less than an hour, I am sure that
you will get your revenge on Bauer.
We'll see.
- Pour me another drink.
- Yes, Ramón.
- Pedro...
- I'm not supposed to talk to you, Jack.
Fine. Then listen. I risked my life
getting Ramón out of prison.
You put him in prison.
I need to tell Ramón
something important.
Before he gets wasted.
You know what he's like.
Yeah. Got drunk one time,
threw some guy off a plane.
Keeps going like this...
you might be landing before we do.
- For God's sakes, listen to me.
- No, you listen to me.
I'm not talking to you.
You're a dead man.
Jack...
Jack?
Quit screwing around, Jack.
We can explain the national security
issue that pulled you offstage,
but the allegation against Anne
will be a lot harder to handle.
Her ex-husband had an agenda.
It shouldn't be difficult to prove he's a liar.
This is dirty laundry,
and we know the public wants to hear it.
Unless you can offer them something
definitive, Anne will hurt you.
Gerry's right.
I'm your brother, I'm your advisor,
and I do have some perspective on this thing.
Now, do you wanna hear it?
Yes, I wanna hear it.
- Distance yourself from Anne.
- Wayne...
Before you shut me down, just hear me out.
You used up the public's goodwill
with Sherry.
They don't want you being involved
with someone else who's not trustworthy.
You have got to respect
the people who voted for you.
Oh, excuse me.
- Hello?
- Anne, it's me. Ted. We need to talk.
About what? What could you
possibly have to say to me?
I can't believe you even
have the audacity to call.
- I'm sorry.
- Well, that's great.
- Now everything's all right.
- I called because I wanna make it right.
How? How can you possibly
undo the damage you've done?
I'm in my office.
Come up and I'll explain.
- I'm not coming over there.
- Anne, listen to me.
I have documents
that'll prove your innocence.
- What kind of documents?
- Letters and memos.
Please. I wanna give them to you personally.
I promise I won't make a scene.
- I'll send someone over to get them.
- No!
No, we will do this my way,
or I swear I'll burn 'em right now.
All right. But you'd
better not be wasting my time.
Simon, we need to talk.
Chase Edmunds.
Sorry, but I'm having dinner right now.
- What do you want?
- Information.
- Are you crazy?
- What's going on?
Rita, take the kids upstairs.
Everything will be fine.
- What do you want?
- Ramón Salazar broke out of prison today.
- He's gonna hook up with his brother.
- I told you, I'm a legitimate accountant!
I don't have any business
with the Salazars.
Simon, I did not come here to bust you.
But I am not leaving
until I know where Hector is.
Do you understand me?
I don't know where Hector is now.
He left Colombia over two weeks ago.
- He didn't tell you where he was going?
- No.
- You're tied into his money flow, right?
- Yes, some of it.
Let's take a look.
Ramón... Hector is meeting us.
Just wait a few minutes.
Ramón, please. Hector said...
Are you ready to die, Jack?
Back off! Back!
- Get back or I'll kill him! Get back!
- Shoot him, Tomás! Shoot him!
I die, he dies. Is that what you want
Hector to see when you get off this plane?
Drop the weapons!
There's no way out of this for you.
He's right.
My brother has an army out there.
- We're not in your back yard any more.
- I'll worry about that. You take a seat.
Ladies, don't worry.
Everything's under control.
The party will continue
once we're on the ground.
The big American hero.
What do you think, Jack?
That Hector's not prepared for you?
Shut up.
Danny, OK. Hey, man, back up.
Rápido, rápido. Get in the car.
Why do you need so many people?
I want to be prepared
when the plane lands.
- Prepared for what?
- Whatever.
I haven't heard from Gael.
He should've checked in.
- So call Ramón's plane.
- Too risky. The Americans are checking.
Come on!
I have to go, OK?
Rápido! Come on!
Who else is working with you, Gael?
Let me make something clear.
I would love nothing more than to hang you
as a traitor and watch you jerk till you're dead.
But I'm a realist.
If there are others, tell me now
and we might be able to cut you a deal.
Is that Hector?
Adam, bring me a tracking node now.
Now! Hector Salazar's calling!
Kim, grab that laptop.
- Put the socket in C5, Kim.
- Got it.
Hurry up.
OK, go.
One wrong word, I swear to God,
I'll make you regret it.
- Hello?
- Where have you been?
Busy. I don't have a lot of time.
- Where is Ramón?
- On his way to you.
- Is he safe?
- I think so.
What about Bauer?
- Don't know.
- What do you mean, you don't know?
- What are you doing there?
- They put me on something else.
They're watching me.
- Call me when you have something.
- Yeah.
Did we get it?
No.
Dammit.
Hey.
How you doin'?
You scared the hell out of me.
I know. I'm sorry.
- How is he, Doctor?
- We couldn't have had a better result.
He'll be on his feet in a few days.
- When can he come home?
- Tomorrow.
I just wanna keep an eye on him,
make sure he stays stable.
Could we have a couple of minutes, please?
- Of course.
- Thanks.
- Michelle...
- Yeah?
Did the president let Salazar out of prison?
No. No, Jack broke him out so the president
wouldn't have to make the choice.
- Did he get away?
- Yeah.
I have to talk to Gael right away.
Wh...
- Gael?
- Yeah.
What, something happen to him?
- Gael's been working for the Salazars.
- How do you know that?
He was using Tech One
to monitor Salazar's escape.
When we found out, he tried to run.
- Where's he now?
- He's still at CTU.
Chappelle and Johnson
are questioning him.
- Where are you going?
- Get me over there.
- No, you're not going anywhere. Doctor!
- Get the car.
- Doctor!
- Mr Almeida, what are you doing?
I have to go.
You can release me to CTU Medical.
- I can't do that.
- All right, look.
If you're worried about liability,
my wife will sign me out.
Look, Michelle, if I ever needed you
to trust me, it's now.
These are the bank transfers
that he made from his account in Bogotá.
They stopped two weeks ago.
Follow the money. Where did it go?
Some of it to a bank account here in LA.
A Davíd Gomez?
Yeah, we already know about that.
What else?
- That's interesting.
- What?
$720,000 deposited.
I've never seen this account.
Where is it?
Banco del Oeste.
It's in a town in Mexico. Las Nieves.
OK, look out.
- That's gotta be it.
- Good. We're done?
- Not quite.
- What else?
- You have a private plane, don't you?
- Yes.
Clear it for takeoff.
- Hey, Kim.
- Hey, Chloe.
Did he hurt you? Gael, I mean.
No.
It's crazy. He's been here two years,
and the CIA five before that.
- How did he end up a terrorist?
- I don't know, Chloe.
Listen. I wanna tell you that
I don't think your dad's a bad person.
If I've ever said anything
to offend you, I'm sorry.
It's OK. Thanks.
There, I said it.
- Hello?
- It's me. Are you alone?
Hold on.
Where are you?
Chappelle ordered you back.
I'm not coming back
until I find your father.
- How are you gonna do that?
- I found out where Hector Salazar is.
Town in Mexico called Las Nieves.
Jack's taking Ramón there.
No, Chase, it's the other way around.
Ramón's taking my dad.
- How do you know that?
- There was a video feed.
And I saw it. They knocked my dad out
and dragged him onto a plane.
A video feed? I don't understand.
Gael works for the Salazars. He's been
watching through surveillance cameras.
- Gael?
- He was helping the Salazars the whole time.
- Is Gael talking?
- I don't know.
Chappelle's got him now. But I don't
know if they're getting anywhere.
CTU has been compromised.
Do not tell anyone you've talked to me.
- Even Chappelle?
- Especially not him.
You cannot go in there alone.
Hector will have an army.
I will call for backup. I need you to promise
me you won't tell anyone you talked to me.
- I don't know.
- Don't do this to us. Too much is at stake.
I'm not doing anything to us.
This is about your life. And my dad's.
I know what this is about. I have to go dark.
There's no time to argue about it. Just do this.
- Kim?
- Be careful, Chase.
Kim? Kim!
So tell me, tough guy. What's the plan?
- You'll know soon enough.
- Come on.
We're interested. Tell the girls.
Do you think you're going to
land the plane and arrest Hector?
No. Even the great Jack Bauer
can't take 50 men by himself.
Oh, I got it. You're gonna drop me off,
turn the plane around.
But wait. You are a criminal in America.
Wanted. So where will you go?
I don't think a third-world country
will suit you.
I think that's called a dilemma, Jack.
Shut up.
Adam...
- Where's Chappelle?
- He's with Gael.
- Where?
- Interrogation 820.
Let's go.
What the hell's going on?
I don't know.
Talk to me, you son of a bitch.
Door.
- Enough.
- What are you doing?
- Ryan, get him out of the room.
- Why?
Trust me, Ryan.
Get him out of the room.
- You too, Ryan.
- What?
I gotta talk to Gael by myself.
Just trust me.
Michelle, what's going on?
I don't care what's going on
between you two.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm staying right here.
Ramón?
Ramón!
- Where is Ramón?
- Hector...
Where's my brother?
Kill him! Kill Bauer! Do you hear me?
- What are you doing, Jack?
- He tried to kill me on the plane!
Why the guns?
This is not what we talked about!
I was worried. Gael wasn't
sure you were on the plane.
Go see your brother.
My brother, I'm so glad to see you.
- What's going on? I don't understand.
- I'll tell you in a minute. I promise.
Good job, Jack.
Come. We have a lot of work to do.
What are you doing, Hector?
Come. I'll explain everything.
- He's in.
- What? Who's in?
- Jack.
- What?
Gael and I have been trying to get Jack
back undercover with the Salazars.
- That signal means he's in.
- I don't understand.
I'll explain everything.
Right now we gotta call the president.