-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚
Season07 Episode12
**********
jack.
Put down your weapon. Now!
What the hell's going on?
- Where's ryan burnett?
- What?
Senator mayer's chief
of staff-- where is he?
Tony double-backed to one of his contacts
who gave him information of a second attack.
It's gonna take place here
in washington within the hour.
Juma's operatives are carrying it out.
Burnett's been
supporting them all along.
He knows where the
attack's gonna take place,
so you can either tell me where
he is, or I will find him myself.
Mr. Burnett, you are a
traitor and a terrorist.
I am not. I love my country.
- mr. Bauer, this is president taylor.
- Where's the target?
What you're doing is
against the law, mr. Bauer.
I am ordering you to stand down.
Where'S...
Take mr. Bauer away. He's under arrest.
You should have comeo me. You
should have presented your case.
And would it really have
made a difference, ma'am?
colonel dubaku is dead.
Laurent must never know about this,
or about his father's cowardice.
There is no sign of my father.
Let me take his place
on the assault team.
Spoken like a true dubaku.
Laurent, it is time for us to go.
This is it, larry, no question.
They're moving out.
- Any idea what the next target is?
- No.
From our location, it is approximately
100 meters to the entrance.
********
let's move.
That's it. I need to see her right now.
Ms.Taylor, the president will
see you as soon as she's able.
Well, you tell her her
daughter is done waiting.
I'm going to the hospital
to be with my father.
I think it would be a good idea to
talk to your mother before you do that.
The president's orders are that
you remain in the white house.
So if I try to leave, you will
actually physically restrain me?
Oh, that would never happen, ms.Taylor,
because I know you have too
much respect for your mother
and her office to ever
let things get that far.
Well done, agent.
You've been at this a while.
Five administrations, ma'am.
olivia, your mother asked me to
fill you in on what's happening.
Well, with all due respect, ethan, you're
the last person she should be sending.
There's about to be anothe
terrorist attack on this city.
That's why she wants you to remain here.
Are we talking about
more planes going down?
We don't know. But whatever's
going to happen will happen soon.
I'm heading to the pentagon.
On top of all of this, there's
also the invasion to deal with.
So, bear in mind, your mother's
under tremendous pressure right now.
It's only a matter of time before the media
picks up on the heightened security measures.
I want to issue a statement
before that happens.
Play down the actual
likelihood of an attack,
talk about the security measures as
being due diligence, rather than...
no, meredith. The public
deserves the truth.
We stress caution and calm, but we acknowledge
we have intel about another terrorist action.
Yes, ma'am. Angela and i will have
something for you as soon as possible.
madam president, larry
moss is calling in.
He says he's got a lead on the attack.
Put him throh.
Agent moss, you're
on with the president.
Madam president, we've discovered what we believe
was a staging area being used by terrorists
on the south shore of the potomac,
near the itp rail and shipyards.
Madam president, we've identified
one of the men as general juma.
What? Juma's in dc?
Yes, ma'am, and we know that there are at
least a dozen other men involved in the attack,
and they are armed for a small war.
Have you found evidence that
tells us where the target might be?
No, ma'am, but we have search
teams out looking for the men,
and we're hoping that agent
walker has more information.
She's the one who I.D.'D juma, but,
uh, we've lost contact with her.
Lost contact?
Yes, madam president, but
we have every reason to hope
that she's still alive and
in pursuit of the terrorists.
If she's out there,
ma'am, we'll find her.
Hold it right there!
I'm agent renee walker, fbi.
Agent walker, we just
got an alert on you.
You need to call larry
moss at fbi right now.
Tell him there's gonna be a
terrorist attack on the white house.
Yes, ma'am. I'll call it in right away.
This is thompson...
Ranger thompson, please respond and
report your location. Ranger thompson...
bill.
The attorney general wants you transferred to
his custody so he can file criminal charges.
Have we learned anything
else about the attack?
I reached tony. He couldn't get
any more information from his guy.
According to the fbi, renee walker followed a lead
on her own to an abandoned warehouse on the potomac.
Got a visual on a heavily-armed
commando unit led by juma himself.
But she went missing right
after she called it in.
- What do you mean, missing?
- We're not sure.
The fbi's searching the area,
but there's no sign of her,
or any evidence telling us
what the target might be.
Burnett knows.
The president offered
him an immunity deal.
He turned it down,
hasn't said a word since.
Damn it, bill, he was
talking when they stopped me.
Put me in a room with him for five minutes,
and we can stop this thing from happening.
Jack, even if I was willing to release you,
he's being transported to kennedy memorial.
You couldn't get access to him.
Fine. Then you do it.
You can get access.
I'm not trained in coercive techniques.
This is not a maybe. Ryan burnett is
an accessory to a terrorist attack.
If you don't do this, people will die.
Look, I'm not arguing about what
needs to be done. But I can't do it.
I don't do that. It's not me.
- That's not good enough.
- Jack!
Damn it, bill. That's not good enough.
You were the one who told
me, people who stand by--
they might as well help
them plant the bomb.
You can do this. Bill,
you have to do this.
I can't, jack. I'm sorry.
Bill?
I can'T.
This is it, general.
we're on the other side of the conduit.
Are you in position?
Yes, general. I'll be ready for you.
What was that?
I thought I heard you say something.
- Just, uh, talking to myself.
- yeah.
Hey, I tell you we're having
people over on saturday?
Nothing fancy. We're
bringing in chinese.
You think you're gonna
make it this time?
Chinese. But I was looking
forward to sheila's cooking.
all clear, general.
Excellent.
we'll have access in ten seconds.
Once we're in, we'll have two minutes
until e proximity alarms come back up.
Five, four, three, two, one...
move!
I've accessed the secret
service tracking grid.
Where is she?
Right here in the oval office.
Let's go.
clear.
We will meet resistance,
which we must counter quickly.
Silently.
We have nine minutes until the
next secret service roll call.
We must find the president by then.
The president is preparing to issue
a statement that will clarify that.
Yeah, I'll let you know, soon
as it's ready for release.
Let go of the phone.
five minutes until roll call, general.
juma had your father killed.
What?
Listen to me, I know that
dubaku is your father.
Juma's been lying to
you. Your father is dead.
My father is alive!
Juma had to make sure that
your father didn't talk.
So he sent a man named
udo to murder him.
No. No, I... I don't believe you.
Look, I was there when udo
did it. That's how I found you.
By following him back to the rail car.
General juma betrayed you.
You are lying. You are lying!
renee!
I know the target.
Reissued warrants and
order for transport, sir.
Sorry, jack.
this way, mr. Bauer.
- Bill buchanan.
- It's larry moss.
Renee walker says the
target is the white house.
- How good is her intel?
- Firsthand.
She says they're getting
in via subterranean access.
I'll initiate a
lockdown. You alert cirg.
This is bill buchanan.
I have confirmation the white house
is a target of a terrorist attack.
Condition red. Repeat: Condition
red. Secure the president.
Get to your posts.
Jack, I could use your help.
I need to know you'll
do exactly as I say.
You have my word.
- Where's the president now?
- Oval office.
What's the meaning of this?
- You need to come with us.
- The white house is under attack. What?
Madam president, we need to go.
Ma'am, we need to go
right now. Ms.Taylor.
I've got the president's daughter.
We're on our way to the lockdown.
Men are down. There's no safe path out.
We need to secure her in
the first floor lockdown.
Bill, we're clear.
What the hell is he doing here?
He's with me.
Madam president, right now, you
need all the help you can get.
How is this happening?
Where's my daughter?
Aaron pierce is taking her to lockdown
as we speak, but we need to move.
Agents in zones five, seven
and nine, please respond.
Five, seven and nine, respond.
I can't reach anyone in the quadrant.
Juma's men are headed straight for us.
They know where she is.
They're tracking her, bill.
Madam president, let
me see your tracker.
Bill, what's the most direct route
to the lockdown? From the east.
I'll head west with the tracker and
draw them away. You go with jack.
Agent bauer.
This is your house. I'll follow.
We're moving the president to lockdown.
Agent hovis, we've got agents
down in multiple quadrants.
We need reinforcements, sir.
Copy that. We're on our
way to the lockdown now.
Let's go.
General. The president
has left the oval office.
She's heading down the west corridor.
Udo, take your team that way.
We'll trap her in between us.
We're getting close
to the president, sir.
Up ahead, around this corner.
The president's tracker, sir.
they know we're here.
They're moving the
president to the lockdown.
Find her.
Take him. We need hostages. Start
gathering 'em up. Let's move.
We've engaged hostiles on
the way to the lockdown.
We do not have a visual on the
president. We're still two minutes away.
get up! Get up! Get up! Get up! move
it! Come on! Come on, move it! Come on!
Aaron, it's jack. I'm with the president,
approaching lockdown. Where are you?
We're still upstairs, jack.
Move! Move!
hostiles are in control of the area.
Looking for a way past
them to the lockdown.
Copy that. Juma's men are
closing on our position.
You're going to have about 30 seconds to
get here before I have to seal this door.
Understood.
You will not close this door
until my daughter gets here.
Madam president, right now, your life is
the priority, whether you like it or not.
Please, step inside.
madam president, are you all right?
Aaron, it's jack. We're sealed off in the lockdown.
We came under attack. We didn't have a choice.
We couldn't have made it anyway, jack.
We'll try to find a way out of the building.
- Copy that, aaron...
- jack.
Jack, do you read me?
Aaron, it's jack. Do you copy? Damn it.
Juma's cut off our communication.
I need to know that my daughter's safe.
Madam president, I
can't answer that yet.
Abo.
General juma, they
brought in reinforcements.
I don't know how much longer we can
hold them off from your position.
Stand by.
Ngozi?
Agents are moving in from all directions;
we will be heavily outnumbered.
Does secret service know the
president is secured in the lockdown?
The only ones who saw are dead.
Put me on to their
communications channel.
Go ahead, sir.
This is general juma.
I have the president.
Evacuate immediately, or she will die.
I need proof you have the president
before I can give that order.
- Let us speak to her.
- Who is this?
Special agent hovis.
Agent hovis, move your men out of the
building and beyond the fence line,
or I will kill the president.
And her death will be on your head.
Agent hovis?
We're pulling back.
All agents, fall back immediately!
I repeat: All agents fall back.
General, secret service is retreating.
They are retreating, general.
- All of them?
- Yes, sir.
Gather all the hostages
and bring them here.
- Lock down the exits. Move.
- Sir.
Confirming secret service
retreat in western quadrant.
Copy, general.
The only reason secret service would retreat
is if they thought juma had the president.
But that man, bauer, said he
got my mother into the lockdown.
Juma's bluffing them.
We need to get out of here and let our
people know that as soon as possible
so they can retake the building.
Get out of here? How?
They're everywhere.
Move it!
Keep your hands on your
head-- move it! Go! Move it!
Move it! Move!
Move it! Come on, move! Move it! Move
your feet. Get out here. Move it. Move it.
Right here. Keep
going. Come on. Move it!
Turn around. Turn around.
Can you open it?
Yes. Assuming the specifications
hodges gave us are correct.
- How long?
- 15 minutes.
We confronted them in one
of the first floor corridors.
At tt point, juma ordered us to retreat, threatening
to kill the president if we didn't comply.
But he never gave a visual
confirmation he was holding the esident?
No, he didn't, but I felt, at that
point, I had no choice but to pull back.
His men were killing
civilians and agents.
Any idea how many people
are still trapped inside?
Cross-checking the evacuees
with the white house manifest.
So far, it looks like 53.
Any secret service?
As far as I know, we have no
agents left in there still alive.
*********
They'll be prepared to storm the
building as soon as the order is given.
Yeah, well, at this point, that order
has to be given by the vice president.
What's his status?
Secret service has him en
route to a secure location.
All right, let me know as
soon as he's locked down.
And hovis, I need an infrared
sat-an of the building.
- Highest resolution possible.
- Got it.
You didn't tell me that
jack was in the white house.
He was under arrest. Being he under
guard when the attack took place.
Under arrest for what?
He found out an aide to senator mayer
named burnett was part of the conspiracy.
He was caught torturing
him... in the white house.
Almost killed the man
before he was stopped.
Renee, the president is our
priority, not jack bauer.
- Are we clear on that?
- Clear.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
They're bringing in more hostages.
Get down! Now! Get in
here! Sit! No talking.
I don't see olivia.
Madam president, that's gd news.
I know aaron pierce. He will do everything in
his power to make sure that your daughter is safe.
This is the white house, for god's sake.
How is it possible that they were able
to get around our security protocols?
There's only one explanation.
They had help on the inside.
From whom?
Oh, this is insane.
Juma must realize that there's no
way for him to get out of this alive.
I'm afraid he does. This is his endgame.
He came here to make a statement,
and he's willing to die for it.
As soon as the rescue teams realize
that you're secure, they'll move in.
It's only a matter of time.
What's he doing? Is that
some kind of explosive?
- No.
- mr. Bauer?
Oh, my god. They've
got the access codes.
I need to get into that panel.
Is there something I can do?
Yeah, give me that toolbox
over there. Put it on the table.
Damn it.
Madam president, plug the cord
into the wall, please. Now.
Okay.
General.
- What's wrong?
- It just went dead.
Somehow, they must have disabled
the circuitry from inside.
Then, we'll use c4
to blow open the door.
We'll have to drill sinkholes into each of
the 11 locking rods. It will take too long.
Depending on how the steel is
hardened, c4 might not even work.
Then we'll find another way.
There can be no room for doubt.
We have the president trapped.
We open up that door, we
become a part of history.
We will find another way.
yes. just a moment.
Call came in on the dedicated uplink.
- I heard it.
- It's him, sir.
Put him on speaker.
General, didn't expect to
be hearing from you directly.
What is it I can do for you?
We have a problem.
The president is
secured in the lockdown.
Well, we prepared you
for that possibility.
We gave you the specs
for the locking mechanism.
Theyhorted the lock out from the inside.
I need you to find me another way in.
General, I've given you
everything I have to give.
My part in this thing is over.
Are you forgetting that you
don't have the shipment yet?
Now, general, I expect you to be
an honorable man. We made a deal.
We held up our end of the bargain.
We got you in the white house.
I expect you to hold up yours.
I don't care about your expectations.
You help me, or I will destroy that
shipment before it ever arrives to you.
Hang on.
Well... seaton, what do you think?
Can he do what he says?
The shipment's not due in the
port for another two hours.
His men will have plenty of time
to destroy it, render it useless.
General? Tell me-- who else is in
the lockdown with the president?
My men saw her enter with another man.
Well, I'm looking at the white house
manifest, and according to this,
olivia taylo is presently
in the building with you.
The president's daughter? Are you sure?
Their system logs everyone
in and out electronically.
If it says that she's
in there, she's in there.
Now, you find olivia taylor, and you'll
get the president to open that door.
Your shipment will arrive as planned.
Thank you.
There, you see--
stress. Stress...
is the fertilizer of creativity.
Let's play some darts.
The president's daughter is
somewhere in the white house.
Let's find her.
Raise your heads. Show me your faces.
What do you think's going on?
I asked you a question, mr. Buchanan.
You think I made the
wrong call with bauer.
You think that if I'd signed off on him torturing
ryan burnett, all of this could have been avoided?
You don't know what
I'm thinking, senator.
She's not here.
Go ahead and find her
and bring her to me.
- What happened? What did you see?
- The door's guarded.
Well, there's got to be another way out.
There are only three exits to
this wing, and they're all covered.
The windows are sealed
and hardened. Unbreakable.
We have to let them know the terrorists are
bluffing; that they don't have my mother.
Our only option is to get a signal out.
We can do it from the
windows of the residence.
Okay, okay, good.
You'll be safer if I
leave you in a secure area.
I'll get the signal out
and come back for you.
I'm not gonna sit and hide in
some damn vent, agent pierce.
Ma'am, it is a long way, and we're probably gonna
encounter more of juma's men. It's too dangerous.
I don't care. I'm going with you, and
don't try to argue. On't have the time.
Okay. Stay behind me.
Agent moss, sat-scan's all set up here.
We can see the cluster of hostages,
but not the individual bodies.
That the best they can do? They
can't boost the resolution on this?
No, sir. The white house is one of the most
heavily shielded buildings in the world.
Yeah, got it.
The vice president's ready.
They're initiating communication.
- Thanks.
- Yeah.
Give us the room.
You're on with the vice president.
Mr. Vice president, I'm special agent
moss, head of the fbi's dc branch.
This is agent walker.
I've been briefed on
the general situation.
What are the latest facts on the ground?
There's nothing further
from general juma,
but an infrared scan of the building shows he's holding
the hostages in a hallway outside the roosevelt room.
Now this is very possibly
good news for the president.
Explain.
The area's not one of the more
defensible places in the building.
Tactically, it makes no sense for
juma to have chosen it as a base.
However, the area is adjacent
to the ground floor lockdown,
which we know the
president was en route to.
So, you think the president
made it into the lockdown?
That's our best explanation
for him being there.
We're therefore are asking you
to authorize the rescue operation
before juma manages to
penetrate the lockdown.
Do you have any other evidence that supports
your theory that the president is in the lockdown?
There's the fact that he couldn't produce the
president when we asked him to prove that he had her.
Couldn't or wouldn't?
You can't be certain
which one it is, can you?
Certainty's not possible
in this case, sir.
We're giving you our best estimation
and we urge you to allow us to launch.
What if you're wrong? What if
juma does have the president?
He will kill her as soon as
he realizes what you're doing.
Inaction has its own risks, too, sir.
The more time juma has
to reinforce his position,
the more difficult it'll be to
take the building and to save lives.
I understand.
But my priority must
be the president's life.
Prudence dictates that I hold off
on authorizing the rescue operation
until we can be more
certain of her status.
Mr. Vice president, terrorists
are in control of the white house.
I would ask you to consider if prudence is
the appropriate response in this situation.
I thank you for your
thoughts, agent walker.
Until you can provide me with more
intel on what's going on in there,
you are instructed to refrain
from launching any action.
Keep me apprised of any
further developments.
All he's interested in
is covering his own ass.
He's the vice president.
Right now, he's calling the shots.
It was the right call, sir.
You can't order an operation that results in the
president's death and your own elevation to the job.
It would be politically untenable.
Never let anyone hear you
talking like that, derek.
- Understood?
- Yes, sir.
oh, my god, aaron!
They would've heard those shots,
so you're going to need to get the
signal out before they get back.
There's a security kit behind
that door in the bureau.
It's got first aid and a flashlight.
You'll flash morse code out the window.
Reach in my jacket. I got a pen. Here.
Give it to me. give me your hand.
this is called "code green." A dot is
a short blink; a dash is a long one.
"Code green" will signal
them to move in. Go!
general juma, I have
the president's daughter.
Bring him.
Sources have confirmed that the siege inside the
white house began approximately 40 minutes ago.
We do not yet have confirmation on
the number of hostages being held,
or if the president is among them.
Behind me, you can see dozen of
tactical assault units standing by.
Government analysts tell us the order to
launch any operation in these circumstances
would rest with the vice president.
General, I discovered fiber-optic
cameras embedded in the chandelier.
- Get me a chair.
- Yes, general.
He spotted the cameras.
Give me a secure channel.
Go ahead, sir.
President taylor, I see now
that you've been watching us.
Good. There is something
I think you should see.
god, no.
If you don't open the door,
I'm going to cut out your
daughter's eyes one by one.
And then I'm going to
cut out her tongue...
- and then her head.
- Mom, don't listen!
I know what you're thinking.
How do you know if you open
the door that I won't kill her?
All you need to know is that I most
certainly will kill her if you don'T.
- open the door.
- Madam president,
- No.Open the door.Open the door!
- I can't! I can't!
That is my daughter out
there. Do you understand?
I've already lost my son.
Have you any idea what
it's like to lose a child?
Madam president, I am genuinely
sorry, but I cannot let them take you.
There is nothing you can do for her now.
Do you have children, jack?
I have a daughter.
Could you do what
you're asking me to do?
Ju stand by and watch her butchered?
No, ma'am. But I am not the
president of the united states.
Well, i am the president.
And I am ordering you to open that door.
You're running out of time.
mom...
perhaps this will make your
mother decide more quickly.
mom, you shouldn't have...
I wouldn't let them hurt you, darling.
Damn it, bauer. What have you done?
all right, general, you've got me now.
There's no reason to hold anyone else.
Let them go.
You... don't give orders to me.
Get the camera ready for her statement.
What statement?
The last one you'll ever give.
-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚