Why would David Palmer call my wife
about a national security threat?
We can't risk having
Mrs. Logan obsess about this call.
If Palmer called her yesterday, our office
will have a recording of their conversation.
Get that for me.
Don't be concerned
that there's any connection
between David's death
and the phone call he made to you.
He said it was a matter of national security.
Those were his exact words.
Martha, it's David Palmer.
I need to talk to you.
It's hardly a matter of national security.
- No, that is not what he said.
- Yes, it is.
I've dealt with the Martha Logan situation.
I altered the tape of the phone call
before the president heard it.
There's no evidence on my end that Palmer
was trying to warn her about the attack.
Sir, I think we can find Chloe.
She's accessing our system to a laptop.
- What'd you get for me on Chevensky?
- He's a baggage supervisor at the airport.
Jack Bauer.
Agent O'Brian.
We know you're down here.
Hold fire!
Do not fire!
What the hell's going on?
Jack's being framed to cover up
the real reason Palmer was assassinated.
- Where is he?
- I can't tell you.
- Where's the baggage claim supervisor?
- Down that hall, to the left.
Chevensky.
- Why was President Palmer killed?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
You will tell me.
It's just a question of how much it hurts.
Mom, do you see those men?
- I have to warn Jack.
- Derek, where are you going? Come back!
No!
Quiet!
You will not be harmed as long as
your president complies with our wishes.
Back up now. Back up right now.
We have a critical incident in progress.
I want a facility lockdown
and a code five evac right now.
- Clear the area!
- My son is in there.
Sorry, we're evacuating the area.
Follow these people.
Grab her!
I have to get my son!
Derek!
I have information for CTU!
My son's in there!
Everyone quiet.
Keep your heads down. Do not move.
If you cooperate, you have a chance
of leaving this building alive.
If you do not, you will die.
Do you understand?
Take out all cellphones and pagers
and drop them on the floor.
We're gonna be OK. We're gonna be OK.
Bring them in.
Move!
Chevensky?
- Da.
- Well?
- Chevensky's not here.
- We have to find him. Keep searching.
- McLaren.
- Listen very carefully.
We have hostages.
If you wish to keep them alive, you will
make no attempt to re-enter the terminal.
We are wearing explosive vests.
We're prepared to detonate ourselves
and our captives.
If you try to enter the terminal, you will spend
the rest of the day collecting body parts.
Hello?
Set up a security perimeter.
We'll operate from the northwest apron
behind hangar 12.
Get those fire trucks outta here!
Everybody out.
Grab that woman in the yellow next to Bailey.
Bring her up here. Quick.
All right. Yeah, thank you.
I spoke to the director of Secret Service.
Now Suvarov has arrived safely,
they're lowering their security level.
We should do the same.
I'll take our tac teams off stand-by.
Have we heard from the unit at the refinery?
Yeah. At least that part
of Chloe's story checked out.
So it's possible Jack was set up.
Jack still has a lot to answer for.
- Buchanan.
- I have Jack Bauer on the line.
- Put it through.
- Yes, sir.
Bill, put it on speakerphone.
Please.
Jack, it's Bill.
I'm inside Ontario Airport. Gunmen have
taken over terminal one. They have hostages.
- We haven't received any alerts.
- Trust me, you will.
- What are you doing at the airport?
- Following a lead.
Palmer knew of the planned attack.
I believe that's why he was assassinated.
Interagency flash -
there's been an attack on Ontario Airport.
Several men
have taken control of terminal one.
Go to alert level four. Launch all tac teams.
- Curtis is in the air.
- Redirect him to the airport.
Have him maintain operational control
the moment he's on site.
Jack, we got confirmation of the situation.
I want you out of there now.
Turn yourself in. Let our people handle this.
Understand this, Bill - I don't work for you.
I'm staying inside.
You want my intel, fine.
But I'm doing this my way.
- How many hostiles are there?
- Approximately ten to twelve.
Gunmen have locked down the terminal.
I'll send you photos of the hostiles.
They should be clear enough
that you can identify them. Hold on.
- OK, they're transmitting.
- We'll forward you a schematic of the airport.
One more thing.
A woman is gonna contact you.
Diane Huxley.
I sent her and her son to CTU for protection.
- Who are they?
- I don't have time to explain.
But I'm responsible for them.
Just make sure they're safe, OK?
- We'll take care of them, Jack.
- Thank you. I'll be standing by.
- We have to alert the president.
- Right.
I want to extend my condolences
on the loss your country has suffered today.
Thank you, Mr. President. I hope
that what you and I accomplish here today
will serve as a fitting tribute
to David Palmer's legacy.
I can't imagine anything more appropriate
than establishing a comprehensive
anti-terrorism alliance between our nations.
- If you'd excuse me for a moment.
- Of course.
Thank you.
What's up?
Terrorists are controlling the main terminal
of Ontario Airport in Los Angeles.
Terrorists?
There are eye-witness reports
of two casualties and they've taken hostages.
- Who are they?
- Unclear.
CTU Los Angeles is prepping a briefing.
Mr. President, I suggest
we move to the situation room.
Now?
CTU thinks this may be related to the summit.
Related in what way?
I don't know, sir,
but we'll find out during the briefing.
Mr. President?
- Sir, we should go.
- Of course.
Mr. President, as you've probably
been made aware,
a situation has developed
that requires my immediate attention.
I have just been informed.
This is terrible news indeed.
Please let me know
if there is anything I can do.
I will. Thank you, sir.
That's all for now.
Spenser?
Pulling the ground plan of the terminal
and sending it to Bauer now.
Good. Edgar, were you able to identify
the terrorists from Jack's photos?
Still no matches. I tried three encoding arrays.
- Widen the parameters?
- Any wider, we could use the phonebook.
Hold on a second.
Try using an np-Safe adaptive search.
- Are you OK?
- Thanks for asking, Edgar.
Chloe, you managed to rack up
four protocol violations.
It's a lot worse than that if you count agency
dot codes. It's more like 26 violations.
Do you want me to figure out whose face
that is? Or I could just go wait in Holding.
See what you can do.
- Did it work?
- We got something.
It's off an archive
from the Bureau of Continental Affairs.
Anton Beresch, ex-army officer
in a Russian breakaway republic.
So this is definitely to do with the summit.
I'll data-mine the interagency server,
see what I come up with.
DOD is receiving a localised broadcast from
the airport. The networks are picking it up.
Spenser, put it on the screen.
Citizens of the United States,
your president and the president of Russia
have come together
to sign what they have called
"an historical accord",
an anti-terrorism alliance.
Your leaders claim it will bring peace
and security to their respective countries,
but you will soon learn
it will accomplish exactly the opposite.
We are acting on behalf
of the oppressed people of our region.
A people whose desire to be free
is every bit as strong as your own.
We are prepared to use every means
at our disposal to achieve our goal.
I have hostages.
Unless President Logan
and President Suvarov
make a joint statement repudiating
this accord, I will order their execution.
You have exactly 90 minutes.
We have to get this lunatic off the air.
Sir, we can contact the networks, but
they're under no legal obligation to comply.
We take these actions
knowing that we will be called butchers.
But we are only responding to the violence
that has been inflicted
upon our own sons and daughters.
Until we as a people
achieve our own due national sovereignty,
terror will be met with terror.
That was a live feed from Ontario Airport
in Southern California.
As we just heard, terrorists are demanding
that President Logan
repudiate the anti-terrorism accord.
This is insane. How do these people
get control of an entire airport?
We've been preparing
for this summit for 16 months.
Every news agency in the world is here.
I've staked my entire administration
on this day,
and now these people are demanding
that I go on national television
and repudiate everything we've done?
- Perhaps you should take a few moments...
- Mike!
I want this handled. Do you understand?
I don't care how you do it.
I don't care what it takes. Fix it.
All right.
- Go ahead.
- It's Jack.
I'm staring down on the main concourse.
I've got six hostiles in explosive vests.
Four are staying near the hostages.
I expect their orders are to detonate if
we make a move. The other two are roaming.
Two security doors on the northeast side,
both chained but currently unguarded.
Get a recon unit over to the northeast wall.
Jack, I need you to quarterback this.
Excuse me. I got a woman, Diane Huxley,
says she has info for CTU.
Diane Huxley?
- Curtis, did you say Diane Huxley?
- Yes, I did.
- Is she there?
- Yeah.
- Let me speak to her.
- Bring her over.
Ms Huxley, over here, please.
- Hello?
- Diane, what's going on? What's wrong?
- Derek is inside the terminal.
- What do you mean? I left him with you.
He saw some men. He wanted to warn you.
Then... I tried to go after him.
There was an explosion.
- Are you sure he made it all the way inside?
- I don't know!
Hold on.
Keep your eyes on the floor.
Eyes down.
Dammit!
I see him. He's with the other hostages,
but he's not hurt.
Please don't let anything happen to him.
Jack, I can't lose my son.
Diane, listen to me.
I promise you on my life, I am gonna get
Derek back to you. Do you understand me?
- OK. OK.
- Let me speak to Curtis.
Jack.
I need to ask you a favour.
Let Ms Huxley stay at the command post.
You got it. Let me know
if the hostiles adjust their profile.
Copy that. I'll get back to you.
Son of a bitch.
His name is Anton Beresch.
He's a member of the Dawn Brigade -
separatists blamed
for numerous terrorist bombings in Russia.
Precisely the kind of organisation
today's accord was designed to combat.
Bill, I have no intention
of calling off this signing.
So you have 90 minutes
to rescue the hostages.
We're operating under that timetable.
We're making an on-site assessment.
Spare the agency patter. Just get it done.
Sir, you need to be aware.
We should be prepared
for additional civilian casualties.
- More casualties?
- It's a possibility.
I'm not prepared to accept any such thing.
Bill, it's your job to get them out alive.
The terrorists are wearing explosive vests.
They've threatened to detonate themselves
if any attempt is made to retake the terminal.
- I'm aware of the situation.
- Have you tried initiating a dialogue?
Yes, what about talking to them?
Have you tried that?
Beresch called an airport sergeant -
a blocked number, but we're back-tracing it.
Whatever you do, just do it by the deadline.
When I sign that accord, I do not want it to be
the death warrant of innocent Americans.
Yes, Mr. President.
- Got the number?
- We just completed the back-trace.
Try it.
We're all gonna die.
It's gonna be OK. It's gonna be OK.
Yes?
This is Bill Buchanan, director
of the Los Angeles Counter Terrorist Unit.
I'm listening.
The president authorised me to speak for him.
I hope we can resolve this peacefully.
I told you how to resolve this peacefully.
Your president must make a public statement.
- He's considering that option.
- We have nothing more to speak about.
There must be some other way
we can address your demands.
I don't think you understand
how serious we are.
I know the president...
- Data-mine that call.
- Yes, sir.
Get up! Up!
Bring him.
Curtis, they're moving one of the hostages.
On your knees.
Oh, my God.
Please. I have a wife.
So do I.
No...
You.
No!
They're moving another hostage.
I can't see where. I'm changing position.
I'm watching. Yeah. OK.
- Derek?
- Ma'am... Please, ma'am.
That's my son. They're gonna kill my son!
- That's my son!
- She can't watch this. Get her out of here.
No! Let me go!
Let me go! No!
In 15 minutes, your president will get
another demonstration of our commitment.
15 minutes.
- I'm in position. How long till you're ready?
- A half-hour.
- We're still transferring personnel.
- Too long. Advance your attack.
- We're just not ready.
- They're gonna kill that kid.
Jack... I heard that woman Diane's
side of the conversation.
This has nothing to do with her. They'll
continue to kill hostages until the deadline.
We can't risk the lives
of all those hostages for one kid.
Just tell your men to hurry.
They will.
Until we as a people
achieve our own due national sovereignty,
terror will be met with terror.
It's all connected.
...threatening to execute
a second hostage in less than 15 minutes.
There's been no reaction from the president...
Maybe that's enough.
The doctor said you shouldn't...
Evelyn, David Palmer called me last night.
He said he had something to tell me.
It was a matter of national security.
I think it has something to do with this.
- The terrorists?
- Yes.
I tried to tell my husband
and Walt Cummings.
They think I imagined the call.
So he checked the phone recordings.
The conversations don't match.
Someone altered the conversation, Evelyn.
Who would do something like that?
I don't know.
Listen to me.
You have got to cover for me. No one
can know I am gone. Do you understand me?
Where are you going?
- O'Brian.
- Chloe, is that you?
- Why are you answering the phone?
- Mr. Buchanan needed my help.
- Are you alone?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna send a picture of one
of the hostiles to your screen. Hold on.
- OK. I got it.
- Enlarge the upper right corner of his vest.
Looks like a secondary detonator,
cellphone activated.
So the leader can set off the charges
if anybody gets cold feet.
- I need the detonation frequency.
- I'll have to ID the detonator. Could take time.
- Just get started.
- Did you clear this with Buchanan?
No.
Chloe, can you see the live feed?
Oh, my God. It's Derek.
I need your help.
OK. I'll get back to you.
Spenser.
I was really worried about you.
Not now. I need you to reconfigure
Jack's phone to emit an alternate signal.
- What for?
- Could you just work up a procedure?
This is off-protocol, isn't it?
Yes.
Spenser, you know more about
bandwidth processing than anyone here.
I need you.
Got it?
Yeah.
It's Agent Pierce. I'm here
to escort Mrs. Logan to the Garden Room.
She's still not ready.
President Logan is expecting her 15 minutes
before the ceremony. Could I speak with her?
What's going on?
She's in one of her moods.
If you push her, you'll make her worse.
- I'll wait out here.
- Thanks.
- It's Mr. Burk, isn't it?
- Uh, Mrs. Logan...
- You work in the communications office?
- Yes, ma'am.
I know all phone conversations are recorded.
Where do they keep those recordings?
Well, the calls are recorded onto a hard drive.
It's part of the central server.
Is there by any chance any hard copies?
Actually, the president insists
on written transcripts as backups.
- He's kind of old-fashioned that way.
- I know.
- Where do they store those transcripts?
- Archive room down the hall.
- Can you show me?
- Access is restricted. Uh...
- I'm the first lady.
- I understand, Mrs. Logan.
But there are security requirements.
You need an entry card.
Do you have one?
- Well, yes, I do...
- Can I borrow it?
It's extremely important.
Mrs. Logan, I'm sorry.
Um, there's nothing I can do.
Mr. Burk, we can continue this little dance
if you really want to,
but you and I both know
I am going to get into that room.
So you can save us both the trouble
and just give me your entry card.
- Mrs. Logan, you wouldn't...
- You know, in three seconds, Mr. Burk,
I am going to scream louder than any woman
you have ever heard in your life.
One, two...
Here's the card right here.
Thank you. Thank you.
I'll return it very soon.
- O'Brian.
- Derek has three minutes. I need a frequency.
- We're trying to find the manufacturer.
- We're running out of time.
If we get the frequency wrong,
we could detonate all the vests.
I can't find a match
on any Czech components.
That leaves the German manufacturers.
Jack, we're trying to narrow it down.
The first team enter through
the southeast door and split into two flanks.
Primary kill shots,
take out hostiles in bomb vests.
Second team enters and forms
a protective ring around the hostages.
We'll only have a few seconds to neutralise
the hostiles, so find your targets fast.
Go.
- What's your time frame?
- On target to launch assault in 15 minutes.
Understood.
How old are you?
15.
Try to control your breathing.
Slow down.
See? Better.
Please don't kill me.
That's up to your president.
- Bill Buchanan.
- Beresch is calling from the airport, sir.
This is Bill Buchanan.
The boy hasn't long to live.
No word from the president yet.
We need more time.
No. The president must announce
the summit is cancelled, or I kill the boy.
We're doing our best
to get an answer from the president.
I implore you to resolve this
without further killing.
This boy's blood will be on his hands.
Come on, Chloe.
We found the manufacturer.
We're trying to figure out the frequency.
- No match on the 2004 series.
- It's gotta be one of these three.
Hold him.
Agent Manning.
I got it.
Here it is.
Go to submenu three on your phone.
- I'm at submenu.
- Enter this code - 6339.
- Now what?
- The phone needs to reboot. It'll say "Ready. "
Then press the star key
and it should set off the detonator.
Your president has abandoned you.
- I'm not getting a ready signal.
- It takes time to reflash the ROM.
Son of a bitch. Come on.
I'm sorry.
I got it. I got it.
- Curtis, what was that?
- There was an explosion in the terminal.
Patch me through to Jack.
Stay in position!
Keep the hostages together!
Check the exits.
Make sure the perimeter's secure.
It was Ibrim's vest.
It must have detonated by accident.
- What's going on?
- A terrorist's vest blew up.
- None of the hostages were hurt.
- Were you responsible for that, Jack?
Jack, answer me!
They were gonna kill another hostage.
I had no choice.
I didn't compromise my position.
Now tell me this -
are Curtis and his team on schedule?
- Yes. Go time is ten minutes.
- OK.
Everyone, pull into formation B
and run circuit checks on your vests.
The terrorists are revising their formation.
I'll contact Curtis with final positions.
Thanks, Jack.
Mr. Buchanan,
President Logan's on the line for you.
Mr. President.
The news is saying there was
an explosion inside the terminal.
Everything's under control, sir. Our units
are in position. Go time is ten minutes.
- Then what caused the explosion?
- We're not certain.
We believe our man inside
may have been trying to stall the execution
and he triggered the bomb vest of a hostile.
Did you authorise this action?
No, sir. He acted independently.
You should know, Mr. President,
the man we're talking about is Jack Bauer.
Jack Bauer?
He was in the terminal when the terrorists
attacked. He's been helping us from inside.
I thought that... Jack Bauer
assassinated David Palmer.
There's evidence to suggest
that Bauer may have been framed.
- What evidence?
- It's complicated, Mr. President.
Why am I only hearing this now?
I didn't want to distract you with details that
can wait till we resolve the hostage situation.
You tell me everything
and I will decide which details are relevant.
- With respect, we don't have time.
- Then talk faster!
Mrs. Logan is due in the Garden Room
right now. Open the door, please.
Just a few more minutes.
Ma'am, it's my job to make sure she's there.
If you don't open the door,
I will open it myself.
- Mrs. Logan?
- How dare you barge in here.
- This is a private residence.
Evelyn, if something happens to Mrs. Logan,
the blame will fall on you. We both know that.
So I am urging you in the strongest
possible terms to tell me where she is.
We're moving to entry positions.
Davies, Matthews, are your teams in place?
All teams in place.
Ready to go, Agent Manning.
All right, copy. Go.
- Oh, my God.
- It's OK. Listen. Derek's alive.
- He's OK.
- Are you sure?
I can't go into details, but he's OK.
I have to go.
We're mounting our rescue operation.
Keep an eye on her. Let's go.
They're waiting for you
in the Garden Room, Mrs. Logan.
- I can get up myself.
- All right.
You still need to come with me.
Whatever you say, Aaron.
Whatever you say.
- I'm so sorry, Mrs. Logan.
- It's all right.
- I'm really sorry.
- Will you stop apologising? It's annoying.
Besides, I got what I came for.
- Yes?
- You have a problem at the terminal.
- Explain.
- Jack Bauer is inside,
providing recon for CTU's rescue operation,
which will launch shortly.
- Are you sure?
- This came from the director of CTU.
And Bauer was responsible for detonating
the vest of one of Beresch's men.
- Can you tell me Bauer's precise location?
- No.
But he has a connection
to one of the hostages.
A 15-year-old boy named Derek Huxley.
I have to go.
Yes, tell him that's being handled
out of the press office. Thank you.
- Yes?
- Mrs. Logan is back in her room getting ready.
- Why the delay?
- She was in one of the archive rooms.
Archive rooms? What was she doing there?
The first lady is safe and accounted for.
You'll need to ask her anything beyond that.
Thank you, Aaron.
C Team.
Go to the ticket counters. The west exit.
- Manning.
- This is Jack.
Beresch has redeployed six men.
Ready for final positions?
Go ahead.
Four men were deployed to the east side,
the ticket counters,
the other two to the west side
in front of the emergency exits.
Copy.
OK, once you deploy I'll give you
real-time updates on their positions.
All right, Jack, I'm starting the countdown.
All teams, stand by to execute.
This is it.
OK.
Hostages up!
Hold on one second.
Hold on.
Hold on. Beresch is changing something.
Jack? Jack?
- Curtis, what happened?
- I lost Jack.
- What do you mean?
- The connection's broken.
- Can you reconnect?
- I'm trying.
Jack Bauer.
Derek is a very brave young man.
I will shoot him in the head
if you don't show yourself immediately.
- Curtis!
- It's not going through.
- Can you move in without him?
- Jack said Beresch was moving something.
He could be moving the hostages
into the kill zone.
Abort.
All teams, abort the operation.
Repeat - abort.
Bauer, if you want to save the boy,
present yourself now.
Mr. Bauer.
Derek has five seconds left to live.
Four, three...
Beresch!
I'm lowering my weapon.
Secure him.