Right now, terrorists are plotting
to assassinate a presidential candidate.
My wife and daughter have been kidnapped.
And people that I work with
may be involved in both.
I'm Federal Agent Jack Bauer.
This is the longest day of my life.
Our son is accused of murder.
The story's too big to hide.
We need to control
when and how this story comes out.
- I'm already taking care of the evidence.
- Taking care of it? How?
That's all you really need to know.
Mr. Drazen.
I'd like to know why the David
Palmer situation hasn't been taken care of.
My brother and I are very disappointed.
- CTU. Myers.
- Hey, it's me.
The police have thrown a net over this area.
I can't help Teri until I get through it.
They're bringing in
Alberta Green to run things.
- Hello, Nina.
- Hello, Alberta.
- I'll put you through to Jack.
- Hey, sweetheart. You OK?
Yeah. Who are these guys?
Why are they doing this?
I don't know but I'm gonna find out.
I just wanna make sure that you
and Mommy get home safely, OK?
It's Tony. I've found something on
Jamey's computer. It might be a lead.
- What?
- It's a name. Ted Cofell.
- Have a nice day, . Cofell.
- You, too.
Secret Service thinks the photographer may
have been in on the assassination attempt.
He hasn't been seen since the breakfast.
He was using the name Martin Belkin. Follow
up and report back to me in 30 minutes.
I promised Division
a threat assessment on Palmer by noon.
Check with Secret Service.
I don't want any overlap.
- Still no sign of Jack?
- Nothing.
- Cofell here.
- It's Kevin. Meet me at the Nordoffgarage.
I'm already on my way to the airport.
- This can't wait. Meet me as soon as possible.
- All right.
Mark, change of plans. I'm gonna be meeting
someone in the parking garage on Nordoff.
Did you hear me?
Who are you?
Where's Mark?
What's going on here? Hm?
Stop the car.
Stop the car!
Give me the phone through the divider. Easy.
Now!
Get up against the door
and sit on your hands.
Who are you? What do you want? Money?
I don't have much with me,
but I'm sure I could find some.
Shut up.
I'm Jack Bauer. Since midnight
my wife and daughter have been missing.
I have reason to believe they're being held by
a colleague of yours, a man named Gaines.
Where are they?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Where's my wife and daughter?!
I'm just a businessman.
An ordinary businessman,
riding around in a bulletproof limousine?
- Yes, for protection.
- From what?
People like you.
This is your last chance.
Where is my family?
I swear to you, I don't know
what you're talking about.
You're a very good liar.
But I've seen better.
You stay put.
CTU. Myers.
- Hey, it's me. Can you talk?
- Let me open a secure line.
- OK. We're clear.
- Has Teri called back yet?
- No.
- What's Green doing?
- Making herself at home in your office.
- She talked to you yet?
Yes.
I told her I severed all ties with you. From
now on, I play on the side of the angels.
- She buy any of it?
- Not a word.
- I've got Cofell.
- What do you mean "got"?
- I've got him in his limousine.
- Has he told you anything?
- I'm working on it.
- In other words, you've kidnapped him.
He's the only link to Teri and Kim I've got.
You don't even know
if he’s the right Ted Cofell.
Every time we talk
you go further out on a limb.
From the second they were taken,
tell me what I could have done differently.
I don't know. I guess you're right. But I don't
know how much longer I can cover for you.
Nina, please. Just focus and stay calm.
I need you right now.
Cofell won't be easy to break.
I need your help.
You want an interrogation profile
in what, 15 minutes?
I'll give you about five.
Nina, if I can't break Cofell, I won't be able
to find my family. Do you understand?
- I'll do what I can.
- Thank you.
I'm gonna look for a place to lay low for
a while. I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
Your father will find us. If he doesn't,
the people that work for him will.
How? They don't know where we are.
They were tracing the call, Kim.
Did they find our location
before the battery died?
Well, we have to hope that they did.
Sorry about the phone.
- Thank you for helping. We hoped...
- I don't wanna know anything.
- Trust me, it's better if I don't know anything.
- What do you mean?
Eli sent me in here to get
information from you.
But can't tell him what
I don't know, right? So...
Whatever's goin' on, don't tell me about it.
What's he gonna do to you?
Rick.
- What'd they say?
- I told you, they don't trust me.
I saw the way that chick looks at you.
She must have said somethin'.
Who was that guy I talked to? Her father?
- They wouldn't say.
- You're lying!
Stop it.
Leave him alone!
I was reviewing the report on the passenger
list. There was an anomaly in first class?
The manifest made it look like there was an
empty seat, but we don't think there was one.
- Who was actually in the seat?
- The photographer, Martin Belkin.
The real photographer died in the explosion.
And the assassin was at the breakfast.
He was enough of a lookalike to fool security,
and according to Secret Service
he had a legitimate ID, not a forgery.
- How'd he get it?
- Still working on that.
- Myers?
- Hey, it's me.
Hi, Bill. Can you hang on a minute?
It's Bill Warner at the bureau.
Shall I call him back?
No. I need to speak to him.
Let me have the phone.
Alberta? I got something
you should probably take a look at.
Tell Bill I'll call him later.
The hitter's connection in Germany
may actually lead to the Balkans.
Our sources indicate our guy's...
- Hey. I'm here.
- Bad timing?
No problem. I just could have used
a few more minutes.
I wish I had 'em. Gimme what you got.
All right. He's the oldest of three children.
His father died when he was a boy.
Means he learned responsibility early.
In college at 16. Intelligent.
First in his class. Vice president
of a company three years later.
OK. So he's ambitious, driven.
Maybe too much so.
- He has a heart condition.
- I know. I've got his pills.
He's very organised.
No charities, no...
He's not generous with time or money. Anal.
I'd guess passive-aggressive. Control freak.
So make him sweat it out for a while,
assume control, then behave erratically.
Yeah. One more thing.
Um, a hunch, really.
With people this tightly wound, the threat
of pain can be more effective than pain itself.
OK. I've got it.
This is all just guesswork.
I could have done more if I'd had time.
You did great.
I'll get back to you as soon as I can.
OK.
Get over there. Now!
This doesn't have to take long. It's up to you.
Do you know a man named Penticoff?
How about Alan York? David Palmer?
- Of course. He's running for president.
- The attempt on his life has failed.
The perpetrators will be in custody soon.
You're implicated.
If you cooperate with me now,
I might be able to help you.
I can only repeat, I have no idea
what you're talking about.
- Your hands are sweating.
- Of course. I'm scared.
Who were you meeting?
- A man named Kevin Carroll.
- Who is he?
He's a businessman, like myself.
He sells machine tools.
- Why meet him in a parking garage?
- It was his choice. I don't know why.
I told you everything I know.
Hey, it's me. Run a background check
on a Kevin Carroll,
allegedly a machine-tools salesman.
Probably an alias.
Yeah.
Let me show you something.
- You ever hear about the Russian Gulag?
- What?
A string of prisons in Northern Siberia.
Russians didn't have hi-tech equipment,
so they kinda had to make do
with what was around.
Sort of like what I'm doin' right now.
You probably don't think I could
force this towel down your throat.
But trust me, I can. All the way.
Except I hold onto
this one little bit at the end.
When your stomach starts to digest it...
I pull it out,
taking your stomach lining with it.
Most people, they take about
a week to die. It's very painful.
What kind of man are you?
I don't want to hurt you.
But I will do everything that
I have to do to protect my family.
I wanna show you something.
It's in my wallet.
Open it. Please.
I know you wanna see your family again.
And I wanna see mine
more than anything in the world.
Mr. Bauer, believe me,
if I knew something that
would help you, I would tell you.
- . Drazen.
- Found Bauer?
No, but we're scanning
police frequencies, checking hospitals,
and I'm expecting to hear from
our contact inside the CTU.
- And if Bauer comes here as you suggested?
- We'll be ready for him.
For an American operation
we thought we needed Americans.
Perhaps we undervalued
our own capabilities.
I'm pulling the plug on you.
You were supposed to frame Bauer for the
assassination of Palmer, but he's still alive.
- You don't know where Bauer is.
- No, but...
You have failed.
For over a year, you've been saying how
important this is. Now you're gonna quit?
Quit? Of course not.
We have a contingency plan. Bauer and
Palmer will be dead by the end of the day.
You never said anything to me
about a contingency plan.
It doesn't involve you.
Just give me a little more time to find Bauer.
Till noon. It's not even two hours.
I'll give you 30 minutes.
If you don't find Bauer by then, I take over.
Your last task will be to kill his wife
and daughter, and pull your people out.
I like your education programme.
But with all due respect,
I do have one or two suggestions.
- That's why I'm here.
- David?
I'm not one to say that teachers
shouldn't be accountable, but...
- Would you excuse me for just a moment?
- Sure.
Carl.
Hello, David. Since you fired me from
your staff, I assume this is a social call.
I need to talk to you, in person.
- Why's that?
- I got a very disturbing call today.
Oh?
I was told that George Ferragamo's
life may be in danger.
Now, who told you that? Frank Ames?
You know what an old lady he is.
Just don't pay any attention to him.
I need to talk to you. Now.
It's a pretty busy day for me, David.
I know a few things about you, Carl.
Things you don't want spread around.
Are you threatening me? Is that what
it's come to after all these years?
It's come to whatever it takes
to get you over here now.
- Where are you?
- Grant Elementary, in the valley.
I'll be there by 11.
- Nina Myers?
- Hey, it's me.
- You got anything on Kevin Carroll yet?
- Yeah. I show six Kevin Carrolls.
One does, in fact, work for
a machine-tool company.
It's a cover. It's gotta be.
There's another possibility -
you've got the wrong Cofell.
No. He was implicated in Jamey's file,
along with Gaines.
That file was partially erased. We can't
rely on it. I think you’re making a mistake.
There's something about this guy.
This is not a mistake.
Jack, I know you think he's all you’ve got,
but maybe that's affecting your judgment.
OK, thanks.
We're going to see your friend Kevin Carroll.
Looks like they're getting ready to leave.
- Mom, what's wrong?
- It's nothing, honey. I'm all right.
Would you stop saying that?
You're not all right. What did he do to you?
Nothing, nothing. I've just...
I've been having this pain in my stomach.
- How bad?
- It comes and goes.
I can manage.
- I should go tell somebody.
- No.
- Mom, you need help.
- I said no.
Your father is coming,
and until then we have to be strong.
- OK.
- Thank you.
- How's the food?
- Oh, better than what we used to eat.
- You went to the same elementary school?
- We've known each other all our lives.
And still as much in love as ever.
Thank you.
I am due at another school, but it's been
wonderful meeting you and those great kids.
- Thank you.
- Would you excuse us a second?
Of course.
I need to know if you've talked
to Carl since I fired him.
- Yes, I have.
- What did you talk about?
I asked him to find a way to stop Maureen
Kingsley from airing the story about Keith.
He said he would.
What did he say exactly?
As near as I can remember, something about
taking care of the evidence against Keith.
And you didn't think
that was worth mentioning to me?
I wasn't sure what he meant, David.
I'm trying to believe that when you deceived
me seven years ago it was a one-time thing.
This isn't making it any easier.
That is so unfair.
See you later.
You asked me to have someone check
on Jack Bauer, the guy at the breakfast.
- Yes. What did you find?
- Typical agency file: lots of gaps, classified.
Was one of those gaps
in the summer about two years ago?
- How'd you know?
- Later. We've got other things to deal with.
Move up to the other seat.
Now!
An average businessman
with a Microtech HALO in his car?
What'd you just say? Say it again.
Say it again! Or I'll break your other wrist!
You speak Serbian? What, are you
from Belgrade? You got family there?
You deserve everything
that's happening to you.
What do you know about
what's happening to me?
There's only one thing that
you need to know, Bauer. You will pay.
- You will pay.
- Who are you?
Who are you?!
What's the matter?
Is it your heart?
I got your medicine here. All I want is a little
information. Where's my wife and daughter?
Where is my family?! I'll give you
the medicine. Tell me where my family is!
Take the medicine.
No. No, no.
No. No!
Please. Please, my wife and family.
Please. Please. Where is
my wife and daughter? Please!
Don't die. Don't.
Hey, listen to me, OK?
It's not your fault. There's no way
you could have seen that coming.
How am I gonna find Teri and Kim?
The man he's meeting, Kevin Carroll,
maybe he knows something.
If he shows up - he's already late.
There's something very wrong about this
situation. This is not just about David Palmer.
This is personal. They're comin' after me.
What's the connection between
you and Palmer? Or you and Cofell?
I don't know!
Look, this is what I want you to do.
Dig deeper into Cofell's background.
Check out his extended family.
- Access my field-assignment files.
- They're classified.
I know. Find your way in.
Check out an assignment I had two years
ago. I was in Belgrade, then Kosovo.
It was called Operation Nightfall.
Then crosscheck everything that you find out
from that with Cofell's file. Understand?
- Yeah.
- OK. Do it now.
Come on, Jack. Come on.
Pull yourself together.
Come on.
Hey.
- What's this?
- Nothing. Act like you're interested.
Alberta probably thinks
we're helping Jack, right?
She can't prove it.
Why don't we just come clean,
tell her what's goin' on?
Jack says no.
Maybe you should stop thinking about
Jack and start thinking about yourself.
It's Jack's family, so it's Jack's call.
After what happened with Jamey,
we don't know who we can trust.
Come on. Green may be a hard-ass,
but I don't think she's dirty.
I agree, but she does things by the book.
If we tell her, she'll call Division, and before
you know it there'll be 30 people in the loop.
If just one of them is another Jamey...
Kim.
Kim, honey. Wake up.
You can't fall asleep. Come on.
Why?
Because if Dad comes,
we might have to move quickly. Come on.
- If we have to move, I'll move.
- Come on.
- Mom, I'm tired.
- I know. And you've been very brave.
You'll just have to stay that way a little
while longer. We can't miss our chance.
Are you OK?
Take it.
It's Dan's. He left it in the van.
It's loaded.
That's all I can do.
And I'm sorry about gettin' you into this.
Sorry about...
Sorry about everything.
What are we supposed to do?
Shoot our way out?
They're gonna kill us. This time they mean it.
Oh, God!
No. No.
Hey, hey, hey. Hey.
Kimberly, listen to me.
We're alive. Come here.
We're alive, and as long as we're alive,
I'm not giving up.
And neither are you.
Right?
Right.
I'm sorry I'm late.
I had a couple of calls to make.
Hello, Alan.
Or is it Kevin?
Where's my wife?
Check this out.
Wake up.
- Where's my wife?
- She's safe.
- And my daughter?
- Safe.
- Where?
- Jack...
Don't make this any harder than it has to be.
- I was about to say the same thing to you.
- But I'm the man with the gun.
If you kill me, how are you
gonna find your family?
Who said anything about killing?
I'm pretty good at withstanding pain.
But if you don't get there soon,
it may be too late.
Since you are no longer any use to us, Jack,
there's no reason to keep your family alive.
So we need to come to an agreement.
I'm listening.
You let me go, and I tell you where they are.
As soon as I know they're safe...
I'll let you go.
You've got my word on it.
Your word? That works for me!
We are talking about my family.
Do you understand me?
All I want is to get them back. So as soon
as I know they are safe, I will let you go.
That is the agreement.
If I say no?
We'll find out how good you really are
at withstanding some pain.
Drive the car.
Your half-hour's up.
Kill Bauer's wife and daughter.
Our contingency doesn't involve them.
Eli.
Tell the drivers to make
their final preparations.
Then kill the women.
I'm well aware that often these days you have
to be surrogate parents as well as teachers.
What can be done about that
at the federal level?
That's a good question, one Mike has
become an expert on. Haven't you, Mike?
I'm in charge of preparing
our position paper on education,
and I've reached some conclusions
I think you'll find interesting.
- Wonderful.
- Studies have proven that...
What's this about Ferragamo?
What difference does it make,
if you're protected?
What difference does it make?
That someone may be murdered?
- I didn't say anything about murder.
- You didn't deny it either.
OK, I deny it. Satisfied?
David, power has a price,
and that price has to be paid. Always.
Spare me the civics lesson.
I will not permit anyone to be harmed
in any way in the name of my candidacy.
You don't permit or not permit anything.
Don't you understand that by now?
These are very serious people, David.
They didn't put all this time and money
behind you to let things fall apart now.
They'll find someone
to do what they need done.
- I can't believe you used to work for me.
- I never worked for you.
You and I have always worked for them.
You, maybe.
Not me.
Information. How can I direct your call?
Yes. Give me the number
on a Dr George Ferragamo.
Just put me through immediately, please.
Dad isn't coming, is he?
I don't know, baby.
So I guess your time's up.
Don't worry, I'll make it fast.
No!
Whoever knew he came in to kill us
was expecting two shots.
That was the second shot.
What do we do now?
We hide the body.
Turn left here.
Where are we headed?
Just drive straight.
I'm taking you to your family.