- For God's sake, pull yourself together.
- You didn't have to kill her.
Yes, I did. Because you didn't
have the courage to kill her yourself.
Courage? To poison a girl
who did no harm to you at all?
This is my husband Navi.
This is Debbie's mother.
- Is she here?
We haven't seen her since yesterday.
Get in the car. Follow her.
Make sure she doesn't go to the police.
You're out of here.
Chloe.
Don't worry. Driscoll doesn't know
you were helping me.
She doesn't?
I'm the one that got you into this.
I'm not gonna sell you out.
Tell me what I need to know.
Richard, your father
was kidnapped by terrorists.
Our analysis shows that you're hiding
something that might help us find him.
There are people on the outside
looking for us. You cannot give up.
I have to do something while I still can.
This trial is gonna be a spectacle,
broadcast all over the world.
Designed to humiliate
and degrade this country.
There's a gas pipe.
- You've checked out the briefcase?
- It's fine.
I was afraid it might be damaged
in the train crash.
The case is very strong.
Get them out! Now!
Hurry! Open the door, now!
I know you.
She recognised me.
She has to be killed.
- Erin, I'm on site.
- Jack, stand down.
What are you talking about?
The president wants to take out
the building with a missile strike.
- With the secretary and his daughter inside?
- Yes.
I'm sorry. You're gonna have to clear the area.
Jack, don't go in there alone.
Jack, clear the area!
The building is going to be destroyed.
James Heller, you have been
brought before this court of law
to stand trial as a war criminal.
We will prove to the people of the world
that these crimes against humanity
are the direct result of the policies
initiated by you in your capacity.
Since the true extent of your evil legacy
is immeasurable,
we have done our best to document the acts
witnessed directly by the chosen followers.
Under your orders,
the death squads of America
continue their imperialist crusade
against the true believers.
How long till we're ready
to launch the missile?
Command and control
is locking on target now.
Mr President?
Erin Driscoll on line three.
Mr President, I'm calling to ask you
to abort the missile strike.
- Based on what?
- We are attempting a rescue operation.
I was told the marine strike force
was ten to 20 minutes away.
They are, sir. Jack Bauer went in by himself.
A terrorist group is moments from executing
the secretary of defense in front of the world.
- I cannot allow that to happen.
- I understand, sir.
But if Jack can effect a rescue before that?
In that case, I'll abort the missile strike,
but he's running out of time.
How long does he have, sir?
Seven minutes.
Try and make a sound
and I'll blow your head off.
This is a map of the complex. Where are
they holding the secretary of defense?
I'm either gonna kill you now or you're gonna
tell me where they're staging the trial.
Point. Now. Where's the secretary?
There is no place in this world
where your evil has not scoured
the sacred land of the true word.
Your imperialist legacy
has devoured the lives of the innocent.
-  Jack?
- Yeah?
- Keeler won't call off the missile strike.
- How much time do I have?
Less than six minutes.
Did you get a thermal read
on how many hostiles?
We estimate 16. Jack...
I'm not turning back, Erin.
Understood.
Good luck.
... the injustices he has committed.
Obedience is a master
who engages the world...
Stop this. Please.
Just stop this, please.
You've got to stop this.
My father hasn't done anything to hurt you.
He's an innocent man. Please.
- Your ignorant followers obey...
- He's innocent.
- Please.
- ... while the true believers wait patiently.
Please, listen to me.
Please. No, no, wait. Please.
You've got to stop it. Listen!
Audrey? Behind you.
Oh, my God. Jack.
- Are you all right? Did they hurt you?
- I'm OK. You've got to stop them.
- I will.
- Get my father first.
Go.
Take this.
Press the button on the handle.
You use that if you have to.
I'll be back for you. I promise.
Jack.
Finally, we hold you responsible
for blasphemy.
For desecrating holy lands and shrines.
And for spilling the blood of our brothers.
James Heller, your guilt on these charges
is not a matter of dispute.
I have here a full confession
which you have signed.
So now it is time for your sentence to be read
and for the execution of that sentence
to be carried out.
James Heller, before the eyes of God,
I sentence you to death.
Carried out immediately.
- Call off the missile.
- Abort. Please confirm.
He's doing it.
- There's one in the pipe. We gotta get Audrey.
- Down the hall.
- It's been aborted.
- Where are the marines?
They haven't crossed the perimeter.
I'll get an ETA.
We're clear.
She was here. We gotta go. Move, move!
Take the two shooters at your 11 o'clock.
You ready?
- Ready!
- Go!
Gimme a clip.
Jack!
It went off my vest.
It's all right. Keep firing.
I'm out!
I'm out too.
It's the marines. Stay down.
Mr Secretary, stay down.
Just stay down until this area's secure.
Jack!
- Stand down!
- Step back or I'll kill her.
- Put your gun down now.
- Step back! I'll kill her!
I will kill her!
Do it! Do it!
OK. Just relax. Audrey, stay calm.
Just relax.
This is over. You are surrounded.
You're right. But first you'll watch her die.
Yes, sir.
- The president sends his gratitude.
- I'm just glad you both are all right.
It's a while since you been in the field.
You haven't skipped a beat.
- Audrey and I owe you our lives.
- Thank you, sir.
I've arranged transportation back to CTU.
I'd like you and Audrey to be debriefed there.
As long as we don't lose time finding out who
these terrorists are and where they're from.
I'll set up a live feed with the office
in Washington. You won't miss a step.
- Those soldiers are waiting to take us to CTU.
- Thanks.
How is she?
A doctor needs to check out
these contusions and she's dehydrated.
- Thank you. We should go.
- Where?
I'm taking you and your father back to CTU.
When I was inside,
I recognised one of the men.
- Who?
- I don't know.
I can't place him,
but I know that I saw him before today.
They're gonna correlate a photo file
of the casualties. Then you can make your ID.
Excuse me. Bauer.
Agent Bauer, this is CTU.
I've got Paul Raines on the line.
He'd like to speak with his wife.
Is she with you?
Hold on one second.
It's Paul. He wants to speak with you.
Paul.
- Audrey. Are you OK?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Thank God.
- Where are you?
As soon as I heard about you and your father
I got on a plane.
- You're in LA?
- Yeah, I'm at CTU.
- Audrey?
- Yeah?
See you soon.
I'll see you soon.
We need to go.
You all right?
OK.
- Make sure Edgar gets this.
- Got it.
Find anything?
I'm trying to connect to the feed from the site.
Division's using up our bandwidth.
Tell them to multiplex.
We need to go through the debris.
Now Heller's safe,
we're no longer in first position.
Ms Driscoll?
- I took care of it.
- What's that?
A list of pass codes for the FBI fibre.
You can use their feed.
- How did you get that?
- I used to consult there. Still have friends.
I saw the load on the routing table
and knew we'd run into a traffic jam.
Good. Install it.
Start cataloguing whatever's there.
Anything that flags, promote it up to me.
Yeah.
You know, if you let me, Curtis,
I could help you a whole lot more.
I don't even know
why you have a problem with me.
Cos I'm ambitious?
OK, I'm ambitious. Aren't you?
I don't sleep with people
to get ahead in my career.
Neither do I. I slept with you
because I was attracted to you.
I still am.
Deal with it.
The White House has confirmed
that the interrupted video transmission
was caused by a raid mounted by the marines
and the Counter Terrorist Unit
who rescued secretary of defense
James Heller moments ago.
- Of course I'm watching.
-  Things look good.
God willing our good fortune
will continue for the rest of the day.
What are you talking about?
It's over, they found Omar.
The government stopped the trial.
- Yes, I know.
- Then how can you say this is good fortune?
Everything is ruined. You made me
kill someone I cared about over nothing.
No, not for nothing, Behrooz.
The trial was only our first step.
- I don't understand.
- There were certain things we kept from you.
- What things?
- Please. I'm busy.
You forced me to kill my girlfriend.
You owe me an explanation.
I don't owe you anything.
See who it is. See who it is.
It's Tariq.
Why is he here?
Tariq.
- Behrooz, you remember Tariq?
- Of course he does.
I just spoke with Marwan.
- He assured me everything is on schedule.
- Why are you here?
Your mother told Marwan
you took care of the American girl?
- Yeah.
- Then you need help getting rid of the body.
I don't need help. I can do it myself.
I'm sure you can,
but we can't afford any more mistakes.
Show Tariq where the body is.
Go.
OK, Agent Manning, this is the last
of the bodies. You should see them now.
All right. Got it. What's next?
Here's some of the terrorist gear
we collected out of the warehouse.
- Wait a second. Stop. Go back.
- You need me to retransmit?
No. In front of you,
gimme a shot of that briefcase.
- This?
- Yeah, can you open it?
- It's empty.
- Are there any identifying marks on it?
- Some kind of logo engraved near the lock.
- Let me see. Zoom in.
- Make sure that's on the next transport.
- Will do.
Sarah, I need a corporate logo search.
I may have a link between the crash
and the abduction. I'll send it now.
We'll pick this up later.
The man I recognised at the warehouse?
I want to make that ID.
As soon as you've been checked out
I'll get the photos.
- Excuse me, Ms Raines. This way, please.
- It's all right, go ahead.
I need you to handle this.
I need to trust you'll take care of it.
OK. Good. Excuse us.
I need your station. Have Driscoll
send me a pass code for the outside feed.
- OK.
- Thanks.
Does he know?
About you and Jack.
- How long have you known?
- Not until today.
I'm surprised I hadn't figured it out till now.
It's not what you think. Paul and I were over
before I started seeing Jack.
Paul doesn't think it's over. Last time I spoke
with him, he thought he had a second chance.
That's more about fixing his wounded pride
than fixing this relationship.
So, he doesn't know about it?
Not yet.
I'll take care of it.
Ms Raines? Right through here.
Yeah. No, not till I get back.
You have a thread connecting the bombing
to the abduction?
Yeah. About an hour ago.
NTSB reported that a passenger was killed.
But not as the result of the crash.
He was shot at close range.
- Who is he?
- Still trying to find out.
He had no ID and his face and prints
don't show up on any database.
But whoever killed him stole something
he had chained to his wrists.
I think it may have been this.
A witness on the train saw
a man with a briefcase handcuffed to him.
Take a look at the damage.
Could've been sustained during the crash.
We recovered this
where Heller was being held.
What are you telling me, the train bombing
was a cover for the theft of this briefcase?
- What was in it?
- It was empty.
But we traced the corporate logo
on the briefcase
- to McLennen-Forster.
- The defence contractor?
- Yeah.
- Have you contacted them?
Just got off the phone to their CEO.
He stonewalled.
Said before he disclosed anything we'd need
clearance from the Department of Defense.
The secretary should be able to get us
whatever clearances we need.
- Let's get a printout of all this.
- Yeah.
Our top story, only moments ago
a second broadcast
showing secretary of defense James Heller
was put on the Internet.
This image was captured from that broadcast.
The transmission then ceased.
At this time we have
no confirmed report on why...
The girl's mother went home.
Even if she calls the police it will be too late.
I heard the news in the car.
Everything was accomplished?
Yes. The trial was cut short,
but it served its purpose.
When they search the warehouse,
will they figure out what we're doing?
Doesn't matter.
It's too late for them to stop it.
If everything is working on schedule,
why do you look so troubled?
Where's Behrooz?
He went to bury the girl.
- But his car is still in the driveway.
- He didn't take it.
I don't understand.
He went with Tariq.
Tariq was here?
My God, he's going to kill my son.
My God.
He's going to kill our son.
Yes.
I told Marwan
that Behrooz took care of the girl.
Marwan must not have been satisfied.
He must have decided
that Behrooz was a liability.
How could you let this happen?
How could you let them kill our son?
- What could I do? What could I do?
- He's our son! Our flesh and blood.
- Dina, listen to me.
- How could you let them kill our son?
Behrooz stopped being our son
a long time ago.
- How can you say that?
- Because it's true.
Living here has changed him.
He's been like a stranger to us.
He proved it to me today,
that he no longer believes in our cause.
Maybe he never did.
Behrooz. Behrooz. Oh, my God.
Secretary Heller would like
to say a few words to you.
I'm incredibly privileged to have the finest
people in the world behind me - all of you.
It's gonna take a lot more
than a few words to express my feelings,
but for now,
from the bottom of my heart, thank you.
- Curtis Manning, head of tactical.
- Curtis.
An honour, sir.
Please, sit down.
Erin, my daughter and I owe you our lives.
Sounds like you had to make some
tough calls, but you made the right ones.
I'll see to it that you get full recognition
for a job exceptionally well done.
Thank you, sir.
Now, before we start the debriefing,
I'd like to visit with my son. Where is he?
- We're actually holding Richard here, sir.
- Why's that?
When we brought Richard in,
we gave him a polygraph.
It indicated that he was possibly
withholding information from us.
About my kidnapping?
We have wildly different political views,
but I can't believe that he was involved.
We don't think he had knowing participation.
We believe he shared knowledge
of your whereabouts with someone
and he refuses to divulge that information
or their identity.
And what are you doing about that?
We discussed a number of options.
You have to understand the circumstances.
Stop BS-ing me. What did you do to him?
A technique that's noninvasive -
sensory disorientation.
You subjected my son to SDT?
Yes, but it was stopped
the moment you were rescued.
- Jack, did you know about this?
- No, sir.
- I want to see my son now.
- Of course. Curtis.
Erin, I realise you've been
under pressure these past few hours,
but you'd better have cause for this.
Jack?
I appreciate you not involving the secretary
in our differences on this operation.
We both did what we thought was right.
I'd like to put the past behind us, Jack.
I could use your help.
What do you need?
I'd like you to function in Ronnie's position
as head of field ops until we avert this crisis.
- Whatever I can do to help.
- Let me make one thing clear.
Ronnie was under my command
and you will be too.
Understood.
The photos from the warehouse,
are they ready for Audrey?
I believe so. I'll have Edgar
port them to a work station.
OK. Thank you.
Dad.
They said you were OK. Audrey too.
Thank God.
I said some aawul things before. I was afraid
I'd never get a chance to apologise.
I said some pretty harsh things myself.
But no matter what was said, you're still
my son and I will always love you.
Me too, Dad.
They said they were using
some interrogation techniques.
They were totally out of line.
I'm gonna sue them blind.
I think it'll be a little more effective
if you let me deal with it.
I promise you,
if they were out of line, heads will roll.
What do you mean, "if"?
Why did they think you were
holding something back from them?
I don't know.
If you know something
that would shed some light...
You don't think I'd tell them
if I thought it was relevant?
- So there is something?
- Now you're giving me the third degree?
Son, do you have any idea
what your sister just went through?
If you know anything that would help us
find the people behind this, tell me now.
Dad.
I'm glad you're alive, I really am.
But I am not going to tell these people things
about my private life they don't need to know.
That you don't think they need to know.
Richard, these people
were trying to save our lives.
These people can't be trusted!
What they did to me is proof.
Agent Manning,
could you come in here, please?
Agent Manning, I am authorising you
to do whatever you feel is necessary
- to get this information out of my son.
- Dad.
I love you, son,
but I have a duty to my country.
You can't be serious.
Dad!
Bring the shovels from the back.
Come on. Help me.
They said it was OK to come in.
Hi, Paul.
My God, I was so worried.
- Are you hurt?
- Just cuts and scrapes. Nothing serious.
- Sure?
- Yeah, really. I'm OK, Paul.
They've OKed me for my debriefing.
On the flight over,
I couldn't stop thinking about us.
How, when we separated, we said
that we'd both take time
to figure out what we wanted. Now I know.
- Paul...
- I want us to be together again.
I'm ready to work at it.
I'll make our marriage the first priority.
Just give us a chance.
I'm sorry, Paul.
That's not what I want.
Audrey.
I am a fool for bringing this up. You can't
make decisions when you're in this state.
Paul.
I'm seeing someone.
Well, how long's this been going on?
Six months.
- Do you love him, or...
- Yes.
Audrey?
I'm sorry, excuse me.
I'll come back later.
No, um...
Paul, this is Jack Bauer.
- Nice to meet you.
- You're the one that saved Audrey's life.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
- Those photos are ready for you to look at.
- OK.
- Paul, we'll talk later?
- Yeah.
You all right?
Yeah.
You ready to go?
Not yet.
Now I am.
No. No.
You're certain you saw this guy before?
Positive, and I could tell
that he recognised me.
No. No.
- That's all of them.
- He must've gotten out before the rescue.
We should go through them again
to be sure.
I will, but there are only two men here that
aren't Middle Eastern and neither were him.
What?
- I remember where I saw him before.
- Where?
There was a Heritage Foundation dinner
about two months ago at the Hyatt.
- Do you remember his name?
- No, but maybe I can get the guest list.
Driscoll wants you in a conference call
that starts in a minute.
OK. Get hold of the Hyatt hotel
security department.
Access their archival surveillance.
Audrey'll give you a date.
Set a parameter, keep Driscoll informed.
Be right back.
It's hot.
You brought me here to kill me. Why?
Why are you doing this?
I did everything they told me to do.
- You know why.
- I took care of the girl. Marwan knows.
It's not Marwan who wants you dead.
Then who wants me dead?
Who?
Who wants me dead?
I want to know! Tell me!
Your father.
No! No!
It's not true! No! No!
Dad!
Please!
No!
Mr Reiss, I'm Erin Driscoll,
director of CTU, Los Angeles.
My colleagues Curtis Manning
and Sarah Gavin are present.
Also Jack Bauer,
advisor to Secretary Heller.
I hope you understand McLennen-Forster
couldn't give you details about that case
until we received permission from DOD.
Understood, Mr Reiss. May we begin?
What was your courier transporting?
It's a device we developed under the NRC's
emergency management programme.
It's a Dobson-type override.
What exactly does this override do?
It can remotely take control
of a nuclear power facility.
Under what circumstances
would the override be used?
The government wants
to control a plant's nuclear pile
in case of a disaster
necessitating evacuation.
A person with this program,
could they do the opposite?
Create a disaster at a plant, a meltdown?
Theoretically, but possession
of the override isn't enough.
- There are safeguards.
- What safeguards?
Anyone using the override
would have to hack into the reactor's firewall.
That would take massive computer power,
which NRC could see coming a mile away.
Is it possible NRC could miss this
- due to heavy traffic on the Internet?
- I don't follow.
Less than an hour ago millions of computers
were streaming the trial
of the secretary of defense.
Is it possible that this trial
was just some kind of a Trojan Horse
to disguise a massive attack
on a nuclear power plant's firewalls?
It might be possible.
How many nuclear plants
in this country would be vulnerable?
- All of them.
- How many is that?
At this time the United States
has 104 nuclear power plants online.
Assume they've used this override to take
over the plants. Get me NRC and find Heller.
Thank you.
- Set up a briefing.
Get me NRC. Pipe it through here.
I want all personnel
in the conference area.
Edgar, can you monitor
my allocation tables for a few minutes?
Sure.
-  Yes?
- It's me.
- You're on a secure line?
- Yes.
I'd have checked in sooner.
This was my first chance.
All right. Go on.
They found out about the override.
Visiontext Subtitles: Katherine Appleby
ENGLISH SDH