- Your wife survived the attack.
- Thank God.
I should never have given in.
I should have ordered back the motorcade.
The attack failed.
We have to assume they'll make good their
threat to use the Sentox on American soil.
Sorry. I made a mistake.
I didn't think I had any choice.
Charles. You didn't stand up to them.
- You saved my life.
- Well, you're welcome.
The country's lucky
to have men like you. I'm lucky.
Mrs. Logan.
Henderson set up the deal that allowed
the terrorists to gain control of the Sentox.
He left me for dead.
Henderson is our primary link.
You are gonna tell me now
how to find the rest of the gas.
Go ahead and do it, Jack.
Get it done. Shoot me.
- Oh, you son of a bitch!
- I shot her above the knee. She can still walk.
If you make me shoot her again,
she'll be in a wheelchair.
- Tell him what he wants to know.
- I can't.
I'm bringing Christopher Henderson into
CTU. I need an interrogation room prepped.
I don't care that you took my wallet.
I just need to get my key card back.
It's of no value to you,
it just lets me in this building.
You told me we were gonna take his cash
and a credit card.
That's how I'm getting us all this money.
A $20,000 line of credit right here.
Who's gonna pay you that kind of money?
- I have the key card.
- How long will it take you to reprogram it?
Five minutes.
Then we will be able to use it to access CTU.
Good.
Yes?
- I'm reprogramming the CTU key card now.
- Will it work?
I need to change the ID but preserve
McGill's executive entry privileges.
- It won't be a problem.
- Good.
Our couriers are delivering
the canisters to the targets.
- When are you launching the attacks?
- After you're done at CTU.
- I'm a few minutes out.
- Call me when you're there.
Understood.
We neutralised
the attack on the hospital.
Good. Do we have any idea
what the terrorists' next target might be?
We're working with state authorities to harden
security around the highest-value targets.
In other words, no. We're just sitting around
waiting for Bierko to hit us again.
We do have one promising lead, sir.
Jack Bauer was able to recapture the man
who escaped, Christopher Henderson.
Henderson was a defence contractor who
brokered the sale of the nerve gas to Bierko.
Is this the same Christopher Henderson
who worked at CTU?
He was head of field ops. Jack brought him
down on corruption charges.
And this Henderson knows
how to find Bierko?
We believe so. He's not cooperating. Jack's
bringing him in for further interrogation.
- Keep me posted on any progress.
- Yes, sir.
Mr. Buchanan. Tony Almeida's
been asking to see you down in the clinic.
Tell him I'll get to him as soon as I can.
And Ms Raines, Kim Bauer is here.
She's just clearing Security.
- Put her in the field ops office, please.
- Yes, ma'am.
What's Kim Bauer doing here?
- Jack asked me to call her.
Does she know?
Not yet.
Who's with her?
- I don't know, but I'll find out from Security.
- This is Bauer.
- Hey, it's me.
- Is Burke prepped for the interrogation?
- Yes.
Jack, Kim just arrived at CTU.
- What did you say to her?
- Nothing yet.
Good. I want her to hear it from me.
Jack, it might be easier for her if she knows
that you're alive before she sees you.
- When I first saw you... It-it's just...
- Yeah, I know.
I- I understand.
Look, when you talk to her,
explain that I couldn't tell her I was still alive
cos I was trying to protect her.
- Of course I will.
- Audrey, thank you.
Kim's at CTU right now.
You know, after you died, Chase left her.
She hit bottom. Did you know that?
It's only right now
she's putting her life back together.
Maybe you did know
but couldn't do anything about it.
- This doesn't concern you.
- I think it concerns me.
Miriam and I were there for Kim
when you weren't.
Whatever you may think of me,
Miriam and I love that girl.
Are you OK?
Both my parents died here.
- I swore I'd never come back to this place.
We can leave right now if you want.
Here, she's coming.
Kim.
- Hi.
This is Barry Landes.
Audrey Raines.
So, what it is? What did you have to tell me
that was so important?
- It would be better if we talked in private.
- You can say it in front of Barry.
- Kim, I really think...
- No, no. It's OK.
It's about your father.
What about my father?
He's alive.
Kim, he wanted to tell you
but he couldn't, in order to protect you.
Someone in the government
wanted your father dead,
so he staged his own death
and went underground.
He knew that you wouldn't be safe
if he told you that he was alive.
I didn't know either until this morning.
I thought maybe if I told you now before
you saw him it might be a little bit easier.
He's on his way in now to CTU.
Hello, Mike.
Mr. Vice President.
I thought you were at Salt Lake City today.
Hal cancelled his engagements
to be here, Mike.
We need all hands on deck
to deal with this situation.
- Of course, Mr. President.
- OK. So, what's on your mind, Hal?
Mr. President, when these terrorists attack
you're gonna need to maintain order.
And I submit to you the plan
you're implementing with CTU is inadequate.
Sir, it was drawn up after careful study
for an attack of just this magnitude.
CTU is already coordinating
with first responders.
Fine, and they should still do so.
But what I'm proposing
is something far more sweeping.
I believe it's warranted by the facts. Andrew.
To begin with,
I'm revising all of CTU's casualty estimates.
Based on the assumptions the terrorists
will hit all of these targets - hospitals, malls,
sporting arenas, transit hubs -
my low estimate is 400,000 casualties.
That's a considerable upward revision.
I'd like to know how you reached it.
You're free to talk to my working group.
There are a lot of people
who don't take this threat seriously enough.
I assure you we're taking it very seriously.
We have no agenda but to do so.
What's your recommendation?
We should think of a pre-emptive declaration
of martial law in the greater Los Angeles area.
Mr. President, martial law is appropriate
only as a last-ditch measure.
- Not as a pre-emptive one.
- Go on.
Every study we've done has shown
it would incite more unrest, not less.
- And you'd need approval from Congress.
- Which is why we won't call it martial law.
We're putting troops on the street
to try to keep people from killing each other.
The panic hasn't happened. Right now
the public isn't even aware of a threat.
You declare martial law,
you'll have to tell them.
- How long will it take to deploy the troops?
- I'm in touch with the Pentagon.
The National Guard is on stand-by
pending your decision.
I agree there's a case to be made,
but for God's sake, let's make it to Congress.
- We can declare an emergency...
- We don't have time.
Hal is right.
This attack could take place any minute.
If CTU can't find this man Bierko,
we're gonna get hit.
It would be smart
to have control of the streets.
- This is a mistake. You don't wanna do this.
- Get out.
I'll get immediate immunity if I talk. You
know it and I know it. I'm not gonna ask for it.
I'm not trying to protect myself.
I'm trying to protect this country.
- What?
- You don't wanna know what I know.
You get me to talk, I promise you
you'll just be opening Pandora's box.
Tell me. Let me judge that for myself.
That's what I thought.
- I'll set him up in Holding.
- Let me know when he's ready.
Jack.
Key card, please.
Well, all clear, sir.
Go ahead.
Yeah. OK, I will.
Curtis is on his way back from the hospital.
OK, good.
Audrey.
Did you speak to Kim?
What was her reaction?
She's a little confused. She's here with
someone. I think it might be her boyfriend.
His name is Barry Landes.
- Where is she?
- She's in the field ops office.
- OK, thanks.
- Yeah.
Hey.
I don't know what to say.
I don't know what you expect me to say.
You don't have to say anything.
Why didn't you just tell me you were alive?
I couldn't. If you knew I was alive
you would have been at risk.
- I had no choice.
- You could have chosen to trust her.
- I'll speak with my daughter alone.
- That's not a good idea.
- I don't care what you think.
- I'm sure you don't.
All that matters is you,
even if it affects those that love you.
Kim.
Barry, please let me speak to my dad.
- I'll be right outside.
- Yeah.
Don’t judge him.
He was there when no one else was.
The most painful thing
that I've ever been through
was having to walk away from you.
Even more painful than losing your mother.
But it was the only way to make sure
that you would be safe.
I buried you.
I know.
You know, there's something wrong
with people like you.
You can't hold on to anything.
Chase couldn't either. He tried for a while,
then he was gone, just like you.
And now you're back,
and I'm just supposed to...
I'm happy that you're alive. I am.
But I can't give you what you want right now.
OK. OK.
I understand that.
- I need you to know that I'm sorry and I...
- Please, just go.
Excuse me. Burke needs you in Holding.
I'll be there in a minute.
I've gotta go. Barry's got a conference.
We have a plane to catch.
Please, Kim.
I want you to stay just a little longer.
There's some things
that I still need to tell you.
Please.
I'll talk to Barry.
Fine.
I'll be right back.
- You called for me, Tony?
- Yeah.
- What's going on?
- That's what I wanted to ask you.
What do you mean?
What do you think I mean, Bill?
My wife was killed this morning
right in front of my eyes.
- Nobody here's told me who did it or why.
- The investigation's ongoing.
Come on, Bill.
I used to work here.
I know that's what you say to people
when you don't wanna tell them the truth.
The truth is you're not an agent any more.
What you're asking me is classified.
Tony, there's nothing you can do.
I know there's nothing I can do!
Look at me, for God's sake.
I just wanna know who did it.
For the sake of all the years I've given this
place, I think I deserve to know, don't you?
All I can tell you is...
Michelle's murder was part of a bigger plan
to supply terrorists with Sentox nerve gas.
Who was behind it?
Who's responsible, Bill?
The highest we've got is someone
you might know from when he worked here.
Christopher Henderson.
W- what?
Why?
We're working on it, Tony.
Don't let him get away with this, Bill.
- Don't you let him cut a deal.
- I won't.
What do we know
about the man who's with Kim?
He's registered with the state
as a clinical psychologist.
- She was his patient.
- I think so, yes.
He's ready.
Whatever he's not telling us is important.
He knows what's coming...
and he's willing to tolerate an inhuman
amount of pain. Open the door.
Dammit, Christopher.
I don't think you became a part of this
because of self-interest.
I believe you think what you're doing now
is the best thing for this country,
but it is not your choice to make.
That's good. Disarm your subject's resolve by
showing empathy and respect for his agenda.
This is not a joke.
Thousands of lives are at stake.
People that we promised to protect,
to make feel safe.
There is enough time for you to tell me what
I need to know to stop this insanity. Please.
I'm sorry, Jack.
I really am,
but I can't tell you what you wanna know.
Start it.
Mrs. Logan.
- Mrs. Logan, if I could have a minute?
- If this is about Aaron it doesn't concern you.
No, Mrs. Logan, it doesn't,
and I'm not here to discuss it.
- Then what is it?
- The country's facing a crisis.
The president needs you.
He... he needs me?
If you think the decision to let the attack
on the motorcade proceed was easy for him,
you're wrong.
I was with him
when he got down on his knees and prayed.
- He did?
- He loves you.
He didn't wanna lose you.
But with the... the lives of so many people
in jeopardy, he felt he had no choice.
We've known each other a long time. Stop
talking about what a positive influence I am
and tell me precisely what it is
you're trying to get me to do.
Vice President Gardner is advising your
husband declare martial law in Los Angeles
in preparation for the release of the nerve gas.
He wants to do it without Congressional
sanction or a timetable to lift it.
- He can’t just rewrite the law.
- Hal's got an agenda.
Well, he's wrong.
This'll make things far worse.
Mrs. Logan, all I know
is the president is listening to Hal Gardner,
and it will only help the country
to have him listening to you as well.
Hold off on deploying units seven to twelve
until we finalise our scenarios. What is it?
I noticed that one of the environmental
systems put out a trouble flag.
It's probably a circuit board change.
I logged on to the manifest
and there's nothing scheduled.
Carrie, I'm in the middle of coordinating
the first responders. I don't have time for this.
You don't have to snap at me.
I thought someone should check it out.
Then check it out.
Carrie!
Can you forgive me?
You acted like
the President of the United States.
Yes, I did.
But you wanted me to be your husband first.
I can't pretend that I didn't.
I still love you as much as I always did.
- Marty...
- Shh. Shh.
There'll be plenty of time for us later.
You have to get back to work.
The country needs you more than I do.
Hello?
Anybody working on the system?
Chloe.
Hi, Kim.
- You're still here.
- Yeah.
My father had to do something.
Do you know how long he'll be?
- No. Sorry.
- Chloe...
I'm kinda busy right now.
You knew my father was alive, didn't you?
For a year-and-a-half you've known.
Yeah.
- He trusted you.
- Because he had to. I helped stage his death.
- You don't have to make excuses.
- I'm not. Four people knew he was alive.
Two are dead, President Palmer and Michelle
Dessler. Tony Almeida's in serious condition.
Michelle's dead?
I'm only alive
because your dad found me in time.
I know this is hard for you and it's none of my
business, but you should cut him some slack.
What's going on, Bill?
Lynn...
What is it?
We just got a call from LAPD.
They found your sister's body
in her apartment.
She'd been shot.
What? I-I just talked to her.
I saw her today. That's impossible. She can't...
I'm sorry, Lynn.
The police ID'd her body.
My God.
If you need a phone to make
some personal calls or talk to the police...
Her boyfriend did this to her.
Tell me he's in custody.
- Is his name Dwayne Thompkins?
- Yeah.
He didn't do it. They found his body too.
Lynn, the police are trying
to make sense of something.
Do you know if either your sister or
her boyfriend were involved in dealing drugs
or had ties to organised crime?
She was a pretty serious user.
But organised crime? No way.
Why?
The killings were clearly
the work of a professional.
My God.
- Who's investigating? I have to talk to 'em.
- I can arrange a meeting.
No. They have to search the apartment,
see if my key card was there.
- What are you talking about?
- My CTU key card. She has it.
- What was she doing with your key card?
- It was stolen from me. Her boyfriend took it.
- Why didn't you report this?
- I am now. We don't have time to argue.
Call and see if anyone used it to breach
Security. It was taken about four hours ago.
Chloe, I'm in Holding with Lynn.
I need you to check the gate logs now.
- What am I looking for?
- If anyone used Lynn's key card to enter CTU.
- Isn't Lynn standing right next to you?
- Chloe, do it!
It's showing that his card was used less
than an hour ago at the executive entrance.
- He was already here.
- Lock down CTU now.
This is Chloe O'Brian.
Initiate a lockdown now.
Mr. Bauer, I'm sorry. I don't know what's
going on. He should be talking by now.
Dammit, Christopher. I don't wanna do this.
- Just talk to me.
- Can't.
I need to stabilise him in the clinic
before administering another dose.
This is Bauer.
We've been compromised. Someone used
a stolen key card to access CTU.
- Did you get an ID?
- Not yet.
They're still here. We're in lockdown.
I'm on my way. Get him to Medical.
Stabilise him. Don't let anyone near him.
- Did you get him?
- Still working on it. Exits are sealed.
Security are going room to room.
Give me a comm unit.
Is Kim still up in field ops?
- With Landes, yes.
- Get her here. I want a guard on her.
- I found the hostile. He's in third west.
- Could exit south or north.
Jack, take north. Mack's team will head south.
Copy that.
Pull up north and south angles.
There he is.
- Run his face through recognition software.
Where's Carrie?
I need her to check for intrusions.
She's checking on a warning signal
on a B socket.
Got it. Checking the grid.
You're gonna help me get outta here.
- He's in the north corridor.
- I wanna see what's keeping Carrie.
All units, the hostile's in the north corridor.
He's got one of our men.
- Enter your pass code.
- But it's a lockdown.
Just do it.
He's in the north hallway, sublevel B.
- Jack, do you read?
- On my way.
- Bill, he's in the stairwell.
- I don't think so, Jack.
- Davis said he checked sublevel B.
- Bill.
It's all clear.
No, he's doubled back.
He's using the stairs to get to the roof.
All right, Jack.
I'm sending units to the landings.
Let me know when you're ready to move.
Copy that.
Freeze!
Let me see your hands.
Slowly.
Drop the gun.
Now!
Hostile's down. He's dead.
It was the only shot I had.
Do you have an ID, Jack?
We got a bigger problem than that. He's got
a device on him. Looks like a relay switch.
- He's got a PDA. Oh, my God.
- What is it, Jack?
A schematic of CTU's ventilation system.
I think he tried to deploy nerve gas.
Order an evacuation.
Code six! Everybody out! Go! Go!
- I have Kim with me.
- Stay with her.
Make sure Burke gets Henderson outta here
as fast as he can.
- I'm on it. Don't move. I'll be right back.
- O'Brian.
- Chloe, what's going on?
- Edgar, get out of the building now.
Carrie.
We have to get out of the building now.
Just hurry.
What's wrong with those people?
Oh, my God.
- The gas is coming in.
- The ducts run from the outside in.
- Outside in? What does that mean?
- They reach the building core last.
Lock the outer doors.
Which rooms can we seal?
- I'm working on it!
- Burke, I need you to stand by.
I'll let you know
where you can move Henderson.
- Chloe, what rooms can you lock down?
- Hold on!
The situation room,
the upper offices and clinic isolation.
- Go, people!
- Kim, everybody, in the situation room. Now.
Burke, you can move Henderson
to the clinic isolation. Seal it off for bio-air.
Get into the situation room now. Move!
Chloe, seal it. Seal all the rooms.
Open the door!
You have to let me in! Open the door.
- Let her in.
- We can't break the seal. Find another exit.
Hurry! Go!
- Chloe, are the rest of the rooms sealed?
- Yes, it's done.
Everybody, stay calm.
There's nothing we can do for her now.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Chloe.