Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net
Mr President, my analysts believe Assad's
organisation cannot survive without him,
and once he's dead, the attacks will stop.
CTU needs to eliminate Assad.
That's all there is to it.
God knows we're paying
a steep enough price to get him.
We were contacted four days ago
by a man named Fayed.
He offered to give us Assad's location for a
list of demands. One of them was Jack Bauer.
We're asking you to sacrifice yourself
so we can eliminate Assad.
The reason why I fought to stay alive in China
was because I didn't want to die for nothing.
Today... I can die for something.
You kept your end of the deal, I'll keep mine.
I have a transponder at Assad's location.
33-58-11 north latitude.
118-21-40 west longitude.
Have Bowen mobilise the helicopters.
I'll tell the president we're a go.
CTU is about to kill the wrong man.
Assad isn't behind these attacks.
He's come here to stop them.
He's come here... to stop... me.
Get out of my house.
- This kid's father's a terrorist.
- He's no more of a terrorist than you or me.
- Tell me what happened.
- The FBI. They took my father.
- Are you sure the FBI didn't find the package?
- Yes. It's well hidden.
You need to deliver it soon.
(flatline)
(speaks Arabic language)
Get in there! Find him!
Wait.
- We have to go.
- Not until we find Bauer.
We're not here to kill one American,
we're here to kill thousands.
But he knows the truth.
It doesn't matter.
By the time Bauer tells anyone,
it will be too late.
Assad will be dead and we'll
be free to finish what we started.
Fayed, listen to me. If we don't leave now,
we'll jeopardise the mission.
All right.
(man shouts in Arabic language)
- This our target?
- This is where Fayed says Assad is now.
- Heat signature?
- They're shielded.
We can't tell how many are in there.
If there's anyone in there at all.
Fayed lied to us.
And Jack bought the farm for nothing.
Shut up, Milo.
What's her problem?
Jack's a friend of hers.
It hurt her that he died that way.
You might want to attenuate your
thoughtless remarks once in a while.
Two Cobra attack helicopters
are being launched.
They'll hit Assad's location in 15 minutes.
- Excuse me, sir.
- What is it?
Jack Bauer's calling in. Line two.
Jack, it's Bill. Thank God you're alive.
What happened?
Listen. We do not have a lot of time.
- I need you to call off the air strike.
- Why?
You're going after the wrong man.
Assad is not responsible for the bombings.
- Where did you get this information?
- I'll explain when you call it off.
I don't have the power
to rescind a presidential order, Jack.
- Put me through to the president. I'll tell him.
- Jack...
Bill, trust me. Just put me through
to the White House.
All right. Stay on the line.
(woman) Bill Buchanan
for the president. Priority three.
- Put him through.
- Yes, sir.
- Bill?
- (Bill) There's new information
regarding the air strike on Assad.
I'm on the line with Jack Bauer.
He escaped from Fayed.
What? How?
I'm not sure, but he's requesting
that we abort the air strike against Assad.
- For what possible reason, Bill?
- He says Assad is not behind the attacks.
Bill, that's insane.
What is Jack basing this on?
He wants to talk directly to the president.
- Put him on.
- (Bill) You're on the line, Jack.
- Mr President.
- Jack...
We don't have a lot of time.
Did Bill explain about Assad?
Yes, he has,
but we're all sceptical here.
- What's Assad doing in this country?
- Trying to stop them, trying to stop Fayed.
So you're saying that Fayed
is carrying out these bombings?
Yes, sir. Fayed admitted to me
that Assad is planning to renounce terrorism.
He's trying to mainstream his organisation,
bring them into politics.
Fayed wants to stop that.
Fayed is behind these attacks.
Jack, this is inconsistent with
20 years of terrorism on Assad's part.
His organisation has waged
nonstop war against the West.
He's responsible for hundreds of deaths.
I am aware of Assad's history,
and I am still telling you
that there is sufficient cause
to call off this strike.
What if we change to a ground assault?
Sir, we cannot afford a ground assault.
We have to take him out
while we've got the chance.
Mr President, if Jack is right,
it's a risk we have to take.
Jack has been in
a Chinese prison for 20 months.
His ability to assess this situation
is highly questionable.
- I believe he's being played.
- I know what I heard. I am not being played.
With all deference to Mr Bauer,
I think Karen is right.
Mr President, if you wanna stop
these attacks, you need to stop Fayed.
To do that, you need to capture Assad
and find out what he knows.
Sir, he might be the only hope you have.
Mr President, I know your history
with Mr Bauer runs deep,
but don't let that impact yourjudgment here.
We have the opportunity
to eliminate Assad. We have to take it.
I want real-time progress
on that air strike.
- I'm sending a video uplink.
- Mr President, don't do this.
Jack, I am sorry.
I am.
Give me your location.
I'll send a unit.
Killing Assad is a mistake. Right now,
he's your only chance of finding Fayed.
It's the president's call.
We'll do all we can when you get back.
- That'll be too late.
- Jack, tell me where you are.
Don't put me on hold again.
Just give me the agent in charge.
I will wait on the line.
Dammit. She says they'll
call me back on this number.
- Where are they holding my father?
- They cannot release that information.
(phone rings)
- Hello.
- (Fayed) You have the package?
I'm at my friend's. They're helping me
find out where the FBI took my father.
- You're not free to talk?
- No.
Just tell me if you have the package.
Not yet, but I'll have it soon.
There are other people
I could have chosen for this task,
but I chose you.
Now get out of there. Retrieve the package.
Call me when you have it.
Yes. I will.
I have to go back to my house.
I'm meeting my uncle.
- Do you think that's wise?
- Are you sure?
- (Scott) Ahmed, stay here.
- I'll be fine. Don't worry.
- Thank you for everything. Thank you.
- OK. Take care.
Don't worry. His family's
taking care of him now.
Ahmed. Hold on.
Listen, I'm sorry. I...
I can't believe this is happening.
It's like the whole world has gone crazy.
It's been crazy for a long time.
We just haven't been paying attention.
Yeah, well, we are now.
You know what, you should take this.
I got this at a fair in Oregon.
It's supposed to mean good luck.
Thanks, but I... can't take it.
Why?
You might need it yourself someday.
- (man) Zebra One lead is cleared hot.
- (man #2) Zebra One is cleared hot.
(man) Flight is cleared
for immediate engagement.
- Buchanan.
- (woman) Please hold for Karen Hayes.
- Bill?
- Yes, Karen?
You're also online with the president.
We're monitoring the Cobras.
- How soon before they hit?
- (woman) Five minutes.
How soon after the strike can we expect
confirmation that Assad is dead?
Curtis will lead a team into the target zone.
He'll do a point-by-point grid search.
Thank you.
(man)... request heading change.
One-five-zero.
(man) Zebra One. Receiving southwest.
3 minutes and 50 seconds to lock on target.
(thudding)
(muffled speech)
(man) Changing course to one-eight-three
for southerly approach to target.
(man #2) Roger, Zebra One.
One-eight-three.
(man) Lock in 2 minutes and 30 seconds.
Drop the coffee.
Don't move. Don't even think about it.
Where is Assad?
- Where is Assad?!
- Put down your weapon.
- My name is Jack Bauer.
- I know.
This house has been targeted for a strike.
I need to get you and your men out.
Check the street.
I came here alone.
I know about Fayed.
- I know you're here to stop him.
- There's no one outside.
Fayed has set you up. He provided CTU
with the coordinates to this house.
- Kill him, Assad.
- In a few minutes, we'll all be dead.
- Don't listen to him. It's a trap.
- There's a transponder in this house.
- US military is using it to pinpoint the strike.
- There is no transponder here.
We've searched the entire house.
One of your men must have it on them.
That's the only possible explanation.
One of your men is working for Fayed.
Have them empty their pockets.
- Assad, don't listen to him. He's lying.
- Dammit, I am telling you the truth.
Why else would I be here? If I wanted
to kill you, I'd have come in shooting.
Have your men empty their pockets!
I'm trying to save your life.
Wait.
- Empty your pockets.
- But...
I said empty your pockets.
Behind you!
Search him.
- You betrayed us.
- No.
- You're the one who betrayed his people.
- Assad, we need to leave now.
If you are telling the truth,
you will not need that gun.
(man) Go, Assad. You need to leave.
We'll secure the files.
(Assad) Hurry up.
Move! Move!
Are you all right? Get him up.
Move.
Mr President, the target has been destroyed.
We are an advocacy group. These people
are all volunteers. They're very good people.
I'm sure. We're assembling a database of
names to crosscheck against our watch list.
- (woman) Excuse me, Sandra. The FBI's here.
- FBI?
They're asking for access
to our personnel records.
(man) We take pride in being good citizens,
and will cooperate to stop the attacks.
May I see your warrant, gentlemen?
I'm Mr Al-Rezani's attorney.
- I also represent this organisation.
- We know who you are, ma'am.
And I'm afraid we don't have a warrant.
I'm afraid we can't
turn over our personnel records.
That information is private,
and privacy is protected by law.
I understand, but in light
of what's happening in the country,
we don't think it's unreasonable
to ask for cooperation.
You're in the wrong place.
There are no terrorists here.
So unless you have a warrant,
I'm gonna have to ask you to leave.
Please don't make me ask twice.
All right, ma'am.
- This is getting out of hand.
- Maybe we should give them what they want.
- You're serious?
- We've nothing to hide.
No, but we have something to protect -
the privacy of everyone
who's ever worked here.
Maybe we have to sacrifice privacy.
The country's under attack.
We cannot pretend it isn't.
- Who are you calling?
- Yes, it's Sandra Palmer.
I'd like to speak with my brother.
We're sweeping the zone.
We've recovered four bodies.
Forensics is running field ID.
They're sending data to CTU.
- Well, let's hope one of them is Assad.
- (phone beeps)
- Yes?
- (woman) The president's sister on the line.
- He'll wanna call her back.
- She says it's urgent.
- I'll take it.
- Mr President, we're...
Tom, it's OK.
Let me have the room, please.
- What's going on, Sandra?
- I'm sorry, but I think you need to know.
The FBI was just here, and they
wanted access to the IAA's personnel records.
- Did they say why?
- Some excuse about expanding a database.
Listen, Sandra. I...
You know I have to do whatever I can
to stop these attacks, right?
Yes.
That includes giving law enforcement
the authority to follow up every single lead.
That's my point.
They weren't following any lead.
They were invading a group of people's
privacy based on their religion.
Look, Wayne, you know
I'm not some idealistic flag burner,
and I understand you're going through
a complicated situation,
but once you start ethnic profiling,
it's a slippery slope.
- I'll look into it.
- Start with Tom Lennox.
- This has his name written all over it.
- Don't start in on Tom.
He treats the Constitution
like a list of suggestions.
He's laying the framework for a crackdown,
and civil protections be damned.
Let's be honest,
you don't like Tom and you never have.
Neither did David.
(phone beeps)
- Yes?
- (woman) Bill Buchanan's on the line.
One moment. Sandra, I gotta go.
Wayne, look,
I'm sorry to put this on you, OK?
I... I just wouldn't have called
if I didn't think it was important.
I understand.
- You take care of yourself, OK?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah. I love you too.
- I hope I got through to him.
- You made a good case. He'll listen.
Thanks.
- For what?
- For making that call.
And for not letting me
lose sight of what we're fighting for.
- (Palmer) Go ahead.
- We completed our sweep of the zone.
- Four bodies. None of them is Assad.
- What?
- (Karen) Are you sure?
- We're checking, but I think Assad is alive.
- How did we miss him?!
- Someone must have warned him.
Or the intel from Fayed was bad,
and Assad was never there to begin with.
Irrelevant. What matters
is that Assad is out there.
We're sealing a ten-block perimeter
around the area. Assad may be in the vicinity.
All right, Bill.
We put everything we had into that strike.
We thought if we could cut off the head
we could stop these attacks, and now...
Tom, what do you think
Assad's next move is gonna be?
Likely, there will be more attacks,
but respond he will, guaranteed.
- (Fayed) Ahmed will have the package soon.
- Good.
- Is he ready?
- Yes. He is waiting for you.
(speaks Arabic language)
That's not necessary.
I will not fail you.
I don't question your devotion, Nasir.
When the moment approaches,
even the most devout can experience fear.
Look at me.
By overcoming your fear,
you prove your worth.
I am proud to have
known you in this life, Nasir.
Your family will learn about your sacrifice.
(man) All right. One more load.
Let's go.
Put him here.
He's unconscious.
CTU's gonna realise you weren't killed.
They'll widen their search grid.
- We can't stay here much longer.
- He knows where Fayed is.
I only need a few minutes.
Fayed told me that you wanted to disarm. You
were gonna start negotiations. Is that true?
Most of my people and the governments
that support us agreed to a cease-fire.
- Fayed wants to sabotage it?
- Yes.
Once Fayed is eliminated,
everyone will fall into line
and I can go public with my proposal.
But finding Fayed
is the key to everything.
I'll be right back.
Buchanan.
I know why Assad wasn't in the building
when the missile hit. I need to show you.
This is an aerial frame enhancement of the
building seconds before it was destroyed.
Jack rescued Assad.
OK, OK.
This makes sense...
from Jack's perspective,
if Assad is trying to stop the bombing.
But President Palmer and your wife -
I mean, Karen Hayes - think he's wrong.
So what am I supposed to do with this?
- Who else has seen it?
- Nobody but me.
OK. Let's keep it that way for now.
Jack didn't save Assad
out of compassion.
- He's gonna use him to find Fayed.
- We should be looking for Fayed too.
Right.
Filter the chatter stream,
see if anything sources out on Fayed.
- OK.
- Good work.
We have a car.
If we're gonna find Fayed in time,
we have to involve CTU.
The people who tried to kill me
and killed my men?
- They have resources you don't.
- They will question me for days.
Fayed worked under me.
I know how he thinks, and I will find him,
but I will do it on my terms.
- Where is Fayed?
- I do not know.
- Where is he?!
- I was just ordered to plant the transponder.
- Where is Fayed?
- I do not know.
Please stop.
Please.
Why did you stop?
I can see it in his eyes.
He's not gonna tell us anything.
Where is Fayed?
I know where some of his men will be.
I heard Fayed giving instructions to go there.
Where?
- Figueroa and Sixth.
- When?
After you were killed.
- You've told me everything?
- Yes.
I swear it.
I believe you.
I understand...
how you felt you were doing the right thing.
I admire your conviction,
but you have taken the wrong path.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
My men are dead. I can find Fayed.
But I cannot stop him by myself.
I don't know how to do this any more.
You'll remember.
- (phone rings)
- Hello?
You'd better come out here.
The FBI is back. They have a warrant.
Who is the applicant for this?
I wanna see the affidavit.
The papers are on file with a district court.
We have a legally executed warrant.
Either you hand over the files,
or we take them. It's your choice.
This is an administrative warrant.
It's not valid in this situation.
That's your opinion.
They're in the media room.
I'll show you.
I need to use your computer.
Malek, I need copies
of all of our personnel files.
OK. No problem.
(computer beeps)
- What is it?
- I can't find the files.
Are you certain? Try again.
- They're not here.
- What do you mean?
- They're not where they're supposed to be.
- They've been erased.
Don't try to recall them.
I used the shredding program.
- Sandra, what are you doing?
- Check it.
She's telling the truth.
You're under arrest. Obstructing
official business, destroying evidence.
- Take Mr Al-Rezani into custody.
- Wait. He has nothing to do with this.
- That's the judge's call.
- But I'm telling you, he's not involved.
Are you sure about this?
- I told you, she gets no special treatment.
- I know, but she's the president's sister.
We have orders handed down,
and we're gonna follow them.
Impound every work station
and hard drive in this office.
Think I forgot about you, huh?
This is for everyone
you bastards killed today.
How do you like it, huh?
Get up. Get up!
You're dead, do you hear me? You're dead.
Please. Don't. Please. Don't.
(shouts in Arabic language)
Ahmed.
What happened?
- I'm gonna call an ambulance.
- We're not calling anybody.
- Ahmed...
- I can't go to the hospital.
- You're hurt. I'm gonna call 911.
- (cocks gun)
You shouldn't have come here, Scott.
Look, I don't wanna hurt you,
but I will unless you do exactly what I say.
Ahmed... we're friends.
What friends?
You can't even pronounce my name.
It's not Ahmed, it's Ach-med.
This is the location Omar gave us.
Over there.
Two men in suits, one carrying a briefcase.
These are Fayed's men.
The man in front
is wearing an explosive vest.
He's setting up another strike.
Go.
They're going in the subway.
(Assad) The detonator is in his right hand.
- They can't get on that train.
- Only the bomber is getting on.
The other man is the handler.
He'll see the bomber off, then he'll leave.
The handler will lead us to Fayed.
You follow the handler.
I'm going after the bomber.
(dials phone)
(phone rings)
- Go ahead.
- He's on a train.
It will reach Union Station
in five minutes.
- When it pulls in, he'll martyr himself.
- The car is at the arranged place. Take it.
Go to Union Station.
Call me when it's done.
Understood.
Thank you.
Ticket.
Ticket, please.
- Sir, do you have a ticket?
- My name is Jack Bauer. I am a federal agent.
You have a terrorist on this train with a bomb.
I need you to walk away.
If he notices anything unusual,
he will detonate his bomb. Now move away.
(shouting / screaming)
(man) It's a bomb!
Allahu Akbar!
(woman) As the wave of violence continues...
(phone rings)
- Talk.
- Fayed, something went wrong.
I'm here at Union Station,
but there's no explosion.
And there's a cloud of smoke
four blocks west from here.
Whatever the case, it doesn't matter.
Our other attacks were successful.
Once again, the streets
are flowing with blood.
Three simultaneous bombings.
One in a shopping mall, another in a hotel.
- Casualties are high.
- What about the third one?
I'll call you back.
It was here. On the Metro Red Line.
It appears to be a suicide bomber.
May be some good news. Aside from
the bomber, no one else was killed.
- How the hell could that happen?
- A passenger ejected the bomber.
The passenger
identified himself as Jack Bauer.
If Jack was on that train, he'll have been
caught on camera. I want visual confirmation.
- Yes, sir.
- Sir, you need to hear this.
It's a cellphone call
red-tagged from the NSA software.
Fayed, something went wrong.
I'm here at Union Station...
We need to contact the White House.
(man on TV) The car bomb
was detonated by remote control,
sending bodies hurling out of windows
from the 20th floor...
Mr President, if it's any consolation,
these attacks were planned
in advance of the raid on Assad.
Tom, all that means is
there will be more attacks.
We're in a full-blown war,
and we have no way to fight back.
Excuse me. Mr President.
CTU just called.
They intercepted a cellphone call
between Fayed and one of the men
behind today's bombings.
Fayed?
Are they sure?
Yes, sir.
Fayed is the one
behind these attacks, not Assad.
Sir, I promoted the strike against Assad.
But I approved it, Karen.
We were all in agreement.
So Jack was right.
He was right all along and I...
This is gonna get much worse.
(ringing tone)
(phone rings)
- Yeah.
- What happened?
Later. Are you following the handler?
Yes. I'm in the car. We're on Alameda,
two blocks from Union Station.
Copy that. I'll find you. Stay with the handler.
He's our only connection to Fayed.
Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net