Five power plants are ready to melt down.
All I care about is making sure
that doesn't happen.
Your name is on a lease on a building in
Chatsworth that was used to plan the attack.
- That makes you a prime suspect.
I don't know about that building.
I don't believe you.
Jack, please don't.
I don't know the specific building
you're talking about. I can find out.
How?
My corporate records
are stored on my laptop.
Here it is. It's Harris Barnes.
Interpol traced the name and listed
foreign nationals who have used it.
- Who used it most recently?
- A man named Habib Marwan.
- We need to find him.
- I think we have.
You OK?
- Yeah.
I overheard a phone conversation.
We have less than 15 minutes.
Have your men secure the floor.
Curtis and I are going after the override.
Stay down!
Stay down.
Marwan is impersonating a CTU officer.
I repeat, the suspect
is impersonating a CTU officer.
Edgar! Line one.
Curtis has the override.
-  The override logged in?
- Yes.
Good. Send it to channel 11. Hurry up.
They're starting to respond.
- It's working, Edgar.
- Yes! Yes!
The temperature is dropping
in all remaining power plants.
Congratulations, Edgar.
Ms Driscoll? It's about Maya.
You'd better go down to the clinic right away.
Maya?
Oh! Oh!
Oh, baby!
No!
-  I got new intel.
- What?
The man you're looking for,
Habib Marwan, works for McLennan-Forster.
But they made the override.
He's working under the alias Harris Barnes.
They had no reason to suspect.
He positioned himself inside the company
so he could use their technology.
Tell 'em to freeze Marwan's personal files.
I did. You want me
to send a comm team over?
- No, we're closer. Jack or I'll go.
- Sure.
Marwan was in the building
within the last 15 minutes.
I want perimeters here,
roadblocks in every direction.
- Done.
- Jack. I just got off with CTU.
Marwan worked for McLennan-Forster
under an alias, Harris Barnes.
- I told CTU we'd check it out.
- OK.
Take Paul and Audrey back to CTU.
I'll be on my cell. Castle'll stay in charge here.
If he's in the area,
our teams will pick him up.
- Curtis will take you back to CTU.
- What about you?
- I have to go to McLennan-Forster.
- Why there?
Turns out the man
we're looking for works there.
- Need to get into their computer system?
- Yeah.
OK. I'll go with you.
- Why?
- My company sold them their IT system.
I designed the database.
It's encoded with military security.
McLennan-Forster has personnel
that can get into his files.
Yeah, well, I can get you in back doors
those people don't even know about.
Fine. You go with me.
Audrey, I want you to stay with Curtis.
I'll be on my cell.
Let's go.
Stop.
Goodbye, baby girl.
OK. I'll let everyone here know.
Yeah, thanks, Nat.
Let everyone know what?
Driscoll's daughter
committed suicide in our clinic.
- How did she do that?
- She slit her wrists.
- Doesn't make sense. She was watched.
- I don't know, Edgar. I wasn't there.
I was just thinking out loud.
You don't have to be so hostile.
Excuse me, Mr Secretary.
Where's Driscoll?
The president's about to come on.
- Something terrible just happened, sir.
- What's that?
Ms Driscoll's daughter Maya committed
suicide in our clinic 15 minutes ago.
Apparently the doctor walked in and she...
Erin.
Sarah just told me. I am so sorry.
Thank you, sir.
- Go back to the floor, Sarah.
- Yes, ma'am.
Erin, you do not need to be here.
Where should I be, sir?
We're still in crisis mode.
Habib Marwan is still out there, and we've no
idea how many other cells he might activate.
- For God's sake, Erin...
- Our systems are in a transition state
that require my constant attention.
I'm not in denial about
my daughter's death, nor am I in shock.
I can perform my duties until
you find a suitable replacement for me.
Ms Driscoll?
The president's coming on now.
Thank you, William.
Jim? Erin?
First, I want to express my deep gratitude
for what you've accomplished so far today.
Wresting back control of the override
has saved thousands of American lives.
And the latest NRC report is that the San
Gabriel Island meltdown is under control.
That's great news.
But has your staff informed you
that we still have a few
problems to deal with?
Yes, and that's why I'm calling you.
The man responsible
for today's attack is still at large.
Yes, sir, he is. His name is Habib Marwan.
He's been a long-term employee
of a major defence contractor.
Yes, I heard. McLennan-Forster.
This Habib Marwan...
Do you believe melting down the reactors
was his endgame, or something else?
As long as he's out there,
we have to assume it's not over.
Erin, exactly where are we
on apprehending this man?
All our resources are being
deployed to that end right now.
I'll have more information
once I've been briefed by my staff.
But we know Marwan's in Los Angeles,
and we will find him.
As Harris Barnes, Marwan worked at
McLennan-Forster for two years as engineer.
His most recent project
was design and development of the override.
- Before that?
- Here's the timeline we pieced together.
He went to graduate school in England,
worked for a company outside London.
It's not clear whether
he was radicalised there or before.
The one thing we know is that
from the day he arrived in the US,
everything he did was about today.
What were his other duties?
We don't know yet.
We're taking a first pass at his records.
I'm looking into the possibility that he used
McLennan-Forster to recruit sleeper cells.
That brings up another issue. We have over
80%/ of field personnel looking for Marwan.
I'm just wondering if we shouldn't divert
part of that to try to root out these other cells.
- Erin?
- I'm sorry. What was the question?
Do you think we should
reduce the field load on Marwan?
How about we take some people off Marwan,
but still keep a floor of 60%/ looking for him?
Would that work?
Yes. That would work.
OK.
- I want you to relocate personnel.
- Based on what?
People who've come in
the last six hours work on Marwan.
- I want alert people on him.
- Are we gonna ignore what just happened?
What do you mean?
- Erin.
She shouldn't be running this place.
Her daughter died a few minutes ago.
Give her time.
Time? Edgar, since when
did we have the luxury of time?
- She knows what's at stake here.
- You're right.
We don't have time. We have work to do.
It does not include deciding Erin's fate.
- I think we have to tell Secretary Heller.
- No, we don't. Not yet. Let's get back on it.
-  Hey. Where are you?
- Curtis and I just arrived at CTU.
Listen, get a security detail,
go back to the hotel and get some rest.
Jack, I can't leave.
My father needs my help.
- Are you at McLennan-Forster yet?
- Almost.
Jack, can you make me a promise?
- What?
- Take care of Paul.
He's not like you.
Please, Jack, promise me
that you will look after him.
- Yeah, I will.
- Thank you.
- Yeah, OK. I'll talk to you later.
- All right. Bye.
Look, uh...
I don't resent you.
Well, I wouldn't blame you if you did.
No, uh...
You didn't steal my wife.
We were separated. That's fair.
But I'm not gonna let you take her from me.
I don't think that's really up to you.
- Or me.
- No, maybe it isn't.
But she still has feelings for me,
I can hear it in her voice.
I'll fight to keep those feelings alive.
Well, Paul, you're gonna
have to do what you gotta do.
None of our field agents at the Rockland
building have picked up a thread on Marwan.
It looks like he might have escaped.
So I think we have to assume
he's going to activate these sleeper cells.
I agree. He'll most likely
launch a strike right away,
create fear that we're still vulnerable.
You'll have to excuse me,
I'm not feeling very well.
Erin!
Sit down. You all right?
-  Clinic.
- Get me medical. Erin needs assistance.
No, I'm fine. I don't need anybody.
I just got a little
light-headed for a second there.
- Ms Driscoll...
- I don't need you here.
I was dizzy, but... I feel better.
Take a break. Get something to eat.
Take Ms Driscoll and get her some food.
I can handle the situation here
while you rest. Come on.
All right. It's probably a good idea.
She's gonna need to be relieved of duty.
Contact Division. Alert them to the situation
and tell them to send someone.
I ran this office for two years.
I could take over for Erin
on a provisional basis.
Forget for the moment
that you technically don't even work here.
You've been away a while.
You're not fluent with the new systems.
With all due respect, sir,
you don't need a programmer.
You need a decision maker
who can stack up protocols.
And you can do that?
Yes, sir. I can.
Fine. Effective immediately,
you're the interim director
of CTU Los Angeles under my authority.
I still want to contact District, have them
send someone on a more permanent basis.
I understand, sir.
Do you have the abstract
on McLennan-Forster?
One second. I'm finishing it now.
All right. McLennan-Forster was a principal
contractor in the design of the override.
And Marwan, under the alias of Harris Barnes,
had full security access on that project.
You ran FBI checks on the others involved?
Yes. They came up clean.
We're dealing with a terrorist who had
inside access to a defence contractor.
Actually, more than that. McLennan-Forster,
in addition to weapons manufacture,
trains their clients to use those weapons.
- International clients?
- Yes.
Several countries in the Balkans,
Asia, and the Middle East.
This is a messy situation.
When Jack gets to McLennan-Forster,
he has to get into company records
and find out who Marwan dealt with.
It's not gonna be that easy.
This reflects on them. They'll be reluctant
to give incriminating information.
Even if Marwan were the only guilty party.
Mr McLennan,
we need to talk before CTU gets here.
- What's the problem?
- It was more than a coincidence
that one of our products, the override, was
stolen and used in today's terrorist attack.
What do you mean,
"more than a coincidence"?
The entire operation,
from Secretary Heller's kidnapping
to the meltdown of San Gabriel Island,
was organised by one of our own employees.
- What are you talking about?
- One of our engineers,
who we now know is a terrorist named Habib
Marwan, was running a covert organisation
- from within our company.
- When did you find this out?
Couple of minutes ago they called.
One of our employees, Harris Barnes,
was actually Habib Marwan.
- Who else knows about this?
- Just the two of us. And Conlon.
Gentlemen. I'm David Conlon,
VP of internal security.
Jack Bauer, with CTU.
This is Paul Raines.
Jack, Paul. How can I help you?
I need to speak with Gene McLennan.
Gene's in a meeting right now,
and he asked me to assist you.
- I have access to everything.
- My office didn't make itself clear.
This is a matter of national security.
I need to speak with Mr McLennan now.
I understand. Let me see what I can do.
- What's the matter?
- Something's not right.
John, I'm not gonna keep this a secret. We
have to let the government know right away.
Sir! If you do this,
it will, with 100%/ certainty,
be the end of this company.
Now, you built McLennan-Forster.
Everything you have is tied up in it.
If this comes out, you'll be synonymous
with what happened. Terrorism. Treason.
What do you want me to do?
Lie to the government?
If I knew 24 hours ago what I know now, I'd
have done whatever it took to stop the attack.
But there's nothing we can do now.
Except protect ourselves.
And keep this company from going under, as
it will if CTU find out the truth about Marwan.
John, CTU will subpoena the file.
They will find out the truth.
No, they won't, Gene. I promise you.
Conlon and I can deal with this.
If you let us.
I don't like the sound of this.
Mr McLennan, we implicitly
violated national security procedure.
This could mean prison time.
We've got to protect ourselves.
- Did you get the latest casualty figures?
- No, not yet.
Which version of the Datalink
security system are you running?
Excuse me?
My company produces firmware
for Datalink. We installed your system.
Are you at 3.4 or 3.5?
Uh, 3.5. Does that work for you?
Yeah. Thanks.
Dave. Come on in.
John Reiss, chief technology officer.
You helped us identify the override.
Jack Bauer.
- It's good to meet you.
- I'm Gene McLennan.
I'm, uh, sorry I was delayed.
- Well, thank you for your time, sir.
- So how can I help CTU?
One of your employees,
Harris Barnes, is actually Habib Marwan,
a terrorist responsible for today's
attack and theft of the override.
We need you to take your IT systems offline
so Paul can look into his directory.
We can do that. Can't we, John?
Absolutely. Uh, follow me.
Thank you, sir.
Certainly.
Maybe you should go home.
I'm afraid to.
When my wife, Susan, died,
I didn't deal with it at all.
Actually, I went to work the next day.
I remember thinking to myself, "That's life. "
"Quit feeling sorry for yourself,
get over it and get on with it. "
A few weeks later I answered
a call from an old friend of Susan's
who did not know she had died.
And when I heard myself saying:
"Susan has passed away",
when I actually said those words,
it hit me.
All the pain I was trying
to shut out just overwhelmed me.
Erin, you can't keep it inside.
You cry, you blame God, you blame yourself,
and then you cry some more.
And all the while
you let your friends help you.
It's pretty simple.
But very painful.
And I am so, so sorry for you.
Dad, I just wanted... Oh.
Um... Uh, I'm sorry. I...
I just wanted to let you know that I was back.
I will go home.
You should go
and make sure your daughter's OK.
If you need me, I'll be on the floor.
Excuse me, sir. Tony just told me
you put him in charge of CTU?
That's correct.
That doesn't make sense. He just got
reinstated, I'm second in command.
Tony had Erin's job.
He has experience running CTU.
- You don't.
- With all due respect...
Relax, Curtis. It's provisional,
till District finds someone.
For the record, I don't like it.
- What do you hear from Bauer?
- He just arrived at McLennan-Forster.
He'll call if he picks up any threads.
OK, that was Marwan's
work station in the corner.
His computer is tied
into the engineering subnet.
What about the rest of the network?
Can we get into it from his account?
Yeah, I think there's a way to do that.
One window shows you his system files,
the other gets you outside the subnet.
Thanks.
Let me know if you need anything.
Thanks for your help.
This guy looks like
he knows his way around our system.
Don't worry. I'll be able to control things
from here. He won't find a thing.
Marwan purged a lot of files.
- When?
- Deletion dates aren't coming up.
That means they could
have been deleted today.
Marwan wasn't here today.
He was at Rockland, with the override.
Maybe someone else deleted the files.
There.
All right. Let me see what I can find.
- Yeah?
- I had to open up a socket for him.
- I can see it.
- Are they gonna be able to find anything?
As long as I can stay ahead of him, I should
be able to delete the incriminating files.
All right. I'm coming up.
What if you can't stay ahead of him?
What happens then?
- There are other options.
- What options?
We'll set off an EMP.
A pulse bomb?
Are you out of your mind?
It'll destroy every piece of hardware we have.
It'll cripple us electronically.
That's the point.
This is the handover sequence for comm.
I left the default password in place.
- You can reset it as soon as we're done here.
- All right.
Here are all the access codes
to CTU and Division.
- Thanks.
- If any of my personal stuff gets in your way,
have someone box them
and put them into storage.
All right.
If you need anything, ask Curtis.
And if he can't help you,
you can always call me at home.
Thanks.
Could I have
everybody's attention, please?
By now, you know that
I've taken over Erin Driscoll's command,
on a purely provisional basis.
All protocols remain the same.
But I want updates from
all department heads every 15 minutes.
Other than that, I'm just here to support you.
So let's get back to work.
- Hear from Jack?
- They're looking through Marwan's files.
- Any promising leads?
- Nothing yet.
Right. Look, Edgar, before Erin left she told
me the one person I should rely on is you.
- She said that?
- Yes, she did.
So anything you think is important,
I want you to bring it to me directly. Right?
- You got it.
- All right. Thanks.
Have you scanned satellite imagery
around the Rockland building?
- Everything since the override takedown.
- All right.
I want you to try
different frequency channels.
- Manually?
- Yeah. Only way we can be sure to see it all.
I'll have to talk to Tony.
I'm supposed to be backing up Jack and Paul.
Put somebody else on that.
This is more important.
What's more important?
We've got 75%/ of our people
on McLennan-Forster.
- I need Edgar to find a thread on Marwan.
- No, we don't have much chance by satellite.
Our best chance is through those files.
Stay on that.
- We can't afford one security-grade analyst?
- One, but not Edgar. Put somebody else on it.
Tony.
Are we trying to accomplish the same thing?
Or is this you establishing position?
I don't have to establish position.
I've already got it.
Now, what do you say we stop
wasting time arm-wrestling here?
I respect your opinion. But we'll disagree,
and when we do, we're gonna do it my way.
Fine. But I suggest you put manpower
into a data search for Marwan.
All right. Grab a couple people from image
processing. Work the satellites with them.
Curtis.
Don't worry. I'm gonna be
out of here when this crisis is over.
In the meantime,
I want the same thing you do.
I want to find Habib Marwan. All right?
Is everything all right?
I heard you had a problem.
CTU got to the override before
the other nuclear plants melted down.
Well, at least you're safe.
For now. But they know who I am. They'll
be tracking me with everything they've got.
- How does that affect our scheduling?
- It doesn't. Stay on task.
Make sure everything
at the Air Force base is ready.
I checked in with everyone
as of ten minutes ago.
We're gonna make this thing happen, Habib.
Now, remember. When you're done,
get in touch with Prado.
He'll get you out of the country.
And you?
Go.
- Good.
- What?
I can rebuild the files
from these empty directories.
- Dammit!
- What's he doing?
He's trying to rebuild the files I deleted.
- How can he do that?
- I don't know.
It's not a documented function.
Must be some hook left in by the designer.
He's gonna find evidence
we sold arms to terrorists.
Not necessarily.
The pulse bomb. We have to use it now.
- Research.
Set it off.
- We weren't scheduled for a test.
- This isn't a test.
Open up the safety chamber
and set it off now.
CTU will know
we're trying to hide something.
Marwan's the suspect.
They'll assume he was behind it.
- And the damage to the infrastructure?
- Better than destroying the company.
It'll take some time, but we can rebuild.
- Yeah?
-  EMP's been activated. Shield's open.
OK. Good.
It's been activated. It'll take
ten minutes to charge up before its release.
Edgar? The phone taps you asked for
at McLennan-Forster aren't holding.
- What do you mean?
- Connection keeps drifting.
- Is there a problem on our end?
- Check power supply. Could be their PBX.
My God, look at this thing.
The amplitude is fluctuating like crazy.
- I thought you checked that before?
- I did. It was fine then.
Let me call Jack.
The cellular customer is out of range.
That's weird. Customer out of range?
- McLennan-Forster.
- I need Jack Bauer.
He's a CTU agent in Harris Barnes' office.
I'll transfer you...
Hello?
- Hello?
- What's going on?
Cell and land lines around
McLennan-Forster are out.
Can we use the network to message him?
- Yeah, the computers haven't been affected.
- Open up a window for me, would you?
What the hell's this?
I don't know.
Something's wrong. I gotta respond. Can you
pipe that window over to this computer?
Yeah, just give me an Ethernet address.
6EFF 3239.
I've almost got these files rebuilt.
- Do we have any data points outside?
- I'm online with the phone company.
They're getting complaints as far as
eight blocks away from the building.
- Have you still got a connection?
- Yeah, I've got it. Look at this.
Son of a bitch, it's encrypted.
That's it. Print it out, now. Now!
- Dammit! They've got something.
- What?
I can't read it. How long till it goes off?
- Any second. We're fine.
- He's printing it.
- What are you going to do now?
- Take care of it.
I don't believe this.
We're dealing with an EMP.
McLennan-Forster were developing
a nonlethal weapon for the military.
- What is it?
- An electromagnetic pulse bomb.
Once it goes off, everything
within its radius that's electrical gets fried.
Lights, cars, computers. Every piece
of electronic data just vanishes forever.
- How long have we got?
- I don't know.
Its capacitors are still charging.
Come on.
All right, the printer's warming up.
Sarah, do we have any choppers in that area?
Yeah, one.
If it's in the air when the EMP goes off,
that chopper's going down.
Get 'em out of the area now.
- Edgar, where's this coming from?
- McLennan-Forster.
CTU 3, do you hear me?
CTU 3, do you copy?
All right. This is coming through.
OK, I'm gonna try and stop it.
If I don't, take the hard copy,
meet me in front of the building.
Dave, Bauer ran out.
He must have found out about the EMP.
CTU agent's heading down towards you.
Don't let him near it.
Mr Conlon. Is everything all right?
As you can see, we're having
some problems with the electricity.
Jack just went to check it out.
- I saw you were printing.
- How'd you know?
Well, we were searching the system same
time you were. Trying to help you guys out.
- Mind if I take a look?
- Sure.
It's, uh, just in the printer.
Conlon, this is Barnet. Do you copy?
- Yeah.
- Two's clear. Moving to three.
All right.
Oh, my God.
It's not gonna stop.
You got nowhere to go, man.
The doors are locked.
Where's the printout?
Where is it?
Come on.
- One of our choppers is down.
- Send medical in now.
Call all field teams outside the perimeter
of the blast. We have to find Jack and Paul.
I'll get back to you. OK. All right.
Someone set off an EMP blast
in the McLennan-Forster building.
We believe Jack and Paul are inside.
I assume that's a response to us. Someone
doesn't want us to get Marwan's files.
Jack was able to pull some info before
the blast. But we don't know who set it off.
Excuse me, sir.
Ms Driscoll's replacement arrived.
Thank you.
- That was fast.
- We got lucky.
Division had someone available with
the qualifications and CTU experience.
- I understand.
- Tony, thank you for filling in.
And I'd like you to stick around
and assist Ms Dessler.
I'm sorry, who?
Michelle Dessler. Do you know her?
I used to be married to her.
Visiontext Subtitles: Paul Burns
ENGLISH SDH