We have waited patiently for you to renounce
this unholy pact with our oppressors.
We have heard nothing.
This is the cost of that silence.
Choose to sign this corrupt document,
understand that you will be staining it
with the blood of the remaining hostages.
If CTU can't pull this off in time,
that's upwards of 60 people, Mike.
If someone altered the recording of your call
with Palmer, the president needs to know.
With the summit and the hostage situation,
he's not in the frame of mind to deal with this.
Till the treaty is signed,
I'm not letting this out of my sight.
- What did she tell you?
- It was a transcript of her call with Palmer.
President Logan wants us
to go in the terminal.
Yes, before the treaty is signed.
Curtis, what's your situation?
We're in place and setting the entry charges.
We should enter on target.
- I assume Bauer's in custody.
- I'll debrief him here, but...
Bring him in, now.
- Diane, what's wrong?
- Derek is inside the terminal.
I see him. He's with the other hostages,
but he's not hurt.
- Don't let anything happen to him.
- This is not your fault.
- I'm the reason you went along with him.
- This is not over.
Fire!
We've got a problem. One hostage is missing.
He was working with the terrorists.
- Give me a description.
- I'll help you. Let's go.
Buchanan ordered to take you into custody.
Beresch gave this guy a key card.
Something else is going down here.
We've got to find this guy now.
Sorry we have to bring you in like this, Jack.
It's all right, Mara. I understand.
A year and a half. How'd you manage
to stay invisible for so long?
Apparently I wasn't as invisible
as I should have been.
- Tyler.
- Mara, it's Curtis. Put Bauer on.
- It's Agent Manning.
- Yeah.
The suspect was hiding among the hostages?
Yeah, until the assault began, around 10:30.
- Then he must have broken for an exit.
- What exit was closest?
Without an alarm,
between gates six and seven.
- Thanks, Jack.
- Yeah.
Pull up external videos starting at 10:30.
All cameras covering gates six and seven.
Hang on, guys.
I'll log you out.
You're good to go.
We're away.
Mrs. Logan.
Oh, my God. Help, someone!
Something's happened to the first lady.
Get a doctor now.
He should be between gates six and seven,
just outside this vehicle.
I got this feed from ten minutes ago.
Try camera seven.
Camera four.
Tighten up.
Yellow tie. Got him.
All right, let's follow him.
- What camera covers the adjacent sector?
- 14A, but it's a bad angle.
Pull it up anyway. Match the timecodes.
OK, got him.
This is two minutes, 25 seconds later.
- What hangar is that?
- Hangar BB.
- Has it been searched yet?
- No. It was outside the secured perimeter.
I'm taking a team over there.
Send this info to Comm.
Team A with me. Let's move!
Hangar BB. Let's go!
CTU. Stiles.
Jack told us about a suspect
hiding among the hostages.
We just picked up surveillance on him.
He entered hangar BB at roughly 10:57.
- Did you check it out yet?
- We're going in now. I need comm.
- On it. What volume is airport facilities on?
- Hennessey four.
Team two, cover the rear.
Check it out. Everyone else,
search the building. See what you can find.
It's clear.
Craig, it's Curtis.
Send a forensic team down here now. They'll
need a full biopack with spectrum analysers.
- Any problems getting the canisters out?
- No. They were exactly where you said.
- Transport on schedule?
- Customs documents are being finalised.
Good. The Russians will learn the
consequences of occupying our homeland
when we turn Moscow into a graveyard.
- When did this happen?
- A few minutes ago.
- I came back in and I found her on the bed.
- What do you mean, "came back in"?
You mean you left her alone.
- What happened, Doctor? Is she all right?
- I'll do tests to find out why she blacked out.
I didn't black out. Someone did this to me.
- Someone attacked me, Charles.
- Shh, shh, shh. Marty.
You have to do something.
They're trying to get me.
No one's trying to get you.
We want you to be well.
- Listen, I had the proof, and now it's gone.
- What proof are you talking about?
Proof that David Palmer called me
to warn me about today.
Are you still on this?
We've never been off of it.
You just wouldn't listen to me.
Sir, is everything OK?
- I think so.
- No! No, dammit, it's not OK.
You people have got to listen to me.
I had a document from the archive room.
- Where was this document?
- I am trying to tell you.
It was hidden in my blouse.
It's gone. Someone stole it from me.
Marty, you've been under a lot of stress,
we all have. Let... No, let Dr Hill...
Let Dr Hill examine you,
and we can figure out how to get you better.
You don't believe me.
You don't believe your own wife.
I have a phone call from the secretary of state
I have to get to.
If there's any changes,
get back to me as soon as possible.
Yes, Mr. President.
- Don't leave.
- I'll be right down the hall.
- No, honey. Don't leave me.
- You need to get some rest.
Please.
Close that door.
- What do I do about this, Walt?
- This is what she was like before Vermont.
- Are you suggesting that I readmit her?
- Consider the option, for her sake.
She said she'd rather die
than go back in there.
Sir, if she's gonna persist
with these conspiracy theories,
it's only a matter of time before
she talks to someone who believes her.
Then we really will have a problem.
I wish you were wrong, but I don't think so.
Do you want me to handle this, sir?
Make the arrangements.
But... don't let Martha find out.
Let me be the one to tell her.
Yes, sir.
- Yeah?
- Have you handled the problem there?
Yes. Martha Logan
won't be giving us any more trouble.
Good. Erwich has completed transferring the
gas to the semi. He's on his way to the port.
- The authorities don't know it's been stolen?
- Not yet.
The only thing left to take care of is Bauer.
- Where is he?
- On his way to CTU.
He's getting too close.
He's started putting the pieces together.
I know. He needs to be taken out.
I'm handling it myself.
How? Once he gets to CTU,
your hitter won't be able to get near him.
I have someone on the inside
who can help us.
Then use him.
Done.
- You sure those readings are right?
- They're right. 2,000 parts per million.
- Could only be military grade.
- I'll tell 'em.
- I need you to finish the shell script.
- Not now.
Since when do you say "not now"?
The hangar was leased
to an offshore company,
but it's been vacant for at least 18 months.
Sir. I just heard from Curtis. He was right.
There was nerve gas in hangar BB.
- It killed the rats.
- There were traces in their blood.
But the concentrations
were definitely mil-spec. Weaponised.
So the suspect Bauer told us about,
that's why he was at the airport?
To steal canisters of nerve gas?
Stealing from whom? The military
destroyed its stockpiles years ago.
Maybe this nerve gas
wasn't produced by the military.
Have Forensics get a signature off the trace.
See if they can tell who manufactured it.
Chloe, elevate our alert status. Activate all
available personnel and get Curtis back here.
Don't issue a statement
about the first lady yet.
Let your successes today
run front and centre on all networks.
That sounds right.
Dr Hill, please, come in.
- How's Martha doing?
- She's asleep.
What caused the blackout?
I spoke with her psychiatrist, and
none of her medication would have caused it.
- So we still don't know what it was?
- Not yet, no.
Mr. President,
I need to speak to you and Walt alone.
Thank you, Doctor. Keep a close eye on her.
- We'll talk soon.
- Yes, Mr. President.
What's up?
The situation at the airport
has taken an unexpected turn.
What? The hostages were saved,
we've captured or killed the terrorists.
Not all of them. One of the terrorists
was posing as a hostage.
- He used the hostage crisis to cover a theft.
- A theft? What was stolen?
A cache of chemical weapons.
What kind of chemical weapons?
Nerve gas.
- Is it ours?
- No, sir. CTU is still trying to source it.
But it was buried in a bunker at the airport.
It seems this man
had another crew waiting for him there.
Do we have any idea
what the terrorists are planning?
They haven't made any demands
or issued any threats yet.
Well, what are we doing to stop them?
CTU is running an interagency search effort.
They're coordinating ground operations.
- Has the press found out about this yet?
- No, sir. It's being kept internal.
Whatever retaliation
we were bracing for is nothing
compared to what
these people are capable of now.
Sir, I'll assemble the Homeland Security team
to discuss evacuation scenarios.
I've sent everyone updates
on the airport forensics. What next?
Check the task list. You don't need to ask me
every time you need something new to do.
I don't care if you are my boss,
or if you regret sleeping with me last night.
- No one talks to me like that.
- Really? I just did.
Yeah.
- What's your problem?
- I don't have a problem.
- Then what do you want?
- Nothing.
Edgar.
I'm sorry that my private life
hasn't remained private.
- I'm thinking the opposite.
- What do you mean?
You're too private. We've known each other
years. And I find out you're keeping secrets?
People keep secrets.
I don't. Not from my friends.
Why didn't you tell me Jack was alive?
Oh, come on. It's called "national security".
Yeah, well, what about Spenser?
I didn't even know you two were going out.
Oh, give me a break.
When we find the gas
and the alert level drops,
we can have some camomile tea
and I'll tell you all my secrets, OK?
- You paged me?
- Has Bauer arrived at CTU?
- No, not yet.
- When he does, I need you to do something.
We have our hands full
searching for the nerve gas.
Bauer is a priority.
I need you to clear an entrance into CTU.
I'm sending it now. OK.
- Ms Raines?
- I'll get back to you. Yes?
- I take it you're up to speed on the nerve gas?
- I was just filling in DOD.
Diane Huxley was brought in to be debriefed.
I'd like you to interview her.
Interview her about what?
Anything that could help us
find the nerve gas.
- What could she know about that?
- I've reviewed the evidence against Bauer,
and I'm inclined to agree that he was framed
for the assassination of Palmer.
- Thank you.
- I think whoever framed Jack
is also involved with the nerve gas,
which means Huxley
could have had contact with that person.
Uh, I'm not a trained interrogator.
But you know Jack Bauer,
better than anyone else in here.
You have something in common with her.
It might help her open up.
I realise it's awkward, but I need you to do it.
Fine.
- I'll see what I can get from her.
- Thank you.
- Where is she?
- She and her son just cleared security.
- Miss Huxley, I'm Audrey Raines.
- Hi. This is my son Derek.
Hi. I want you to be checked out
by a doctor while I speak with your mother.
- There's nothing wrong with me.
- It's just procedure. Then we'll speak.
Can you take him to Medical, please?
It's OK. I'll see you in a bit.
- Don't worry. He'll be fine.
- Is Jack gonna be here soon?
He's on his way in. Come with me.
I had no idea he worked in a place like this.
It's just up these stairs.
- Did you know him before?
- Yes.
I knew him.
A lot of people here thought you were dead.
Yeah, I know. Excuse me.
Chloe.
- Hi, Jack.
- Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm OK.
We wouldn't have made it
out of that airport without you. Thank you.
- You're welcome.
- Mr. Bauer. Lynn McGill from Division.
I'll assume custody at this point, thank you.
You're no longer a suspect
in Palmer's murder, but you will need this.
- Level two clearance.
- Thank you.
Did Manning apprehend the suspect?
No. It seems the person you identified
used the hostage situation as a cover
to steal a cache of nerve gas from the airport.
Nerve gas? How do you know that?
Curtis found trace amounts
in a hangar adjacent to the terminal.
We don't know how much there is,
but it is a military-grade chemical weapon.
- Any leads?
- We'll run the search operation.
That's not gonna
track these terrorists fast enough.
The only way you're gonna get that gas is if
you find out who ordered the hit on Palmer.
I agree. I think David Palmer was about to
expose this plot. That's why he was killed.
If you can help us identify who framed you,
we can intercept this while there's still time.
- Hello, Jack.
- Hey, Bill.
The president's been informed of the nerve
gas. He doesn't want the media to find out.
I'll make sure Division restricts information
flow. We'll continue this when I'm done.
- Good to see you again, Jack.
- It's good to see you, too, Bill.
I'm so sorry about Michelle.
I never meant to put her in jeopardy.
- Of course you didn't.
- How's Tony doing?
He's still unconscious,
but the doctor says he's gonna pull through.
Good. We need to speak to him
as soon as possible.
They know to call us.
Jack, Audrey has been working for us.
- She's here in the building now?
- She's debriefing Diane Huxley.
Why is she talking to Diane?
Lynn asked her to.
I'm not used to calling him Jack.
He said his name was Frank Flynn.
I thought he worked for the oil company.
You probably know more about him than I do.
- We all thought he was dead.
- So what do you want to know?
Jack was living with you
for the last six months. Is that correct?
He was renting a room.
So you don't have
a personal relationship with him?
- I'm not sure that's any of your business.
- I'm sorry, I...
I need to know how close you and Jack were.
Whether he confided in you or not.
Jack's a private person.
I always knew he was keeping
something from me, I just never pushed it.
I accepted him for who he was.
Ms Raines, whoever he was before,
doesn't change the way I feel about him.
He was good to me.
He was good to my son.
He meant a lot to us.
He still does.
I see.
Did, um... did anyone ever come by
and ask about Jack?
- What do you mean?
- Someone knew Jack was alive.
It's critical to our investigation
that we find out who that was.
No. No one ever asked about him.
No one ever came to see him.
Can... can you excuse me
for a minute, please?
Yeah.
Jack.
I don't even know where to begin.
I couldn't tell you I was still alive.
- Jack, you don't need to apol...
- I did it for your own protection.
It's been hard for me thinking that you died
believing that I was angry at you,
that I hated you.
I wasn't able to forgive myself for that.
You had every reason to hate me. I was
responsible for Paul's death. I lied to you.
Jack.
You made a hard decision.
I never imagined...
I'd get another chance to tell you this.
But I...
I want you to know that I don't blame you
for what happened with Paul.
Thank you.
Jack.
There's so much I want to say to you.
It's not the right time...
- Mr. McGill needs to see you.
I'll be right down.
I should go.
Evelyn. Is Mrs. Logan still asleep?
Yes. She's finally getting some rest.
Good. You should probably
start gathering some of her things.
- I thought the president was staying.
- He is. But she'll be leaving today.
Where is she going?
Just make sure she has the essentials
to make her trip comfortable.
Yes, sir.
What are you doing?
Setting up a new socket.
We're overloaded from the NSC database.
- Why are you here?
- Looking for you.
- What for?
- I need to get into your utilities volume.
- Why didn't you message me?
- I wanted to say something too. No drama.
What?
I was unfairly harsh to you a few minutes ago.
I didn't mean anything.
All right. Apology accepted.
It wasn't really an apology,
it was more of an observation. The fact...
Spenser.
Dammit. Why do I do that?
- Stiles.
- It's Chloe.
- What is it?
- I need to know Spenser's clearance level.
- Why you asking?
- Spenser works for me and I need to know.
So you could please open the header file
and give it to me?
Fine.
Level three.
Chloe.
Call Buchanan. Tell him
I need to talk to him now. It's important.
Division sent me. One of your
mainframe servers is cycling slow.
- You're not here.
- I was told it'd be taken care of.
I'm gonna have to clear this
with the systems administrator.
- Are you Hank? From Outside Support?
- Yeah.
My fault. I was supposed to advance him
an emergency clearance.
All right. Place the bag on the conveyor belt.
Walk right through, sir.
- All clear.
- Thank you.
Thank you. I'll show you the way.
Mr. Cummings told me
it would be best to keep you off the manifest.
Classified material
runs on servers nine and twelve.
All the information you need on Bauer
should be there.
I don't know
what Cummings asked you to download,
but you need to keep vector counts the same,
or it'll get flagged.
I got it.
OK. I need to get back to my station.
Evelyn, what are you doing?
Mrs. Logan, are you feeling better?
Why are you packing my things?
Walt Cummings asked me to.
Why? Where are we going?
I don't know
if the president's going with you.
Evelyn, stop. What's going on?
They just asked me to get you ready to leave.
They're sending me to Vermont, aren't they?
Charles is having me committed.
I'm sorry, Mrs. Logan.
I honestly don't know anything else.
Fine.
I'll get dressed.
Edgar. My FGA is locked. Where's Chloe?
How should I know?
- Can you unlock this?
- No.
Mr. Wolff. Please come with us.
- What do you want?
- Mr. Buchanan ordered us to take you to him.
- I'm in the middle of a critical task here.
- Mr. Stiles will take over your workload.
Did you know about this, Edgar?
Yeah. I just got the bulletin. Sorry.
Mr. Wolff. Please.
I'm coming.
Chloe? Sir. What is going on here?
Sit down, Spenser.
You've been burrowing into classified
CTU protocols without authorisation.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Stop. You logged on to the subsystem.
We're going through your system.
Tell us what you were doing.
- I told you I was opening a...
- That's enough!
You've accessed files outside your clearance
level at least 18 times in four months.
Sir, whatever you think you've found,
it's a mistake. I've done nothing wrong.
- You obviously have your own agenda here.
- I don't have an agenda.
Why don't you explain
why you had to crawl into my bed,
which wasn't what it appeared to be, just like
your work here isn't what it appears to be?
Let me handle this.
Sir, you can't take anything she says
into consideration.
I was careless, and inadvertently,
I caused her some emotional pain.
- Oh, please.
- And now she's trying to get back at me.
- I don't think so.
- Sir, I'd like to talk to a lawyer.
Forget about a lawyer. We're in the middle of
a terrorist crisis. There are lives on the line.
You're going to tell us what you've been
doing here, and you're going to tell us now.
I hope this goes better than the last time.
- Dr Hill and his staff are on stand-by.
- I'm not looking forward to this.
- Evelyn.
- Mr. President.
- Where is she?
- She's in the bathroom, sir.
Martha!
Marty!
- Are you sure she's in there?
- Yes, sir. She's getting dressed.
Marty.
Aaron, my wife is gone.
This is Pierce. We have a priority alert.
The first lady is unaccounted for.
All agents, move north and west.
Anyone spotting her, check in immediately.
Got it.
So the only people who knew you were alive
were Palmer, Tony, Michelle and Chloe.
And at least one other person
who killed Palmer and tried to frame me.
- And you don't know who that might be?
- No.
Any theories?
David Palmer called me. Told me someone
in Logan's administration was targeting me.
- Which is why you faked your own death.
- Yeah. Except it didn't work.
I believe that whoever tried to kill me
18 months ago found out I was still alive,
and waited until today to exploit that.
Someone inside
President Logan's administration.
That's what David Palmer told me then,
and I believe him.
That means someone in this administration
is also tied to the theft of the nerve gas.
Yeah. You're gonna have to look into that.
There are hundreds of people
in the administration.
It would take an investigation of that
magnitude months to gain any traction.
Mr. McGill,
Dr Paulson is calling from Medical.
- Put him through.
- Mr. McGill.
- Yes?
- Tony Almeida has regained consciousness.
- Can he talk?
- Yes. He's very weak. You'll have to be brief.
- I'll be down in a few minutes.
- Tony asked if he could speak to Jack Bauer.
Says it's important.
He's a friend of mine.
- Jack will be down in a few moments.
- I'll let him know.
Thank you. I'll be right back.
- Jack.
- What's going on?
I know you're busy,
but... I just wanted to apologise.
- You have nothing to apologise for.
- Yes, I do.
I thought you were just another loser
trying to take advantage of my mom.
I was wrong.
You were trying to protect her. Your mother
is lucky that you love her so much.
As soon as this is over, I promise you,
you and I are gonna get a chance to talk.
- Right now, I have to go.
- Yeah.
Take care of your mother.
Who gave you the level five authorisation?
- Don't look at me. Answer him!
- I can't.
I can't talk to anyone here about this.
Whatever you were doing is over, Spenser.
I pulled Spenser's screen activity
from the archive.
This is what he was looking at
ten minutes ago.
Looks like he was using in-house surveillance
to track someone through CTU.
Why are you tracking Jack Bauer?
I'm sure if they're tracking Jack Bauer,
they have a reason.
Who is "they"?
I won't say anything else.
Chloe, phone security.
Have them locate Jack now.
- Dr Paulson?
- Yes.
Jack Bauer for Tony Almeida.
Oh, of course, Mr. Bauer.
Just remember to please keep it brief.
Thank you, sir.
Tony.
Tony, it's Jack.
Jack! Are you all right?
I think he cracked my rib.
The lines were locked out.
What happened? Who is he?
He's a professional.
He killed Dr Paulson, and tried to kill me.
- You have any idea how he got into CTU?
- We identified a mole in Chloe's department.
- Who?
- Spenser Wolff. He hasn't talked yet.
- Where is he?
- Holding.
Get a doctor down here to monitor
Tony Almeida now. Lock this room down.
Contact Lynn McGill.
Have him meet me at Holding.
Bring up visual surveillance
on medical room two.
Open the door.
I want to show you something. Get up!
Did you let that man into CTU? This man is
a professional assassin. He killed Dr Paulson.
- Did you let him into CTU?!
- They said he was here to tap the server.
Who?
I was here as part of
an Internal Affairs investigation.
Do you understand how much trouble
you are in? One more chance.
Who told you to let that man into CTU?
The White House.
Mr. Cummings. The White House.
Cummings recruited me.
He said that they wanted to make sure
that CTU was operating within the rules.
You have to believe me.
I thought I was serving the president.
Yeah. Take him back to Holding.
Walt Cummings killed David Palmer.
He tried to have me killed.
We have to build a case
before we call the president.
We don't call him - he's here in California.
We go see him now.
Cummings is the president's
chief of staff and friend.
- Without hard evidence, CTU can't touch him.
- I'm not CTU.
I'll go get Walt Cummings myself.