Terrorists are controlling
the main terminal of Ontario Airport.
Today your president and
the president of Russia have come together
to sign an anti-terrorism alliance.
I have hostages.
Unless President Logan
and President Suvarov
make a joint statement repudiating
this accord, I will order their execution.
I want this handled!
Do you understand?
I don't care how you do it.
I don't care what it takes. Fix it!
David Palmer called me last night.
He said it was a matter of national security.
I need to talk to you.
It's hardly a matter of national security.
- That's not what he said.
- Yes, it is.
No, that is a trick.
I know all phone conversations are recorded.
- Where do they store those transcripts?
- Archive room down the hall.
This is Bill Buchanan.
I'm hoping we can resolve this peacefully.
I don't think you understand
how serious we are.
If you try to enter the terminal, you will spend
the rest of the day collecting body parts.
Jack, I need you to quarterback this.
I'm staring down on the main concourse.
I've got six hostiles in explosive vests
with orders to detonate if we make a move.
I got a woman, Diane Huxley,
says she has info for CTU.
- Diane, what's going on?
- Derek is inside the terminal.
You.
No!
Curtis, they're moving another hostage.
Oh, my God. It's Derek.
You have a problem at the terminal.
Jack Bauer's inside, providing recon for CTU.
Hold on one second.
Mr. Bauer.
Derek has five seconds left to live.
Four...
Beresch!
We've been trying,
but we can't make contact with Jack.
- Can you make a visual?
- Negative.
- Maybe Jack went dark intentionally.
- Unlikely.
- He was talking when he was cut off.
- We assume he's been captured or killed.
We mount the assault without his help.
Without Jack directing our team,
success probability falls to less than 20%.
President Logan
will sign this treaty in an hour.
If the terrorists remain,
they'll kill all the hostages.
What do you want me to do, Bill?
Work up an assault plan
that doesn't include Jack.
I'll go back to the staging area
and coordinate from there.
Get back to your stations.
Prepare to reconfigure.
All teams, stand down.
We're working up a new mission profile.
Copy that. All teams, stand down.
Keep down. Keep your head down.
Mr. Bauer, what is CTU's assault plan?
The boy means something to you, or you
wouldn't have given yourself up so easily.
Tell me the plan.
They're gonna storm the north
concourse doors on my command.
I'm coordinating the operation from here.
Is there anyone else inside?
No.
Get me the plans to the terminal.
You've been a great help.
We'll keep the boy alive for now.
Bring me another hostage.
Anything you do in here today
will not stop that treaty from being signed.
The US government does not negotiate
with terrorists. You know that.
Your president is a weak man.
He'll back down once more blood is spilled.
- On your feet!
- Not him.
- You, get up!
No! Don't!
Please. Please, you don't have to do this.
- Vlad.
- I can help you buy more time.
Please!
No! You don't have to do this now.
On your knees!
CTU was supposed to have raided the
terminal by now. Why haven't we heard?
- Buchanan said they had a setback.
- What kind of setback?
- They lost contact with Jack Bauer.
- Why? What happened to him?
They're not sure, but they need
to reconfigure their assault plan.
- Beresch is back online.
- I'll tell the president.
Beresch is transmitting from the terminal.
He's got another hostage.
We've waited patiently for you to renounce
this unholy pact with our oppressors.
We have heard nothing.
This is the cost of that silence.
What happens next
is your choice, Mr. President.
If you choose to sign this corrupt document,
understand that you will also be staining it
with the blood of the remaining hostages.
If CTU can't pull this off in time...
That's upwards of 60 people, Mike.
You know I've never done anything
I didn't feel was right for the country.
Of course not, sir.
Nobody thinks otherwise.
I know I'm ambitious and that I want this
treaty to be the hallmark of my presidency,
but I never thought
I would sacrifice innocent life.
Mr. President, you are not responsible
for the actions of these murderers.
- I could postpone this.
- Sir?
I give them what they want, nobody else dies.
Do you think these people
would release the hostages?
We both know that'll never happen.
You're doing the only thing you can do.
The terrorists are calling the treaty
an "unholy pact"...
If someone altered the recording
of your conversation with David Palmer,
- the president needs to know.
- No, not now. Not yet.
- What are you waiting for?
- Charles is preoccupied.
With the summit and the hostage situation,
he's not in the frame of mind to deal with this.
Besides, he thinks I'm unstable,
which means I have to show it to him
in the right way.
So, until the treaty's signed,
I'm not letting this out of my sight.
- What's happening?
- Sorry, no time to explain.
- You were going in to get the hostages.
- We lost contact with Jack.
- What does that mean?
- We're not sure, but we need to change plans.
- Is Jack OK?
- We don't know.
- What about Derek?
- As soon as we know, you'll be told.
- Please, I...
- Miss Huxley, I need to go.
The situation
continues to grow more tragic.
We've just received a video feed confirming
that another hostage has been executed
inside the main terminal at Ontario Airport.
- Jack...
- Don't say anything.
We're gonna get through this.
Just don't say anything right now.
A White House spokesperson has
reiterated that President Logan will sign
a historic pact with
his Russian counterpart as scheduled.
It has, of course, been a long-standing
foreign policy not to yield to terrorists...
You're going to call CTU and tell them
you've revised your assault profile.
Tell them to come to the emergency door
south of gate 12.
They won't do that because I ask.
They'll need an explanation.
That's your concern, Mr. Bauer.
Overwrite volume four
and re-key with the airport grid.
- Just one second.
- We don't have a second.
We're running out of time.
- Want some help, Spenser?
- He doesn't need it.
Keep managing the two-ways,
or else we'll have dropouts.
- Excuse me. You're Miss O'Brian, right?
- Who are you?
Lynn McGill, from District. I met you
at that memory-management lecture.
- If you say so. What do you need?
- I need to talk to Bill Buchanan.
He's in the situation room.
He's kinda busy right now.
I see him. Thanks.
Looking forward to working with you today.
- You don't know who McGill is, do you?
- No, and I don't care. Get back to work.
Once Curtis's teams go in there,
I want an update on the deployment of HIT.
Hi.
- Mr. Buchanan, did they say I was coming?
- Lynn, please, call me Bill.
If we were having a beer, but at work
a more formal mode of address is better.
Whatever makes you feel comfortable.
We're in the middle of final prep.
I understand President Logan
wants us to go in as soon as possible.
- Yes, before the treaty's signed.
- Is Manning ready to send his teams in?
He is, but we're flying blind.
My briefing sheet says
we have Jack Bauer on the inside.
We haven't heard from him for 20 minutes.
That's interesting.
I read the bulletin from Division,
but I don't know why you're here.
- We were getting heat from the White House.
- About what?
Jack Bauer. They wanna know
things are running smoothly.
- We're on track, Lynn.
- I'm sure you are. That's my assignment.
- Is your tactical wired through to all servers?
- Yes. You can plug into station four.
I'd prefer to work from your office,
Mr. Buchanan.
I think I should have a central vantage point.
I wanna make sure you're OK
working from another station.
Fine.
Good. And it's not a big deal, but just so
everyone's clear on the chain of command,
I think you should address me
as Mr. McGill in front of the others.
You know, Lynn, I'd rather not.
Just a suggestion.
Anyway, I need your office.
That's not a suggestion.
- Fine.
- Mr. Buchanan?
It's Jack Bauer on line one.
- Is Curtis plugged into this call?
- I'm on, Bill. Put Jack through.
- You're both on with Jack Bauer.
- What happened?
One of the hostiles got too close.
I had to end the transmission.
- All right, we'll restart the countdown.
- Negative. Scrap the existing plan.
- Find a new breach point.
- My men are in position.
They moved the hostages within the kill zone.
They'll be taken out with the crossfire.
There's an emergency door south of gate 12.
It's unguarded. You should be able
to punch through with no opposition.
I see it,
but I'm not comfortable with this entry.
It's the only shot we've got.
- Are you there now?
- Yes, it's clear.
I'm in a flank-two position.
I repeat: I am in a flank-two position.
Curtis, how long before
your teams can redeploy?
- About 20 minutes.
- The president's signing within 30 minutes.
I'll go as fast as I can. Jack,
I'll call you when my men are in position.
Copy that. I'll be standing by.
Ivan and Ishmael, stay with the hostages.
The rest of you, come here.
Vlad, guard them.
You're doing great.
- Manning.
- Buchanan.
How long until your people can move in?
- About 15 minutes.
- Why so long?
When Jack changed breach point,
I modified everything, including explosives.
They have to be repositioned.
Is it a mistake to act on this?
It might take too long.
Jack knows our deadline. If he didn't think
it was worth a delay, he wouldn't call.
- I trust him.
- All right, Curtis, 15 minutes.
You have to make this happen.
- I will.
- Call when you're in position.
Mr. Buchanan,
Mr. McGill needs to see you in his office.
- It'll have to wait. Tell him I'm busy.
- He said it had to be now.
Fine.
I'm settled in fine. If I need anything, I'll call.
What is it? I'm trying to coordinate
this hostage situation.
- Sit down, Mr. Buchanan.
- Stop with the "Mr. Buchanan".
We need to get this assault in motion now.
Sit down, Bill.
I told the White House
the rescue is back on track.
Thank you.
I found it a little inappropriate talking about
an operation I hadn't personally reviewed,
so before you send your men into
the terminal, I'd like to see the playbook.
I can't have you micromanaging my work
here. If you wanna do my job, I'll go home.
Please don't be defensive. I'm not
challenging you. I'm just trying to do my job.
I'll have it sent to your laptop. Anything else?
That's all for now.
Bill.
Fighting me isn't gonna increase our chances
of saving those people's lives.
Lynn wants to see the revised assault plan.
- Is he running point instead of you?
- He just wants to see the plan.
Bill. Curtis confirmed his team will be ready
in ten minutes, based on Jack's new intel.
There is no word as to whether or not
the president will call off
the signing of the historic treaty agreement
of the United States and Russia,
scheduled for just under an hour.
The terrorists...
Any response from the White House
since the last killing?
They confirmed the signing of the treaty
is going ahead as planned.
They won't capitulate as long as
they think their rescue attempt will succeed.
Once we kill their men,
they'll realise their options have run out.
The only chance these people had
of being rescued is gone because of me.
People were gonna die here today.
That was their plan. This is not your fault.
I'm the reason you went along with them.
If I wasn't here...
Stop it.
This is not over.
With no official rebuke
of the terrorists' demands,
a statement from the White House confirmed
the president's position is unchanged
and the treaty will be signed
within the hour as scheduled.
It puts the lives of the 60 men, women and
children being held hostage in question...
Good news, sir. CTU has
re-established contact with Jack Bauer.
The rescue operation is back on track.
- But that's still no guarantee.
- Excuse me, sir?
The hostages may be killed
when we go in there.
Let's be honest, that's more likely than not.
We don't know that, sir.
- President Suvarov is waiting outside.
- He is?
You're walking outside together onto
the stage. We all agreed to the protocol.
- It's time already?
- Yes, sir.
Mr. President. Shall we?
My people tell me
the assault has been delayed.
It's happening now. It will happen
before the treaty is signed, don't worry.
Mr. President, like you,
I have staked much of my political future
on the success of this treaty.
If this rescue attempt fails,
it will not only be rendered meaningless,
it will become a mockery.
And so will we.
I'm here to escort Mrs. Logan.
The ceremony's beginning.
- She'll be out in a moment.
- May I... have a word?
You're aware Mrs. Logan was found
in one of the archive rooms.
I don't know anything about that.
Aaron Pierce said you lied to him.
You said Mrs. Logan was in her room when
she was going through classified documents.
I don't think you understand
how grave this situation is.
- What do you mean?
- Mrs. Logan removed a document
that contains highly sensitive
intelligence protocols.
- That's not what she said it was.
- What did she say she took?
- I think that you should talk to her about this.
- This is important. What did she tell you?
She said it was a transcript
of a call she had with David Palmer.
I'm sure when she said that she believed it.
If this document finds its way into
the wrong hands, you'll be responsible.
- I didn't take it.
- You aided and abetted.
You'll not only lose your job,
you'll be prosecuted.
That's not fair. I tried to talk her out of this.
All I'm asking is that you tell me...
where did she put it?
She has it with her. It's in her blouse.
She said she wouldn't let it out of her sight
until she talked to the president about it.
Walt? Sorry to keep you waiting.
I'm ready now.
Presidents Logan and Suvarov
will each make statements,
which will be followed
by the signing of the treaty.
How much time will there be
between the moment I step out on stage
- and when I sign the document?
- Not long.
Does CTU know
that's how long they have for the rescue?
Yes, sir. They're completely synchronised
with what's going on here.
I hope so.
The lives of those hostages depend on it.
Today was to be the crowning achievement
of my presidency.
Instead everybody's waiting to hear
what's gonna happen at the airport.
- So how are you feeling?
- I'm fine. Don't worry about me.
How come you just keep getting
better-looking as you get older?
- I just keep getting older.
- What?
You're the most beautiful First Lady
Pennsylvania Avenue has ever seen.
Ladies and gentlemen,
President Logan and President Suvarov.
They're a minute and a half ahead of
schedule. Should we tell Curtis to speed up?
No, Curtis is moving as fast as he can.
A call from me won't make him move faster.
- I just thought he might like to...
- I said no, Chloe.
The only way to make sure
the assault happens in time
is to try to slow down the signing.
- What's wrong with Buchanan?
- Nothing.
I think he just realises we're not
gonna be able to save the hostages.
Before we begin the treaty signing,
I would like to address what's happening
just a few miles away from here.
As you know,
terrorists have already taken innocent life
in an attempt to stop this historic treaty
from being signed.
President Suvarov will not let this happen.
I will not let this happen.
- Yes, Mike?
- I should have heard from you by now.
- Have you gone in yet?
- We're not quite ready.
You have to go in now.
The president's about to sign that treaty.
We're pushing as hard as we can.
- Is there anything you can do?
- Like what?
Can you stall things,
slow down the ceremony?
Bill, the entire world
is watching this on live television.
The presidents of the United States
and Russia are on stage now.
This process is set in motion. No, I can't stall.
- OK, I'll call you back.
- No, stay on the phone with me.
- I need to know when your people go in.
- Yes, sir.
This barbaric lawlessness that's taking place
at Ontario Airport only underscores the need,
the necessity for this accord
and for our continued
vigilance and commitment
to fighting terrorism around the world.
It looks like President Logan
is going through with the signing.
He's not going to give in to your demands.
- Are you sure this is going to work?
- It will work.
The only reason he is so confident is that
he thinks his rescue attempt will save the day.
- You're sure you can fend them off?
- As soon as CTU comes in that way,
they'll all be killed.
One of the president's aides
will then walk to the podium
and whisper that there'll been no rescue.
That his signature on the treaty
will be the death warrant of the hostages.
That will stop him, I assure you.
Just in case you're wrong and he signs
the treaty, be ready to carry out your threat.
Every one of my men is committed
to doing what needs to be done today.
We've upgraded our estimate of the number
of wounded. I need ten more ambulances.
Right.
The new rescue operation is
radically changed from the initial approach.
It was revised based on
new intel from Jack Bauer.
Which he phoned in
after being dark for 20 minutes.
I need to call you back.
His explanation for being out of touch
is unsatisfactory.
Jack said he was trying to avoid detection.
What are you suggesting?
There's too many
unusual circumstances here.
I want to understand it better before we go in.
I need the transcripts of
your communication with Mr. Bauer.
- To what end?
- Thoroughness.
Just the raw transcripts will be fine.
- Fine, I'll send them to you.
- Thank you.
Curtis is on line three.
- What's the situation?
- My men are in place and setting the charges.
- Any complications?
- No.
We're jamming the frequency so they can't
remote detonate. We should enter on target.
Good. Stay on the line until we give the go.
All right, Bill. Copy.
- O'Brian.
- Miss O'Brian, I'm trying to understand
the transcript of Jack's last call,
and a few items...
I'm busy trying to keep this revised assault
on schedule. What do you need?
I don't want to slow you down, but
if you'd unlock volume five, I'd like to see...
I don't need to know what you'd like to see.
OK, it's unlocked.
Good.
- Lynn McGill is really slowing things down.
- That's his style.
I worked with him before.
He usually loses 20% of his staff in the first
two days after taking control of a new office.
- That many people quit?
- No, most of them were fired.
In the volatile climate of the 21st century,
the sharing of deterrent technologies
by responsible powers
is the surest guarantee of global peace.
But let this accord be proof that
our two great nations stand together
in their commitment to fight
the enemies of peace and freedom.
Achmed found Chevensky.
He's dead. He killed himself.
- He found him in the baggage room.
- The keycard?
Chevensky had it hidden
right where he said he would.
Round up your men.
The rest of you will work clean-up,
whoever makes it through that line of fire.
Assume CTU is in body armour,
so go for the head shot.
You and you.
Guard the hostages.
Kill anyone who tries to break away.
Head down!
It is time the black night is broken
by the dawning of the light of global peace.
- Curtis.
- Jack, my men are in place.
OK. Remember, I am in a flank-two position.
Make sure your men don't hit me.
Roger that.
Ready to start the countdown on your word.
Jack?
- Move in at your discretion.
- All teams, we have a green light.
Counting down from 60 seconds on my mark.
Now. Jack, see you inside.
Everyone, 60 seconds!
Look out.
- Stop the assault!
- Put Curtis on hold. What?
They're walking into a trap.
Look at the transcript.
When Jack issued a directive,
he said, "flank-two".
- He was trying to give us his position.
- No, it's a duress code. He's under duress.
We ran Jack's calls through a protocol filter.
They would have found a duress signal.
That's current codes. When Jack was active,
"flank-two" was a duress code.
Chloe, confirm that.
Jack is telling us he's being used
to send misinformation.
If Curtis' teams go in now,
they'll be ambushed.
- He's right.
- Curtis.
Abort the countdown. Repeat: abort, abort.
Stand down. All teams stand down.
We're aborting entry.
We're standing down. What's wrong?
We detected a duress code in Jack's call.
We have to assume the terrorists
are feeding him the information.
Redeploy according to the original
assault plan and do not contact Jack.
- If Jack contacts you, buy time.
- Copy that. We're moving.
- You're gonna outflank the terrorists?
- Yes.
That should work.
All teams, reposition for entry through
the east and north gates. Plan Bravo.
Plan Bravo, through
the east and north gates. Go.
Acknowledged. Redeploying protocol one.
- What's happening?
- Please step back to the vehicle. Now.
They said 60 seconds two minutes ago.
What is CTU waiting for?
I don't know. You heard what I heard.
It's Jack.
- Jack.
- What's happening?
There was a malfunction
on the entry charges.
- What's the time frame?
- Any minute.
We're resetting the detonators. Stand by.
Copy that.
They're in position.
Stay ready!
Presidents Logan and Suvarov
are preparing to sign the treaty,
but what should be a moment of triumph
has become a grim test of wills.
Yeah?
- Is it done?
- No. CTU hasn't attacked yet.
You said it would happen before the signing.
And you told me
the president would never let it go this far.
He's signing it.
You have no choice. Kill them all.
Fire!
No!
- You OK?
- Yeah.
We've secured the terminal.
Besides the hostiles, no further casualties.
- The remaining hostages are unharmed.
- Good work, Curtis.
- Did you get that, Mike?
- Got it. Thanks, Bill. Good work.
Mr. President, I have some good news.
I have just received word
the crisis at the Ontario Airport is over.
The rescue operation
that I authorised was successful.
The terrorists have been captured or killed
and, best of all,
it's all been accomplished
with no further loss of innocent life.
Excuse me, agent. My name is Jack Bauer.
- I know who you are, sir.
- Can I use your pick?
This is Derek Huxley.
His mother is at the command post.
- Could you please take him there?
- Of course.
- What about you?
- Come here.
Hey.
I have to finish this.
- Take care of your mother.
- Yeah.
OK?
Go.
We're missing one.
Everybody, I need your attention.
We want a man
who was being held with you.
He's a white male, mid-30s.
He was wearing a bright yellow tie.
Did anyone see him leave? Anyone?
Keep them here until I get back.
Mom?
Derek!
They were gonna kill me.
Jack saved my life.
He saved everyone's life.
Ms Huxley,
I need you and your son to follow me.
- Can I see Jack Bauer?
- I'm sorry.
I have instructions to transfer you to CTU.
This way, please.
Mr. President.
- Congratulations.
- Thank you very much.
Thank you.
- Watch your step.
- I need to talk to you.
Sweetheart, smile. It's over.
- I need a few minutes alone with you.
- Yes, soon.
No, not soon, right now.
This is very important.
Martha, when I'm done with this,
I'll call for you.
- I promise.
- All right, this ends now.
I have played my role without interfering.
Now it is time for you to attend to me.
- And I will.
- Do not patronise me!
Something is going on.
I am not crying wolf again.
Martha.
Please.
Do not ruin this moment for me.
We'll talk later.
Martha?
- Everything all right?
- No, it's not all right.
I have to talk to my husband. The situation
is more dangerous than he realises.
What situation is that?
I'm sorry, Walt.
I can only talk to Charles about this.
Colette confirms the area's been contained
with only minor injuries among the hostages.
Good, thank you. Route all field updates
through Mr. McGill for the time being.
OK.
- Bill, if you have a moment...
- Lynn, uh...
- I owe you an apology.
- For what?
If you hadn't recognised the duress code
that Jack transmitted...
Bill, you're the reason
I figured out what he was doing.
- What do you mean?
- I admit I was suspicious of Mr. Bauer.
You were so adamant about his integrity,
I looked to reconcile the contradiction.
So, thank you.
- Has Mr. Bauer been taken into custody?
- We'll debrief him here, but not as a suspect.
He's not cleared in the deaths of
David Palmer and Michelle Dessler.
Based on mitigating evidence
and Chloe's testimony,
we're confident that Jack
was framed for those murders.
I appreciate that,
but it doesn't change the situation.
We have surveillance footage placing Jack
at the site of David Palmer's assassination.
- Clearly it was doctored.
- Not according to preliminary tests.
To get to the bottom of this,
Jack Bauer has a lot to answer for.
Bring him in, now.
- The rest of the terminal is clear.
- Yes, sir.
Jack.
- It's good to see you again.
- Good to see you. We got a problem.
A hostage is missing.
He was working with them.
- Describe him, I'll take care of it.
- I'll help you.
You need to go back to CTU. Buchanan
gave orders to take you into custody.
I watched Beresch give this guy a keycard.
Something else is going down.
- We've got to find this guy now.
- I'll get right on it.
But I need you to go with these men. Please.
He's a white male, mid-30s.
He was wearing a dark suit and a yellow tie.
- He's about 5'8".
- We'll find him.
OK. Thanks.
- These are my weapons.
- OK.
Alteri, Hutchison.
Possible sleeper among the hostages.
We're looking for a Caucasian male,
5'8", dark suit, yellow tie.
- Where have you been?
- We had a problem with Chevensky.
- Where is he?
- Dead.
You have the key?
Masks.
- Do you have the merchandise?
- Yes. We're moving the canisters out now.
Good. Transportation's been arranged.
Call me when you're out.
I will.
Today is a historic day for both
the United States and Russia alike.
Presidents Logan and Suvarov,
having signed the arms treaty agreement
which will impact on arms reduction
between both countries,
will now greet the press
to discuss the unprecedented weight
of what has just been put in motion.
This will be remembered as a significant day
for President Logan, perhaps...
Evelyn, did you have a chance
to speak to my husband?
Aggh!