-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
&
... ::: www.SubCentral.de ::: ...
proudly present
24 - Season 7
Episode 22
Previously on 24...
Agent Walker told me
that there's a chance...
a small chance that I could help you.
I'm dying. And whatever small chance
there is to stop that from happening
it is not worth the pain for me to
let you sit there and watch me die.
Daddy, I don't want to lose you.
- Come here.
- I don't.
What is it?
Sweetheart, I'm sorry,
but you need to go.
Hodges was behind everything
that happened today,
from the planes going down to the
attack on the White House. - What?
He's also responsible for
the death of my brother.
All you need to know
is Hodges worked a deal.
Witness Protection.
My mother approved it
and he's going free...
unless someone intervenes.
I'll get you contact information, a price
and instructions on how
to transfer the funds.
Martin, it's Olivia Taylor,
I spoke to the contact,
but I couldn't go through with it.
Listen to me, Jibraan.
If you don't do exactly as I say,
you're going to watch your younger
brother die right in front of your eyes.
And then...
I'm gonna kill you, hmm?
It was the Americans who
killed our parent Hamid.
I'm going to make them pay.
What have you done to my brother?
You've poisoned his mind.
This isn't my brother.
We're looking for a
man who worships here.
His name is Jibraan Al-Zarian.
Do you know him?
I know him, but he is not a terrorist.
We did not come here to debate
this with you! Where does he live?!
You come into a house of worship with
information you should not have,
an outrageous accusation,
no legal warrant and threaten me.
I have not threatened you.
Not yet, but we both
know where this is going.
Jack, it's Chloe. I found something weird
about these hits on Jibraan Al-Zarian.
You know how I said that the $2.000.000
was deposited into his account
over a period of six months?
Well, that wasn't right.
They were backdated.
What about the extremist
Web sites he was visiting?
Same thing with the time stamps.
The hits were backdated 30 minutes ago.
Jibraan could be innocent.
What do you have, Agent?
Armed hostile in the back
room holding a hostage.
- What about Almeida?
- He's not in there.
See for yourself.
Is that who you're looking for?
- No.
- It's Jibraan's brother Hamid.
They're using him as leverage
to make Jibraan do what they want.
- How can you be sure?
- Because that's what I would have done.
Hamid, stop! Put it down.
We're FBI. We need him alive.
The following takes place
between 05:00 A.M. and 06:00 A.M.
The canister's being retrofitted
to maximize dispersion.
We're on target to release the bioweapon at
Washington Central Station within the hour.
Your casualty estimates are holding up?
I think they're conservative.
A significant portion of the pathogen will
escape into the station's ventilation system,
which will circulate it for us.
Between 8.000 and 10.000
commuters will be exposed.
Tell me about Mr. Al-Zarian.
Is he compliant?
Yes. His primary concern at this
point is for the safety of his brother.
All right. What's his level of
awareness regarding the plan?
He won't know anything about
the canister until it's too late.
Good. We'll talk once it's done.
Trigger mechanism's working.
This device will tell me
where you are at all times.
It will also allow us
to talk to each other.
Talk about what?
You still haven't told
me what you want me to do.
Right now I just want
you to get on the subway
and take the Red Line all
the way to Washington Center.
And when I get there?
I'll let you know then.
I'm not stupid.
I know you are going to
blame me for something.
- Jibraan...
- What's your plan, huh?
You are going to hurt people?
Jibraan, the only person you need to
worry about right now is your brother.
You follow my instructions,
and Hamid lives.
You do something stupid, and he dies...
badly. Understood?
Good.
Red Line, westbound, to
Washington Center, got it?
Let's go. Come on.
Sorry this had to happen like this.
We will find your brother.
You should talk to him.
Kid doesn't know anything,
except that his brother was taken
by Tony about a half an hour ago.
He didn't overhear anything
about a target or the time frame.
Right now, he's our only lead.
He's badly injured. I don't know
if he's in any condition to talk.
My God!
Hold his head. I'm going
to give him some morphine.
No, you're not.
His wound is in the
middle of a nerve cluster.
He can go into shock from the pain.
I know. Back off.
You should step out of the room.
Do what you need to do.
Where's Almeida?
Please, just give me the morphine.
I'll give you the morphine as soon
as you talk. Where's Tony Almeida?
- What's the target?
- I don't know...
- What's the target?!
- I don't know!
I'm telling you the truth!
My job was just to watch the
kid and monitor things here.
Almeida didn't tell me where he
was going or where the target is.
How do you contact him?
I can't.
Okay, okay. I have a number.
But I'm not supposed to use
it unless there's a problem.
You better start thinking of one fast.
Where is his phone?
I have it here.
Give him enough morphine so that he can
take the pain out of his voice. Nothing more.
I want you to get Chloe to
run a trace on this number.
Tell her to feed it
back to our cell phones.
You better start thinking
about what you're going to say.
You try and screw with me on this,
it'll be the last thing you ever do.
You understand me?
- Do you understand me?
- Yes.
- Janis Gold.
- It's Renee.
I need Chloe to run a peer-to-peer
cellular trace from a GSM I.D.
I can do that.
Jack asked for Chloe to run point on this.
What's the number?
- Alpha-Charlie-3316.
- Got it.
I'll need you to run it
backthrough to me and Jack.
Hold on.
- She's working on it.
- Good.
I'll open up the locate protocol.
You establish a secure VPN.
All right, opening a
channel on the Inter-Sat...
- Why would you do that?
- What?
You know connecting through a
DMA node would be a lot faster.
No, I don't know it's
quicker to use a DMA node
or else I would have done just that.
I had no idea the DMA
nodes were up and running.
Really? Because they've been up
and running for about two years.
It's obvious I'll never be able to
do things as well as you did at CTU.
All I ask is that you not make me feel like
an idiot while you're pointing that out.
All right.
Agent Walker, the trace is up and
running whenever you're ready.
- Jack.
-Chloe, I'm on.
You ready?
What's the number?
202... 555...
0147.
It's ringing.
- Why are you calling me?
- I was checking Al-Zarian's computer,
- double-checking everything we planted.
- And?
The bank that we use in
Switzerland just e-mailed him,
rejecting one of the transfers
we made in Al-Zarian's name.
You know how to resubmit it?
I'm not sure
Are you getting this?
Tony's got something on his phone
that's encrypting his location.
I'm trying to get around it.
All right. Call our man in Zurich.
He'll walk you through it.
All right. I just wanted to get
your authorization before I did that.
Any other problems?
- No.
- Good.
Chloe, did you get that?
I didn't have time to
decrypt all the location data.
All I know right now is that he's
somewhere in the Adams Morgan district.
We're running out of time.
We're going to have to narrow that down.
I'm trying. I have to decrypt
the rest of the location data.
- How long is that going to take?
- I don't know.
Damn it, Chloe, we've got
to do better than that.
I need to get off the phone.
Janis, I want you to contact Metro P.D.
I want you to get them
to move their Hazmat teams
and their Tactical teams
over to Adams Morgan.
We're on our way now. Let's go.
Metro passengers, this weekend there will be no
Blue Line Express service to Arlington and McClean.
Express service will
be resumed on Monday.
- I need you to call the police.
- Excuse me? Speak up, sir.
I can't do that. They're listening.
Who's listening?
The people who have my brother.
The terrorists.
They're going to kill my brother
unless I do what they say.
They want me to get on this train.
That's it? Just get on the train?
Yes, please. You have to help me, okay?
You have to call the police.
Is there a problem here, sir?
Yes, yes, thank you, officer.
Please, I need your help.
Sir, just calm down and step this way.
What is it?
Listen, they have my brother hostage.
Okay, you have to believe me!
Put the earpiece back in.
- What?
- I said, put the earpiece back in.
Now.
Listen, Jibraan, I
understand you had to try.
But don't do it again.
Your brother's life depends on it.
Yes, okay, please, okay, just
don't hurt him, okay?
Well, that's up to you.
Yes, I'll do whatever you say, okay?
I won't cause any more problems.
I promise.
All right.
Do you remember your instructions?
Yes, uh...
Westbound Red Line to Washington Center.
We'll be watching.
We're always watching.
Hello?
Ms. Taylor, this is Agent Pierce.
Yes, Aaron?
Secretary Woods was asking for you.
You told me you were
retiring to the residence,
but upstairs detail confirmed
that you're not there.
Why is Tim looking for me?
The Justice Department is investigating
the Jonas Hodges car bombing.
They're requesting phone and internet records
and want to interview everyone as well.
I didn't realize Justice
was getting involved.
Apparently, there were only 11
people who knew Hodges was alive.
It stands to reason that
information was leaked.
- Okay, I'll get there as soon as I can.
- Where are you?
I needed to run a personal errand.
Ma'am, am I to understand that
you've left the White House premises
without Secret Service protection?
I won't be long, Aaron. Ten minutes.
Ms. Taylor,
this is a serious breach of protocol.
Your safety is my responsibility.
Aaron, I know.
I promise you it won't happen again.
Just cover for me till I get back?
Will you do that for me, Aaron?
- Yes, ma'am.
- Thank you.
This is a mistake, Martin.
We shouldn't be meeting.
Okay, you need to calm down, Olivia.
I needed to see you;
you were hysterical on the phone.
No, you don't understand!
There's an investigation.
The Justice Department is
asking about my whereabouts!
Okay, did you think no one would bat an
eye when a government witness was murdered?
I told you I changed my mind.
I didn't transfer the funds.
The man you put me  touch with said he
wouldn't act until he received payment.
Why would he go ahead and
kill Hodges if he wasn't paid?
Because I told him to.
What?
He called me and told me the
money hadn't come through yet.
I told him you were
good for it and to proceed.
Why, Martin?
Why would you do that?
Hodges was going into
Witness Protection,
there was a finite
window of opportunity.
And because it's what you wanted.
Right?
Despite all my warnings
for you to reconsider,
you looked me straight in the eye
and you said you wanted Hodges
dead, to make it happen.
And I did, and he's dead.
Oh, my God...
But my phone records...m-my
computer... everything...
Don't worry about any of those.
I'll send you a program to
erase your internet tracks.
The calls to me mean nothing.
Olivia, the time to worry
about your conscience
was before you put this in motion.
If you let this eat away at you,
people are going to
notice and get suspicious.
You will bring us both down...
destroy your mother and her
administration. Think about it.
- Is that what you want?
- No.
Okay,then pull yourself together.
I promise you, this will all
pass if you do what I say.
Can you do that?
Say it.
I can do it.
You need to transfer the funds, Olivia.
You do not want this
man unhappy with you.
- Hey, honey.
- Sorry I woke you.
No, no, no, that's okay. I've been
up with Teri a couple times anyway.
She's been having a rough night.
I think she misses her mother.
Oh, well, listen, I just called to let
you know that my flight's been delayed.
Yeah, how long?
Well, they're saying an hour.
Which probably means two.
Okay.
- What? - I don't know, maybe
you should see this as a sign.
A sign?
That you should stay there...
try to convince your father
that, uh, he should be spending whatever
time he has left with his only dauter.
As much as I want to,
he made it very clear that he does
not want me around to watch him die.
Okay, all right. Sorry I brought it up.
Teri and I will be at
the airport to pick you up.
Wha... Oh... My battery is dying.
Is the hospital okay with that?
Yeah, I talked to Kevin.
He said he'd cover my rounds.
Well, that's-that's... that's great.
Well, I can't wait to see you guys.
- Love you.
- Okay, bye.
- Oh, excuse me, sorry.
- That's all right. Sorry.
- Everything okay?
- Yeah, yeah, sorry.
This stop, L Street. This stop, L Street.
Next stop, Washington Center.
Next stop will be the last one.
Next stop Washingto Center.
The package is in place.
The dispersal mechanism is set to go off
while the train is stopped at Washington Center.
Good, we're on the move.
I'll pick you up at 22nd.
Jack, I unlocked Tony's location data.
Where is he?
Three blocks immediately
south of your position on 22nd.
Where exactly on 22nd?
West side of the block
you're coming up on.
900 feet ahead of you...
800 feet...
All teams, bring your units up from
the south and prepare to move in.
You probably got him.
- Okay, we've got him.
- Suspect is in a black van.
We can't let this turn
into a pursuit. Hold on.
Hold on!
Tony was trying to destroy some
kind of device when I grabbed him!
I got it!
Lock down this piece of crap.
What do u got?
Some kind of mobile computer,
but he damaged it pretty badly.
This has got something
to do with the attack.
Contact Chloe, see what we can find.
I'm gonna sweep the
van for the canister.
Tony's UMPC device is
damaged everywhere I look.
I don't think there's a way
to get it back up and running.
Well, then try a partial reconstruct.
Anything that can help us find
out what Tony's been up to.
At this point I don't even know
about our chances of even doing that.
- Chloe.
- I know.
Do me a favor. Send me your screen.
- Why?
- Why not?
What?
Looks like I can reconstruct the memory
state of the UMPC at the time it was damaged.
No. There isn't enough intact data.
Yeah, there, in the PROM module.
A lot of handheld devices back
up their memory state there.
That can't be done, not
without the file headers.
Really?
Mr. Bauer, Almeida just
regaet consciousness.
Thank you. Stay with this.
I need you to walk away.
Please, can you and
your men just walk away.
Where is it?
Where's the canister?
I am not going to stop until
you tell me where it is.
Why did you betray me?
Why?
I have nothing left to lose.
You either tell me where that canister is,
or so help me God,
I will lay you down right here right now
You think I've got anything left to loose Jack?
Do it.
There were a number of applets running.
We should be able to run them on our hardwe.
I'm uploading a mirror to you now.
You should have it.
You think it's Jibraan?
I can't tell. But whoever it is, they're
southbound on Connecticut at 30 miles an hour.
And they just went right through
St. Matthew's Cathedral and out the other side.
He's got to be on the Metro.
Yes, the Red Line ending
at Washington Center.
Washington Center's the target.
Put these in the car.
Jack, we have Jibraan.
Jibraan is on the Metro,
headed toward Washington Center.
Chloe, it's Jack. I'm back on comm.
How much time do we have?
Not long. He's almost there.
Okay, listen. Tony had to be able
to communicate with Jibraan somehow.
See if they were using some kind of comm frequency
that was strong enough to work in the subway.
Looking... okay.
Wait. There's a proprietary K-band running.
That's it. Okay. Patch me through.
Go ahead, Jack.
Jibraan? Jibraan my name is
Jack Bauer. Can you hear me?
Uh, yes.
Your brother is safe.
I'm working with the FBI.
The man who was holding him hostage
has been taken into custody.
Let me talk to Hamid.
He's not with us right now.
No, no. I need to talk to him.
Jibraan, listen to me.
Your brother is safe, but you are not.
The people who are doing this,
they gave you some kind of a package.
No, no, no.
They didn't give me anything.
We've got real time
coverage of the station.
Jibraan, these people are trying
to frame you for a terrorist attack.
They had to give you
some kind of a package.
Then it's got to be on the train. I want you
to start looking for an abandoned suitcase,
gym bag, knapsack, anything like that.
No, I can't tell. There's nothing.
It's got to be there. Keep looking.
There was a woman.
What woman?
She was with them when, uh,
when they took Hamid.
I think maybe I saw her get off the train.
Are you pulling into the station right now?
Uh, yes.
Okay, I want you to stay on the train and
wait for all the passengers to get off.
It's a bomb, isn't it?
It's a biological weapon. If it goes off,
a lot of people are going to die.
Are all the passengers off the train?
Yes.
- Can you see the package?
- I don't know.
Jibraan, keep looking.
It's got to be there.
Jibraan?
Yes, yes. I see it.
I see a duffel bag.
I need you to open it.
Wait. Why me?
W-W-Why must I do this?
'Cause right now,
you're the only person that can
and if you don't,
thousands of people are going to die.
Jibraan, I need you to open the bag.
Look, I know I'm asking you a lot.
Please.
Jibraan, are you still there?
It looks like a bomb.
I-I see a light.
It's a timer.
It's counting down.
How much time is left?
Uh, two minutes, ten seconds.
That's not enough time
for us to get down to you.
I want you to try and
get the device outside.
There's an escalator to your right.
I want you to start moving now.
Start moving now.
I'll meet you on the street.
We're about a minute out.
Okay.
That's him. Hold on!
- Hold on. What's the hurry?
- I have to get out. I have to get out.
What is that?
Is that even yours?
I have a bomb! Okay?
This is a bomb. Get back!
Everybody, get back!
Get back! I have a bomb!
Wait, he's with us. Jibraan!
Jibraan. I'm the man who was
talking to you. Give me the canister.
Go with these men.
They'll help you. Go!
- Is he all right?
- Yes.
- You're Mr. Bauer?
You did great. Thank you for everything.
I want to see my brother.
I know.
We're going to bring him here.
But right now, I'd like you to go with Agent Moran,
so he can take your statement, please.
Follow me.
- Jack...
- It's all right, it's all right.
You need to give yourself a shot.
I already did, 20 minutes ago.
It's not working.
It's okay. It's okay.
We stopped it.
You can finally rest.
Can I have a piece of paper?
Yeah, sure, you can have all this.
What's that?
This is section "A";
it's the only thing I want.
I'll give it to you
as soon as I'm done.
Excuse me,
do you mind if I sit here?
No, of course not.
- You heading home?
- Yeah
Us too.
We live in Glendale.
Woodland Hills. Oh!
My husband's parents live there.
You know the Pelusos?
I don't think so.
You mind doing me a favor?
Sure.
Do you see the man behind us at a table?
He's wearing a suit.
Uh, short, dark hair?
Yes. Yes, is he staring over here?
No. You know him?
No, it's just that he
was staring at me earlier.
Well, you're very pretty.
-What?
-No, he's moving away now.
I've got her in sight.
She's waiting at the gate now.
They should begin boarding
within the hour.
Okay, look, I know that
the bioweapons threat is over,
but I'd feel a lot better if you'd watch
over her until she gets on that plane.
Yes, sir, I'll let you know
when she's in the air.
Thanks.
I need you to contact the Bureau office.
Tell them we need a full interrogation
package ready for when we arrive.
- Yes, sir.
- Thanks.
Jack?
I just got word.
Jonas Hodges was killed with
a car bomb less than an hour ago.
What? How?
We don't have any leads yet,
but obviously somehow the people he
was working for found out he was still alive.
That means they're going
to be coming after Tony.
We need to transport him in a convoy...
full guard detail, weapons ready.
We're not losing him again.
The FBI located Al-Zarian.
There was nothing we could do.
You're telling me the canister is gone.
Damn it!
Without that pathogen,
everything that we've worked for is finished.
You should also know the FBI has Tony.
Then you need
to have him eliminated.
- Alan.
- He knows too much, Cara.
We can't take the risk that he'll break.
You need to take him out.
I'm trying to tell you
that won't be necessary.
Tony won't be in custody for long.
- What are you talking about?
- Trust me.
We've got another play.
You better have.
The incoming flight from Boston
will be arriving shortly.
Once the passengers have deplaned and
the maintenance crew is given a chance
to clean up the aircraft,
we should be able to begin boarding.
We appreciate your patience.
Thank you.
Well, at least we know the plane's on its way.
I'll believe that when I see it.
Well, I'm gonna get some coffee.
Does anybody want anything?
I'll take a decaf.
Nothing for me, thanks.
Oh, come on.
Are you sure? It's my treat.
No, no, thank you.
Your husband's really nice.
Hmm, he has his moments.
You know what?
I'm, I'm gonna use the restroom.
Do you mind watching my bag?
- Sure.
- Thank you.
Miss Taylor.
Agent Pierce.
I know you're upset I went off protocol,
but as I told you, it won't happen again.
No, ma'am, it won't...
or you'll need to find
someone else to do this job.
Aaron, that won't be necessary.
Ma'am, you said you left the
grounds to run a personal errand.
May I ask what it was?
I just needed to get of here,
be alone, clear my head,
if only for a short time.
Everything that's happened today...
being held hostage,
Jonas Hodges' murder...
and seeing my father
so weak and vulnerable...
I was feeling overwhelmed.
Aaron, I'm trying to live up
to my mother's expectations.
And I didn't want her...
or anyone else for that matter...
to know I was being affected by the pressure.
I hope you can understand that.
Yes, ma'am, I think I can.
You feeling all right now?
I am, actually.
I guess I just needed to tell
someone what was going on with me.
I'm glad
it was someone I could trust.
Well, thank you, ma'am.
I'll have those phone and internet records ready
for the Justice Department investigators shortly.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you, Aaron.
This is Kanin.
Sir, this is Agent Pierce.
I hope I didn't wake you.
No, Agent Pierce,
I'm wide awake.
What can I do for you?
Mr. Kanin, some years ago,
while I served on
President Palmer's detail,
I was made aware of some modifications
made to the Chief of Staff's office.
You mean,
during Mike Novick's tenure.
Yes, sir, specifically the installation
of a voice-activated recordinsystem.
It allows staff meetings
to be logged and archived.
If you're asking whether I used the
recording equipment, the answer's yes.
Sir, did you disconnect it when
you resigned and left your office?
No. Why you asking?
I'd prefer not to
answer that at this time.
I need to know how to
access the digital recorder.
You can't.
It's secured with biometric lock.
You need my thumbprint.
Look, Aaron, if you want my help,
you're gonna have to
tell me what this is about.
Olivia Taylor's still using my office.
Does this have to do with her?
I really can't talk about
this over the phone right now.
I'll be at the White House
within a half hour.
Thank you, sir.
Do you have something
you'd like to say to me?
- Like what?
- Oh, I think you know.
I don't think I do.
How about "Good job, Janice,
on reconstructing the UMPC"?
Or "Just maybe I should have considered the
possibility that you actually know what you're doing."
Oh, you don't know me,
but  you did, you would understand
that this is the last place you
should look for any type of validation.
How about just
acknowledging you were wrong?!
We're almost ready to go.
Okay. Is this her?
Uh, yes, but when I saw her in the Metro,
she had on this dark wig and a leather jacket.
Jibraan, your brother's here.
Hamid!
- Let's pack up.
- Hamid!
Well, the coffee place over here...
excuse me...
didn't have decaf,
so I had to go all the way to
the other end of the terminal,
but I want you to know I got it.
Thank you.
This is Bauer.
I'm sending a link to your phone.
It's something I think you should see.
Who is this?
Open the link, Mr. Bauer.
Who the hell is this?
Your daughter's in the
company of our operatives.
And Agent Franks
has already been neutralized.
You will help Tony Almeida escape
or my people will murder your daughter.
Any effort to contact her
or warn anybody about this
will have the same result,
you understand?
What you're asking
me to do is impossible.
Tony Almeida's already been secured.
He's under heavy guard.
Well, that's your problem.
Put this call on your earpiece
and keep the line open.
I'm gonna be listening
to everything you say.
Now, Bauer.
You're gonna pay
for what you did to Larry.
I thought you were going with Moran.
Changed my mind.
I wanna see this through.
You're gonna make your move
to break Almeida out soon.
I'm gonna tell you what
to do and when to do it.
Oh, and Mr. Bauer,
if any of those agents in
that van get in the way,
you will have to eliminate them,
or your daughter will die.
presented by
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
... ::: www.SubCentral.de ::: ...