Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net
I'd like you to appear on television and
appeal to members of Islamic communities.
Your cabinet feels
you're making a tragic mistake.
The man has murdered countless innocents
and you are putting your hopes
for this country's safety on him.
They will come after you.
I assure you of that.
We're talking about removing the president.
We are in a national crisis
and he is in over his head.
He's brought this on himself.
I need his itinerary,
specifically in regards
to Assad's televised address.
- Why?
- The less you know, the better.
Because of me, Fayed has a device that
can arm all the suitcase nukes he wants.
(Chloe) Don't blame yourself.
When the next bomb goes off
and thousands of more people die,
everybody will remember
I made it possible.
CTU found me. I needed to preoccupy them
with a bomb to enable my escape.
The delivery system software
was programmed for five detonations
at five high-priority targets.
Because of your carelessness,
we are now down to three.
More than enough for our needs, Gredenko.
Our country lost the Cold War
because it was afraid to use these weapons
against the Americans.
Today we will correct that mistake.
And the Arabs will take all the blame.
Marilyn, it is vital that we find Gredenko.
If we retrace the route you took that night,
do you think you'd recognise the house?
Maybe.
What's goin' on with you and Jack?
He's looking for someone.
He thinks I can help.
You mean Gredenko?
What do you know about him?
I followed Graem to a house one night.
He met with some Russians.
Jack wants to take me over there
to see if it can jog my memory.
You won't take Jack where Graem met
the Russians but to a different address.
Now, you do this for me,
and I promise you you will see Josh again.
If you don't, he dies.
Marilyn, is any of this familiar?
Yes. That's it - the blue house on the right.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Go, go!
Bomb! Everyone out!
Come on, come on. Move.
Go, go. Don't stop!
- (phone rings)
- Buchanan.
- It's Jack.
- What do you got?
We've been ambushed. The house that
Marilyn led us to was wired with explosives.
Half my team is down.
Send paramedics to 9407 Hindry Place.
- They knew we were coming.
- Gredenko?
I think so. I'm trying to find Milo and Marilyn.
I think they're being pursued by hostiles.
I'll have a team there.
I'll monitor local bandwidth.
Bill, hurry. We need to find them.
This way. This way, come on.
- Marilyn?
- I can't...
- We gotta keep moving. Move, move.
- I can't.
Come on.
Come on, this way.
(man) Over there. The other way.
- (phone ringing)
- (woman on TV)... within miles of ground zero.
Survivors are being treated at local hospitals
and at makeshift medical facilities.
Local authorities continue to urge people
to stay in their homes until further notice...
- Yeah.
- We took out the CTU team.
- So is my son dead?
- Yes, sir.
Right, well.
Had to be done.
Do you have Marilyn?
- No, sir, not yet.
- Why not yet?
She escaped with someone.
We're tracking them now.
Dammit.
We'll find her soon, sir. The man she's with
doesn't look like a trained field agent.
Make sure you take her alive. I need her
to find Gredenko so I can end this mess.
I understand.
I'll call you as soon as I have her.
(thud)
Ed.
They know we're here.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Marilyn, listen to me.
I'm gonna cover you.
When I do, head back towards the alley.
Run as fast and as far away from here
as you can. You understand me?
- Yeah.
- OK.
Targets are right behind us,
behind those dumpsters.
Remember, we need to take that woman alive.
Just wait. Wait till I tell you.
Go!
(screeching)
Let's go, let's go.
- I told you to go!
- I couldn't! Oh!
- Let's go.
- Wait, wait!
Kill him.
Drop your weapon!
- Let her go!
- Drop your weapon or I'll kill her.
If you wanted to kill her, she'd be dead
by now. Drop your weapon or I will use mine.
Do it!
On your knees! Hands on your head, interlace
your fingers. Turn around and face the fence.
Milo, let me see it.
(moaning)
There's no arterial bleeding.
You'll be OK. CTU will be here in a minute.
Take this gun, make sure he doesn't move.
That call you took was from Gredenko. You
tipped him off. Over half my team is dead!
- You don't understand!
- What, that Gredenko knew we were coming?
It wasn't Gredenko on the phone.
Those aren't his men.
If they weren't Gredenko's men,
whose were they? Who sent them?!
Your father.
- What are you talking about?
- It's true, Jack, I swear.
Your father called me in the car.
My father?
He told me to lead you to that house.
He said if I didn't, he'd...
He said that he killed Graem
and that if he had to, he would kill Josh.
I'm sorry.
He has my son!
Marilyn.
Do you have the address
to Gredenko's safe house?
Yes.
- I need you to give it to me now.
- I can't. Not till I have my son.
I will help you get Josh back,
but I need that address now.
Gredenko is our only chance
of recovering the nuclear weapons.
You saw what happened in Valencia
earlier today? This is going to be worse.
Please, just give me the address.
I recognised the house as we were driving.
It's on Glasgow - 9421.
Don't move.
- (phone rings)
- Buchanan.
I've got the correct address
for Gredenko's safe house - 9421 Glasgow.
Turner's team will be there. Run point.
I want you to send me
a smaller team to my location.
I'm at an industrial park on Pine,
just south of Oxford.
Have the team bring me a vehicle
with a full tactical kit.
They have to transfer Milo to CTU.
He's shot. It's not critical.
Divert the rest of the team to the address
on Glasgow to initiate attack.
Get back to me when you've got Gredenko.
- What's going on?
- I'll explain later.
- That's not good enough.
- Bill, please. Just trust me.
This is personal.
Jack!
How could I have been so stupid?
- Hi.
- Hey.
- Did you finish the vectors?
- No.
If you're having trouble,
I can help you.
I'm just not finished.
And I don't want this to turn into another
conversation about whether or not I'm OK.
I'm sorry, love.
If you can't talk to me,
talk to a staff psychologist or your sponsor.
I don't need them. I'll be fine.
We just heard from Jack. Marilyn Bauer
is safe. She gave us Gredenko's location.
- Milo was shot but he's gonna be OK.
- What happened?
He held off three armed hostiles till
Jack got there. He's up for a commendation.
Debrief him when Medical gives you the OK.
I will. Thanks for rubbing
that salt in the wounds.
- What?
- The nukes are armed cos I'm a coward.
And now you want me to listen to Milo
talk about what a bloody hero he is.
Coincidence?
- It'll be taken care of. Thanks.
- Taken care of.
We're coordinating the Gredenko operation.
TAC teams are moving in on his location.
I'll be right there.
I pushed you to work too soon.
Someone from District will relieve you.
They'll just make me feel worse. I need a few
minutes. I'll be fine. I'm gonna take a walk.
- I'll cover for you. Be back before we launch.
- Yeah, I will.
Give me the phone.
We need to make the call.
"Scramble caller" has to be enabled.
- Give us a second.
- Does he know where Phillip has Josh?
- No. I'll have to force my father's hand.
- Meaning what?
He'll call my father
and tell him he's apprehended you,
but you won't give him Gredenko's location
until he takes you to see your son.
What if Phillip refuses?
You have to stay firm. Say it's not
a negotiation, no matter what he threatens.
Jack, you're asking me
to put Josh's life at risk.
Josh's life is at risk.
My father won't give away his location
unless he thinks he has to.
Is that what this is about, finding Phillip?
Josh is secondary?
My father will have Josh with him.
Marilyn, I will do everything in my power
to make sure your son is safe.
How do you know he won't betray us?
He wants to live.
Let's go.
(man on TV) As biohazard and hazmat units
make their way to the hot zone...
You don't want to watch this.
You know, Josh.
Your father was very proud of you.
He'd tell me how blessed he felt
knowing everything he was working so hard
to build would be left in such good hands.
- Do we have to talk about this now, Grandpa?
- No, of course not.
He loved you very much.
Remember, I'll be able to hear both sides
of this conversation. You're set, dial.
(phone rings)
- Do you have her?
- Yeah.
But we took casualties.
I'm on my own now.
- You're getting a team to take out Gredenko?
- Yeah, I am.
She won't say where Gredenko is
until she sees her son.
Put her on.
- I did what you asked. Now, where's Josh?
- Marilyn, look.
I know you're frightened.
This doesn't have to end badly.
If you help me find Gredenko,
we can all survive this as a family.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I just want my son!
I'm just saying, you made your deal
with Graem, now make a deal with me.
With enough time, you and I and Josh
can rebuild whatever is left of this family.
After all, the legacy I'm trying to preserve
will someday be his. We can do this.
But first you have to tell me
where Gredenko is.
Only after this man takes me to see my son.
That will only complicate things.
I need Gredenko now.
Tell me where he is.
No.
You may have misunderstood my offer as
a sign of weakness, so let me make it clear.
If you do not help me,
I see no future for you or Josh.
I will walk into the next room
and I will kill him.
Right now.
Tell me... or Josh dies.
I will not tell you
what you want to know until I have my son!
Give him back the phone.
Yeah.
Bring her here to me
at the Grandmont Hotel, room 2132.
We're on our way.
We got the address. You did great.
Cuff him, put him in the back.
- Josh?
- Uh...
I'll go downstairs to get a soda.
You want anything?
- No, thanks. Did you look in the mini bar?
- Uh...
There wasn't anything that I wanted.
Why don't you call room service?
Well, I just feel like getting out.
Josh. Don't even think about it.
No one's life is worth the destruction
of everything I've built.
Now, step away from the door.
I was beginning to worry.
The meeting went long.
Here is the president's itinerary.
Oh, good. This will work.
- So when does all this happen?
- Now.
Authorise clearance for someone to get inside
the bunker. Once he's in, he'll carry the ball.
Carry the ball?
You mean kill the president.
I like to think we're beyond
doubting ourselves.
This president has endangered
the lives of millions.
You do not need to tell me
what the stakes are here.
- So who are we putting inside?
- A security specialist, private sector.
I requested that he advise my group
on several response options.
He has level-two clearance. Upgrade him.
- They will trace this thing right back to me.
- No, you won't even be investigated.
We have a cover.
- A cover? Who?
- Assad.
You're trying to make it look like he did this?
Just call in your authorisation code.
That's all the information you need.
(phone rings)
- Yeah, Dan?
- The president's asked to see you.
OK, tell the president
I will be with him in a moment.
Sir, our man will be here within the hour.
Call me when you're done with the president.
Oh, Tom, come in.
- You asked to see me?
- I'd like to hear your thoughts on something.
- My thoughts? On what, sir?
- Assad's speech.
He's going live in less than an hour. Before
I give him my thoughts, I wanted yours.
Is there a problem?
- No, sir. It's just...
- What?
I assumed you were no longer
interested in my opinions.
Tom, I still value yourjudgment.
And if I've made you
feel otherwise, I apologise.
All right, sir.
How much longer?
I'm not sure. I have to recalculate
the profile for two of the target cities.
Hurry. I don't want to be exposed like this
any longer than necessary.
You think the authorities know
we're working with Fayed?
If they don't, they will soon.
I was in my kitchen when I saw the flash.
I turned to look out my window
and it just exploded.
All the windows.
There was glass everywhere.
And then there was this sound.
It was so loud.
- Oh, man. Hell of a day, huh?
- Yeah, you could say that.
- Can I get you anything else?
- No.
Yeah.
Whiskey, pint, single malt.
- What kind?
- That kind.
- This?
- Yeah.
- And these.
- OK.
- Wait, your change?
- Keep it.
- I'm on my way.
- From where?
I told you, I went out for a walk.
The TAC team is about to move in
on Gredenko. I need you at your station.
- I'm on my way.
- Morris...
Come with me.
I want you to put this on under your clothes.
It's just a precaution.
- My hands are shaking.
- Here.
I'm gonna do everything I can
to get him back.
He's the only reason I stayed with Graem.
He's the only good thing I have left since.
You ready?
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
Get out.
You do exactly what I tell you,
you understand me?
Let's go.
(woman) Agent Pressman,
I just want to make sure you understand that
you need to not exert too much pressure...
- Hey, Milo.
- Hey.
- How are you holding up?
- They say I'm gonna be OK.
It's... So, what happened?
I was stupid.
They don't pay me to be a field agent.
Maybe they should. You protected
Marilyn Bauer. That's what I heard.
I had no idea what I was doing.
The thing just happened so fast.
You don't have to downplay it to make me
feel better. You don't have to do that.
- OK.
- Yeah.
Hey. You OK?
Yeah.
- Well done.
- Thanks.
We'll push Assad to make these changes.
Your suggestions are all excellent, Tom.
- Just doing my job.
- I'd like you to be there when he delivers this.
I will be. Excuse me,
I have a briefing with Senator Benson.
Of course, Tom.
Melinda, I have notes
that need to be taken to Assad.
Yes, Mr President. I'll be right in.
- What did he want?
- He asked me to review Assad's speech.
He'll never get the chance to deliver it.
You need to authorise that clearance.
- Our man will be here any minute.
- It's in the works. It's just taking a while.
- We need it before he's here.
- I will call Security again.
I'll call if there's a problem.
Go meet with him.
All right.
(man) Operations.
I need to speak to the ranking
Secret Service agent on site.
- Yes.
- (man #2) Agent Hollister.
This is Tom Lennox.
I need to see you immediately.
I can meet you as soon as I get someone
to man my position in about 15 minutes.
I've got something to show you.
Where are you right now?
- B wing, room 17.
- I'm on my way.
Carson wondered if you were playing us.
He didn't want to bring you into this.
But I said that we could trust you.
I told him that you understood!
- Nothing justifies killing the president.
- This president is giving us no choice.
- Don't do this.
- It's already done.
- (man) Operations.
- This is Reed Pollock.
I have a message
for Agent Hollister from Mr Lennox.
Tell him the issue has been resolved and
that Mr Lennox won't need to meet with him.
- I'll tell him.
- OK, thanks.
We confirmed the intel. The Glasgow house
is owned by a Russian shell corporation
that Gredenko has an interest in.
- Is Turner's team in place?
- They'll say when they're ready.
Chloe, lock the satellite
and establish a comm link.
Nadia.
- I told you not to take too long.
- Sorry.
- The backup module needs to be reset.
- Do it. The operation starts in two minutes.
Come with me.
Do you realise what a betrayal this is?
I was a little late.
Morris, I can smell it on your breath.
Yes, I took a drink.
But I spat it out straight away.
- Please.
- I swear. Chloe, look at me. Look at me.
I am stone-cold sober.
You're losing control.
You're placing other people's lives in danger.
I'm gonna have to tell Buchanan.
After everything that has happened.
Something had to give.
The important thing is that I realised
I didn't want to throw everything away.
Especially you, especially you.
And I stopped myself
and that is a little victory. Right?
I swear it will never happen again.
Don't tell Buchanan because you're right.
Me getting back to work is the best medicine.
- I'll be watching you for the rest of the shift.
- Fine.
- Call your sponsor.
- I will.
- Terrorist team is taking final positions.
- Chloe, open the video link.
Hal, what's your status?
No sign of a lookout.
- Windows are covered but we're good to go.
- Commence at your discretion.
- Ryan, is your team ready?
- Yes, sir.
OK, we're going in on three, two, one.
Cover, cover.
- (man #1) Clear.
- (man #2) Clear.
- (man #3) Clear!
- (man #4) Clear.
- (man #5) Clear.
- (man #6) Clear.
First sweep all clear, sir.
Roger that.
Mr Buchanan,
there's no sign of Gredenko or anyone.
Hal, when you complete the sweep,
process for evidence.
Yes, sir.
Chloe, text Jack's cellphone
and tell him we don't have Gredenko.
Open it.
Hold up here.
- What's wrong?
- It's nothing.
Don't think about warning my father.
Once he sees you brought me here, he's more
likely to shoot you than I am. Understand?
Both of you go up to the door. You knock.
When he lets you in, I'll follow. Let's go.
Marilyn, get back.
Open the door. Now, go.
- Where the hell is my father?
- I don't know. I swear.
- Where's Josh?
- Marilyn, just stay calm.
Put these on.
(phone rings)
Answer. Put it on speaker.
- Hello?
- (Phillip) Hello, Marilyn.
Jack, even when you were young
I learned not to underestimate you.
I didn't want to hurt Josh.
You forced my hand.
Take a look out the window,
the adjacent roof.
Oh, Phillip, please don't!
Dad, you only have one play left here - that's
to try and cut a deal with the government.
Explain your connection to the nuke
and that you'll help in exchange for immunity.
That is your only option. You pull that trigger
and that option is gone. Understand?
I'm no fool, Jack. They're never gonna
give me immunity after everything I've done.
You don't know that for sure!
Right now, they are desperate. But either way,
for you, this is over. Dad, it's over!
There is no empire to protect,
there's no legacy left.
There is Marilyn, Josh and me. That's it.
Please, Dad.
I know you don't want to hurt Josh.
I'm the one you want.
You let Josh go, I will surrender.
Come alone, unarmed, and I'll let Josh go.
But if you bring anyone else into this,
I will kill him.
I understand.
Hang up the phone.
- (man) Field Ops.
- This is Jack Bauer.
Send a team to the Grandmont Hotel to pick
up a hostile. He's secured. He's in room 2132.
Right away.
Jack.
This is our only chance.
Hey, I need to talk to you.
- About what?
- Morris.
- Not here.
- He came and saw me in the infirmary...
- I know he's been a little shaky.
- Has he been drinking?
- You smelled it on his breath?
- Yeah.
I did too. We talked.
He didn't metabolise the alcohol.
"He didn't metabolise the alcohol"?
It sounds weird, but it's true.
He spit it out.
- How do you know?
- Cos he told me.
- And you believe him?
- We were married. If he was drunk, I'd know.
He's not drunk.
He's been sober for three years.
- I didn't know he was an alcoholic.
- Now you know.
- You don't think Buchanan should know?
- No.
If he slips up again,
I will personally tell Buchanan.
Let's just leave it for now.
OK.
OK, I want you to wait here for Josh.
Do you think your father will keep his word?
If I keep mine.
You know how to use this?
- No.
- Point, hit, shoot.
Do you want me to call CTU
and tell them to send help?
No. I need to take care of this myself.
Jack... thank you.
Everything is gonna be all right.
Just wait here.
I'm unarmed!
Dad?
I'm unarmed.
- Come out. I am unarmed!
- (Phillip) That's close enough.
Turn around.
Now show me that you're not
wearing an ankle holster.
Take one step toward me
for every step Josh takes away.
Josh.
Slowly.
Your mother is waiting
in the stairwell. Go! Go!
That's it.
Oh, Josh! Oh, God!
Are you OK? Are you OK? Let's go. Go!
I never meant for this to happen, Jack.
I didn't have a choice.
I don't know how, but Gredenko found out
about my role in Palmer's assassination.
So he blackmailed me.
Forced me to cooperate.
So Gredenko had you divert the bombs your
company was responsible for destroying?
He's a radical nationalist.
Told me that he wanted to preserve arsenal
for the day when the Soviet Union
would be re-established.
I believed him because I had to.
- When did you know he sold them to Fayed?
- When the bomb was detonated in Valencia.
- That's the truth?
- Absolutely.
I've been looking for Gredenko ever since
so that I could find out
what he knew about Fayed and stop this.
I'm a patriot, Jack. I never wanted
any harm to come to this country.
You wanna lie to yourself, you go ahead.
But stop lying to me!
You let all of this happen
just so you could cover up what you did.
You have all the smarts
that Graem never had.
You'd have handled Gredenko
before this all got out of control.
You know, none of this would have happened
if you hadn't turned your back on me.
So that you could become what?
A civil servant?
So your people will use Gredenko
to find this terrorist.
- The truth will come out about all I've done.
- We never got Gredenko.
Then all of this was for nothing.
On your knees.
It didn't have to end like this, Jack.
You could have had it all.
I want you to know...
I never wanted you to feel
like I had turned my back on you.
That I had turned my back on the family.
I just had to go my own way.
Do things for myself. I...
I was never good enough for you.
I'm sorry.
Anyway...
I'm ready.
What are you waiting for?
Do it! Damn you.
(rings)
Yes.
My name is Jack Bauer.
Who am I talking to?
You must have exhausted
your options to find Gredenko.
Who is this?
It's Charles Logan, Jack.
I might be able to help you but we need
to talk face-to-face. Where are you?
- I'm near the airport.
- Good. You're local.
CTU knows where I am.
Come and see me, Jack.
As soon as possible.
And come alone.
I'm looking forward to it.
Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net