- Have you got it yet?
- I told you I'd call when I have everything.
I'm paying you a lot of money, Collette.
If you could've got the specs of a facility this
secure from someone else, you would have.
CTU is no longer an obstacle.
This facility has been contaminated
with Sentox VX-1 nerve gas. I repeat...
Move, people.
In the situation room. Now. Seal it.
Lynn, it's Jack. We found
a computer interrupt in the AC control.
If we shut that down in the next few minutes,
we can stop the gas permeating safe zones.
You're the only person
close enough to get to it.
Lynn, the truth is if I could get there, I would
do this myself, but I'm not close enough.
But I'm gonna have to ask you
to do it without any protection.
He did it.
CTU is protecting this city. Are you saying
they're no longer capable of doing that?
They've been seriously compromised.
We've got terrorists with nerve gas out there.
Who will stop them?
Mr. President,
I suggest an emergency restructuring.
CTU is no longer an operational entity.
It's a building with workers
who will report to us.
I can see no other option but to impose
martial law on the city of Los Angeles.
What I will not do is stand by
and watch Hal Gardner use you
to promote his own agenda.
You killed my wife,
Michelle Dessler, this morning.
She was my life, and you took her.
He's got a gun. You can't do this.
We have to get him talking. He's our only lead
to Bierko and the rest of the Sentox canisters.
- You've had your chance. He's mine now.
- Tony!
- I am so sorry.
- Has security found Henderson yet?
No, he got out of the building
before the lockdown.
An external cam got a shot of him leaving.
His car was found a block away.
- But I think we got what we need.
- What are you talking about?
Chloe decrypted a file from his computer.
She found someone connected to Bierko.
Who is Collette Stenger?
She's an intelligence broker.
State secrets, intellectual property.
- What's her connection to Bierko?
- They met twice over the last eight months.
And we think she brokered the deal.
Is she in LA?
She gave a hotel name to customs,
but nothing to say she's there.
Curtis is prepping a tactical team.
OK, good work.
Manning.
- When is the tac team leaving?
- Right now.
- I'm going with you.
- All right.
Ladies and gentlemen,
members of the press,
just so you're aware, there will be no Q and A
following the president's statement...
Are you having second thoughts?
Putting soldiers on the streets of LA -
this will not be popular.
Maybe not, but it's the right move.
Hal, would you excuse us, please?
Mrs. Logan, the president's
about to go on the air.
I'll be brief.
I would like a moment alone
with my husband.
I've made up my mind.
I'm not debating this any more.
Listen, please.
Mike Novick spoke to someone at CTU.
They have a lead on Bierko and they may
find him before he launches another attack.
CTU was just hit. 40% % of their people
are either dead or unable to work.
To think they could stop this
is just wishful thinking.
Maybe not.
Bringing the military in
is the best way to maintain order.
The vice president's right about that.
Of course he is.
What does that mean?
Has it ever occurred to you that he proposed
this whole thing to set you up for a fall?
- So he gets the nomination next year.
- That's insane.
Hal's only motivation
is what's best for the country.
There's going to be fallout.
Hal knows it and you know it.
Mr. President.
- I have to go.
- Charles.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the President of the United States.
As you all know, America has been hit today
by a series of terrorist strikes,
beginning with the assassination
of former president David Palmer
and the murder
of innocent Americans at Ontario airport,
followed by the attempted assassination
of President Yuri Suvarov.
These events are being orchestrated
by terrorists operating within our borders.
Our most recent intelligence suggests
that they will strike again and soon.
I can and will do my sworn duty
to ensure the safety of the American people.
Therefore, I am issuing an executive order
imposing a curfew on all civilians
in the Los Angeles metropolitan area.
This curfew will be effective immediately
and will be enforced by the military.
As disruptive and distasteful
as I know this is for many of you,
I ask that you remember that we are at war.
Bracing ourselves against future attacks...
DOD is asking
for a list of our casualties.
I don't want any names released
until the next of kin have been notified.
- Let me know when that happens.
- OK.
This place is a sinking ship. We should
take over now, not go through an assessment.
Until we transition,
we need everyone here functioning.
Once the canisters have been found and the
terrorists captured, then we'll assume control.
- Karen.
- Hello, Bill.
Bill Buchanan, Miles Papazian.
Your coming wasn't necessary.
We just need to replace some personnel.
We're sorry, but the White House
feels you may need more than that.
They want an assessment
of how Homeland may best assist CTU.
- I'll brief you in my office.
- Fine.
Familiarise yourself
with the networks and start the survey.
- Let's go.
- Upstairs.
- Chloe O'Brian?
- Who are you?
- Homeland Security.
- I asked your name.
- I need a vacant station set up.
- I'm kind of busy right now.
I'm seeing Edgar Stiles
listed on my report as a casualty.
Is that right?
Yeah.
Then his station should be available.
I'll set up over there.
I'll be reinstalling operating protocols
so I'll need your key card.
No.
- I'm sorry?
- You can't have my key card.
We're here with a priority admin directive.
You can confirm that on your own time.
We're live in Los Angeles.
A few minutes ago,
army units stationed in LA County
began moving in force across city limits.
This is the first time
a military presence of this scale
has been activated
in a major metropolitan area.
While White House officials have
stopped short of officially declaring...
- Where are you going?
- I just need some fresh air.
These divisions were activated
shortly after the president's press conference,
in which he declared...
- I do not trust him.
- Ma'am?
The vice president.
- This is Aaron Pierce.
- Aaron, it's Wayne Palmer.
Sir, I am so sorry about President Palmer.
More sorry than I can describe.
I know you were close to my brother.
He felt the same way about you.
Thank you for saying that.
He's the reason I'm calling. There's something
from my brother I need to give you.
- I'll be there in an hour.
- You're coming here?
It sounds impulsive,
but I'd rather see you sooner than later.
- Well, there's a curfew in effect, sir.
- I know. I left before it was declared.
If I may say so, this is an odd request.
Aaron, my brother trusted you with his life.
- I am asking you to trust me.
- All right.
I'd also appreciate it
if you would keep this between us.
I'm hoping there's somewhere
we can meet discreetly.
- I'll find a place.
- Thank you. I'll call you when I'm close.
The effects of this will ripple
across the country as other cities take note.
While legislators debate the legality
of President Logan's action, martial law is...
Mike, turn it off.
"Debate the legality of
President Logan's action. " Did you hear that?
They're talking about this
like it's an illegal action.
Don't worry, Mr. President.
I'm in control of the situation.
Our legal people are working on it right now.
Do we have anything more from CTU?
They're still following up on this Bierko lead.
As soon as they have something to report,
we'll be the first to hear.
Give me details
of the current threat assessment.
There's a high probability that Bierko
is planning an attack on a much larger scale.
That's why he targeted CTU,
to cripple our ability to stop him.
And the question is, was he successful?
Looking at the numbers,
you were harder hit than you thought.
We're still functioning - not at 100% %,
but with the people I've asked for
we'll be back to fighting strength.
Any progress finding Bierko?
We've identified a woman
who might lead us to him - Collette Stenger.
- We've just sent a tac team to bring her in.
- Good.
I enjoy watching you get dressed almost as
much as I enjoy watching you get undressed.
You should get dressed yourself
and send the bags down.
This deal you're working on -
I hope you're getting a lot of money for it.
I never talk about my business.
I know, but Maria called
about this villa in Positano.
She said when you see it, you'll love it.
We'll call her later.
I'll see you at the airport, OK?
In 45 minutes.
I'll be there.
- Yes.
- I'm on my way.
- And you have everything I asked for?
- Of course.
- Good.
- Do you have the money?
When I verify the merchandise,
I'll transfer it to your account.
I'll be there soon.
- Does she have the schematics and codes?
- Yes. Everything we need.
The distribution centre is a difficult target.
It would be easier
to hit a less secure location.
No, Mikhail, this is the place.
We'll release the Sentox here...
and 200,000 people die.
And we need a second satellite repositioned
as soon as possible. Good. Thank you.
I saw a request for proficiency evaluations for
all CTU personnel on my secondary screen.
That's a formality.
We don't have time for evaluations.
- Why was it put in the pipeline?
- It's a formality.
You're shutting us down, aren't you?
The evaluations will be filled in later.
- I told you before, the White House...
- I know what you told me before.
Now tell me the truth.
The truth is,
CTU is being absorbed by Homeland,
which means from now on every
operational decision needs to go through me.
What did you expect? 56 of your people
have been killed. The others are demoralised.
They're not demoralised.
They're angry. They want to fight back.
- They're willing to lay down their lives.
- It's done, Bill. The decision's been made.
Neither of us wants this transition
to interfere with ongoing protocols,
so let's just keep it between us,
at least until this crisis plays out.
Bill.
Homeland is being overly aggressive
with their survey. What is going on?
Nothing. It's just a formality.
They'll be gone
as soon as they finish their evaluation.
Where are we on the military mobilisation?
Martial law is in effect
in nine of the 15 LA districts.
I'm setting up checkpoints
for the rest of the county now.
I hope the president's doing the right thing.
Alpha team,
we're approaching Stenger's room.
- We're ready to move. Are you in position?
- We've got the lobby covered.
All right. Copy.
I think she went for the roof. Cover the stairs.
Let's go. We're going up top.
Drop the gun!
Stand down or he dies!
I said stand down!
Our people are all around you. They will
drop you before you can pull that trigger.
Put the gun down.
- What do you mean? Who are you?
- Counter Terrorist Unit, Los Angeles.
Show me identification.
I'm with the German
Federal Intelligence Service.
My name's Theo Stoller.
- What are you doing here?
- I'm here on special assignment.
By agreement between our governments.
Get the hell out of here
before you destroy my cover.
That's not gonna happen.
- O'Brian.
- It's Jack.
I want you to check on a foreign agent
on the SA list - Theo Stoller.
OK.
Got it. Theo Stoller.
Height - 5'11", brown hair, brown eyes.
He's a German operative,
but trained in England at Ml6.
- There's even contact information.
- Chloe, that's enough, thanks.
- I told you. You have to get out of here.
- We can't. You were with Collette Stenger.
- We need her to help us find Vladimir Bierko.
- I don't know him.
He's responsible
for the terrorist attacks today.
He's preparing another one.
Collette Stenger is the only way to find him.
Where is she?
- I can't help you.
- Why not?
- Giving you her jeopardises my operation.
- What operation?
I've been gathering intel on her clientele.
We've identified cells in three countries.
She's connected to a dozen more.
She's too valuable to give up.
If we don't find Bierko, hundreds
of thousands of innocent people will die.
That is more important than your operation.
It's not about importance.
It's about different agendas.
Your job is to save American lives,
mine to save German lives.
You're asking me
to betray my duty to my country.
Ask yourself what you'd do in my position.
You better ask yourself
what you would do in mine.
- Let's go.
- I'm here by permission. You can't touch me.
Right. We'll see about that.
Make sure your superior knows
that if this attack happens,
my government will hold
your country accountable.
Jack, it's Buchanan.
Audrey will be joining us momentarily.
You're on the line with Karen Hayes
from Homeland Security.
She's supporting CTU.
She's been in contact with the White House.
Did the president
contact the German chancellor?
- He's unreachable for another hour.
- We don't have another hour.
- There's nothing we can do.
- Jack, I just spoke with German intelligence.
They're refusing
to order their agent to cooperate with us.
- Maybe you can get a deal with him.
- I'll talk to him.
- Call me if you get him to change his mind.
- Yeah.
Curtis.
- Give me a moment with him.
- What are you doing?
It's all right.
All right.
Let's go.
Your intelligence service denied our request
for cooperation. So has your government.
I'm not surprised.
Collette Stenger's a golden goose.
There's no upside in giving her up.
Maybe I could provide you with one.
Meaning?
I will give you something
that is more valuable than Collette Stenger.
It's hard to know what that might be.
Our roster of all known terrorist suspects
working around the world - our WET list.
As allies, we've requested
this WET list many times before.
But the NSA has always said giving us
the list would jeopardise their operations.
It will, but I don't work for the NSA.
I don't work for CTU.
This is personal. Right now,
you're not giving me another choice.
All right.
I'll give you Collette
in exchange for the WET list.
Good. Let's see what we can do.
Agent Bauer.
I'm aware of several names
that should be on that list.
Don't try and pass me a fake.
O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Jack. Do we still have
a back door to NSA's secured mainframe?
- I can't really talk now.
- OK, fine, then listen.
I need you to log on to their server, download
the WET list and send it to my PDA.
Why?
The WET list is what we have to pay
to get Collette Stenger.
That list is as top-secret as it gets.
Homeland sent a team.
You'll have to clear it with them.
We can't afford for them to say no.
I'm not saying I won't do it, I'm saying I can't.
They took my key card.
I can't get into the NSA mainframe.
Do what you have to.
It's our only way to Bierko.
Fine. I'll call you back.
- Here you are.
- OK.
- Excuse me, Miles.
- My God! What is the matter with you?
Sorry.
What's wrong with you?
I'll pay for the dry-cleaning.
- Yeah?
- Jack, I got on the NSA server.
- Did you get the file?
- Not yet. They put extra authentication in.
- Can you get around it?
- Hold on.
OK, I got it. I hope you know
what you're doing. I'm uploading it now.
Thanks.
I got it.
Well, it appears legitimate.
It is. Give me back the memory card.
You can't upload the WET list to your people
until I have Collette Stenger in custody.
Fair enough.
We have to go now. We're supposed
to meet at Van Nuys airport in 20 minutes.
- What kind of a car is she driving?
- I don't know. I have to wait in car lot C.
She'll recon the area before
she makes contact. She's cautious by habit.
Curtis, Van Nuys airport.
We'll give you details on the way.
Copy that. All teams, move out.
When you receive the funds,
transfer them to the Caymans account.
- In what currency?
- In euros.
One moment
to enter the authorisation... Logged in.
My bank is ready to accept the transfer.
The file is encrypted.
What is the decryption key?
Transfer the funds.
- It's been sent.
- Your transaction is completed.
Thank you.
Email me confirmation of the transfer.
The decryption key
is Charlie, Alpha, three, nine, Alpha.
It worked. This is what you wanted.
Of course it is.
Until next time, gentlemen.
- Are the men ready?
- Yes.
Torch this place. We're moving out.
I'm not trying to coopt your authority,
but we are in the middle of a crisis here.
Either transmit my orders
to the National Guard,
or I can federalise them and give them
my orders directly. Your choice.
- We'll do it your way.
- Excellent. Thank you, Governor.
I look forward to your cooperation.
We have a situation at a roadblock.
- The commander needs your call.
- Tell me.
Wayne Palmer is insisting he be let through.
- He claims he's on official business.
- And where exactly is that?
- He was on the access road to the retreat.
- He's on his way here? To do what?
He wouldn't give the officer in charge
of the roadblock any information at first.
What should I tell the roadblock, sir?
All I'm asking you to do
is call and confirm I have clearance.
Regardless of clearance, authorisation must
come down through the chain of command.
And just who would that be, huh, Captain?
Who's in charge of the military's role in this?
- Riggs.
- Mr. Palmer's clearance is approved.
- Understood.
- He's allowed into the retreat.
Thank you, sir.
You can go on through now, sir.
Let him through.
Thank you, Captain.
All teams are in position.
- No one moves in until I confirm that it's her.
- Copy that.
Collette won't show herself if she senses
anything's wrong. Make sure he stays hidden.
Don't worry. He will.
What'll happen to her, to Collette?
- I don't know yet. Why?
- Just curious.
Have you been in my situation?
I've been undercover
for long stretches of time, yeah.
Ever been involved with a woman
during that time?
We're doing
what has to be done for our countries,
but sometimes it's harder than others.
- Could you join us in the situation room?
- Sure.
- What's going on?
- Why don't you tell us, Ms O'Brian?
I don't know.
We've got you hacking into
a top-secret NSA archive.
- I don't know what you mean.
- I pulled an archive of your traffic.
Whatever you took from NSA
was uploaded to Jack Bauer's remote node.
Ms O'Brian, tell us exactly
what document you passed to Jack Bauer.
Chloe, this is gonna get much worse
if you force me to have NSA run a back trace.
What is it?
- Jack needed the WET list.
- What?
Why on earth would you give him that?
Stoller wouldn't lead us
to Collette Stenger without it.
Giving that list to another
intelligence agency could be disastrous.
Years of work could be rendered useless.
- Jack needed it, OK?
- No! No, It's not OK!
And you expected us
to give your agents a chance?
Get me Bauer.
Put it on speakerphone
or I'm getting out of this car.
Fine.
- It's Bauer.
- Jack, it's Bill. Karen Hayes is here as well.
If you're with Stoller,
get someplace you can talk privately.
I can't. If I move, I'll jeopardise our position.
You'll have to speak in front of him.
Have you given him the WET list?
- Yes.
- Has he given it to German intelligence?
- No.
- Then get it back now!
I can't. Stoller won't cooperate and we'll lose
Collette Stenger. Bill, explain this to her.
It's not his decision. Retrieve the WET list
now or I will order Agent Manning to do it.
Collette Stenger
is our only connection to Bierko.
If you blow this, you will be responsible
for every life lost in his next attack.
- I don't like to be threatened, Mr. Bauer.
- That's not a threat, that's a fact.
German intelligence will move
on people we have been watching for years.
Our ability to prevent terrorist attacks
will be threatened.
It's a risk we'll have to take.
We have to deal with this situation.
It's not your call or mine.
- We need authorisation from the president.
- Then get it!
Our team ID'd a woman
fitting Stenger's description
driving a red Lexus making a circuit
around the lot. It could be her.
We have a possible suspect approaching.
Ms Hayes, are you telling me that
I have to abort this operation? Yes or no?
Ms Hayes, this is your call.
You don't know for certain
that she will lead us to Bierko.
No, not for certain.
But right now, she's our only lead.
Are you willing to take this chance?
You've left me no choice. Proceed. But you
have severely compromised this situation
and I promise you
there will be repercussions.
Fine.
Are we all right?
We're fine.
Red Lexus turning the corner.
100 yards away.
No one move until I give a go.
The red Lexus has parked.
Move the centre mirror
so that I can see the car.
There.
Now get her out of the car.
- Hi.
- Hello.
I have a positive ID. Move in.
All teams, move! Let's go!
- Put your hands where I can see them!
- Get in the car now. Let go of me.
- Let me see your hands!
- Let go now!
- Theo, get out of there.
- I'm sorry.
Theo, who are you?
Move! Let him go.
He's given us what we want.
Put your hands up!
Turn and face the car.
Put your hands on the roof.
Do it!
Where is Bierko?
We know you're working with Bierko.
Where is he?
Fine.
Take her back to staging.
I want a team searching this car.
Everything goes back
to the staging area. Now!
- Yeah.
- It's Theo. I'm going to the hotel.
Tell Heinrich I'm uploading something
he's been wanting for a long time.
- Stoller.
- Theo, it's Jack.
- I'm sorry.
- We had a deal.
When this is over, I will help you rebuild
your investigation. I give you my word.
I had your word. Now I know what it's worth.
- What have you got?
- There's no sign of what she sold to Bierko.
Come with me.
Collette Stenger, my name is Jack Bauer.
- Who is Theo? Really?
- German intelligence.
He sold me for a price. German and US
intelligence don't work together often.
Where is Bierko?
The fact is, I actually had feelings for Theo.
I never once suspected. He was very good.
I always thought that
there were some things that you cannot fake.
Bierko.
- Tell them to leave.
- Jack?
It's all right.
Curtis, have your men move back.
Just give us a second.
You heard him.
Theo had a price. What's yours?
- I'm not for sale.
- Everyone is for sale.
This isn't a game, lady. We're
running out of time. Tell me what you want.
All right.
Full immunity, no holdbacks,
signed by your president and transmitted
to lawyers in Zurich and Tripoli.
- But I can't tell you where Bierko is.
- Why not?
He's gone. I met him at a safe house.
- He was going to carry out the attack.
- What did you sell him?
- I don't know.
- What do you mean?
- I don't know. It was a schematic.
- What kind of a schematic?
I'm paid to broker the information,
not dwell on the details. It's my firm policy.
You want me to believe you acquired
information and didn't know the specifics?
You can believe whatever you want.
I got the schematics from a source
and they were digitally encrypted.
That source can tell you what they mean. Give
me immunity and I'll give you my source.
Those are my terms.
You haven't offered us very much.
I'll see what I can do.
Buchanan.
It's Jack. She wants full immunity.
She claims she doesn't know where Bierko is,
that she brokered a deal for schematics
and delivered them.
She doesn't know what building they're for,
but she can provide the source.
- She doesn't know what she sold him?
- She said it was encrypted.
- Do you believe her?
- She's an independent contractor.
In her work, sometimes
what you don't know will save your life.
If she's telling the truth, we don't have much
time. She said Bierko left for his next attack.
Call Mike Novick. Get this started.
Jack, this better work.
And for the record, I don't like it.
We've paid a steep price.
There'll be fallout on the WET list.
The fallout will be from German intelligence.
I programmed the memory card
to self-destruct.
- Why didn't you tell us this before?
- I was in the car with Stoller.
Get back to me as soon as this is done.
We need to move fast.
I think it's clear - CTU was hit,
but we're still doing our job.
I believe that's an argument
to maintain our autonomy.
I'll withhold judgment. We're giving
a free pass to a terrorist collaborator.
I've yet to see what we're getting from it.
- Has the document been received in Tripoli?
- Yes.
- It meets with your approval?
- It does.
There's no way
they can fail to live up to the terms?
- Not if you give them what they want.
- Merci, Hervé. Au revoir.
The safe house is a manufacturing facility
at 12451 Saticoy Boulevard.
As for the data I sold to Bierko, I received it
from a contact at the Department of Defense.
- What's his name?
- Her name.
Audrey Raines.
You are lying to me.
She sold me the information, Mr. Bauer.
Apparently, she had a price.
Put her in the car.