You're a traitor to this country,
and a disgrace to your office.
Logan wants me dead
because I know too much.
Logan isn't worth protecting.
- Aaron?
- Ma'am, please stay where you are.
- Bierko's escaped.
- What?
How long ago?
- Davis, Karen Hayes. What happened?
- Our lead car got taken out by an IED.
I overheard Bierko talking to his men.
He said they're not finished.
I'm certain he said something
about a nerve gas canister.
Henderson set up Bierko with the nerve gas.
- Trust me, he's not gonna help us.
- He will if we offer him a deal.
- What do you want?
- To disappear.
Just like you did, so they wouldn't
turn you over to the Chinese.
Anything less than Bierko's head on a plate -
this deal is off.
Bierko's gonna release the gas soon.
We need to know where.
It's a Russian submarine.
What is the armament package
on a Russian Delta IV class sub?
12 Scorpion land-attack missiles.
They carry multiple warheads.
One could take out several city blocks.
We believe the Natalia
has been targeted for a terrorist attack.
The terrorists are after your missiles.
Secure your vessel. Lock down
your weapon systems immediately.
That way.
We have control of the weapons system.
I've flushed the Sentox.
The atmospheric readings are all normal.
It's safe to breathe.
The coordinates for the targets,
upload them into the missiles.
Begin the launch countdown.
Remove your masks.
We are close to finishing
what we started today.
I have identified 12 high-value targets.
Financial centres, transportation hubs,
high-population density areas.
The Americans will wake up this morning
to discover how steep a price they've paid
for their alliance with Moscow.
And what we're about to accomplish today
will be remembered
by our countrymen forever.
- Ms Raines.
- Admiral Kirkland.
You're reporting some type of emergency
at the Port of Los Angeles?
In anticipation of today's treaty,
the Russian submarine Natalia is
docked here for inspection by the navy.
I know the exercise.
I authorised it myself.
Terrorists have seized control
of that submarine.
What? We haven't received
a distress signal from the crew.
Because they're dead, all of them,
including the Russian crew.
We believe the terrorists flooded the sub's
ventilation system with Sentox nerve gas.
- My God.
- I don't mean to pre-empt your protocols,
but how long will it take you
to scramble a flight of F-18s?
You want me to sink the submarine?
They have 12 multiple-warhead missiles,
which they will use against civilian targets
unless we stop them first.
- I'll need this confirmed.
- Our ground team can confirm.
Now I need to know precisely how long
it will take to scramble these fighters.
I'm sending you the estimated approach
vectors and ETA for my F-18s.
I can have my fighter jets there
within 22-25 minutes.
We have a problem.
According to our simulation,
Bierko will have his missiles
in the air in less than 20 minutes.
I'm scrambling the jets now. It seems as if
this will be up to your team on the ground.
We have visual contact with the sub. Hatches
are still closed. Ship's been locked down.
One hostile topside, standing guard.
Chloe's simulation has Bierko firing
the missiles in less than 20 minutes.
Sooner than that if he's already
started programming targets.
The navy can't intercept in time.
I just got off the phone with Admiral Kirkland.
He's scrambling F-18s, but they won't
be in the air in time to destroy the sub.
- How far out are reinforcements?
- Too far.
Additional teams won't arrive
until after the launch.
- Then we have to take out Bierko ourselves.
- That's not a real option.
There are only four entry points,
presumably locked down and defended.
Bill's right. You don't have the
manpower or resources to get on that sub.
We might. Somebody just launched
a signal tube off the starboard side.
What's a signal tube?
A radio beacon crewmen can send
to the surface in an emergency.
If there are friendlies inside, they can help us
board. Scan all emergency frequencies.
- On it.
- Standing by.
Jack, just so we're straight...
We stop Bierko, my wife and I
disappear for good, with your help, right?
- Yeah.
- One other thing.
If I'm going on that sub, I need a firearm.
- I'll cover you.
- That's what I'm worried about.
I don't go in undefended against hostiles.
- I still consider you a hostile.
- I don't get a gun, I don't go in.
You were right.
A survivor is sending a distress signal.
- Can we receive here?
- Yeah.
Patch him through.
I repeat. This is Petty Officer Tim Rooney
on Natalia K-524,
Code Seven. SOS. We are under attack.
Petty Officer Rooney, my name is Jack Bauer.
I'm with the Counter Terrorist Unit.
What the hell's going on, sir?
Everyone's dead.
People are in the control room
trying to operate the launch system.
- Who are they?
- Russian separatists.
They were responsible
for the attacks earlier today.
- Does the navy know?
- They sent fighters, but they won't be in time.
- So what do we do?
- Did anyone else from your crew survive?
- No, I don't think so.
- Where are you?
Uh, lower level, auxiliary engineering. I was
doing an inventory when the alarms went off.
The atmospheric gauges redlined.
It's a sealed compartment. I shut it down.
The men that attacked the ship,
were they wearing gas masks?
Yes, but they took 'em off
a few minutes ago.
Good. That means they flushed
the Sentox out of the air system.
You should be able to move around freely.
Hold on one second.
Chloe, get me the nearest entry point
to Petty Officer Rooney's current position.
The closest hatch is the forward escape hatch.
Petty Officer, do you have a firearm?
No, the armoury's on
the other side of the ship.
You need to find something
to use as a weapon.
I have a utility tool.
It has a knife on it.
That'll work. Go to the upper level.
Let me know when you get there.
- What do you want me to do?
- Find the forward escape hatch and let us in.
- There's a man there, guarding it.
- Then you're gonna have to kill him.
Officer Rooney?
I'm an engineer. I'm not trained for that.
The men on the Natalia plan to use its
missiles on civilians, unless we stop them.
Make your way to the upper level.
Do it now. We are running out of time.
- I'll contact you when I get there.
- Copy that.
We need to get closer to the sub.
Are you ready?
I know you've got Malina's. 45
in that bag. Give it to me.
Let's go.
We're generating a list of potential targets,
but we have no idea what Bierko plans to hit.
- Are we evacuating?
- We don't have time.
The missiles will strike before
we can mobilise anyone to the safe zones.
How could this happen? How could
these people even access the submarine?
The sub was attacked while
it was being serviced at a civilian port,
not on a naval base, where security
would have been more substantial.
There has to be a way to destroy that sub
before Bierko can launch.
F-18s are scrambling as we speak.
But according to the latest estimates,
they won't get there on time.
Yes?
I'm still waiting to talk to Mike.
He's in a crisis meeting.
There's no telling how long he'll be.
Then I should get off the ranch on my own.
No. Without Mike's help, you'll be seen.
Charles can't find out you're still alive.
- I'll call you when I get ahold of Mike.
- OK.
Jack, the missiles will launch
in less than ten minutes.
Copy that.
How long to cancel the launch sequence?
I won't know until I see
how their targeting software's configured.
- The petty officer is back on.
- Patch him through.
Petty Officer Rooney,
you're on with Jack Bauer.
- What's your position, son?
- I'm 30 feet forward of the hatch.
Have you got a visual
of the hostile guarding the hatch?
Yeah, he's still there.
- What do you want me to do?
- You need to kill him
without alerting the others.
- Are you right-handed or left-handed?
- Right.
Approach him from behind.
When you're within 18 inches,
put your left hand on his mouth, pull his head
back onto your chest, exposing his neck,
- then take your right hand and slit his throat.
- Oh, my God.
You need to cut deep to sever the vocal cords
and the carotid artery.
I- I don't... I don't know if I can do this.
You don't have a choice, son.
You need to focus on the objective.
You cannot afford to think about this, son.
You need to do it.
There's less than nine minutes till the launch.
Petty Officer Rooney?
OK, I can do this. I have to do this.
Cut him deep and cut him fast.
Agent McCullough, cover us.
We're moving in on the tower. Go.
Petty Officer Rooney, what is your status?
My status is, uh... He's dead.
Did anyone hear you?
- No, no one's coming.
- Good. Open the hatch.
- Are you ready?
- Yeah.
I'll take out the guard. Let's go.
The guard is down. We're going in.
Oh, no. The sub's missile hatch
has just opened.
I see them. What does that mean
in terms of our timeframe?
You have less than seven minutes.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm OK.
Which way's the control room?
- You lead, we'll follow.
- OK.
The control room's down that hall.
I'll need your help drawing the hostiles out.
- What do you want me to do?
- Is there another way into the control room?
I can go down one level
and come up behind them.
OK. When you get there, create a diversion.
Something loud, just get them out of there.
Then lay low and stay there.
Do not engage them, do you understand?
- Yeah, I can do that.
- Go.
With the last three missiles, overlap
these population centres in San Francisco.
Looking up GPS coordinates, sir.
Keep working.
- Did you hear that?
- Yes, sir. Down there.
Come with me, both of you.
The control room's right behind us.
I have a visual on one hostile. Agent
McCullough, I'm moving into position.
When he's directly above me,
signal me with the mirror.
Jack, the missiles are armed.
Three minutes till launch.
We're all clear.
- I have to manually reverse all these codes.
- Do you have enough time?
I'll do my best. I don't wanna be in here any
more than you if the F-18s take out the sub.
We'll keep Bierko and his men out
so you can finish this. Let's go.
Agent McCullough's down.
Bierko and one hostile remaining.
- Henderson, what is your status?
- I need more time. Hold 'em off.
60 seconds until they launch.
Jack?
Hang on, Jack.
Aaargh!
I'm almost there, Jack.
A few more seconds.
Ten seconds.
It's done.
Launch sequence is cancelled.
I repeat. Launch sequence is cancelled.
- Audrey, recall the F-18s.
- I'm on it.
Bierko's dead. Submarine is secure.
- Jack, are you OK?
- Bill, I'm fine.
- I'm getting feedback. Take me off the com.
- OK, Jack.
Hold it, Jack!
Now lower your arms, real slow,
and turn around.
You were never really
gonna let me go, were you?
No.
Good for you, Jack.
You were responsible for the deaths of David
Palmer, Tony Almeida and Michelle Dessler.
They were friends of mine.
That's the way it works.
- Hands above your head!
- Identify yourself!
Jack Bauer, with the Counter Terrorist Unit,
Los Angeles. All the hostiles are dead.
Holster your weapons!
Sir, you need to contact
Bill Buchanan immediately.
OK. Lieutenant, I need access to a vehicle.
Petty Officer, get me a vehicle, now!
Thank you.
- Jack?
- Yeah.
The navy's running cleanup
and security on the sub.
Yeah, they're here now.
Christopher Henderson's dead.
What? What happened?
He fired on me. I didn't have a choice.
- Are you coming back to CTU?
- Yeah, I'll be there soon.
- All right, we'll see you then.
- Chloe, the navy needs access to our logs
so they can use them for their report.
Can you pick up?
- What codes do they need?
- They don't. Get somewhere private.
I'll have to get that from my screen.
Let me get back to my station.
I'm here. What's going on?
- I'm not coming back. I'm going after Logan.
- What do you mean?
I'll fill you in later. Now I need you
to walk me through modifying
some field communications equipment.
- That's not exactly my area.
- Then get some help.
Chloe, are you with me on this?
- Yeah. What do you need?
- Hold on. I'll give you a list.
OK.
The missiles no longer pose a threat?
Yes, Mr. President.
We have complete control of the boat.
And Vladimir Bierko and all his known
associates are dead or in custody.
- So, then, it's all over, Mike?
- It's all over.
I'll make a statement
before I go back to Washington.
- About the successful resolution of the crisis.
- Yes, and about David Palmer.
Sir?
His cask is being flown to Arlington for burial.
I'd like to say a few words at the airfield.
And then I'll fly back to Washington.
- I'll get to work on it right away.
- Good. Thanks, Mike... for everything.
It's been a hell of a day.
Yes, sir. It has.
Mike?
- You need to come with me.
- Come with you?
Please.
Oh, please.
- Mrs. Logan, have you been...?
- No, I...
I've never been more sober.
Or more sane.
- What's this about?
- My husband.
What about him?
I know you've been troubled
by Charles's actions today.
You know that something
is terribly, terribly wrong.
You just can't put your finger on it.
OK. Tell me what this is about.
No, I'll show you.
It'll explain everything. Please come.
The mission to retake the submarine
has been successful.
So I understand.
You'll also be interested to know Christopher
Henderson was killed during the operation.
- You're certain of this?
- CTU has confirmed the information.
That's excellent. But let's not fool ourselves
into thinking that's the end of our problems.
There's still Bauer to deal with.
Don't worry.
Mr. Bauer will be taken care of.
Good.
Mike, over here.
Aaron, what happened to you?
Agent Adams tried to kill me,
on the president's orders.
That doesn't make any sense.
Where's Agent Adams?
Mike, we need your help.
My God.
What the hell's going on here?
The president had something to do with this?
Everything. He was involved with
everything that happened today.
Supplying the terrorists with the nerve gas,
the murder of David Palmer.
- And Walt Cummings?
- Walt was just their scapegoat.
He didn't commit suicide. He was murdered
by a man who works for Charles.
Charles told me to be quiet
for the good of the country.
Keep my mouth shut.
I can't do that, not any more.
Do you have proof?
Jack Bauer was in possession of
a recording that implicated the president.
That's why Logan was willing to go so far
as to shoot a plane full of people down.
Because Jack was on it.
- Where is this recording?
- It's been destroyed.
I didn't want to believe it either, Mike,
but it's the truth, so help me God.
All right.
If this is true, we need to find another way
to make a case against the president.
You're right, but first
we have to get Aaron off the ranch.
There can't be a record of it.
All right, all right. We need to move fast.
I know the man at the western gate well.
They won't inspect the vehicle if I'm driving.
- Hide in the back, out of sight.
- Thank you, Mike.
Give me the keys.
Aaron.
I'll be fine.
I'll go somewhere
your husband's people can't find me.
Will you let me know that you're all right?
It's probably safer
if we don't have any contact.
Goodbye, Aaron.
Thank you.
- Mike Novick.
- Mike, it's Jack Bauer.
I know this is an unusual request,
but I'm looking for Aaron Pierce.
I can't reach him on his cell.
- It's Jack Bauer. He's trying to find you.
- Put him on speaker.
- Aaron's with me right now, Jack. Hold on.
- It's all right, Jack.
You can speak freely in front of Mike.
He knows what I know.
Where are you?
- A few miles from the ranch.
- What happened?
The president tried to have me killed,
but Mrs. Logan saved my life.
- We decided to bring Mike into this.
- I'm still trying to process it. It's a real mess.
I'm calling Aaron because I need his help.
I need yours too.
- Help with what?
- Bringing President Logan to justice.
Aaron said the recording implicating him
was destroyed. Is that true?
- Yes.
- Without it, you can't mount a case.
I can if I can get
a direct confession from Logan.
Someone inside CTU is
setting up a digital uplink.
If I can get Logan to acknowledge
everything he's done, that's all we need.
Jack, if you intend
to physically coerce the president...
We need to do this now. The longer
we wait, the more vulnerable we are.
Logan tried to take me out, like he did Aaron.
He was responsible for
David Palmer's assassination
and a terrorist attack on US soil.
He cannot be allowed to remain in office,
not for one more day.
How long till you get here?
- 20 minutes.
- That's too late. Logan will be gone.
He's leaving for Washington then.
- Then you have to delay him.
- I'm not sure I can.
Mike, just tell me you'll try.
All right, but get here as fast as you can.
OK, thank you.
- You understand?
- Yes, sir.
I'll go as soon as I finish
our debrief with the navy.
Very good, Ms Hayes.
Homeland's ordered me to Washington
as soon as I've filed the Bierko case.
The request came from the White House.
Logan's looking for an excuse to clean house.
I'm sure I'll be next.
Come in.
- Yes? Do you have something?
- I need an authorisation code.
- For what?
- Access to a high-clearance workstation.
- You already have access.
- It's for some new personnel.
What?
Morris? You're bringing Morris back?
- Yes.
- Why, Chloe?
I'm still trying to salvage something
from the recording.
If anyone can do it, it's Morris.
I didn't think he was
on the government payroll now.
- He's not.
- What's he doing?
He's selling women's shoes in Beverly Hills.
- What?
- Is this a joke?
No. I wouldn't have brought him in
if there was anyone else.
Please, Mr. Buchanan.
Thank you.
- Bill...
- It'll be all right.
- Who is this guy?
- Morris O'Brian.
Chloe's ex-husband.
Not like that. The beauty of the beast is,
if you leave these fields blank,
it'll prompt you for a code. Ba-bing!
See that? You just saved 60 seconds.
Two of those a day, an extra cigarette break,
or whatever it is you do to take the edge off.
Morris!
- What are you doing?
- Making your people more efficient.
- You picked the most attractive one.
- Wrong. You're the most attractive one.
- Here's your clearance.
- Surprised you got Buchanan to sign me off.
This is a really good opportunity for you.
Why not surprise me and not screw it up?
OK, I'll pretend this requires all my attention,
when we both know I could do it in my sleep.
- Sit down.
- So, where is this recording?
Nothing, forget it, it's fried.
I'm missing something.
You wanted me to salvage a recording.
That was an excuse.
I need some com unit modifications,
a certified audio transfer rate of 6.8. I can only
get to 6.5. Can you do that without talking?
I could, but it would be
a terrible waste of my charm.
OK, I'm not listening any more.
Call me when you're done. Thanks.
Behind me you can see preparations as
the casket bearing the body of David Palmer
is expected shortly, to be met...
Come in.
- Is Aaron safe?
- Yes.
Thank God.
I can't believe Charles is gonna do this.
With David's blood on his hands, he has the
audacity to eulogise him in front of the world.
Mrs. Logan, I said there was no way to make
a case against your husband. I was wrong.
Jack Bauer, a former CTU agent, contacted
Aaron and me. He's on his way here now.
- What for?
- To confront your husband directly.
Confront him? Will he hurt him?
Jack Bauer will do whatever it takes
to compel your husband to confess the truth.
He's the only one I know who can do this.
- When will he be here?
- 15 minutes.
Charles is leaving for the airfield immediately.
I tried to delay him,
but he wouldn't change his schedule.
That's why I'm coming to you.
I need you to keep him here.
Martha.
If you want your husband brought to justice,
this is our only chance.
You have to find a way to stall him.
Aaron, it's good to see you.
Was Mike able to delay the president?
He's trying, but he had to ask
Mrs. Logan for some help.
- The first lady knows what we intend to do?
- She does.
- Aaron, can she be trusted?
- She is with us, Jack, 100 per cent.
Can you access
the Secret Service deployment grid?
I have. Security's been beefed up around the
main building - you won't get him alone there.
- Is Marine One taking him?
- No, this was last minute.
They're moving him by reduced attachment
in a navy helicopter.
That's where this must happen.
I need to get on that chopper.
- I don't see how that's possible.
- Get me as close to it as you can.
We'll figure it out from there.
All right. Let's go.
I agree. Wayne Palmer should be
at the airfield, but if you can't find him,
I'm not gonna wait for him.
- Will you be leaving soon?
- Yes, I'm leaving now.
All right, sir.
Have a copy of my speech on the chopper.
I'll work on it on the flight over.
- I'll be out of your way in a second.
- I saw on your schedule that...
you're meeting David Palmer's casket
at the airfield.
If you came to judge me, I don't have time...
No, that's not it. I...
I've had time to reflect and I...
I think I owe you an apology.
All right.
- I said some horrible things to you.
- I've had horrible things said to me before.
And by you.
But there was one thing you said
that I can't get over.
- What?
- That I broke your heart.
And that you hated me.
Well, I wish I could take those words back.
All I can ask now is that you forgive me.
Please, Charles.
I don't know how to respond, Marty. I...
I never expected you to say anything like this.
I mean it, Charles, I...
I mean it. I need you to forgive me.
You mean it now, but you know how you are.
Tomorrow I could be the man you hate again.
I know.
It'll take time for me to prove myself to you.
The truth is,
even though sometimes
I don't understand you,
I still need you.
And I still love you.
And that will never change, Charles.
Not tomorrow,
not ever.
I need you too, Marty.
Fly with me to Washington.
- We could spend some time together.
- On a plane, surrounded by Secret Service?
Why can't we just spend
a little more time here together, alone?
You know that's not possible. I have to go.
I have to go five minutes ago.
OK, Charles.
You go.
Come with me.
I have a better idea.
- There's a helicopter waiting for me.
- Let it wait.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
You're the president.
- Yes, Mr. President?
- Tell the helicopter to stand by.
Yes, until I'm ready.
- Yes, Mr. President.
- And make sure I'm not disturbed.
It's clear.
Yeah?
Logan just told Secret Service
he'll be delayed.
How long?
He didn't say, but Mrs. Logan knows
we need as much time as possible.
Jack...
If Logan doesn't confess,
how far are you actually willing to go?
As far as I have to.