Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net
(man) America has been victimised again.
Last night's terrorist attack in San Antonio
was the latest in this series of bombings
that began 11 weeks ago
in ten different cities.
Retrieve the package.
Call me when you have it.
- What happened?
- You shouldn't have come here, Scott.
I don't wanna hurt you,
but I will unless you do exactly what I say.
I'm Mr Al-Rezani's attorney.
There are no terrorists here.
Yes, it's Sandra Palmer.
I'd like to speak with my brother.
The FBI was just here, and they
wanted access to the IAA's personnel records.
I have to do whatever I can
to stop these attacks.
That includes giving law enforcement
the authority to follow up every single lead.
- I can't find the files.
- They've been erased.
Don't try to recall them.
I used the shredding program.
- Sandra, what are you doing?
- You're under arrest.
- Take Mr Al-Rezani into custody.
- Wait. He has nothing to do with this.
- Don't move. Where is Assad?
- Put down your weapon.
I came alone. Fayed set you up. He provided
CTU with the coordinates to this house.
Move! Move!
Most of my people and the governments
that support us agreed to a cease-fire.
- Fayed wants to sabotage it?
- Yes. But finding Fayed is the key.
- These are Fayed's men.
- They're going in the subway.
They can't get on that train.
(Assad) Only the bomber is getting on
the train. The other man is the handler.
(Jack) You follow the handler.
I'm going after the bomber.
(screaming)
(phone rings)
- We're heading in your direction.
- I'll find you.
Stay with the handler.
He's our only connection to Fayed.
- You still have Fayed's man in sight?
- He's in a grey sedan, about six cars ahead.
(phone rings)
- Yes?
- (Fayed) Are you on schedule?
There was traffic by Union Station.
I'm on the road now.
There has been a change. I need you to stop
in Newhall before you come back here.
The Americans will be feeling helpless.
I'm making the call.
(Buchanan) The casualty estimate
in St Louis has risen to 112.
The mall attack in Baltimore is even worse.
Over 200 dead,
many of them children.
My God. What about
the bomb in Los Angeles?
Jack Bauer averted the attack
at Union Station.
Surveillance from Metro Transit
also confirmed he's working with Assad.
Have you made contact?
Jack's been dark since he called
to warn us about Fayed and we didn't listen.
I didn't listen.
Fayed is demanding
to speak with the president.
Mr President, we're receiving a call
on a scrambled channel from Fayed, sir.
- He's demanding to speak with you.
- Put him on.
This is President Palmer.
Mr President, we've proven
we can strike at you any time, anywhere.
But I am prepared to offer you a cease-fire,
if you meet my demands.
Your demands?
We met your demands when you deceived us
about Assad being behind these attacks.
Now you expect me to accept
your assurances of a cease-fire?
I expect you will take action that promises
to avoid the loss of more American lives.
What do you want?
You are holding 110
so-called enemy combatants
at your Palmdale military facility
in violation of international law.
You must have all these freedom fighters
on a nonmilitary aircraft in the air
by the end of the hour.
The pilot will be told the destination
once the plane is outside your airspace.
If I agree, there is not enough time...
You'll find a way. If you don't
release the prisoners by the deadline,
the consequences will be
immediate and devastating.
I will only make this offer once,
Mr President.
For your country's sake, I hope you accept it.
Is that what these attacks have been about?
Releasing the prisoners?
Sir, I feel it's wishful thinking
to assume this is Fayed's endgame.
Contact Palmdale. Find out what
would be involved in making this happen.
Yes, sir.
Mr President, you cannot seriously consider
giving in to this man's demands.
I mean, you said yourself,
Fayed cannot be trusted.
No, he can't. I do not believe he has
any intention of stopping these attacks.
Not permanently. But doing this
buys us more time to find Fayed.
At the very least it gives the country
a respite from the bombings.
Sir, you'd be releasing
110 extremely dangerous terrorists.
Karen, I am very well aware of that.
But unless we find Fayed, I may be forced to.
- Oh, no. We got a problem.
- What?
He's heading north. The farther he gets,
the less traffic we'll have to hide in.
It'll be hard to track him to Fayed
without him seeing us.
- What else can we do?
- Call CTU. They'll give us satellite coverage.
No CTU. They killed my men.
They tried to kill me.
Fayed made them believe
you were behind the bombings.
I will not work with my enemies.
You are working with one now. You might
hate this country, you might hate its values.
If you're serious about disarming, bringing
your organisation and others to the table,
then you know you have to compromise.
- That is your political reality.
- What's to say they won't put me in prison?
I can't tell you they won't, but right now
that is our only lead to Fayed.
- Make the call.
- Thank you.
- Morris, I need you to load this.
- What is it?
Fayed is asking the president
to release all the prisoners from Palmdale.
We need to vet each one in case he does.
He won't. They are serious high-grade
terror suspects. No one's letting them go.
Excuse me. Are you refusing to do this?
Give this to the girls in archives. I'm working
up Fayed threads. It's more important.
I don't care what you think is important.
It's not your place to tell me.
Just calm down.
I'm trying to help you do yourjob.
You have to evaluate directives. Don't waste
the time of your most important analysts.
- I'm...
- Morris.
What? What?
Put filters on each of these files.
If I don't have results on my screen
in 20 minutes, you are out of here.
- Grow up.
- (phone rings)
- O'Brian.
- Chloe, this is Jack.
- I didn't think I'd ever hear your voice again.
- I need to speak to Buchanan.
Hold on.
Buchanan.
- (Chloe) It's Jack on line one.
- Jack, where are you?
With Assad,
tracking a suspect in the train bombing.
We know you're working with Assad.
Are you sure you can trust him?
I think so.
- What do you need?
- Suspect's on Florence, crossing Ormond.
We believe he'll lead us to Fayed.
We need satellite support.
Logging on to the NSA server now.
Fayed contacted the president and demanded
he release the prisoners at Palmdale.
What's the president's position?
If we don't find Fayed by 9am,
he'll go through with it.
It'll take me ten minutes to get satellite
coverage. I had to use the subserver.
That's too long. He's entering Route 7.
If we try to follow, he'll see us.
Chloe, can you speed up access?
Sat queue's overloaded.
The country is on high alert.
- We'll use Caltrans cameras to track him.
- There isn't a traffic cam on Route 7. I looked.
Figure out another way to track him
till the satellite's up.
- Where's your nearest TAC team?
- 12 miles away.
Send 'em in my direction.
I'll get back to you.
- Do you think this man will recognise you?
- No. What do you have in mind?
All right, thanks. Manning on comm.
I spoke to Jack. He's surveilling
one of Fayed's men and needs backup.
- Where is he?
- Florence Boulevard, near Route 7.
He's running this operation with Assad.
Did I hear that correctly?
We're working with Assad?
Rendezvous with them and lend support.
All warrants on Assad are rescinded
for the time being, understood?
Curtis?
We're on our way.
Don't get up.
(horn)
Hey! What's wrong with you?
I know you saw me coming!
- It was my right of way!
- You telling me I don't know how to drive?
- I'm talking to you!
- You all right? I saw the whole thing.
- This has got nothing to do with you!
- I'm a witness. You drove into him.
What is it with you people?
You're gonna stick up for him?
Fine, I'll wait here until the police arrive.
Screw both of you. Screw you!
Where are you going? Hey! Hey!
This is your fault!
I saw his license for the police.
I can't wait for the police.
I can't drive this.
I need to be somewhere.
I'll deal with this later.
Where are you going?
- Newhall. I was getting on Route 7.
- So was I. I'll drop you there. Come. Come.
Thank you.
(phone rings)
I hope you won't let that bastard get away
with this. You must file a police report.
I know.
Come on.
- (woman) CTU.
- I need to speak with Bill Buchanan.
Hold, please.
(phone rings)
- Buchanan.
- Fayed's man is now in a car with Assad.
- What happened?
- Suspect was in a traffic incident. Listen.
Assad left his phone open so we can monitor.
I'll be following roughly two miles behind
in a white Jeep Cherokee.
Assad will let us know where he's going.
- I'm ready to transfer you into the call.
- Go ahead, Jack.
Bill, they can't hear us on our side.
You should be on the call now.
I don't know Newhall very well.
I need you to guide me.
(man) I will.
Nadia, do an all-agency data pull on Newhall.
Set up parameters for a sort.
When we get satellite,
make sure we have coverage of that area.
Let Curtis know he's to intercept Jack
on Route 7 on the way to Newhall.
- Fayed.
- What is it?
Our scout reports increased activity
around the Palmdale military prison.
The transport buses are starting to arrive.
Good. By the time our brothers are on the
aircraft, it will be too late for the Americans
- to realise what's happened.
- We still don't have the component.
We will. Ahmed should be
on his way to pick it up now.
- Scott, is that you?
- Yeah.
Honey, we were beginning to get worried.
- My God, Ahmed, what happened?
- Mom, he has a gun.
- What's going on? What is this?
- Where's Ray?
Just put the gun down
and tell me what's happening.
Call him.
Ray!
Yeah?
- What the hell?
- I don't wanna hurt you,
but I will unless you do exactly what I say.
You're a nurse, right? You have bandages?
- Yeah.
- Go get them. Now!
You two, on the couch, now. Come on.
Sit down now.
I need you to patch this leg,
stop the bleeding.
My God, Stan was right.
You are a terrorist.
- Stan's dead. He killed him.
- What?
- I can't stop this bleeding.
- Don't tell me that!
The wound's too deep. You have muscle
tissue damage. You need to see a doctor.
Just bandage it!
There's a package in there. I'm supposed to
take it to a man who has an item for me.
- Press.
- Ah!
Obviously I can't do that now,
so you're gonna have to.
I'm not leaving you alone with my family.
Your family will be safe
when you do what I say.
When you pick up the item, you'll call me
and I'll give you further instructions.
- What's in this package?
- None of your concern. Just make the drop.
Grab that phone and come here.
Come here, come here.
Understand this.
If I see anyone - the police, FBI, anybody
outside this house, or if you take too long -
your wife and son are dead.
Do you understand me? Look at me!
I understand.
Where am I going?
There's an address on the front pocket
of that backpack. It's a man named Marcus.
Go.
(phone rings)
- How far away are you?
- Less than five minutes.
Get there fast. Assad and Fayed's man
are on open road, five miles ahead.
Got it.
- Oh, darling?
- What?
- Since when do you take Milo's side?
- You're doing it again.
- What?
- Pick on your bosses when you're stressed.
- Milo's not my boss, heaven forbid.
- He might as well be.
He could bounce you.
I think you want it sometimes.
And why would I want that?
I don't know.
It's your character flaw, not mine.
The files you wanted are all unlocked.
They'll be on your screen in a minute.
Good.
Mr President.
I just got off the phone with CTU.
They've reconnected with Jack Bauer.
- Where is he?
- He's following one of Fayed's operatives.
CTU is coordinating support for Jack. They
believe this man will lead them to Fayed.
Did CTU offer a time frame for locating him?
No, sir. At this point,
any estimates are premature.
- Have you spoken with the Palmdale facility?
- And the airfield.
If we wanna have the prisoners in the air
before the end of the hour,
we have to have them on buses
and on the road within the next ten minutes.
If you still want to proceed with that option.
I know you disapprove of my decision,
but unless Jack and CTU
call to say they have Fayed,
there is no other option here.
- Tell them to load the buses.
- Yes, Mr President.
(Assad) Sand Canyon Road.
What?
I was just remembering. I had a friend
who lived on Sand Canyon Road.
We can take the service route from here.
They're two miles ahead.
We can monitor with this cellphone.
CTU wants you on comm.
- You copy?
- Ten-four.
- CTU, this is Manning.
- (Bill) Go ahead.
I'm with Jack.
Do we have satellite access yet?
- It's coming up. Is Jack on the line?
- I'm here, Bill.
We're redirecting the NSA satellite to the
area around Sand Canyon Road exit marker.
When we have a fix on Assad's vehicle,
we'll upload it to your GPS.
Copy that.
It's good to see you, Jack.
I'm sorry for what you were put through.
- But I'm glad you're back.
- Thanks.
Now you have to work with Assad.
Doesn't that bother you?
The man's a terrorist, responsible for taking
hundreds, maybe thousands of innocent lives
over the past 20 years.
Doesn't that mean anything to you?
I don't know what means
anything any more, Curtis.
I spent my whole life defending
this country against people like Assad.
And now he's trying to disarm his people,
renounce terrorism.
- The playing field has changed.
- That doesn't change Assad's past.
We have to make sure that
he pays for the crimes that he's committed.
If he's our only chance at a peaceful
resolution to this, that might not happen.
Anyway, it's not our call to make.
We'll see.
What is that supposed to mean?
Nothing.
Good.
This isn't working.
There's still too much pain.
I need something stronger.
Uh, there are some
prescription painkillers in the kitchen.
Get them, and some water.
Make sure I can see you.
They're in the cabinet over the TV.
Give it to me.
Sit down.
Sit down!
Sit down, sweetie.
Form an orderly line.
Head count will be taken.
Then, and only then,
you'll be loaded onto those buses.
Understand, any problems you cause
will only delay this process.
Get in line.
I'll tell him. Right.
Uh, that was the FBI.
Your sister, she's been arrested.
- What? When?
- Less than an hour ago.
FBI agents were sent to the offices
of the Islamic-American Alliance
to serve a warrant for their personnel files.
Sandra deleted them in front of the agents.
- They had no choice but to arrest her.
- Dammit. Where has she been taken, Tom?
She's being detained.
One of our provisional facilities.
(woman) Yes, sir.
(yelling, chanting)
Walid, I'm so sorry I got you into this.
I deleted those files. It wasn't right
for them to arrest you for my actions.
Don't apologise. You were protecting
the rights of innocent Americans.
That's what this country stands for,
even if the government's forgotten.
Back away. Move back.
Come on. That's it.
You take him.
Where are you taking him? Walid?
I'll be all right.
Over here, Ms Palmer.
Take off her cuffs.
For you.
I'll be right here.
- Hello?
- (woman) Please hold for the president.
- What were you thinking deleting those files?
- I was standing up to an unlawful seizure.
You making a point
is the last thing I need today.
I ordered your release.
Agents have instructions to take you home.
I don't wanna be released.
I wanna fight this,
bring attention to the liberties
your administration allowed to be violated.
- Do you have any idea what's going on?
- Of course.
Innocent people are dying all over
the country. You make a civil rights case now.
Somebody has to. If you're gonna
release anybody, it should be Walid.
He's the head of the organisation
under investigation.
The FBI wants to hold him until they know
what was in those files you deleted.
There is nothing incriminating on those files.
You have my word. Walid is innocent.
Then Walid has nothing
to worry about, Sandra.
Listen, I don't have time for this.
You are released.
Go home. I will call you later.
- I need to speak with Walid.
- That's not going to happen.
I'm his attorney.
You have to give me access to him.
Don't tell me what I have to do.
I'm following orders.
- Walid has rights.
- Limited rights, Ms Palmer.
He's being held under
the revised enemy combatant statute.
Applying this statute
to somebody like him is ridiculous.
Is the law being
completely thrown out of the window?
When you're through with the lectures,
I have orders to drive you home.
Ma'am?
Stay to the left.
Once inside the secure zone, you will disrobe.
After a cavity search,
you'll be given back your clothing.
- Sir, you have to keep moving.
- I don't care. I'm innocent.
I wanna talk to somebody in authority.
- We're not gonna ask you again.
- Don't touch me.
- Let him alone!
- Sir, get back in line.
Not until you let go of that man.
Take your hands off me.
Take him to interrogation.
Do you live around here?
No.
Visiting relatives?
- Why do you ask?
- To make sure you can get back to your car.
- I'll be OK.
- "I'll be OK."
My son, he says this. He has a memory
like a fish. His mother is very worried.
On the next corner, make a right.
Drop me off at the end of the street.
- Did you copy that?
- It's the 6500 block of Alderton.
Bring up the data on all buildings
within a half mile and begin a pre-sort.
Like I'm doing already?
Right over here.
- All right, thanks again for your help.
- Please, it's nothing.
He's crossing 64th Road, heading towards
the commercial district. I'm turning around.
- There he is.
- We've acquired the suspect on satellite.
- Have your men set up a moving perimeter.
- Collier, take your men across 64th.
Set up a moving perimeter behind the target.
- He'll be well trained. Be careful.
- My men know theirjob.
- Do I know you?
- No, but I know you.
He's entering a commercial building
one block south of you.
Copy that. Boorman,
we're gonna take Assad with us.
- Watch him. Search him for weapons.
- Assad is part of this operation.
Not any more.
Wait. Wait.
I'll take care of it
as soon as this is over. I promise.
Thank you.
It's a self-storage facility -
one floor, 200 units.
- Boorman, keep him here.
- Team leader, do you copy?
Go ahead, Collier.
I see two dozen cases of ammunition,
boxes with Czech writing.
This is a dead drop. Fayed's not here.
We only have a few minutes, Jack.
If the suspect won't lead us to Fayed
to stop the prisoner exchange,
we have to move now,
get information through interrogation.
Bill, that's too risky. We have no
guarantee we can make him talk in time.
That's a risk we have to take.
Move your men into position.
Understood. All teams, we're moving in.
Silent approach, non-lethal force.
(clang)
Get out where I can see you!
Step out with your hands up!
Curtis! Everyone back!
Get a fire hose.
Get the fire department and ambulances here!
Bill, it's Jack. Suspect is dead.
He was taking a laptop out of the storage unit.
We'll check the hard drive, but it's damaged.
Understood, Jack.
I need the president.
Yeah, got the feed
of the prisoners at Palmdale.
(intercom beeps)
- Yes?
- (woman) I have Bill Buchanan on the line.
- Put him on.
- Yes, sir.
- We've had a setback to our operation.
- What happened, Bill?
The suspect Jack was following
killed himself rather than be apprehended.
We're examining for evidence.
There's no telling how long that will take
or if it will lead us to Fayed. I'm sorry.
- So am I. Keep me informed.
- Of course.
If you're intent on following through with
this prisoner release, we await your orders.
Load them on the plane.
This is Lennox. The president has made his
decision. Load the prisoners on the plane.
Head count is correct.
All men accounted for on bus three.
I want confirmed head counts
on all other vehicles.
(man) Copy that. Bus one confirmed.
Roger that.
We will proceed single file
in an orderly manner onto the plane.
There will be no mistakes and no disorder.
Is that clear?
Let's get these buses
out of here as soon as we can.
- Let's move.
- Yes, sir.
Fayed, we just heard from the airport.
Our people are being loaded onto the planes.
The president has given in to us.
Hello?
(man) Back here.
- You Marcus?
- Who are you?
I'm supposed to give this to you and you're
supposed to give me something in return.
It's not enough.
What do you mean?
The component cost me more than
I thought it would. I need another 50,000.
- But that's all he gave me.
- Well, then go back and get the rest.
I can't do that.
Look, I need whatever it is
you're selling, please.
Just take the money. I am begging you.
Hey.
Until you get more money,
we have nothing more to talk about.
- C-can I use your phone?
- Yeah.
- (phone rings)
- Hello.
- He, um, wants another $50,000.
- Tell him you don't have it.
I did and he said to come back when I get it.
There is no more money. I don't care what
you have to do, but get that item from him.
You understand what happens here
if you don't?
(clears throat) Yeah.
I understand.
- What'd he say?
- He says he'll get the money.
And before I bring it back here, he just
wants to make sure you really do have it.
There it is.
You son of a bitch!
I'll kill you!
Shut up, just take the money!
Just take it.
The hard drive is mostly toast, but I was able
to recover the most recently accessed file.
Some kind of wiring schematic.
How much do we have?
About a page and a half.
Mostly in Arabic, some of it in Russian.
Get Assad over here now.
Boorman, bring him.
Do you know what this is?
A list of electronic components,
build specifications,
programming instructions for a detonator.
But this is for a nuclear device.
Is it possible Fayed
could've acquired a nuclear weapon?
His organisation has tried
unsuccessfully in the past.
- He may have found a way.
- Son of a bitch!
- You knew about this all along, didn't you?
- Curtis! Curtis! Let go of him now!
Assad, please.
There is a reference file
at the bottom of the page. Sovtel Three.
That's a compact bomb the Soviets made
till the late '80s - a suitcase nuke.
- They're all accounted for?
- Destroyed.
There was a claim a device was diverted to a
nuclear scientist with suspected terrorist ties.
- Calls himself Saif al Din.
- Looking up his file.
There won't be much. It's a code name,
means "sword of the faith".
- Intelligence never discovered his identity.
- We have a six-year-old surveillance photo.
Put it up.
- Do you recognise him?
- Yes. I saw him with Fayed a year ago.
- His name is Hasan Numair.
- Chloe, did you copy that?
- Looking up his name.
- We need to know where this man is now.
I think we already do. He's a terrorist being
released from the Palmdale military prison.
Call the White House.
Bring up the feed from the airfield.
This is what Fayed
has been planning all along.
These bombings were designed
to make you free this man.
Son of a bitch.
- Have they freed the prisoners?
- It'll be a couple minutes till they're in the air.
Call the airfield. Send it to my office.
Tell the president I'm stopping the release.
This is Nadia Yassir from CTU. I need
to speak to the president, priority three.
This is Buchanan. The prisoner you want
is Hasan Numair. I'll send his picture.
Roger that. Let's move it, boys.
Prisoner Numair, raise your hand.
- I've got the photo.
- Copy that.
Prisoner Numair, identify yourself now.
We need to go over every square inch.
Someone tell the sarge
he needs to get up here now.
(gunshot)
Hurry up. Fayed is waiting for you.
Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net