CTU is being absorbed
by the Department of Homeland Security
and Christopher Henderson
remains an open protocol.
Ms Raines signed a statement documenting
the numerous missteps made today by CTU.
And by you in particular.
I don't understand. Why am I staying?
Because Ms Raines requested
that you keep your position.
I had to keep Karen from replacing you.
That's why I signed. I didn't have a choice.
- Why were those men trying to kill you?
- David had a source inside the White House.
- Who's this source?
- Mrs. Logan's assistant.
I have proof about who's behind
everything that's happened today.
Someone killed David.
And then just tried to kill me.
- I have to go now.
- Give me what I need!
They kidnapped my little girl.
Evelyn. I promise you
we're gonna get your daughter back.
I already told them I wouldn't give up
any information until I have my daughter.
We need Henderson alive.
Do not shoot to kill.
- Did you bring what we discussed?
- I have the evidence with me.
I want my daughter.
She's moving.
- Give me the evidence, Evelyn.
Now.
Wayne, I didn't get him.
If you've got a shot, take it.
Henderson escaped in Evelyn's car.
Do you have him on satellite?
- We can't lose him.
- Evelyn's been hit.
It's not serious, but it has to be dressed.
You got your daughter,
now tell me what I need to know.
Who is behind this? Is it the vice president?
The vice president has
nothing to do with this!
You promised you would control this.
I didn't count on Jack Bauer showing up, sir.
Bauer and Palmer won't be around long
enough to tell anybody else what they know.
I will not let you down.
See that you don't.
With White House-imposed martial law
and curfew still in effect throughout the area,
- all traffic is restricted to emergency vehicles.
Wayne, turn that off.
OK, Evelyn, I need you to stay focused.
The recording of the call
between Logan and Henderson
is in a safety deposit box. Which bank?
Which bank?
- City Trust and Savings in Agoura Hills.
- Where's the key?
My jacket pocket.
- Mom?
- It's all right, your mom's gonna be fine.
She's gonna be fine, OK?
You heard what they said. We have to get off
this road. There are patrols everywhere.
There's a motel up there on the right,
turn in there.
- I wanna go home.
We're gonna get you home.
Wayne, can you get us a room?
I'll keep watch.
Keep pressure on it. I'll be right back.
- Hello?
- Have you got Henderson on satellite yet?
No. Chloe didn't reposition in time.
- Dammit. Are you still on a secure line?
- Yes. Why? What's going on?
Evelyn didn't implicate Gardner.
She implicated President Logan.
Oh, my God, Jack.
Logan? Are you sure?
She said he's responsible for everything,
starting with giving them the nerve gas.
David Palmer found out, so they killed him.
President Logan ordered
Palmer's assassination?
Henderson gave the order, but Evelyn
has evidence Logan was complicit.
What evidence?
She recorded a call this morning
between Henderson and Logan.
It's in a safety deposit box.
We're on our way to get it.
Jack, the city is under martial law.
I know. Upload every military checkpoint
to my PDA so we can navigate around them.
- All right, I'll take care of that.
- Audrey.
As soon as I have the recording, we'll have
to involve your father to present the evidence.
All right. He's on his way back
from a summit in Japan.
- I'll call him on the plane.
- Leave CTU before you do anything.
- You don't think they can be trusted?
- We can't trust anyone.
Logan has every federal agency, the military,
at his disposal, and he'll use them to stop us.
Don't fill your father in on the particulars.
Just set up the meeting.
- I'll call back when I have the recording.
- I'll upload those checkpoints.
Wayne.
That's the bank manager's address -
he's not far.
Good. Let's get them in the room.
Hey. We need to get inside now.
- Come on, it's OK.
- Just try to stand up.
I need you to sit right here, OK?
OK. Lay down here on the bed.
I'm sorry, but it's not safe to take you
to a hospital yet. Let me see. Let me see.
Wayne, take Amy outside for a second.
Come on, sweetie.
OK. Even though the bullet went through,
I still have to clean this wound.
It's gonna hurt, but I promise
I'll get you to a hospital as soon as I can.
- In the meantime, Wayne will look after you.
- No, I'll be fine.
You need to get the evidence.
I don't need help.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
OK.
Put pressure on it.
- Sweetheart, you can see your mom now.
- Go ahead.
Give me the car keys. Let's go.
- I haven't picked up Bauer's trail yet.
- So he got away.
And there's nothing to stop him and Wayne
from going to the media with all they know.
Jack knows there's no point
going public until he has proof.
He won't make accusations
until he has that evidence in his hand.
This evidence, this recording
that Evelyn made of our conversation,
are you any closer to finding
where she's hidden it?
No, not yet,
but she was wounded and I will find her.
We're monitoring hospitals.
This is containable, I promise you.
Please, spare me your promises,
Mr. Henderson.
It's all gone wrong. None of this
should have happened. All these killings.
This whole thing was planned
to make our country safer, stronger,
to protect our interests.
And it all spiralled out of control
when you decided to kill David Palmer.
Mr. President, what's done is done.
Right now, we have to focus on stopping
Bauer before he finds that recording.
No. You have to focus on it.
- Haven't the analysts finished the hourlies?
- They're still getting up to speed.
We knew this wouldn't be seamless.
Sometimes I wonder if it was even necessary.
Karen, CTU's performance today
has been considerably less than stellar.
Dozens have been killed, and they couldn't
even prevent an attack on themselves.
Do you believe, under the circumstances,
that we could have done any better?
Ms Hayes. The president's on line one.
Put him through to Buchanan's office.
I'll work there.
Have Medical notify me as soon as Bierko
has regained consciousness. Miles.
- Yes, Mr. President?
- Karen, do you know where Jack Bauer is?
Not at the moment. He was due back 30
minutes ago to lead the Bierko interrogation.
- He's gone off-grid.
- I'm not surprised.
Karen, I'm issuing an executive order for the
immediate apprehension and arrest of Bauer.
I want you to run point on this, and
I want you to make this CTU's top priority.
Yes, sir. For purposes of the warrant, I'll need
to know what Bauer's being charged with.
His role in the assassination of David Palmer.
But I understood he'd been exonerated
of that charge. You reinstated his credentials.
I know, but I didn't have all the facts then.
Some new evidence has come to light.
- New evidence?
- Yes. I'm looking at it right now.
And I will forward it to you
at the appropriate time.
- Yes, sir.
- Karen.
Obviously this is a very sensitive matter.
For now, I'd like you to treat
the origin of this warrant as confidential.
- Understood, sir.
- Good.
Put out an alert on Jack Bauer to all
federal law-enforcement agencies and NSA.
I'll also tell Military.
They have more men on the street.
I don't like this.
Pulling our resources off Henderson to go
after Jack without knowing the evidence?
It's a direct order from the president.
If we really want to find Bauer,
we need to keep watch on
anyone he might contact for help,
starting with Audrey Raines.
- What's this?
- Make it look like we're talking about it.
OK.
Can you get me a secure channel
so my calls can't be monitored?
Using a VPN pathway, sure.
It takes about an hour to crack.
- Why, what's going on?
- I just spoke with Jack.
Gardner isn't the one who's behind this.
It's President Logan.
What?
Jack is getting proof. I'm leaving to help him.
Take a CTU walkie.
Audrey.
It's a warrant for Jack's arrest.
- It's starting.
- What do we do?
Heading out?
Yes, I'm gonna try to grab some sleep.
- I came to talk to you about the warrant.
- Start with why it was issued.
There's new evidence implicating Jack
in David Palmer's assassination.
That's ridiculous.
The assassin confessed. Check the logs.
I know about the logs, Chloe.
My orders are to bring Jack in.
New evidence? Have you seen it?
- It's forthcoming.
- Who ordered this, Karen?
I can't discuss that.
When was the last time you spoke with Jack?
About an hour ago.
We haven't had contact since.
I don't have to remind you that you have an
obligation to notify me if Jack contacts you.
Look, I know this may seem odd
to the both of you. Frankly, it does to me.
But let's remember it's in everyone's
best interests to bring Jack in peacefully.
Have a good night.
Thank you.
- Harris.
- Audrey's on her way. What's your status?
- We're placing the transponder on her car.
- Good.
There won't be many cars.
Use the tracker and stay out of sight.
Will do.
We don't want anything to stop Audrey
from leading us to Bauer.
- That's the house.
- OK.
- What's the bank manager's name?
- Carl Mossman.
- You got your gun?
- Yeah, but we don't need one for this, do we?
He won't let us into his bank
unless he thinks he has to.
- Why don't we just tell him the truth?
- Would you believe it?
The only way we'll have compliance
is if he's scared.
If you're uncomfortable with that,
you should stay here.
They've got a magnetic alarm.
We're in.
...within the hour, President Logan plans
to make a statement to the American people
about the successful resolution of today's
terrorist threat. As of now, however...
- Did you hear something?
- Like what?
I don't know.
- Carl?
- Hang on.
- Carl!
- I'll be right back.
Don't you move!
Rose, call...
Cover him.
Put the phone down.
Put the phone down now!
Bring him in here!
Just stay calm and everything will be fine.
Let's go!
- Oh, my God! Carl!
- Take a seat on the bed.
Hey, look. Our money and jewellery's
in a floor safe in the closet.
We're not interested in that.
You're gonna get us into your bank.
I can't do that.
It's not that I won't. I can't. The alarm system
will only allow entry during business hours.
Don't lie to me. Every bank has procedures
to allow access during an emergency.
Hey! No, no! I'll take you to the bank.
Slowly, get up and get dressed.
Carl!
- It's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
I want four of your neckties.
Tie her up to the chair. Ankles and wrists.
Make sure she doesn't move.
All right, go ahead.
She's got clearance.
Come on.
Hi. I need to speak
with Secretary Heller, please.
Mr. Secretary, there's a call coming in for you
on an encrypted channel. It's your daughter.
- Audrey, is everything OK?
- Hi.
Yes, I'm OK.
- Dad, I need your help. Is this a secure line?
- Very secure.
Is this about the arrest order for Jack?
I was just informed.
I can't go into details now,
but Jack is innocent. He's being set up.
Set up by whom?
What the hell is going on, Audrey? You call
me this morning to tell me that Jack's alive.
Now I get word he's a suspect again
in the Palmer assassination.
I can't talk to you about it right now.
I need to see you in person.
Can you reroute your plane to Los Angeles?
Dad, I would never ask you to do this
if it wasn't extremely important.
- All right, yes.
- Thank you. The closest airport is Van Nuys.
We're about an hour out.
I'll call you on final approach.
- OK, thank you. I'll see you there.
- I'll see you.
Bye.
Doug!
Yes, sir?
We have to make a stop in LA,
and keep it off the manifest.
Yes, sir.
Pull over. She's stopped.
The corner of Elderton and Davis.
It's a gas station.
- O'Brian.
- Chloe, it's me.
Hold on.
I switched to my VPN. They can't monitor
the conversation. Do you have the walkie?
Yeah, hang on.
- All right, what do I do with it?
- Tune to proprietary channel 17.
Turn sensitivity up all the way
to pick up a pilot signal.
OK, hold on.
- Wow. Do you hear that?
- It's what I figured. They put a tracker on you.
I found it. All right, Chloe, I got it. Thank you.
You need to disable your phone
by taking the battery out.
I have to wait for a call from Jack,
and then I will.
- Yes?
- Sir.
It's almost time.
Yes, the press conference. That's right.
Mr. President, if I could have a moment?
- I'll be done with my statement shortly...
- This is potentially time-sensitive, sir.
I just got an alert that a warrant
has been issued for Jack Bauer.
Thank you, Aaron.
Yes, sir.
- What about the warrant?
- It's an executive branch warrant.
I didn't issue it, so it must have been you.
That's right, it came from me.
As you put me in charge of overseeing CTU
and the Homeland Security transfer,
don't you think you should have
discussed it with me first?
I appreciate everything you've done, but last
time I checked, I was still commander in chief.
Of course, Mr. President, but Jack Bauer?
It doesn't make any sense.
We should be treating that man like a hero.
I've gone over it. Cummings confessed that
he arranged the assassination, framing Bauer.
Well, clearly Cummings
was protecting Bauer.
- Why?
- I don't know why.
The fact remains I received confirmation
from intelligence sources
that Bauer was, without question, the shooter.
- Which sources?
- That's enough.
I'm not gonna stand here
and have my orders challenged.
You have concerns, Hal. We will
sort this all out once Bauer's in custody.
Does that suit you?
- Yes, sir.
- Good.
Mom?
Amy?
I'm coming.
Sweetheart? Ow!
Mom!
Mom.
- 911. What's your emergency?
- My mom passed out. I can't wake her up.
- Calm down. Tell me, what's your name?
- Amy. My mom's name is Evelyn.
- And what's your mom's last name?
- Martin. Her name's Evelyn Martin.
All right, honey, now tell me where you are.
Yeah.
Sir, a call is coming to the 911 operator
from a motel at 1850 Porter Valley Drive,
requesting assistance for an Evelyn Martin.
I'll be there shortly.
My fellow Americans, it is with great relief
that I announce that the terrorist threat
our nation faced today is over.
More than an hour ago,
counterterrorist agents, under my direction,
thwarted the latest attack on civilians,
the nature of which was kept secret
due to national security.
This was done
with the public's best interest in mind.
- He really did it.
- Ma'am?
Charles.
He stopped the terrorists,
the treaty was signed.
He said he would ride out this crisis
and everything would be OK.
And it is.
I should have trusted him.
Yes, ma'am.
What's wrong, Aaron?
I'm just a little battle-worn.
- Why are we stopping here?
- There's too many checkpoints in the area.
- We'll go the rest of the way on foot.
- How far's the bank?
About a quarter of a mile that way.
I'll be right back.
- Aaron, it's Jack.
- Jack.
Are you aware Logan's issued a warrant
for your arrest for Palmer's assassination?
- No, but that makes sense.
- The vice president's not behind this, is he?
No, it's Logan.
They'll have every agency looking for you.
Logan is the only one who can call them off.
As soon as we have the evidence, we'll pass it
off to Secretary Heller. Then it won't matter.
- Is there anything I can do?
- Keep your eyes open and watch your back.
Will do.
Get out of the car. Come on.
Let's go.
Move, move.
Take cover. Go!
Not a word.
Ms Hayes, Valerie Harris
on line two for you. She says it's urgent.
- Valerie, what's happening?
- We lost Audrey.
- What?
- She transferred the tracker to a DWP truck.
Dammit. How? She's got no field experience.
I don't know. We only found it cos the DWP
guy stopped to check a faulty power line.
All right, hold your positions
and wait for my instructions.
- Papazian.
- Audrey ditched her transponder.
Redirect satellite surveillance and track her.
I can redirect Caltrans and one sat-link,
but the rest are dedicated to finding Bauer.
Following Audrey should lead us to him.
Tell me when you've got something.
I'm on it.
Take the wall.
Watch him.
Just do what he says, Carl,
and you'll be home before you know it.
What's the emergency procedure?
I have 30 seconds to put my key in,
then I enter my code.
If you enter the wrong code and alert the
police, your wife is dead. Do you understand?
- Yes.
- Let's go.
Where's the vault?
Take us around the back.
Stay away from the windows.
- How do I open it?
- It's a 12-digit code, but it's a timed unlock.
It allows enough time for the police to arrive
if someone triggers the silent alarm.
Write the code down for me.
Take him to one of the desks.
Keep an eye on him.
You heard him.
I know you.
- No, you don't.
- I do. You're David Palmer's brother.
I saw you on TV this morning.
You were there when he was shot.
What the hell are you doing in my bank,
and who is he?
I know it's absurd to ask you to trust me
in these circumstances,
- but, believe me, you don't want to know.
- Oh, come on!
You threaten me with a gun,
you kidnap me, you're robbing my bank.
I deserve to know
what the hell is going on here.
All right.
We believe there's evidence
in one of your safety deposit boxes
that's gonna prove who was behind
the assassination of my brother, OK?
Wayne.
- What's going on?
- What could I say? He recognised me.
It's all right. Mr. Mossman,
how long is the delay before the vault opens?
Five minutes. Is that true?
Is that why you are here?
Yes.
Why don't you wait and get a subpoena?
The people behind this would never let us.
They've already tried to kill me twice tonight,
and they're gonna try again
the very first chance they get.
Mom!
Ms Martin, you're in shock,
but you're gonna be OK.
You know my name?
Where's Bauer?
You did? Well, that's good. I'm glad.
I'll get back to you.
- I thought you went to bed.
- No.
I, uh, watched you with the press.
Well, um, that was Maury,
and he thought it went pretty well.
Good.
But that doesn't begin to describe it.
Charles, you have had to
deal with more crises today
than any president in an entire term.
You... were magnificent.
Magnificent? Well, I like the sound of that.
Especially coming from you.
I'm so proud of you.
I hope I haven't embarrassed you
too much as your first lady.
Don't be ridiculous. You walked up to the
edge a couple of times, but nobody noticed.
I'll try to find a compliment
in there somewhere.
I'm sorry, Marty. I didn't...
Wow.
I was selfish today. You had so much on your
plate, you didn't need me piling more on.
- No...
- Don't say anything. Just accept my apology.
I do, I do. I accept your apology.
- I have to take this privately.
- Who is it?
- What difference does it make?
- I thought the crisis was over.
- I thought you and I...
- All right.
- Yes.
- We know Bauer's location.
Evelyn gave him up.
- Well, then, take care of it.
- My men are heading there now.
- Good. Let me know when it's done.
- I will.
I'm sorry, honey. I guess I haven't
gotten used to the idea that the crisis is over.
- When what's done?
- What?
- You just said, "Let me know when it's done. "
- That was Jamie.
I asked her to write me a radio speech
for tomorrow morning.
- We found Audrey Raines.
- Where?
Heading north toward Mulholland.
- Get me Harris.
- Yes, ma'am.
There.
- Harris.
- Valerie, we have a fix on Raines.
She's heading toward the Sepulveda Pass,
coming up on Mulholland.
Let's go.
- Chloe, do you have a minute?
- No.
- What is it?
- I was assigned to log all video activity.
But part of the vector's locked out.
- What do you mean?
- Someone's taken control of a satellite
using a class-one priority override.
- Do you know anything about it?
- No. I'll look into it.
Thanks.
Crap.
- Yes.
- All points covered. Perimeter is secure.
- Do you have a visual?
- Yes, I did briefly.
All right, listen. You tell your men the instant
that Bauer steps outside that bank building,
you take him down,
then kill the others and secure the recording.
- Which one is it?
- 23.
Mr. Palmer, I admired your brother
a great deal. He was a great man.
Thank you.
- It had to be done.
- I decide that.
I never authorised you to kill David Palmer.
Palmer found out
about your involvement. He called your wife!
I can handle my wife. My concern
is keeping this operation from collapsing.
- That's Logan.
- All threads end with Cummings.
He thinks he's running this. Keep it that way.
I know my part, Mr. Henderson.
You just do as you're told.
- Oh, my God!
- We got what we need.
I'm sorry we put you through this. It'll be
safer for you to stay here. Please let us out.
I'd like to help. I've come this far.
- We'll need your car a little longer.
- Sure. It's insured.
Wayne, there's someone outside.
Mr. Mossman, get back in the vault now.
- Is there any other way out?
- No, front door only. Security.
Dammit.
Both of you, stay here. I'll be right back.
- Men are taking up positions.
- We'll have to turn ourselves in.
They didn't come here to arrest us,
they came to kill us.
- What are they waiting for?
- They're waiting for us to leave the building.
So what do you wanna do?
- How do you trip the silent alarm?
- A key.
But if you trip that,
LAPD will be here within minutes.
That's what I want. Henderson's men
outnumber us. If we leave now, we lose.
The cops get the recording
if we go into custody.
We won't. When Henderson finds out LAPD
have arrived, his men will engage them.
He doesn't want the police
to have the recording either.
- They shoot each other. How does that help?
- We have to use that as a diversion.
It's our only way out. Trigger the alarm.
Let's get ready.
Valerie, the feed should be coming through
to your laptop now.
I've got her. She's heading west on Chandler.
- How close are you to Audrey's car?
- About two miles.
- Close the gap to one mile.
- Will do.
Something's wrong. The feed's breaking up.
We're experiencing the same difficulty
with ours. Hold on.
- What's going on?
- I don't know.
That satellite's positioned correctly.
I'm tracing the corruption.
It's the server.
- What is it?
- O'Brian's gone.
- What were you doing?
- What?
What were you doing?
Are you kidding? If you really want
the details, I'll write you a report.
Let's go. Now.
They're here. Mr. Mossman, like I said before,
it might be safer for you to stay here.
If these guys find me, they assume I know
about the recording, they kill me, right?
I'll take my chances with you.
Stay as close to Mr. Palmer as you can.
I'll provide cover fire.
Once we leave the bank, you break left.
- Yes, sir?
- What's your status?
- No change. They haven't come out.
- They've seen you. Tell your men to move in.
Dammit. The cops are here.
- We can't let 'em have Bauer. Take 'em down.
- Yes, sir.
Drop your weapons!
Take 'em out! Now!
Let's go.
We need to go to the police car now. Move!
He's been hit!
- How's he doing?
- He's dead.
Dammit.
- Where are you?
- On my way. Has your father agreed to meet?
He's landing at Van Nuys airport
in 15 minutes.
- I'm here now.
- Good. We got the evidence.
- Have you listened to it?
- There's no doubt it's Logan.
You understand what this means?
We're talking about taking down
the President of the United States.