President Hassan's security forces--
they're still cracking down on the opposition
and they're not showing any signs of letting up.
The rumors have already started
that the British are pulling out as signatories to the accord.
Assemble the representatives.
I want to appeal to them myself
to stay the course.
One of the suspects
has family connections
to a member of our delegation here at the UN.
Who?
Jamot.
Are you arresting me?
I demand to speak with President Hassan.
President Hassan is the one who gave this order.
What's wrong? You sound upset.
I need to speak with you about your father.
I have to go to the embassy right now.
I'll meet you in private when I get back.
This has the address and schematic
of the evidence lockup.
This keycard will get you access.
How do we find the money?
The evidence bins are numbered.
Do exactly what I tell you to do,
and you'll be in and out.
No one will know you're there.
The authorities know
about the nuclear material.
Putting Oleg in a clinic would lead them right to us.
No doctors.
The doctor said that Oleg could be treated.
He showed me how.
Who are you to question my judgment?
Never disobey an order from your father.
I'm sorry, my son.
Tell me about this buyer.
His name is Ernst Meier,
German arms dealer.
What's he looking to buy?
Weapons-grade uranium.
I'm going to have to meet this Meier,
and I need a good-faith payment up front.
I'm not going to tell you again.
Leave me alone and let me get dressed.
Damn it, come here
or the deal's off.
Meier?
That's right.
Where is the $5 million?
The money is in your account.
Drop the weapon. Now! Drop it!
Meier. You really think you can roll me for $5 million?
Let me talk to my man.
Yes.
Bring him back here.
He wants to see you.
Get up.
fjdlafjlasjl
Thank you so much.
Well, that went well.
Unanimous support for the treaty--
well, nearly unanimous, anyway.
I have the distinct impression
that I am running out of goodwill.
Maybe,
but you bought yourself some breathing room.
These people are already up past their bedtimes.
I don't think we'll be hearing any more grousing
until tomorrow morning at the earliest.
Congratulations, Madam President.
Thank you, I appreciated your support.
Good.
Now I hope you'll explain to me what's really going on.
I thought I did.
You invoked national security,
which, with respect, is not an explanation.
It's saying "Don't ask."
Madam President,
our countries have a unique relationship
based on a trust developed over nearly a century now.
Anything you say to me is
in the strictest confidence.
You may tell your prime minister and no one else
that President Hassan's crackdown
isn't just a response to the attempt on his life.
There are unsecured nuclear materials in play.
Apparently a faction inside his country was so disturbed
by the prospect of disarmament,
they decided to take matters into their own hands.
Where are the materials?
Here on our soil.
CTU is running an undercover operation
to retrieve them as we speak.
Who is that?
My guess is, it is my backup.
No calls till we get to Vladimir.
Does this look like a situation
where you get to make demands?
It's Meier.
I lost my sight line on you.
I'm leaving the building.
I understand.
Everything okay?
The money's been transferred to Vladimir's account.
We're going to his office.
We should be there in a few minutes.
I'll follow with a backup team.
That might not be necessary.
After what they just pulled,
you're sure you're comfortable without backup?
There are other considerations.
You mean they have Renee.
That's right.
Okay, we'll stay back.
I'll let you know.
What was that?
Let him know what?
Shut up and drive.
Okay, I got 'em on traffic cam.
Is everything okay?
Jack seems to be in control.
Looks fine, all things considered.
Driver looks a little worried.
Who is this guy anyway?
Should I pass him on to facial recognition?
Dana?
I've got to take this.
Yeah, sure, no biggie.
Just unsecured nuclear materials.
Yes.
We're there, outside the evidence building.
You're in the side alley, right?
No,
we parked out front so everyone can see us.
Come on, what do you think I am?
Okay, look, I need to walk you through this step by step.
I know, we're ready.
Well, something just came up here and I need you to hang on
for a few minutes.
Here? We're kind of exposed, Jenny.
You'll be fine if you just stay still.
We have a 30-minute window before the next security pass.
I will be with you the second I can.
Arlo, Hastings wants us in his office for a field update.
Can I ask you a hypothetical question?
If it's about Dana, it's not hypothetical.
If your fianc? Was cheating on you,
would you want to know?
Hypothetically, who'd be asking--
some creepy stalker who's about to get fired?
I'm serious.
So am I. Just go upstairs.
It's none of your business.
Dana, Cole just called about Jack.
He's almost to Laitanan.
Hastings wants us in his office.
Pass me back the keys.
Slowly get out,
put your hands on the roof.
Let's go.
So this is how you do business?
I wire you the $5 million
like we agreed, and then you try and take me out.
I did not think you were for real.
It was a misunderstanding,
but it's past.
We are here.
As an act of good faith,
Vladimir has already started calling his contacts,
inquiring about the nuclear materials.
I don't care what he's done.
I want to talk to you.
So talk.
I want to talk to my partner alone now.
Look, he's upset,
understandably.
It will be fine.
Yeah?
This is our chance.
We should take him out now.
No, we need him to do this deal.
Don't risk everything for a whore.
You ever talk about her like that again,
I'll kill you.
You understand?
What the hell are you doing?
I have authorization to pull you out.
No, that's not possible.
Renee, you've taken us this far, I'm going to finish it.
Jack, you can't. He doesn't trust you, first of all.
The only reason he's agreeing to continue this is me.
I'm fine, really.
You want to make calls,
let's go.
You don't have a say in this.
I am pulling you out. No, look,
it's not a big deal.
I know what he did to you six years ago,
and it is a big deal.
Jack, if we stop this now,
then everything that I have done is for nothing.
We're running out of time.
Let's go.
We're almost there, it'll be worth it.
Kevin, are you there?
Yeah.
I thought you forgot about us.
I wish I could.
Come on, don't be like that.
Are we good to go?
Yes, move now.
Let's go.
There's a security panel next to the door.
Use the keycard I gave you.
The code is 1668.
1668.
166...
Keep moving, it will stop in a second.
If you want the $120,000
you will be out of there in less than 20 minutes.
Okay, which door is it?
It's the last one on the left.
The code is 4660.
Four...
It's like Christmas... with chain link.
Okay, how do we find the money?
It's in section 3101.
3101. It's down the aisle on your left.
3101. The code is 2824.
The last one on the left.
3101-- do you see it?
Yeah, right here.
What the hell, man?
Jen, what the hell is going on?
What number is it?
Is it 3101?
3101-- this is 3110.
Come on.
What is wrong with you two?
Hey, it's called a mistake, all right?
Back off.
So where is it?
3101 is down the aisle on the left.
Down here, down here. The code is 2824.
2824, 2824, 2824.
Bin number's 4301.
4301.
Oh, man, it's too many numbers.
4301, 4301.
Boom! Got it!
That's beautiful, man.
That's beautiful.
Just shut up and get out of there.
The next patrol is in less than 15 minutes.
You've got the money.
Close the doors and leave.
15 minutes. We're leaving.
Call me when you're clear.
I sure will, Jenny.
Let's go!
Not yet.
Check out some of this stuff.
Hey, seriously, come on, man.
Patrol's on its way.
Yeah, 15 minutes.
Are you sure, then?
You haven't heard of anyone
dealing in these materials?
All right. Well, thank you for your time.
I'm sorry to trouble you.
Nothing.
They did not appreciate being called so late.
Renee, cut me some bread.
Here.
You might want to ease up on the drinking.
You've got some calls to make.
I drink what I want.
Renee, where's the bread?
Coming.
Drink.
What is this?
It is too thin.
It should be thick.
Nice and thick.
There we are.
She's changed, you know?
Six years ago,
she thought she was too good for me.
Now, she is much more friendly.
Maybe I should thank you-- all that time you were together
in Mexico City.
Come on.
I see how you look at her.
Don't tell me you didn't.
You want to keep talking, do it on the phone.
Otherwise, the nuclear
materials will be gone, and this deal will be dead.
Fine, but I don't like you breathing down my neck.
Lugo, get him out of here.
And I'm running out of my vodka.
Go get me some more.
Sit down.
I won't be long.
My younger son.
I wanted to bury him, Father Gregor.
Of course, but that will take a little time.
The cemetery workers need to prepare the grave...
No. You will do it now
out back.
My men will dig his grave.
Sergei Petrovich,
this isn't right.
Then make it right.
Treat him like a soldier
who died on the battlefield and must be buried there.
Is that how he died?
In battle?
You just make it right.
Say all the prayers.
Where I end up, I don't care.
But this boy is with the angels.
My men will be with you soon.
Leave us.
Get up.
Look at me, Josef.
I want you to understand
that everything I've done, I've done for you
and for our family.
You killed my brother.
Because I loved him,
because I couldn't bear to see him suffer,
because there was no other way.
There's always another way.
Not when we are dealing with nuclear materials.
We cannot risk the authorities finding out.
You know that.
You don't know why I'm doing this?
Because when I die,
I want to leave you
and your family a worthy inheritance.
Wealth, respect,
consequence.
Can you understand that?
One day you will.
As your son grows older, you will.
And you will understand
how much I love you.
My only son.
Father Gregor is here to bury Oleg.
Will you help him?
He's my brother.
Thank you.
Call when you are ready.
What is it?
Vladimir Laitanan.
He says it's important.
Vladimir, what do you want?
Sergei Petrovich.
I apologize for calling you out of the blue like this, sir.
Uh, your family is well?
I said, what do you want?
I have a business proposition.
Then call me in business time, not in the middle of the night.
No, no, no, this can't wait.
I hear there are materials for sale,
expensive materials, dangerous ones.
Talk straight. What materials?
Nuclear rods.
Highly enriched uranium.
So, why are you calling me?
If anyone has the organization
to pull off such a deal, it's you.
I'm flattered.
I have a buyer here, a German.
He's willing to pay a great deal of money for them.
Double any offer you have.
Then he is as stupid as you are.
Are you out of your mind?
Nobody deals in nuclear rods, nobody.
I'm sorry.
A misunderstanding.
Don't call me again.
He had no idea what I was talking about.
All right, then we call the next person.
You're not listening.
He says nobody sells these things.
Nobody.
You're close to the biggest deal of your life, Vladimir.
He's just jealous that he's not in on it.
Come here. Come here.
Look, later.
Later.
Once you've made more calls.
Come on.
Okay. Okay, okay, okay.
We have a problem.
Vladimir Laitanan knows about the fuel rods.
What are you going to do?
Da.
fafadsfa
fadfasdfa
fadsfasdfa
fasdfasdfasd
Anton?
fdsafasdf
fsadfasdfasdf
Yes?
Mr. President, it's Allison Taylor.
We were scheduled to resume our discussions.
I'm late, I know. I apologize.
The events of this evening...
The events of this evening make it more important than ever
that we complete our work on this treaty.
Mr. President, I need to know your intentions.
My intentions?
The crackdown on your countrymen.
I've been informed
that you've even arrested one of your own delegation.
That's an internal matter.
No, sir, it is not.
Less than an hour ago,
I assured delegates from two dozen countries
that you were still our best hope for peace.
I personally guaranteed them you'd observe
Tarin, are you all right?
When did you get back from the embassy?
Just now.
May I come in?
What is it?
It's only me here.
It's safe.
What's wrong?
You know your father has had many people arrested,
including Jamot.
Now he's having Jamot's wife
and two children detained back home,
so they can be used to force him to talk.
No.
There must be some mistake.
He gave the order himself.
I thought I'd convinced him not to,
but he was lying to me,
he went behind my back.
Kayla, your father is a great man.
I respect him more than anyone I have ever known.
But Farhad's betrayal has changed him.
What can we do?
Open up, please.
What are they doing here?
I don't know.
Open up.
Tarin, stay here.
Yes, Nabeel? Miss Kayla,
we've been looking everywhere for Tarin.
Have you seen him?
No.
Is there some problem?
What do you think you're doing?
We have orders, Miss Kayla.
I said he wasn't here.
I'm sorry, but I don't believe you.
You can't just barge in here!
I need to talk to my father!
Nabeel.
Why do you need armed guards to come looking for me?
The president says you may be involved with his brother.
Based on what?
Nothing.
Only that I would not allow
an innocent family to be tortured.
He's ordered me to detain you.
I have no choice.
You do have a choice, Nabeel.
Tell my father he's made a mistake,
that there's no one more loyal than Tarin.
Nabeel, this is insane,
and you know it.
Don't make this worse, please.
Don't you see? My hands are tied.
Let me talk to my father.
He's given orders not to be disturbed.
Even by you.
I'll talk to him!
I'll get him to change his mind!
No, I understand, Roman.
We'll do business some other time, okay.
That's it.
Last one.
He also knows nothing about nuclear rods.
He also said it's suicide to deal in them.
Meier has wasted our time.
No, look, Meier's intel is good. So we need to think.
Who else can we call? No one.
I've called everyone who could possibly deal in these things.
Then somebody that you've already talked to
has to know something.
Renee, it's-it's done.
Look, maybe they don't want to admit it.
Maybe they don't know how serious you are.
You should call them back. I said no.
Tell them that you have the buyer, tell them you have the money.
Shut up!
Just because I like your face doesn't mean
I have to put up with your crap.
We made $5 million.
A good night's work.
Why settle for five when we can have 50?
When did you get so greedy?
$5 million is plenty.
Plus we have each other, that's not too bad, is it?
Oh, it's not bad.
But it could be better.
Call them again.
Do it for me.
I said no.
Come on, Vladimir, push them harder.
Somebody knows something. What is your problem?
Nobody knows. There's no one left to call.
Now you go out there
and you tell Meier to leave, okay.
I'm not telling him anything!
What?
Not until you try again.
Look, it's over!
What is wrong with you?! I need this deal.
That is why you're here? The deal?
Why else? Do you think that I'm here for you?
Get up.
Renee.
Stop! Stop!
Stop!
Oh, God.
Oh, God!
It's all right. It's all right.
It's over.
It's over. It's okay.
Laitanan contacted everyone
he thought might have information
on the nuclear materials.
No one responded.
That's when he said he was finished.
Renee kept pushing him,
and it got ugly.
Laitanan's dead.
He attacked her.
And so, what, you took him out?
No, she did.
She did?
Half an hour earlier,
she was having sex with the guy.
How does that even happen, Jack?
What, she lose it?
She was defending herself.
Look, we knew this guy was violent before we even went in.
He's violent?
He's dead on the floor. Yes, he is.
And right, now,
we still don't have the nuclear materials secured,
so I suggest we move on.
Move on?
He was our only lead, Jack.
Now, where do we move on to?
We can start by working the phone calls that Laitanan made.
There's also physical files here
and a computer to go through.
Yeah, fine. Cole,
are you getting this?
Yes, sir. We're en route
from the staging area, five minutes out.
We're gonna need forensics to rip this place apart.
Yeah, I got Bennett with me.
He can coordinate till the full team arrives.
Just do what you can.
And bring Laitanan's body
back here for autopsy.
I want to know what the hell happened.
Any other good news?
Jack?
Cole?
Dana?
Excuse me?
I said, anything else?
No, sir.
Okay, then.
We'll see you when you get here. COLE: Yes, sir.
Our entire operation just went south.
You think you could show a little interest?
Pull it together!
You didn't have to do that.
Do what?
Cover for me with Hastings.
All I did was tell him the truth.
When they see Vladimir, they'll know what happened.
What do you think happened?
It's like you said.
I couldn't handle it.
God, I'm sorry.
It's all right.
No, it's not.
I could have killed you.
I've made such a mess of everything.
I just thought that if... if I did this,
I could make it all right.
I could have my life back.
Hey. Hey!
You can have your life back any time you want.
You just need to want it.
How?
I've tried, and I don't know how.
I don't...
I don't have anything, anyone.
You've got me.
Okay.
Hey. Hey.
Look at me. Look at me.
Okay?
I didn't want it to end like this.
I know.
Look, we're a lot farther ahead than we were three hours ago.
Every call Laitanan made is a solid lead
that we can follow up, and that's because of you.
You did your part.
Now let CTU do their job.
Please?
Let me take you home.
Okay.
Damn it, they really must have been moving.
CTU's here already.
Listen to me. This is really important.
Vladimir attacked you, and you defended yourself.
That's what happened.
I don't know.
I do, and if anybody else
wants to ask you questions about that,
I'll be right there with you to answer them.
Okay.
Let me go talk to them.
They're Russian.
Vladimir must have contacted whoever's got the rods.
They just didn't want him to know.
Hold on to this.
What are you doing?
I need to let them take me.
No. We have to get out of here.
Listen to me.
You want everything you've done so far to matter?
I need to do this.
When CTU gets here, you tell them
to start tracking me from the air.
These people are gonna lead us
to everything we're looking for.
They will kill you.
No. At worst, they're going to have to vet me,
find out how much I know.
It should buy us enough time.
Hide in here.
Take this.
If this door opens again, you start shooting.
Don't shoot!
Please!
I'm opening the door.
I'm unarmed.
See? Both my hands.
See? No problem.
I'm unarmed.
Don't shoot.
What happened here?
What happened?!
They tried to rip me off.
But you and I-- we can do business. Wait! Wait!
No! Don'
If you kill me, you're gonna cost your boss a lot of money.
Who else is with you here?
No one. Everybody else is dead.
All I want to do is business.
Mikhail!
Ӳ
Hansen, upload to CTU.
Mr. Hastings,
site is secured.
Video's coming through.
Three bodies. Are you getting this?
Yes, we are.
Any sign of Jack or Renee?
No, sir.
I'm here.
Here.
It's Renee, sir. She's alive.
Renee, where's Jack?
The Russians took him.
The ones that have the nuclear materials.
How? We've been monitoring the building.
No vehicles left this area.
I don't... I don't know.
They just suddenly appeared, but...
Wait. Jack let himself be taken.
He said that you'd be monitoring him from the air.
We haven't seen anything.
Our drones have been overhead the whole time.
They saw nothing.
Where is he?
We don't know.
Step up.
Sync by YYeTS.net
www.tvsubtitles.net