When I have it, we have to involve your father.
You know I don't like to be kept in the dark.
Tell me what this is all about.
I will. I just need a minute.
I decide what needs to be done.
I never authorised you to kill David Palmer.
- President Logan?
- And Christopher Henderson.
I know what you did and what you're doing.
And I'm here to put an end to it.
- You asked to see me, Mr. President?
- Hal.
I'm asking Secretary Heller to tender his
resignation. I wanted you here as a witness.
- What?
- He thinks I was complicit in today's attacks.
Miles set me up.
Please come with us.
We traced your call
to a public phone at Van Nuys airport.
If Audrey is at that location,
you're in a lot of trouble.
You're supposed to be in custody.
You helped Audrey break surveillance.
You need help. If you try to stop me, I will
recommend you for psychiatric evaluation.
Get in here.
- I couldn't contact Jack or Audrey.
- I haven't either.
Whatever you tell me will remain between us,
I promise you.
Not here.
Outside the south stable.
- Is Bauer dead?
- Not yet, Mr. President.
- He has the recording?
- Yes, sir.
That evidence directly implicates me
in David Palmer's death.
Son of a bitch.
- What's going on?
- They want the recording.
Audrey!
I have her, Jack.
What have you done?
- The left brachial artery.
She has three minutes before
she bleeds to death. Throw me that recording.
Jack, don't do it.
She's running out of time!
Don't give it to him.
- Here it is!
Easy. Easy. Easy.
- Stay with me.
- Jack, go get it.
Stay with me.
I need to loosen the tourniquet.
The bleeding's stopped.
He didn't sever the brachial artery.
- I need to get you to a doctor.
- I can wait. Do what you have to do.
- Are you sure?
- Yes.
Keep your arm elevated.
This is Chloe O'Brian. I'm not available now.
Chloe's not picking up her phone.
Can anyone else help you track Henderson?
No one who has access
to CTU's satellite network.
- I'm so sorry. This is my fault.
- Stop it.
I'll be right back.
- This is Jack Bauer.
- Jack?
Why are you
answering Wexler's phone?
He's dead. Henderson and a commando unit
attacked us 15 minutes ago.
They took the recording back.
Is Audrey all right?
She's fine. Did you cut your deal with Logan?
Logan accepted my terms,
then he took a call
and suddenly changed his mind.
That must've been Henderson.
We have to get the recording back.
If there's anything I can do, let me know.
With all due respect, Mr. Secretary,
I asked you for help, and you betrayed me.
Jack, I did what I thought
was best for this country.
I made a mistake. Please, forgive me.
I need to go, sir.
Come on.
- Hello?
- It's Jack.
Jack, did you get the recording
to Secretary Heller?
Henderson's got the recording.
I need Chloe to find him, but I can't reach her.
Chloe's here. She was arrested by Homeland
Security for helping you, but she got away.
Put her on speaker.
- Where are you?
- I'm at Van Nuys airfield. Listen.
Henderson left here
ten minutes ago with the recording.
I need you to access CTU's
satellite data streams to find him.
If I log onto their system,
they'll find me eventually.
You don't need to track him for long.
Can you do it?
- I can try to slip in through the subnet.
- Get back to me.
I'll set up a VPN pathway so they can't
trace us. It will only work with that phone.
OK.
I got ahold of Chloe.
We need to go. Can you get up?
- Yeah.
- Move slowly.
Ow.
Come on.
For satellite tracking,
I need more than my laptop.
I'll network onto your computer,
even though it's pathetic.
- And get that screen to work for me.
- All right.
I hope you don't mind,
but I don't work for you now.
- It's all right, Chloe.
- Good.
Bauer.
Jack, I'm pulling up footage of the airfield
from 15 minutes ago.
- Look for an explosion in the northwest.
- I see it.
Five minutes later, a vehicle leaves.
That's Henderson.
He went south on the service drive
and east on Menders. Then I lose him.
Use another satellite, traffic cams. Find him.
It'll take us a few minutes, but we're on it.
Copy that. Get back to me
as soon as you've got him on a live feed.
What makes you think that Henderson
hasn't destroyed the recording?
He would've done it in front of me,
giving me less of a reason to come after him.
- Why would he keep it?
- It's his insurance.
- Yes?
- Is Bauer dead?
- No.
- What happened?
- All that matters is that I have the recording.
- Have you destroyed it?
- No, sir, I have not.
- Why? What's the problem?
I'm making sure there won't be any problems.
I don't understand.
I may need protection.
That recording gives it to me.
- Protection?
- Yes, sir.
Do you mean from me? That's absurd.
With all due respect, it isn't absurd,
as evidenced by Walt Cummings' "suicide".
That was different.
You told me yourself that was necessary.
I assume that one day others
will tell you the very same thing about me.
Chris, you and I have been in this
from the beginning.
Destroying that recording protects both of us.
I'm sorry, Mr. President. I give you my word
it will be kept in a very safe place,
and it will only be made public
should I meet with some... accident.
- Chris, this is completely unnecessary.
- I'm sure it is, sir.
Then again, I am a very cautious man.
- Chloe, have you got Henderson?
- He's three quarters of a mile ahead.
He should be farther along.
- It's definitely the car he left in.
- How long until I've got a visual?
The road curves.
You should see him once it straightens.
Hold on.
Got him.
Get down.
Damn!
It's over, Christopher.
Turn around.
Put the gun down
and keep your hands where I can see them.
Do it or I will kill you.
- You kill me, Jack, Secretary Heller dies too.
- What are you talking about?
There's always a contingency plan, Jack.
You know that.
My men have been tracking Heller from
a chopper ever since he left Logan's retreat.
If I can't contact them every 15 minutes on the
dot, they have orders to kill Secretary Heller,
which means you got about...
three minutes to save his life.
Jack.
- Audrey, please get back in the car.
- Is he lying about my father?
Slowly, walk towards me.
Put your hands behind your head.
Get on your knees.
Cuff yourself.
Yeah, Jack.
Patch me through to Secretary Heller's
cellphone. Lock a satellite on his signal.
Download a visual of his vehicle on my PDA.
He left the retreat just before one o'clock.
On it. Open up a parallel channel
on the NSA's land sats.
Scan radio slices in three-mile
increments emanating from the retreat. Sir.
Jack, I'm pulling up the DOD database.
Here it is. I'm patching you through.
Copy that.
- Heller.
- It's Jack.
I need you to confirm for me
if a helicopter has been tracking your vehicle.
- What's going on, Jack?
- Time is critical. Is there a helicopter or not?
Yeah, there's a chopper. Who are they?
Henderson's men.
He claims they'll kill you if I don't let him go.
- Is he bluffing?
- He doesn't do that, sir.
Jack, I've got Heller's car.
I'm patching it to your PDA.
Copy that.
Jack,
they have a laser sight trained on me.
Get up.
You give me the recording, I let you go.
No. Come on, Jack. You're wasting time.
We both know you're not gonna let Heller die.
Don't let him do this.
I'm gonna walk out of here,
and you're not gonna stop me, so uncuff me.
- Jack, don't let him go!
- I don't have a choice, sir.
Yes, you do. If I had listened to you,
none of this would be happening.
This is my responsibility.
I will not allow Logan and Henderson
to use me as a pawn.
- Sir.
- Do not let them get away with this.
Make sure that the recording
gets to the right people.
Tell Audrey I love her.
- Mr. Secretary, what are you doing?
- No.
Chloe, are you on the line? Can you confirm
that Heller just drove his car into the lake?
Yes.
Damn you!
Oh, my God! No!
How could you do this?
This isn't about
what you think is best for the country.
This is about your greed for power.
Today you have been responsible for killing
David Palmer and the Secretary of Defense.
- Two real patriots.
- Oh, God.
Damn you.
What happened to you?
- Give me the recording.
- I don't have it.
Where is it?
I'm not gonna tell you, you know that,
no matter what you do to me.
Do it.
Kill him, Jack. Do it!
Yeah?
- Graham?
- Cancel the action against Henderson.
- Why?
He has the recording, but he's arranged to
have it released if anything happens to him.
- You should've exercised more control.
- There's a limit to what I can do.
- Apparently.
- Don't you use that tone with me.
We've both made mistakes.
You're right. Mr. President, my apologies.
But the fact is
we have a bigger problem than Henderson.
What are you talking about?
At least he acts rationally in his own interests.
Unfortunately this is not true of your wife.
My wife?
There's a Secret Service agent named Pierce
who knows more than he should.
- He intends to share that with Martha.
- I've taken steps to deal with Agent Pierce.
The real problem is Mrs. Logan. She continues
to ask questions, talk about her suspicions.
People don't take her seriously.
There are too many loose ends.
We cannot have her unravel everything.
- You think I don't realise that?
- I think you are in a very difficult position.
You hoped the situation with Martha
would resolve itself. You must silence her.
I know. But I'll handle this myself.
Mrs. Logan, Agent Pierce was transferred.
That's what you keep saying, but it doesn't
make sense, not at one in the morning.
We work around the clock, ma'am.
It's quite common for agents
to get pulled off details at odd hours.
Right when they're supposed
to have a meeting with the first lady?
- I don't know anything about a meeting.
- Well, I do.
I found Aaron's phone on the ground
where we were supposed to meet.
Now, I want you to find Agent Pierce,
and get him back here right now.
There's a glitch in the scheduling software.
- Are these glitches quite common as well?
- Actually, no.
Mrs. Logan.
I'm Agent Adams.
I think I can explain everything.
- Well?
- This is a sensitive issue.
President Logan
would like you to come with me.
What is this sensitive information?
Is it about Agent Pierce?
- You need to talk to the president about that.
- I'm asking you.
Do you know where Aaron Pierce is?
- No, ma'am, I don't.
- Is this where my husband is?
I want to talk to him.
Charles?
Hello?
Yeah.
- Henderson doesn't have the recording.
- Is it in his car?
- No. There must've been a hand-off.
- What do you mean?
That explains why he wasn't
farther ahead when I left the airfield.
- He must've given it to someone.
- OK, I'll back-trace the route with the satellite.
- See if I can spot anything.
- Yeah.
Jack, we're getting that recording
and exposing Logan.
I don't care how far I have to go or
what I have to do. Do you understand, Jack?
Yes.
- Go ahead.
- You were right. I found the hand-off.
- Henderson rendezvoused with another car.
- Can you track the other car?
We're tracking it. It headed back to Van Nuys.
Looks like the civilian side of the airfield.
Pulled onto the tarmac.
- Whoever it was got onto the plane.
- Isn't air traffic grounded?
- Yeah, this is not a commercial flight.
- The plane is servicing. It's about to take off.
Was Curtis relieved of his duty
or is he at CTU?
He's at CTU taking orders
from Homeland Security, but I trust him.
Where is he?
According to the deployment grid,
25 miles northwest of you with a tac team.
Call him.
Get him to this location as soon as possible.
I want him to transfer
Henderson and Audrey to CTU.
Is that a good idea?
Logan's in control at CTU.
Curtis will protect them. It's our best chance
to get Audrey medical attention.
I'm calling Curtis now.
- Thanks.
- What's happening?
The person Henderson gave the recording to
boarded a plane at Van Nuys.
- Why aren't you going now?
- I'll go when Curtis gets here. He's not far.
- I'll be fine until then.
- I won't leave you alone.
Jack, if you don't get that recording,
my father will have died for nothing.
Jack...
for me.
Henderson is secure. When he regains
consciousness, don't go anywhere near him.
- You don't even talk to him. You understand?
- I understand.
We have to assume his people are looking
for him. They'll monitor non-VPN traffic,
which means you can't make or receive
any calls unless they come from me.
- It's Wexler's cell. I've got the number.
- All right.
- Audrey, I don't feel right about this.
- I'm gonna be all right.
I'm so sorry.
Jack, you have to go now.
Jack.
Make sure you get that recording.
I will.
Let me know when you're done.
Bierko has regained consciousness.
We're waiting for the medical assessment
before we begin the interrogation.
- Let me know when we get the go-ahead.
- Final protocol shifts.
You can tell Washington the transfer of
authority from CTU to Homeland is complete.
OK.
Two hours ahead of schedule, Karen.
That is remarkable.
- I'm sorry. My head is somewhere else.
- Where?
We gave the president Bauer's location
an hour ago. We should've heard something.
- The military authority is handling Bauer.
- I know, but this doesn't make any sense.
The president insisted we focus on Bauer. We
find him, he hands the mission to the military.
Karen, we're out of that loop.
- Karen Hayes.
- We have a problem.
Chloe O'Brian got out of Holding,
and she is not in the building.
How's that possible?
I'm gathering details. I reviewed the tape.
It looks like Shari talked to her,
and Shari let her go.
Shari didn't try to stop her? Why?
I don't know.
I had security take her into custody.
Good. Bring her up here right now.
We need to focus on how we find Chloe now.
- My guess is she'll try to contact Bauer.
- I agree, but how?
She was using CTU resources before
to help Bauer. Maybe she'll try again.
She could try to access our system remotely.
- All she needs is a laptop.
- That's right.
- She'll disguise her traffic.
- Can you get through it?
- I can trace her location from the binary.
- Do it.
Wait outside.
Why did you let Chloe escape?
- She intimidated me.
- She intimidated you?
Sit down.
You are in a great deal of trouble,
Ms Rothenberg.
You had better start talking to me now.
She said she'd recommend me
for psychiatric evaluation and I'd lose my job.
I'm sorry, Ms Hayes. There's something
wrong with me. I should see someone...
Shari, did Chloe tell you why she
was helping Audrey Raines and Bauer?
- She thinks Jack is innocent.
- Based on what?
Based on some absurd idea
that President Logan framed Bauer.
She said something about the president being
involved in David Palmer's assassination.
Can you believe her?
And people think I'm crazy.
Dammit! Open this door!
I don't know what you think you're doing.
- Unlock it.
Open it!
Charles.
I want that man arrested!
- And I want to know where Aaron Pierce is.
- Shh.
Martha, calm down.
All right? Aaron's fine.
I just transferred him back to Washington.
In the middle of the night? It makes no sense.
Why am I locked in this room?
Because we need to talk.
About what?
I've been wanting to tell you this, but I told
myself that you were too fragile to handle it.
But that's not the truth.
The truth is I've kept this from you
because it's horrible, and because it's ugly.
What are you talking about?
What happened to Palmer shouldn't have. He
got involved in something he shouldn't have.
What are you saying?
That I never authorised his death.
You mean...
- you know who killed David?
- Yes.
How do you know that?
- He works for me.
- What?
- It's very complicated.
- There's an explanation.
- What? An explanation? Oh, my God!
- Stop! You don't understand.
- Go to hell!
Oh, my God!
You're involved with David's murder.
- Martha.
- Oh, my God! Why are you telling me this?
Why are you telling me this?
Because you're on your way
to finding out the truth on your own.
And because you need to stop.
- Stop what?
- Asking questions and talking about this.
Never again. Do you know how traumatic this
would be for the country if people found out?
Oh, yes, you're worried about the country.
Dammit, that's the most
important part of this!
This would destroy the American
people's faith in their government.
It would destroy our credibility
all over the world.
You lied to me.
Everything,
this whole day has been one giant lie.
- What you've done makes me sick!
- Martha, enough.
I know that what I did, what I allowed
to happen, was a terrible mistake,
but it's done.
Right now, I need you to swear to me
that you will do as I ask...
for the country, Martha.
I've forgiven you many things, Charles,
but not this.
You've broken my heart.
I'm looking at you, and...
I hate you.
But I will keep my mouth shut,
because the people of this country
don't deserve to suffer.
You do, Charles, you do.
Are you sure we're going to get through this
the way we planned?
- What does that mean?
- There are too many loose ends.
What operation
doesn't have loose ends? Hm?
Of course we won't get through this
the way we planned.
I have never made a deal that didn't feel
like it would fall apart in the 11th hour.
Now, if you don't have the stomach
to deal with a few bumps,
then this is not the room where you belong.
And that goes for all of you. You're starting to
have doubts. I can smell it, and I don't like it.
We need to remember the strength we had
18 months ago when we started this thing.
We OK, Ron?
Yeah.
Think about your kids.
That's what I do when I need to get focused.
Yeah.
The situation with Martha is taken care of.
- I spoke to her.
- And?
And I made it very clear
that if she continues with this behaviour,
I will send her back
to the hospital in Vermont.
Well, you were going to have her committed
earlier today, but you changed your mind.
That's because she found out the truth,
and I decided I should keep her close.
- What if she finds out the truth again?
- She won't.
And if she does, I will handle it,
just like I have all day.
OK.
Fair enough. You have done a remarkable job
today, Mr. President. I will admit that.
Thank you. It's about time
I heard some words of appreciation.
We were just talking about
how you've had to be on the front line,
how you've had to get your hands dirty,
while we could just sit back
and watch from a safe distance.
You've earned our trust, and I am sure...
that you will do whatever it takes
to keep your wife in line.
Audrey.
Where's Jack?
Audrey, I'm sorry about your father.
I never intended your father
to get in the middle of this.
I've known Secretary Heller a very long time,
and he's an honourable man.
Wait a minute. What time is it?
It's ten or twelve minutes since...
If the windows didn't collapse when the car
hit the water, there could be an air pocket.
20, 30 minutes in a submerged car,
if there's an air pocket...
- Stop it.
- Your father could be alive, Audrey.
Secretary Heller could be alive inside that car.
If he's alive, you gotta do something about it.
If there's a possibility he's living, you gotta
call military authority or emergency services.
- For God's sakes, he's your father.
- Stop it! Stop it! Stop! Stop! Stop talking!
What do you think? I'm stupid?
You want me to make that call
so your people can find me.
Audrey, my people are gonna find us anyway,
and Jack's not gonna stop all this.
I'm trying to help your father.
He's drowning in a car
and you're not doing anything about it.
- You're gonna live with that?
- Shut up.
He is dying and you're doing nothing,
Audrey. You are doing nothing.
I swear to God,
not another word.
Yeah.
- Jack?
- I've got a visual on the plane.
It must be a diplomatic flight.
There's a lot of security.
- We have a problem.
- What?
I'm tracking the helicopter
Henderson's men used to shadow Heller.
- And?
- It's heading towards Audrey and Henderson.
- How could they find them?
- Maybe by using satellites.
- But they'll be there any second.
- Where's Curtis?
He might not make it there
before Henderson's men, Jack.
Upload your visual to my PDA. Advise
Curtis of the situation. I'll get back to you.
- Jack.
- Listen.
Henderson's men
are heading back towards you.
- You've gotta get out of there.
- And leave him?
- We don't have a choice.
- Yes, we do. I have the gun and I can kill him.
We need him alive. Curtis's team is almost
there. They'll secure him. Get out of there.
He's responsible for the death of my father.
I can't leave him here!
Audrey, please, listen to what I'm telling you.
You've gotta start moving now! Audrey!
On the right.
Take the other side.
Stipe, get over
and get these handcuffs off me.
Dammit!
Heller's daughter is in this building. Kill her.
Then get back here. We'll deal with Bauer.
Audrey, it's Curtis.
Stay behind me.
Hold it right there! Hands on your head.
Let's go. Move.
- Secure him for transport back to CTU.
- Yes, sir.
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Tac team, hostiles are down.
We have Henderson.
Roger that, sir.
Copy.
We need medical attention for Audrey Raines.
Yeah?
- It's me.
- What's happening?
Curtis's team killed Henderson's men,
and they're taking Henderson into custody.
Jack, I tried to shoot him, but I couldn't.
- All that matters is that you're safe.
- Yeah, I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
OK, good. Let me speak to Curtis.
Curtis. It's Jack.
Go ahead.
Yeah, Jack.
Transport Audrey back to CTU as quickly
as possible, and get her over to Medical.
Tell Karen Hayes
that no one is to have access to Henderson.
She'll be taken care of,
but as far as Henderson goes,
CTU wants to apprehend you,
not take your advice.
Just do what you can, and I'll get back to you.
- Jack, is Audrey all right?
- Yes. Curtis is in control of the situation.
- What do you have on the plane?
- Details just came in.
It is a chartered diplomatic flight.
Security level eight, leaving at 2am or sooner.
Find out who's on board so we can figure out
who Henderson gave the recording to.
It won't be easy getting past the firewall.
I understand. Bill, slow down the departure
of this flight so I can get on it.
All right, Jack. There's a maintenance gate
on the northwest side of the airfield.
- You'll be able to get close to the plane.
- I'm there.
Just get back to me
as soon as you've got the passenger list.
Here you go.
He's clear.
- Go ahead.
- Yeah.
- Jack.
We've tried everything. We can't
delay the plane. It takes off in ten minutes.
- OK. Has Chloe got the passenger list?
- I still can't get past the firewall.
- Chloe, I need that list.
- Jack, I'm trying.
There you are.
Yeah.
- I got O'Brian.
- On our system?
Yeah, she's trying to log in
to the State Department network.
- Do we know why?
- No. She used a work-around I'd never seen.
- I machine-coded a matrix to get through...
- We just need to find her. Where is she?
I'm running a physical trace.
It's a private house.
Cross-referencing with property records.
Karen, she's working
out of Bill Buchanan's house.
- Are you sure?
- Positive.
We have a tac team not far away.
I'll dispatch them now.
- What's their ETA?
- I'm showing less then seven minutes.
Good. Keep me posted.
- Novick.
- Mike, it's Karen Hayes.
Karen. How are things going over there?
It's a bit of a rough transition
but we're getting through it.
- That's good to hear. What do you need?
- Some clarification.
We were sent here by the White House,
but we've been dealing exclusively with
Vice President Gardner, until two hours ago.
What happened?
The president ordered me to arrest Jack Bauer
on evidence
he was unwilling to share with me.
Yes, I know about that.
- Have you seen the evidence?
- No, actually, I-I haven't.
- Mike, who has seen it?
- I don't have a good answer for that.
Are you telling me you're not in the loop?
Actually, I don't even think there is a loop.
The president
is keeping his own counsel at the moment.
- That's a first.
- Yes.
It is.
Is there anything else you want to tell me?
Nothing that I can say with any authority.
All I know is that...
it's been a strange night.
- I see.
- I wish I could be more helpful.
No, Mike, actually, you've been very helpful.
Thank you.
- Hello?
- This is Karen Hayes.
You have less than seven minutes
to get Chloe out.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Bill, stop.
Miles traced Chloe through a remote node,
and if you don't believe me, tell her he used
a machine-coded matrix to find her.
- Karen, why are you warning us?
- Because I may have made a mistake earlier.
A lot of things didn't make sense today,
until Shari told me what Chloe said
about President Logan being... involved.
I've gotta go. Just get Chloe out of there now.
- You have to go.
- I can't. Jack needs the passenger list.
Chloe, if they find you here,
you'll be arrested. You have to go now.
Not yet.
- Closing doors.
- That's the last one.
Let's get this thing out of here. Let's go.
Let's go.