- Identify.
- Victor Rovner.
- Requesting permission to transmit.
- Log in.
Permission granted.
Excuse me.
This is Walsh.
We just heard from Rovner. He confirmed
that there will be an attempt today.
- Did he find out who the target is?
- Senator David Palmer.
I hate this.
"On this historic occasion"?
Well, it is an historic occasion, sir.
But it's self-serving to say it.
I wanna stay low-key.
Wrong. Play it up, inspire people.
- Honey, what do you think?
- I agree with Patty.
OK, but not "occasion".
Sounds like we're having brunch.
"On this historic day"?
Deal.
- You going to bed?
- How can I sleep?
No, I'm gonna write a few thank yous,
and you call me if you need me.
Thank you, angel.
- You're in trouble, Dad.
- Really?
Yeah.
So...
- is she still giving you the cold shoulder?
- If by "she" you are referring to your mother,
I'd appreciate it if you'd
call her by her name - Mom.
- And, no, she's just busy.
- She's busy a lot.
And it's a school night
for you, so time for bed.
- Good night.
- I love you.
I'm glad you moved back in, Daddy.
Me too, sweet. Have a good sleep.
- Night, sweet pea.
- Yeah.
She still giving you a hard time?
I don't know when I became the enemy.
I think she blames me for you moving out.
I never gave her any reason to.
Maybe not.
I think you let her manipulate you, Jack.
No, I don't.
Let me guess. Just now
she was sweetness and light?
- Then she said something nasty about me.
- And I just busted her on it.
I don't know why you take this so personally.
It's just that mother-teenage daughter thing.
Hey...
Maybe you're right.
Maybe we should talk to her right now.
Tell her she can't play us off each other, that
if she's insulting you, she's insulting me too.
- OK.
- Good.
I really appreciate that.
So you just said that you appreciate that.
- You kind of appreciate it?
- I really appreciate it.
Do you really, really appreciate it?
You really appreciate it?
- How much do you appreciate it?
- Jack.
OK.
Kim.
Kim?
Honey?
(car drives off
Kim!
She snuck out.
That's it. She's grounded
for two months. No exceptions.
She can forget about
getting her driver's licence.
- Hello?
- Teri, is Jack there?
Yeah, he's right here. It's Nina.
What? Hey, Nina.
Now? No. No, I can't.
Yeah.
OK, fine. Get a hold of
the others and bring 'em in.
Yeah. OK. Bye. It's Walsh.
He's coming into the office.
He wants everybody in as soon as possible.
It's only a briefing.
I should be back within an hour.
If she's not here when I get back,
we'll call all her friends,
everyone we know,
until we find out where she's gone, OK?
OK.
I'm sorry.
I'll call you from the road.
- Hello.
- Vincent.
Jack Bauer. Are you planning
on seeing Kimberly tonight?
- No, man, we broke up. You know that.
- I just want to make sure you know that.
- Snuck out on ya, huh?
- Don't screw with me, Vincent.
Chill, man. Look, I don't know
where she's at. You got my word.
That's a real comfort, Vincent.
Knowing that I've got your word.
Why are we meeting
at a furniture store?
- Dan works there.
- When are we supposed to be there?
- Midnight. We're late.
- Yeah, they'll wait.
You sure about that?
Well, you told them I'm hot, right?
And you're hot, so they'll wait.
Dan's a sophomore at San Diego State.
Yeah, you told me that.
And so is Rick. I mean, they're not just,
you know, a bunch of high-school idiots.
- And your point is?
- They're men, not boys.
- Good. I'm glad to hear it.
- Really?
Yeah.
- CTU, this is Myers.
- It's Jack. What exactly did Walsh say?
- Just bring everyone in. No details.
- Why does this have to be tonight?
- Problems at home?
- I'm almost there. I'll see you in a few.
- How long is this gonna take?
- Why? Are we interrupting your social life?
- At least I have one.
- Funny.
- Have you called Langley?
- Sure did. Called the bureau too.
- Nobody knows anything. Jack on his way?
- Yeah, unfortunately for us, the mood he's in.
- Hello.
- Hey. Did you hear from Kim yet?
No.
I was thinking we should try to remember
what it was like when we were kids.
- It's a different world now, Jack.
- Yeah, I know.
- Evening, Jack.
- Hey, Paul.
I was talking to Denise the other day and
she and Steve took Nicki to a therapist.
They said it helped.
We should think about that.
Yeah, well, maybe.
Can we talk about it when I get home?
Honey, I'm already here. Let me
give you a call back in a little while.
- Who's here?
- Everyone.
We're waiting for Walsh.
I activated a satellite uplink in case.
OK, good. Tony? I need detailed background
on everyone on David Palmer's staff now.
Why?
Cos I think this is about him
and I want us to be prepared.
Bad time to play a hunch.
If it leaks out that we're screening Palmer,
- people might think it's cos he's black.
- It is because he's black.
- It makes him the most likely target.
- It might not be interpreted that way.
I don't care. I just gave you an order
and I'd like you to follow it, please.
Good. Thank you. Let me know as soon as
Walsh gets here. I gotta make a phone call.
- Hey.
- Hey, how are you?
Come on. Let's go in.
Hi.
- You must be Rick.
- I must be.
- Janet said you guys like to party.
- As a matter of fact, yeah.
As a matter of fact, me too.
Glad to hear it.
Let's get this party started.
Yeah.
Follow me.
- Come on!
- No. I'm not going up there.
- Smoke?
- Yeah.
Polls open in less than seven
hours here in California...
Detective Cox-Lovell, please.
Yeah.
Senator Palmer arrived this morning...
Frank. Yeah, it's Jack Bauer over at CTU.
This is kind of embarrassing,
but my daughter Kimberly snuck out
and she's not come back yet.
I wondered if we sent her vitals over,
if you could keep an eye out.
- Is she OK?
- Yeah, I'm sure she's OK.
No, that'd be great.
Frank, thanks a lot. I owe you. Bye.
Richard. Everybody's inside. Come on.
- Mr. Walsh.
- Hello, Nina.
- Shall we get started?
- Please.
We believe that by the end of the day an
attempt will be made on David Palmer's life.
- How good's his security?
- Very good.
Maybe not be good enough
to handle what's coming today.
- A shooter, well-funded, from overseas.
- What foreign power wants Palmer dead?
Probably none. Most likely a domestic hate
group hired someone from out of the country.
It's harder to trace. Check the background
of everyone around Palmer.
- Cross it with terrorist databases. Start now.
- OK, we're on it. Let's go.
Jack.
I'll be right with you.
How you doing?
- I can't complain.
- Can't or won't?
Things better at home?
Yeah. Yeah, we're trying.
What I'm about to tell you
doesn't leave this room.
Fine.
There may be an element inside the agency
involved with the hit on Palmer.
- What?
- The next 24 hours, I want you all over this.
You'll interface with every division.
I am the last person that you want
to bring something like this to.
- I don't agree.
- Richard...
I built a case against three of our own
agents and busted them for taking bribes.
If there's a conspiracy in the agency,
I'll never get anywhere near it.
Well, you'll have to, Jack.
Because you're the only guy that I can trust.
If Palmer gets hit, the first African-American
with a real shot at the White House,
it'll tear this country apart.
- I'll look into it. I'll do the best I can.
- Good. Good.
George Mason is coming to give you
a more detailed briefing on Palmer.
You think I should trust George Mason?
Until we get a better handle on things,
don't trust anybody.
Not even your own people.
We gotta find the shooter, Jack.
Whatever it takes.
Excuse me? How much longer
till we land in Los Angeles?
Well, let's see. It's 12.20. Just over an hour.
Thank you.
Brooks here.
Hey, Martin, how you doing?
It's the photographer.
I'm very well, Patty. I'm landing in one hour.
Are we still on for breakfast?
Meet Secret Service in the lobby at seven.
They'll take care of you.
- Will Senator Palmer be at the breakfast?
- You bet.
Good. I'll see you then.
Drive safe.
Um, excuse me. So, you know David Palmer?
Not yet. I am, uh, meeting him tomorrow.
We have been sitting here
this whole time making small talk
and you never even mentioned it.
I am going to be taking a few pictures of him.
Are you...? You're a photographer.
Have I...
Have I ever seen one of your photographs?
What's next?
George Mason's gonna be here in a couple
of minutes and then he's gonna brief me.
You, not us?
- You can't shut me out, Jack. Not here.
- It's Walsh.
- He wants me to meet Mason alone.
- Why?
He didn't say.
You're lying.
Yes, I am. But you're still
gonna have to trust me.
One of these days
you're gonna ask for too much.
I'm terribly afraid that
today's gonna be that day. Yep.
- Hi, it's me.
- Did you hear anything?
- No.
- What's wrong?
- I found three joints in her desk.
- Terrific.
I know it's not the end of the world,
but I don't like it.
I don't either. Maybe you can get into her
email, check her messages or something.
We gave her her own password
to show that we trusted her, remember?
Yeah.
Honey, I'm so sorry that I can't
be there with you right now.
Look, I can't really talk right now.
Let me call you back, OK?
- OK.
- OK, bye.
- Everything OK?
- Yep.
So when I got into San Diego State,
I figured, what the hell, give college a try.
- Do you live near the beach?
- Yeah.
- Do you surf?
- No. Surfing's way too motivated.
You gotta get wet, there's sharks,
you gotta call everybody "dude".
- Why?
- Oh, no reason.
My dad surfs. Surfed.
He doesn't any more? He's too old?
My father's dead.
Hey. My bad.
It's OK. He was this... really great guy,
and then, uh, six months ago...
I'm sorry.
I'm over it.
Getting over it. It's hard, but I am.
Mason's on his way up.
- George.
- Jack. How's it going?
- Good to see you. Come on in.
- How much did Walsh tell you down there?
Not much. That Palmer's the target,
the shooter's the real deal. That's about it.
- I can narrow it down for you if you like.
- Please do.
We think the shooter's European,
probably German,
and that he's either here already
or he's coming today.
This'll get you into secured data nationwide.
See if it clicks with anything you have.
- Who's the source on this?
- That I can't give you.
- Because?
- Because I'm not authorised to.
How can I crosscheck the data if I don't know
where the original information's come from?
What do you know about Palmer's politics?
You know he's no friend of the agency, right?
If he gets elected, this place gets gutted.
- What are you trying to say?
- I'm not saying anything.
I'm saying do your job
and stay out of what doesn't concern you.
Fair enough.
Good. Then we're done.
George, I need a favour. I need you to call
your boss and ask him to give me clearance
- on the identification of the source.
- We agreed it didn't matter.
I've still gotta call Walsh
and tell him I did everything I could.
I would like to cover my own ass.
Jack, you're finally learning
how to play the game.
Sure, I'll call Chapelle for you.
Use your phone?
Please do. You want a cup of coffee?
No, I'm good. Thanks.
I wanna hear Mason's call.
At the sound of the tone,
the time will be 12.29 and 30 seconds.
At the sound of the tone, the time will be...
Yeah, yeah. I'm talking to my boss, Jack.
Right, you stupid chump.
- What are you doing?
- He's screwing with us. Get me that binder.
- What?
- The binder. Get it.
At the sound of the tone...
Do we need to talk about this?
Nina...
Well, you can consider your ass
officially covered. Chapelle said no.
- You are out of your mind.
- Mason's holding something back.
- I need some bargaining power.
- How are you gonna get it?
Remember Phillipe Darcet?
Heroin dealer, Barcelona?
Yeah. Mason was a point man
on his bust last August.
When they rolled up Darcet's assets,
$200,000 was missing.
I always thought it fell into
Mason's pockets. Now I need proof.
You're gonna blackmail a district director?
I want you to check Darcet's accounts.
You can access them through
the secured files. Use this.
Nina, he's gonna wake up
in half an hour or less.
Palmer blending intelligence,
political courage, hard work and luck.
Dammit! Hello.
I'm sorry to bother you at this hour.
My name is Alan York.
I found this number
in my daughter's calendar.
- Who's your daughter?
- Janet. Janet York. Do you have a son or...?
Daughter. Kimberly. She snuck out
of the house. Is Janet gone too?
Yes. I bet they're together.
Any idea where they might be?
None. Did Janet say anything?
She was gone when I came home from work.
Can I give you my number in case you hear?
Oh, yeah, of course.
- I've got Darcet's account number.
- Good.
It's encrypted. I can't get around it.
- Ask Tony to do it.
- He'll need a reason.
If he thinks he's doing it for me,
not if he's doing it for you.
I'm surprised you noticed.
I noticed.
Well, you shouldn't have.
- Tony, I need you to do something for me.
- For you or for Jack?
I need you to get into this account.
What does Phillipe Darcet's
bank account have to do with Palmer?
We don't know yet.
We're trying to pick up a thread.
That's interesting, cos I've been
trying to pick up a thread of my own.
About what?
Whether you're still sleeping with Jack.
Who says I ever did?
What do you see in him? He turned in
his own people, for Christ's sake.
- They were dirty.
- Oh, and he's Mr. Clean, huh?
Yes, he is. Look, we don't have
a lot of time. Will you help me out here?
Please.
I'll see what I can find.
Jamey. If I give you a phone number,
could you get all the Internet
passwords connected to it?
- Sure, if you have a warrant.
- And if I didn't have a warrant?
- It's important?
- It's pretty important.
Go.
- Hello?
- Hey, it's me. I got her password.
What is it?
- "Lifesucks". One word.
- Perfect.
So, um, are you gonna be
around this weekend?
I could be.
Be.
- Where are they?
- I don't know.
- Did you ever meet Princess Di?
- Yeah.
But I never took her picture.
What was she like?
She was cool.
Can I, uh...
Can I see one of your photographs?
- My photographs?
- Yeah.
Yeah.
How about this one right here?
It's very beautiful.
Hmm.
- Munich?
- Yep.
Finish the speech?
Taking a break. The guys
got tired of me yelling at them.
Big ol' grumpy bear.
- How you doing?
- Fine. Just a few dozen more to go.
- You don't have to do these yourself.
- Personal little touch never hurts.
- Sure doesn't.
- Ooh, yes. Yes, yes, yes. Mm.
Sir?
Phone call, Senator.
It's Maureen Kingsley from the network.
- Come on, Patty, it's after midnight.
- She says it's urgent.
Maureen, this better be good.
- Can I get you some coffee or anything?
- Thank you, Patty.
My response? Here's my response.
You air that allegation
or anything remotely like it...
This conversation is over, Maureen.
That'll be all, Patty.
Sweetheart, what was it?
Just more media nonsense. Not important.
It didn't sound not important.
Since when don't we talk about things?
This is Richard Walsh.
At the tone leave a message.
Richard, it's Jack.
Call me back. It's important.
I thought you wanted
to get your life together.
Make things right with your family.
You think this is helping?
- He's got information that I need.
- What information?
Never mind. You can't tell me, fine.
But, Jack, if Tony doesn't find anything,
you could end up in jail.
- Probably.
- Then what are you doing?
Jack,
answer me.
Nina, you can look the other way once
and it's no big deal,
except it makes it easier
to compromise next time
and soon all you're doing is compromising
because that's how you think things are done.
You know those guys I blew the whistle on?
You think they were bad guys?
Cos they weren't. They weren't bad guys.
They were just like you and me,
except they compromised once.
I'll see how Tony's coming along.
Thank you.
- Hello?
- Hi, it's Teri Bauer.
- Hi. Have you heard anything?
- Yeah. I broke into Kim's email.
Janet sent her one.
They're meeting two guys in the valley.
- Did you get an address?
- Yep. I'm going right now.
Would you mind if I came along?
I'm getting stir crazy just sitting around here.
- All right.
- I'm leaving now. Tell me where you live.
- Where are we going now?
- Wasn't there a party at Lacy's?
- Anybody got a phone? I'll call.
- Yeah, I do.
- Um, I gotta go home.
- Why?
- My mother left five messages.
- Run home to Mommy.
Hey, her father just died, OK?
Maybe her mother needs her.
Your father?
- Shut up.
- Whatever.
- I don't wanna go home.
- But...
We'll drop you off, OK?
Uh, yeah.
- So, what's your name?
- Martin.
I'm Mandy.
Hey, maybe we can get together
when we're in LA or something.
I'm gonna be pretty busy.
See ya.
- Yeah.
- I got into the Darcet account.
- Nina said you wanted it.
- Thank you. Send it to my screen.
All right.
Wake up.
Sit down.
Who's the source?
Who tipped us on the Palmer hit?
Last August, when you led
the takedown of Phillipe Darcet,
all his assets were transferred to
a custodial account in Langley, Virginia.
$200,000 fell out along the way.
I traced that money
to an offshore account in Aruba.
I got a funny feeling about that account,
George. I think it's yours.
Yeah. Well, that's a lie.
Good.
Then you won't mind
if I send Chapelle the information.
The source, George.
You have no idea
what you're getting yourself into.
Why don't you explain it to me?
You've got five seconds.
Wait.
There's your source.
- Thanks for your help, George.
- You'll live to regret this, Bauer.
I promise you that.
- Um, excuse me.
- Ma'am, we're about to land. If you could...
Sh!
- Sir, would you remain in your seat?
- I lost my wallet.
- Hello?
- Hey. It's me.
- Turn left at the light.
- What?
I'm in a car with Alan York. He's the father
of one of Kimberly's friends, Janet.
- What are you talking about?
- Kim got an email from Janet.
- We think they might be out together.
- Where?
Don't know yet. They're meeting
some guys in the valley.
Wait a second. You're going to
the valley with this guy Alan York?
What are you gonna do if she's not there?
We haven't thought
that far ahead yet. I'll call...
Hello?
Teri?
- Hey.
Could you do me a favour?
Could you cover for me?
Sure.
OK, forward all my calls to my cellphone.
I'll be back as soon as I can.
- Jack.
- What?
A 747 just blew up over the Mojave desert.
Preliminary reports make
it sound like it was a bomb.
Passenger list.
Get me Walsh on the phone now.
Janet?
Oh, turn here. I live on Tenth.
- Dan, I just told you that I...
- Why don't you just relax?
- Can you please tell him he missed the turn?
- You heard him. Relax.
Night's just getting started.