The coordinates for the targets. Upload them
into the missiles. Begin the countdown.
How long to cancel the launch?
- I won't know until I see their software.
We'll keep Bierko and his men out
so you can finish this.
Ten seconds to launch.
It's done. Launch sequence is cancelled.
You were never really
gonna let me go, were you?
No.
You were responsible for the deaths of David
Palmer, Tony Almeida and Michelle Dessler.
- I'm going after Logan.
- What do you mean?
I'll fill you in later.
Now I need you to walk me through
modifying some equipment.
- Who is this guy?
- Morris O'Brian. Chloe's ex-husband.
I need some modifications.
Can you do that without talking?
I could, but it would be
a terrible waste of my charm.
Jack Bauer's on his way here now.
He's going to confront your husband directly.
Charles is leaving
for the airfield immediately.
You have to find a way to stall him.
- There's a helicopter waiting for me.
- Let it wait.
- I can't.
- Yes, you can.
You're the president.
Aaron said the recording
implicating the president was destroyed.
- Yes.
- Without it, you can't mount a case.
Someone inside CTU
is setting up a digital uplink.
If I can get Logan to acknowledge
everything he's done, that's all we need.
- I need to get on that chopper.
I don't see how that's possible.
If Logan doesn't confess,
how far are you actually willing to go?
As far as I have to.
Ah.
Here. Let me get this for you.
Watch your hair.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I got a flight suit.
Go ahead.
- Are you in the Secret Service outbuilding?
- Yeah.
Morris and I have a way
to pull the copilot from the flight.
- What about reassignment protocol?
- Working on it.
Mike Novick has to verify the pilot codes.
It'll take one minute.
Hold on a second. I'm switching to comm.
OK.
- Do you copy?
- Yeah.
I'll get back to you when I'm on the chopper.
Mike Novick's gonna call.
- Morris?
- Yes, sweetheart?
I need you to do one more thing.
Some guy from Central called.
Says your packet's messed up.
- I got that straightened out.
- He wants to talk to you.
- Now?
- Right now.
I patched it through
to the Secret Service outbuilding.
Mike?
I've delayed him as long as I can. Have you
heard anything from Jack Bauer yet?
He's in the Secret Service outbuilding.
I'm sending him the documents now.
There's not much time.
Yeah, Mike?
Reassignment protocol and authorisation
are coming through to you. You'll need both.
- How are we doing for time?
- Hurry.
Hello?
John.
Aaron. I thought you transferred out.
Not quite yet.
Some guy from Central called,
said my packet's...
You'll need this. Don't worry about him.
Carouth has been relieved. Guess there
was something wrong with his packet.
Ron Franklin. There's my protocol.
This is not bad,
but needs to be more positive. Like, uh...
Jack Bauer's on the helicopter. You have
to find an excuse not to get on board.
Charles, excuse me.
Could I talk to you for a second?
Absolutely.
Will you excuse us for a second?
I know it sounds silly, but I didn't bring
my medication. I just wanna have it with me.
- We'll send somebody back for it.
- I don't wanna delay you. I'll be along later.
Besides, Charles, I think that when you land
it would be better if I wasn't with you.
- Why?
- This is your moment, Charles.
I think that when you step out of that
helicopter, alone, after saving the country,
that is an image
that history will never forget.
All right.
Thank you, Marty.
But don't be far behind me, now.
Captain.
I can fly this if I have to,
which leaves you two choices.
You do as I say and you live, or you don't
and you die for nothing. You understand me?
Wait until I give you my command,
then follow these instructions slowly.
Disconnect your helmet
from the comm system,
then I want you to rip out the mic cable,
take your helmet off and stow it.
Do it now.
I'll know if you deviate from your flight plan.
Mr. President, I have a message for you
from the White House.
What the hell are you doing?
Put these on.
You.
- It's Jack. Do you copy?
- I'm here. Where are you?
We just left the ranch. I have Logan with me.
Is Morris standing by with the equipment?
He's on his way.
Make sure the pilot takes heading 286
for two miles, then breaks south.
Captain, I want you to follow heading 286
for two miles then break south.
There should be an industrial park.
There's an abandoned printing facility
you can use. I'll get back to you.
Copy that.
What are you trying to do, Jack?
Whatever it is,
you know you won't get away with it.
Are you going to kill me?
I suppose you want some sort of revenge.
I understand that.
Bad things happened.
I didn't want them to happen.
People who work for me, they went too far.
They did things that they thought
I wanted them to do, but they were wrong.
You have to understand, I have always
acted in the country's best interest.
But you're just trying to get even.
Do you realise what effect this will have
on the American people?
This day has been trying enough.
And now the president is being attacked.
If you wanna do what's right,
you will turn this thing around and go back.
Dammit, Bauer, say something.
Hello?
- Morris?
- Yes, love?
The helicopter's landing in an industrial
park one mile east of you. Head over there.
OK. Now, I give this guy
what we worked on, and then I'm out, right?
Yes. Make sure you have him call me
when you do the hand-off.
- All right.
- Thanks.
Shut it down.
Undo your safety belt.
Move towards the door. Slowly.
Get out now. Move!
Jack, we can work something out.
There's still time. What do you want?
I could help you get away
with enough money to start a new life.
Maybe find that daughter of yours and...
and try to work something out.
Whatever you want, it's yours.
You have my word.
Your word.
Jack, I'm the President of the United States.
I'm not carrying any weapons.
Don't you make a sound.
Hey.
- Give me the case.
- Jack Bauer. I should have known that.
- Modified equipment?
- Yep.
- That's President Logan, Jack.
- Get out of here.
Yeah. Chloe wants you to call her.
Go.
- Yeah, Jack?
- I have it.
I just checked the response deployment. You
have less than ten minutes till they're on you.
- Fine.
- Listen, Jack.
I don't mean to put pressure on you,
but if you don't get a confession
we'll be arrested for treason.
Yeah, I know.
Is this some kind of broadcast?
What is this?
I would like to know,
is this an assassination?
A confession.
Don't count on it.
I know you're good at extracting information.
I saw what you did with Walt Cummings.
I think you'll be surprised to find out
that I'm a little tougher than that.
Take a seat.
Chloe, it's Jack. Can you hear me?
I wanna make sure you have good reception.
Who are you talking to?
Are those your friends at CTU?
You know you're
putting them in danger as well?
- Coming through fine, Jack.
- OK, good.
My people can't be far behind, Jack.
There's still time to get away. Take it.
The plan involving nerve gas was designed
to fool the terrorists and the Russians.
Whether you planned it is irrelevant.
You authorised it.
- You're delusional.
- David Palmer uncovered evidence.
He asked questions, and he was assassinated.
Other people were killed to cover that up.
People who served this country.
People I worked with. Friends.
No. You're wrong. This is all a pack of lies.
The terrorists discovered your deception, and
deployed Sentox nerve gas on American soil.
Every American who died today
as a result of terrorist activity
is another murder that you're accountable for.
Before you leave here,
you're going to admit it.
I suppose if you hurt me enough, Jack,
I'll say whatever you want.
But that won't make it the truth.
And everybody who watches this
will know that perfectly well.
- Who are your co-conspirators?
- There are no co-conspirators...
Walt Cummings, Christopher Henderson,
James Nathanson
have all admitted to being part
of this conspiracy. Now they are dead.
Before Henderson died, he acknowledged
that there were others. What are their names?
A man will say anything under torture.
This won't mean a thing.
Mr. Logan, I'm not gonna torture you.
But you are going to tell me
what I want to know.
Or, so help me, God, I will kill you.
A year and a half ago,
I was warned that my life was in danger
by someone within the government.
I was told the only way I could stay alive
was to create the illusion that I was dead.
I was forced to deceive people that I loved.
My only daughter will never forgive me.
And as I see the depth
of your corruption unfold,
I have no doubt
that you are that source of danger.
David Palmer was a great man,
and he was a great president.
But he was also my friend.
He tried to warn me about you
and now he is dead.
Other people tried to help me
and they are dead too.
So, Mr. Logan, I hope you understand...
I have absolutely nothing to lose.
You are going to be held accountable for
your part of everything that happened today.
You can't hide behind the presidency. Right
here, right now, you are gonna face justice.
And make no mistake about this,
this is personal.
And if you think for a second
that I'm scared to put a bullet in your brain,
you don't know me.
I'm gonna ask you one last time.
Who are your co-conspirators?
You have until the count of three...
or I will kill you. One.
I'll go down in history
with Lincoln and Kennedy,
but you'll go down with John Wilkes Booth
and Lee Harvey Oswald.
Two.
You're a man of honour.
How can you assassinate a president of
the United States in front of the entire world?
If you love your country, you won't fire.
Three.
You can't do it.
No, Jack, it's all right. Jack...
It's all right. It's all right.
It's right that you can't.
I'm the president.
Jack...
Jack, they're here.
Lie flat on your stomach! Put your
hands out in front of you. Extend your arms.
- Mr. President, are you all right?
- I'm fine.
I actually feel sorry for that man.
He's delusional.
It would be better if he were put in some sort
of solitary confinement for the time being.
Yeah?
Jack Bauer wasn't able to get the president
to confess, Mrs. Logan. I'm sorry.
Why not? What happened?
I'm not sure of the details. Bauer's in custody.
Gentlemen.
Thank you.
Couple more, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Thank you very much,
ladies and gentlemen. That will be all.
- Oh, God. David.
- Martha. Martha, please...
- Marty, no. Don't do this to me now.
- You killed him. You killed him.
- Marty, stop.
- You're a murderer! You're a criminal!
- My wife is not well.
- Don't you... Let go of me.
- Please escort her into the hangar.
- Don't you touch me! Don't you touch me!
You don't know what he is.
He's not fit to be president.
It is a sacrilege for him
to be even speaking David's name!
Don't you... No!
Let go of me!
I wanna make sure that she's all right.
- Has this hangar been cleared?
- Yes, sir. All secure.
Good. Let them know
that I'll be back in a moment.
Yes, Mr. President.
Are you wearing a listening device?
What are you talking about?
I have to watch you, Marty.
You said that I was a good liar,
but I am nothing compared to you.
Charles, stop it. Stop it!
Stop...
OK, now, Marty. Tell me the truth.
You're hurting me.
You don't know what pain is.
I'm onto you.
I should have seen it from the first,
but I wanted to believe
that you still cared for me.
Making love to me was just a ploy, wasn't it?
Took a lot of planning to get Bauer
on that helicopter. You were part of the plan.
It was your job to delay me, wasn't it?
Wasn't it?
- Please...
- Wasn't it?
They used you so Jack Bauer could get
to me. Come on, Marty. Come on, Marty.
- Admit it. You were part of it.
- Yes. Yes.
Why?
Why... why did you help them?
Because you killed David Palmer.
I told you, I didn't realise
that was going to happen.
You... Your people killed him to protect you.
You covered it up, that's just as bad.
I covered it up because I had to.
- And others died to cover that up!
- For the good of the country.
You sold nerve gas to terrorists.
You're insane. You're insane!
I did it for the good of the country
as I saw it at the time.
You're such a hypocrite.
After your performance today,
you're in no position to call me a hypocrite.
And I will tell you something else.
If you blow up like this one more time,
I will fill you so full of drugs
you won't even remember your own name.
And then I will ship you off to an asylum
and you can stay there the rest of your life.
Are we clear?
Now clean yourself up. You're a mess.
Ladies and gentlemen,
the President of the United States.
Martha.
My fellow Americans,
this has been a terrible day
in the history of this country,
and yet at the same time a triumphant day.
Because in the end we won a significant
victory over the forces of chaos and terror.
We have preserved and protected our
way of life despite the loss of innocent lives...
I'll transmit in one minute.
Is the attorney general there?
I'm here, Ms O'Brian. I certainly hope this
recording is as important as you claim it is.
- Chloe, what's this about?
- I set up a call with the attorney general.
- Are you serious?
- I'm very serious.
- This is Karen Hayes, Homeland Security.
- Bill Buchanan, CTU.
Sir, I apologise. Ms O'Brian
placed this call without authorisation.
We had to do things under the radar
to protect you all in case things went wrong.
- In case what things went wrong?
- It would help if I just played the recording.
What recording?
A conversation that took place five minutes
ago between the president and his wife.
How could you possibly have
a recording of something like that?
An agent named Jack Bauer
placed a listening device on the president.
- Bauer? Isn't he the one under arrest?
- I'm going to play the recording now.
I don't wanna listen to it. Ms O'Brian,
at the least this is a violation of privacy,
and we're talking about the president!
Because you killed David Palmer.
I told you, I didn't realise
that was going to happen.
You... Your people killed him to protect
you. You covered it up, that's just as bad.
I covered it up because I had to.
- And others died to cover that up!
- For the good of the country.
You sold nerve gas to terrorists.
You're insane. You're insane!
A poet once said, "No man is an island. "
On a day like this,
we can feel the truth of those words.
Any untimely death is a tragedy,
yet some men embody
such greatness of character
that their death serves as a unifying force
for those who remain behind.
David Palmer was such a man.
A great president. A great American.
And, on a more personal note,
a wonderful friend.
He'll be missed...
Olson.
Yes, sir.
With all due respect, Mr. Attorney General,
are you sure this isn't some kinda mistake?
Yes, sir.
I understand, sir.
I'll do exactly as you say.
...strength and moral courage, this country
might have not survived in its present form.
It is very appropriate that David Palmer
will be laid to rest at Arlington cemetery,
for he was a soldier in the truest sense.
He was a man whose courage rose in direct
proportion to the threats his country faced.
In closing, I would ask that the country
observe a national day of mourning
for one of the greatest Americans
this nation will ever see.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Federal marshal. Come with us.
What the hell are you doing?
You came close to disrupting my speech.
On behalf of President Logan,
I wish to thank you all for joining us.
And, uh, I am sorry,
but out of respect for today's ceremony...
Those are ridiculous accusations.
Excuse me. If I may, sir.
You've probably never seen one of these,
Mr. President.
It's a microtransmitter.
Agent Clark, arrest these men
and get them the hell out of here.
- Sorry, Mr. President. We have our orders.
- You take... You take your orders from me.
Not any more.
After you, sir.
Watch your head, sir.
Give me a second.
- Hey.
- Thank God you're safe.
- Everything's gonna be all right.
I heard you kidnapped the president.
I was just trying to get him
to give me a direct confession.
Jack...
How much longer do you need to stay here?
Not much longer.
They can debrief me tomorrow.
Are you sure?
I can't believe you're really...
you're really here.
Agent Bauer? Excuse me, but
there's a call for you from your daughter.
- From my daughter?
- Yes, sir.
Kim Bauer. It's been put through
to a landline just inside that door.
Thank you.
I'll be right back, I promise.
Take as long as you need.
I'm not going anywhere.
I love you. I'll be right back.
Hey, Kim.
- Any word on Logan?
- No.
My guess is he'll try to cut a deal. Resign
without a fight in exchange for clemency.
He doesn't deserve clemency.
The country doesn't deserve
a long impeachment process either.
In any event, we can expect Hal Gardner
to be sworn in as president soon.
So this'll probably be
the last time I see this place.
I don't think so.
Not if I have anything to do with it, and I will.
You'll be back here running CTU.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
When I came in here last night,
to save the day,
I was a little bit condescending and tactless,
to say the least.
I had no idea what you were up against.
I'm sorry.
No, no need to apologise.
Mistakes were made.
You were right to come in with a firm hand.
Well, I'd better go.
Karen...
I was thinking of, uh,
getting some breakfast before going home.
I have to go over to Division
for one last briefing. Bureaucracy...
Rain check?
Sure.
Chloe.
Really good work today.
You too.
I found this in Edgar's possessions.
I thought you should have it.
Thanks.
Hey.
What's all this, then?
A friend of mine who died today.
You, um...
Do you wanna talk about it?
Yeah. Come on.
Jack?
Oh, my God.
Agent Davies, Jack Bauer's missing.
Attention, all units. We have a missing
agent - Jack Bauer. I repeat, Jack Bauer.
You two men, search the lower levels.
Give me three men on a perimeter search.
You surely must be aware, Mr. Bauer,
that China has a long memory.
Only 18 months ago you invaded our territory
and killed our consul.
Did you really think
that we would forget? Hm?
I know how this works.
I need to make one phone call.
Please.
Just one phone call.
Kill me.
Just... kill me.
Kill you?
You're far too valuable to kill, Mr. Bauer.