Jack, look out!
Paul?
Get me a medic.
He's losing pressure.
I need ten cc's of adrenaline.
He was hit before I could do anything.
How bad is it?
We don't know. We just don't know.
Please tell me he's not gonna die.
Why should I help you?
I'm offering you freedom. You and Behrooz
will go into a witness protection programme.
You'll be given new names,
identities, everything.
What do you need me to do?
I need you to go to Fayed, and tell him
that you need to speak to Marwan.
He won't let me through his front door,
let alone get near Marwan.
He will when you tell him
that you've got a hostage that can help him.
Who?
Me.
- What if Fayed doesn't believe us?
- Then we're both dead.
Close the door.
Put your gun over there. Do it.
What is it?
A woman named
Dina Araz came to me.
- What does she want?
- She has a hostage.
A CTU agent named Jack Bauer.
You've caused me a lot of trouble.
Kill him.
Just what I thought.
Let's go. Come on, let's go.
Meet them at the hotel.
I'll need his flight package,
including clearance and identification codes.
You'll have whatever you need.
Get your things.
We've got a plane to catch.
Let me talk to my family.
Your family is dead. And so are you.
Edgar, have you found any way
to locate Jack?
We're trying. Marwan covered his tracks.
Michelle.
What do we have, Chloe?
- The PD found the van Jack and Dina were in.
- Where?
Abandoned at an industrial warehouse
at the far end of San Fernando Road.
Dina's body was in it.
OK. Tell local police to look for witnesses.
We need a licence plate,
something to follow. Edgar.
- Pull up satellite from 8:45 to 9:00.
- I'm on it.
All right, everyone, listen up.
Jack Bauer is missing.
There's a good chance he's being held
by our primary target, Marwan.
We believe Marwan is preparing
for another domestic attack today.
We need to pool all our resources to find him.
All comm teams, coordinate with Edgar.
Thank you.
- Yes.
- There's a problem.
What?
Got onto the base and through security
using the pilot's ID.
As I was about to do a pre-flight check,
they grounded the plane.
Why?
Checking a trouble sensor.
They might have to swap out a defective part.
- How long will it take?
- I don't know yet.
Resolve this now.
It's time to earn your money, Mr Anderson.
The window of opportunity
on the target closes in an hour.
I understand.
- Excuse me.
- Yes, sir.
- You working on the Phoenix?
- Yes, Captain. Sent me down from Hawkins.
- You taking her up?
- What's the ETA on getting me into the air?
The sensor's correct.
There was a hairline fracture on a strut pin.
But, uh, a replacement
won't be until morning.
Is that the only problem? A strut pin?
Yes, but it would be one hell of a problem
when you try to land.
Rear assembly would disintegrate on impact.
Only way out would be to parachute out.
- Did you report to the chief officer?
- I'm about to head over there now, Captain.
Then I'm gonna head up to Ventura
for a little R and R.
- Sounds great. Don't let me hold you up.
- All right, thanks, sir.
Thanks.
ME says Dina's been dead
less than 30 minutes.
We can only assume that
that's when Marwan grabbed Jack.
- What's the search range on Marwan?
- 1500 square miles and increasing.
Chatter?
I filtered through everything
from Langley, NSA and Interpol.
- None of it's correlating.
- Volume?
It's actually slowing down, which may mean
we've incurred all the damage we will today.
- Or it could be the calm before the storm.
- Yeah.
The one thing we know for sure is if Jack's
alive, he'll find a way to contact us.
We just have to wait
until we pick up the thread on Marwan.
- Tony.
- Yep?
So I heard Jack called you earlier today.
Yeah.
And that you saved his life.
Well, we both know I owed him one, right?
Audrey's been waiting
for her husband to get out of surgery.
I think we should tell her about Jack.
Why?
- They're involved.
- She's married.
Separated.
- Then I'd prefer not to tell her anything.
- Why?
We may have to make
a very tough call on Jack's capture.
She's a professional. She knows it's
a possibility. It'd be wrong to keep it from her.
- I don't want her interfering.
- I think she has a right to know.
But, hey, you're the boss. It's your call.
Excuse me.
- How's Paul doing?
He's still in surgery.
I won't know until he gets out.
Have you heard anything from Jack?
Jack is missing.
Missing?
We think he was taken by Habib Marwan.
Oh, my God.
- What are we doing to get him back?
- Everything we can.
I thought we were tracking him.
He's supposed to be protected.
- No one is fully protected in the field.
- Who was in charge of this operation?
I was.
Get him back, Michelle.
I have a few questions.
If you answer them, there's a chance
you might survive today.
Don't waste your time.
You located me through a man named Fayed
who, you might be interested to know,
has since martyred himself.
It would help me if I knew
he was the only link you had to me.
Whatever you've planned next is going to fail,
just like everything else you've tried today.
Fail?
Almost 40 dead in the train crash, many more
near the San Gabriel Island nuclear plant.
That wasn't really your plan.
We managed to stop the other 103
power plants from melting down.
That's what America will remember,
that we stopped you.
No, they'll remember the image
of Secretary of Defense Heller
held hostage on your own soil,
and it will burn in their psyches.
This country will be afraid
to let their leaders appear in public.
For all the hatred that you have for this
country, you don't understand it very well.
Whatever you throw at us, I promise you,
that'll never happen.
- Marwan, we have a problem.
- What is it?
- The family of the pilot that we killed.
- What? We disposed of the bodies.
Yes. A relative showed up at the house and
became suspicious when no one was home.
- He called the police who are looking into it.
- Has it gotten to CTU?
No, but he was a military pilot.
It will be flagged by other agencies
and will get to CTU within the hour.
What do you think we should do?
We have to make sure CTU is too busy
to realise its significance.
- Distract them.
- How?
Tell me about the boy.
- What boy?
- Behrooz Araz.
- What do you care about him for?
- Does CTU have him in custody?
Yes, he's safe.
You answered the question,
but are you telling me the truth?
Call CTU, ask them yourself.
- Edgar Stiles.
- What's the password for the central server?
- I'll get you on.
- Don't get me on, just give me the password.
- It's not your area any more.
- What? You work for me.
No, I worked for you.
Worked, with an "ed" at the end. Past tense.
I've been reinstated. Quit being
territorial and give me the password.
No.
Curtis, could you please explain to Edgar
that I've been rehired as head of comm?
Things have changed, Chloe. Edgar took over
for you. You'll be working for him now.
You're kidding. Michelle called me in because
things were falling apart here under Edgar.
Now, give me my command or I walk.
You have equal authority.
On paper it has to look like you work for him.
- I won't do it as a matter of principle.
- You'll be bumped up to a term-four analyst.
That's a 35 per cent increase in salary,
plus bonus.
I should get that anyway.
That's not my point. Edgar works for me.
Not today, Chloe.
Fine.
What's the password to the central server?
C- I-S-1-5-A
Thanks.
A man who says he's Habib Marwan is on line
one. He wants to speak to the director of CTU.
Put it through a high-risk filter,
activate all tracers and recorders. Michelle.
Someone claiming
to be Habib Marwan is on line.
- Are you prepped for the call?
- Yeah, take it there.
Put him through.
This is Dessler, Director of CTU.
To whom am I speaking?
This is Habib Marwan.
- Jack Bauer is alive and in my custody.
- I'll need to speak to him.
I will return him to you unharmed
in exchange for Behrooz Araz.
You have ten minutes
to secure clearances with your people.
- I'd need more time to agree to that.
- Ten minutes.
I will call you then with exact details
on how the exchange is to proceed.
Did you get a trace?
OK, confirm Marwan's identity off voice.
And we may need to move Behrooz Araz.
Why is Behrooz Araz
worth trading for Jack?
I don't know. Have all tactical teams
meet me in the situation room.
Have the police sent the report
about the pilot's missing family to CTU yet?
I don't think so, but our contact at LAPD
says the report has been flagged.
It will go out to all the agencies
within 15 minutes.
If CTU gets a hold of it a minute too soon,
they can stop us.
- Tell me the second that report gets released.
- Yes, Marwan.
Marwan wants to exchange Jack Bauer
for Behrooz Araz.
- The obvious question is why?
- The way I see it, there are two possibilities.
One, there's a personal connection.
Two, Behrooz has information
that can damage Marwan.
I agree. Edgar, have your team sift through
everything we have on Behrooz Araz.
Go back as far as you can.
See if there's a family link between them.
Did the interrogation reveal
that he knew anything
that might make him valuable to Marwan?
No, but the focus was on the mother.
We really didn't push him very hard.
Curtis, push harder.
See what you can find, but do it now.
My guess is Marwan will want
to make this exchange within the hour.
Tony, monitor him from the observation
room. Chloe, what do we have on audio?
- The voice print matched. It was Marwan.
- So, how are you gonna handle this?
He thinks his mother made a deal
to protect him. I'll tell him that deal's off.
- The psychological approach is too slow.
- What do you suggest?
He'll drag his feet unless we put
some physical pressure on him.
He's a kid. I'm pretty sure
he's given us everything he knows.
You're pretty sure?
- I'll call Richards.
- Tony.
- Go ahead, I'll catch up.
- Have you heard anything on Jack?
We got some information
a couple minutes ago.
- Why didn't you let me know?
- Things are going pretty fast here.
Look, Jack's alive.
He is being held by Marwan.
- How did you confirm that?
- Marwan contacted us.
He contacted you? Why would he do that?
- He wants to make a trade. Jack for Behrooz.
- When is that gonna happen?
- We don't know if it is gonna happen.
- What do you mean?
If he wants to trade,
it means Behrooz has tactical value.
If that's the case,
then we may have to hold on to him.
There's a lot we have to go over
before anything happens.
I'll keep you posted, but right now I have
to get in that room with Behrooz, all right?
Thank you.
All right, keep it at that level.
Let me know if the readings fluctuate.
- He doesn't know his mother's dead.
- I know.
- Hello, Behrooz.
- How much longer do I have to stay here?
- These things take time.
- Where is my mother?
- She's still in the field.
- With Jack Bauer? Is she OK?
Yeah, she's fine.
- Tell me about Habib Marwan.
- Why are you doing this?
Your mother gave us a little information.
She said you could give us some more.
You promised not to hurt me!
Get this guy away from me!
Back over here.
We're just gonna have a little talk.
Marwan's the leader.
That's all I know.
I heard my parents talk about him, that's it.
Go ahead.
What are you gonna do?
- What is he gonna do to me?
- We don't have a lot of time.
No! No!
No! Please don't do this! Please, no!
This is Marwan.
Get me Michelle Dessler.
Ms Dessler, it's Marwan.
Everyone on this!
- This is Dessler.
- Union Conduit Dam, 30 minutes.
I need to know Jack Bauer is still alive.
Very well. Michelle Dessler
wants to make sure you're alive.
I'm being held in a warehouse
somewhere downtown.
Satisfied?
- I can't make this happen in 30 minutes.
- You'll find a way.
Wait, I...
Dammit.
CTU will never go through with the exchange.
I'm expendable.
Yes, you are.
If Behrooz is of value to you,
he's of value to them.
They'll never let you have him back.
Marwan.
In the next few minutes CTU will be alerted
that the pilot and his family are missing.
All right.
The LAPD hourlies are here.
What do you do with them?
I promote any flagged items to the analysts.
I can't do that now. I have to get ready.
I can't. I'm tracking Behrooz.
I'd get on those hourlies if I were you.
I'll tell Meg to sift through it and deal
with any flagged items after the exchange.
OK, boss.
This is Meg.
Hourlies just came in.
Chloe and I need you to sift through them.
- Do you know how backed up we are here?
- It's worse up here. Just do it, OK?
Fine. Send it to four.
- Phoenix is ready to go.
- I thought we were waiting on a part.
It's a good thing they called me in. That
strut's fine. It was just a faulty trouble sensor.
- You're sure?
- I triple-checked it.
It's just a false alarm. Here's my report.
All right. I'll clear it for takeoff.
-  Flight Ops.
- This is Hoader.
Yeah, Phoenix is clear for takeoff.
All right.
- Were you able to narrow it down?
- So far, nothing.
We need to get this out
to all departments.
Chloe, what's wrong?
Nothing. There's no bad news about Jack,
if that's what you're asking.
Since Jack isn't here,
you're the DOD representative.
These are some standard nondisclosures.
Read them whenever you get a chance.
- I've flagged where you need to sign.
- I'll do that now.
- I'm really sorry about your husband.
- Thank you.
I can't imagine how I'd feel
right now if I were you.
I feel like someone
afraid of losing her husband.
No, I meant, you know, you and your husband
are separated, and you fall in love with Jack,
then your husband takes a bullet that saves
Jack's life. What do you do with that?
I can't think about that now.
I just need Paul to pull through this.
You just assume
that the terrorists won't kill Jack?
Chloe.
I don't wanna talk about it. Here.
I was inappropriately blunt, wasn't I?
I do that a lot.
Sorry.
Sorry, I'm gonna go.
I have a... field meeting anyway.
When your father spoke to Marwan,
was that on the phone
or did he come to your house?
Both.
Did you ever speak to Marwan alone,
away from your parents?
No.
When they made the preparations
for today's attacks, were you in the room?
I told you, they didn't want me in there.
Almeida.
-  Tony, the briefing's about to start.
- All right, I'll be right there.
If he produces something relevant,
let me know.
Yes, sir.
O'Brien.
Is anything you're doing
yielding a military connection?
- No, why?
- It may be nothing,
but there's an incident report
that might be worth looking at.
What is it?
An Air Force pilot's wife and kids were
reported missing as of two hours ago.
How can someone be missing in two hours?
I'm just telling you what it says.
Should I run it?
- No, we have to do it up here.
- Then why did you send it down here?
- It was Edgar's decision.
- Should I give it to you?
I'm the main tactical in the trade for Jack.
Give it to Edgar.
He said he's too busy.
- Just run it through county and get it to him.
- OK.
- Edgar.
- What?
Meg found something in the hourlies
I need you to look at.
- I'm preparing.
- Can't Meg do it?
It's the job of the lead tactical.
Isn't that what you think you are?
- I don't need your sarcasm. I'll take care of it.
- Fantastic.
- Hey. Is this briefing about Jack?
Yeah. Marwan called us again.
Has a decision been made?
- It'll be decided in this meeting.
- By whom?
Division. Look,
they sent someone down to run point.
Is Division thinking about not doing it?
Honestly, it could go either way.
But Jack would want us to do what's best
for this country, not what's best for him.
- I know.
- I'll let you know as soon as I can.
All right. Thanks, Tony.
Did you get anything out of Behrooz?
I don't think he knows anything,
but, uh, Curtis is still trying.
OK. Bill.
- Are you up to speed?
- I got briefed on the way.
All right, everyone, listen up.
This is Bill Buchanan from Division.
He'll be overseeing the operation.
Run everything through him. Bill?
Habib Marwan wants to make an exchange
at the Union Conduit Dam,
Behrooz Araz for Jack Bauer.
Now, before we decide whether or not
to go forward, I need to know a few things.
Why does Marwan want the boy?
What's his value?
We could not find evidence
that Behrooz had any information.
- Did you push him?
- Yeah. I don't think he knows anything.
- Who's doing backgrounds?
- Me. Nothing ties these two people together.
Could Behrooz have had something
implanted in his body?
He was scanned when he was brought in.
- Did you do an MRI?
Yeah.
I don't like giving him up
unless I know his value.
What happens if we don't
agree to the exchange?
- We don't get Bauer back.
- That can't be the deciding factor.
If we don't go through with this,
we may lose an opportunity to trap Marwan.
Marwan has to know
that's what we're thinking.
The chances of him actually
being present are small.
But we could put a tracer on Behrooz.
He might lead us to Marwan.
We tried to trace Dina and Jack.
He grabbed Jack and killed Dina.
We'll take a different approach. Two tracers.
One to be found, the other subcutaneous.
- There's no guarantee he won't find that one.
- There are no guarantees.
But the fact is we have
no viable leads on Marwan.
We have to run with every chance we get.
Have tactical finish up the profiles. Let's get
field teams on their way to the dam now.
- How do you wanna approach the site?
- We'll figure that out when Marwan calls.
Go.
Yeah.
-  What's your status?
- Airborne in 30 minutes.
Very well.
Get Bauer.
We've got him.
We have to have a satellite repositioned
before the exchange takes place.
Edgar, Chloe wants you to take a look at this
when you have the time.
Hang on, let me write that down.
Just put it right there. Thank you.
Yeah, OK. Got it.
Mrs Raines? The doctor says your husband
should be out of surgery in the next hour.
- How is it going?
- That's all he said.
Thank you.
Audrey.
- Any word on Paul?
- We still don't know yet.
We've decided to go ahead with the exchange.
We're getting Behrooz ready right now.
- It's not gonna be that simple.
- These things are never simple,
but if Marwan really wants the kid,
he's got no reason to hurt Jack.
- And if he doesn't and it's a trap?
- We'll be prepared.
- Our field agents have the area fully covered.
- Will you be there?
No, I'm gonna be running point from here.
But Curtis will be on the ground.
Is the operational objective to get Jack?
No, it isn't.
Audrey...
We have to consider Jack expendable.
This thing's about creating
an exposure point for Marwan.
I know.
Thank you for being straight with me, Tony.
Look.
Jack's about the only friend I have left,
so I'm gonna do everything I can
to keep him safe.
All right?
OK.
What are you doing?
Where are you taking me?
Habib Marwan offered to exchange
one of our operatives for you.
- We accepted that offer.
- What? What does he want with me?
We don't know. We'll be behind you every
step, and recover you as soon as possible.
Does my mother know about this?
Yes.
You made a deal with her,
to put us both in witness protection.
- We'll do everything to abide by that deal.
- Then don't do this!
That's not an option.
- Now put this watch on.
- No.
- Get off me!
- These devices will help us track you.
And I give you my word,
I'll do everything in my power for you.
Hang on. This will sting.
It's a microtracker, implanted under your skin.
You don't care about me,
or your word.
You're just using me.
Let's go.
I need you to sterilise a video feed to the van.
I got teams that need tactical uploads.
These hourlies need are 30 minutes past due.
And now I gotta put video together?
- Video's a priority. I'll see to the uploads.
- What about the hourlies?
Get on it as soon as the link's in place.
- Is it working?
- The red dot is the decoy.
When they remove the watch,
we can still trace the tracker in his neck.
Edgar, make sure all cellular stations
are put on autotrace.
Got it.
When our vehicles are two miles
from the dam, have them hold.
Nobody goes in until we hear from Marwan.
Castle's team will be there as soon
as possible. Behrooz is on his way.
We don't have time
to make sure it's not a trap.
We don't have a choice.
- CTU, Edgar Stiles.
- This is Marwan. Get Dessler.
Ms Dessler, it's Marwan.
- Dessler.
- I'll give you final instructions now.
Make sure you follow them implicitly.
Are you ready?
- Go ahead.
- How are you transporting Behrooz?
- In one of our tactical vehicles.
- Good.
Now, approach via the Frontage Road.
Pull up at the back gate of the dam,
and have Behrooz get out by himself
and walk toward the gate.
- A van will be there to pick him up.
- What about Jack Bauer?
He'll be in the van.
That doesn't work for me.
I wanna see Jack before I give up Behrooz.
- That's acceptable.
- And I want him unharmed.
- Your boy scout is just fine.
- OK.
Remember, Behrooz gets out by himself.
If any of your agents interfere, Bauer dies.
- Understood.
- Don't be late.
- Our vehicle's five minutes away.
- Then we'll see you in five minutes.
- That should keep them busy.
- What do you want to do about Bauer?
As soon as we have Behrooz, we kill Bauer.
- Who's going to protect me?
- We are. That's why we put trackers on you.
You don't think Marwan will find them?
He will.
Hopefully it won't
come to that, Behrooz.
What does that mean?
We're gonna have the area surrounded.
We will protect you.
Why would you protect me?
I'm nothing to you people.
You think I'm a terrorist.
I don't believe you are.
If Marwan is going to be there,
why don't you grab him when we get there?
He's probably not gonna be there.
- We need you to lead us to him.
- Oh, God.
- It's gonna be all right.
- It's not.
- I'm in position.
- Does CTU have anyone there yet?
Rasheed has spotted vehicles at the edge of
the access road. We think it might be them.
OK. Wait until the exchange,
then I'll give you the word to take out Bauer.
All right.
Once the trade is made, how much longer
do we need to keep CTU distracted?
Ideally until we hit the target,
but as long as possible.
And what should my men do
with Behrooz once we have him?
I haven't decided yet.
- Yes.
- They are here.
Good. Send in the van.
I don't wanna do this. I'm afraid.
- We'll be behind you every step of the way.
- What good is that if he wants me dead?
He's not going through all this
just so he can kill you. All right?
All right, the van's here.
Come on, move it.
- I see Jack.
- We could converge on them now.
Is there any indication that Marwan
has other personnel in the area?
No, just the van.
Marwan's not gonna be there.
If we close in now,
they could take the van out themselves.
We proceed.
- Curtis, it's a go.
- All right. I'm sending Behrooz.
Go ahead. It's all right.
Go.
Is my mother in the van?
She was working with you. Where is she?
- I don't know.
- I don't wanna die.
They have Behrooz.
Bauer's in my sights.
Take him out.
No!
Sniper's down! Move out!
Take cover!
Why'd you give 'em that kid?
He's double-tagged.
We'll be tracking him.
All right, you two, secure the area!
Let's go.
Almeida.
- Tony, it's Jack.
- I've got Buchanan here. You're on speaker.
- OK.
- You OK?
Fine. I need you to pick up a phone matrix
within a 20-mile radius of the dam.
- What are you thinking?
- I managed to short-circuit some phone lines.
If you can find two service obstructions at
the same coordinates, we can get to Marwan.
- I'm opening up an interface now.
- We don't have a lot of time.
Marwan's not gonna stay
at the building for long.
We have tactical teams ready.
I'll reposition for assault.
- OK. I know the layout. I'll run point.
- Copy that.
The van's heading west.
Both trackers are registering.
- Good. Let me know if anything changes.
- OK, I will.
Marwan, we have the boy.
They will have placed
tracking devices on him. Find them.
- We are looking for them now.
- When you destroy them, report back to me.
Very well.
- Where is my mother?
- Your mother is dead.
No.
I don't believe you.
What are you gonna do to me? No!
Curtis.
- They found the decoy.
- How's the injected device looking?
Still tracking.
Wait. No, it's not!
- They must have found it.
- Damn. Can you get me a visual on the van?
Hold on.
Yeah.
- We need a satellite pumped into the servers.
- I got something you should see.
- Later.
We need that satellite to find
Behrooz Araz before they kill him.
I'm on it.
We have a location from the phone company -
where Marwan was holding Jack.
Edgar, download these coordinates
to tactical right now.
Our window's closing.
We will only have this one opportunity.
- You've gotta get into the air now.
- No problem. I'm ready and on the move.
Visiontext Subtitles: Margaret Burke
ENGLISH SDH