-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ﬂ«»‚»‚ µ∞∏‚∏‚
Season07 Episode09
**********
You son of a bitch.
You're behind my son's death.
Madame president... I have your husbanD.
You will have your forces withdrawn from around
my country, sangala, immediately and permanently.
Or your husband will die
a slow and certain death.
I just wanted to make sure that you
were still coming to dinner tonight.
Marika, I can'T. I'll make it up to you.
If you're looking for
marika, she's not with me.
I'm looking for you, samuel.
Or whatever your real name is.
Now, I don't know who you
really are, and I don't care.
I just want you out of my sister's life.
Keep an incident quiet until what
jack and i are doing goes down.
What incident?
Vossler's dead.
Jack killed him at the hotel on
18th and reagan. It was self-defense.
Damn it, renee, what the hell
are you doing with this guy?
You're supposed to bring
suspects in, not murder them.
Until we know who dubaku's source is there,
you've got to handle this outside of the bureau.
Dubaku is the only person
with the names of the people
who betrayed you within your government
it's imperative that we find him.
You resigned from government service and the
senate regards you as having been a renegade agent.
How am I supposed to know
where your loyalties really lie?
With all due respect,
madame president, ask around.
I got an address for henry taylor.
Get an ambulance!
*********
no one else gets
through here. Follow me.
It's henry taylor, the president's husband, but
that information is not to be disseminated. Clear?
I...
mr. Taylor, don't speak. I
need you to save your energy.
over here!
Excuse me. Step back, please.
This is unit six. We have a
gunshot trauma to the chest...
nine-millimeter round.
Nine
- millimeter substernal. Pulse is rapid.
- Are you okay?
- Yeah.
I'm gonna call the president.I
want you to search all the rooms,
see if you can get anything off their hardware
that's going to tell us where dubaku went.
******
This is jack bauer. I need
to speak with the president.
Hold one moment, please.
Madame president, I would
encourage you not to lose hope.
Dubaku knows we tried
to deceive him, ethan.
He has no reason to keep henry alive.
jack bauer is on line
one, madame president.
Put him through.
Mr. Bauer, this is president taylor.
Madame president, we have your husband.
He is alive, but he sustained
a gunshot wound to the chest.
How bad is it?
Emts are stabilizing him.
They're getting ready to transfer
him to west arlington hospital.
Mr. Bauer, be more specific.
Is my husband going to be okay?
We're not gonna know anything
until the doctors see him.
Ma'am, I have to warn you,
he has lost a lot of blood.
Jack, it's bill. Do you have dubaku?
Negative-- he was gone
before we got here.
Madame president, since your husband was
the only leverage that dubaku had left,
it's safe to say that he is
trying to leave the country now.
Have you any idea how
he intends to do that?
Not at this time.
Unfortunately, all his men
were killed during the assault.
Agent walker and i will stay behind.
We'll continue to search the area.
We have to assume that dubaku has
an exit strategy already in place.
Whatever we're going to do to find
him, we're going to have to do it fast.
Yes. Thank you, mr. Bauer.
Please keep me apprised on everything.
Yes, ma'am. I'm sorry.
I am so sorry, madame president.
Ethan, I'm going to the
hospital to be with my husband.
Ma'am, that's not possible.
You're executing a military invasion.
My generals can execute it
perfectly well without me.
We can't ignore the fact the
secret service has been compromised.
There's no way we can ensure your
safety outside the white house.
I don't give a damn.
I am not going to be held prisoner in this
office while my husband is fighting for his life.
Now, either find someone to take to
the hospital or I'll drive there myself.
Madame president, you
know my record of service.
If it's acceptable to you, I'm willing to
assume responsibility for your security.
Bill, you're no longer credentialed.
You don't have the authority.
Until we capture dubaku and interrogate him, we have
no idea who in the government is working for him.
You do not know who you can trust.
But I can trust you.
I brought this conspiracy to
your attention, madame president.
I would hope that I've earned it.
What do you need from me?
Reinstate my government clearance, allow
me the authority to vet white house staff,
and allow me to bring one of my people into
fbi to provide larry moss with tactical support.
Who is it that you want to bring in?
Chloe o'brian. I can vouch for
her; she's the best there is.
Her clearances were also revoked
when ctu was decommissioned.
Isn't there anyone capable of handling these
duties without our having to reinstate her?
Someone in the bureau
is on dubaku's payroll.
Until we find out who it is, larry moss can't
take the chance of bringing his own people
into a manhunt for dubaku.
All right.
The director of white house secret
service operations is agent hovis.
I'll order him to turn over
security protocols to you.
I know ted hovis, madame president. He's
not gonna like this; he's gonna fight us.
Well, considering that agents under h charge
are responsible for what happened to my husband,
I don't give a damn what he likes.
You have your provisional appointment, mr.
Buchanan, under the authority of this office.
Thank you, madame president.
You can thank me by
getting me to the hospital.
I'll make the arrangements.
Madame president...
your concerns are clear to me,
ethan, but I've made my decision.
I'm only trying to do my job--
looking out for your interests.
My interest right now
is catching ike dubaku.
He has killed scores of americans
today, he tried to kill my husband,
and he has corrupted our government.
Whatever it takes, I want
that son of a bitch found.
Marika... marika.
Samuel, what are you doing here?
We need to talk.
Uh, okay, well, I get
a break in 20 minutes.
No, now.
Okay, what is it? You're scaring me.
Something has come up. I
need to leave the country.
What? When?
Right away.
I don't understand.
W-when are you coming back?
Marika, listen to me.
I haven't been entirely honest with you.
My passport visa expired a couple months
ago and I've been in the country illegally.
I'm afraid the immigration
people have caught up with me.
It was my sister, wasn't it?
She reported you, didn't she?
That doesn't matter now.
What is important is I have to leave the
country tonight, and I want you to come with me.
Tonight?
Marika, we've talked about this.
I promised you that one day i would take you away
from here, give you the happiness that you deserve.
Samuel, I-I want that, too, but...
but not tonight, not so soon.
Marika, I don't have
time to argue with you!
I'm sorry.
I can't leave rosa.
She needs me; I'm the only one she
has to take care of her. You know that.
I know, I know. Which is
why she's going to join us.
Join us?
As soon as possible.
I could only arrange tickets
for both of us tonight,
but I want you to promise not to tell
your sister of our plans, at least not yet.
I have to; I can't just run off.
No, no, no, she might cause trouble for
us, make it impossible for us to leave.
I promise you your sister will join us
within a couple of days of our arrival. Okay?
- Our arrival where?
- Belize.
I have shown you the
photographs of my home there.
Do you love me?
You know I do.
Then trust me. Say you'll come.
I'll get my things.
I still need to finalize our arrangements.
I want you to go home and pack.
- Wait for my call.
- All right.
- Yes.
- It's me.
Have you made the preparations?
Almost.
It's been tricky
clearing a flight corridor
since faa still has most private
and commercial aircraft grounded.
I have faith you'll manage.
The arrangements are for two passengers?
Just as you requested.
Are you sure you want
to leave now, colonel?
I can't imagine general juma will be pleased
to learn that you're abandoning your mission.
The mission is over. I
have done what I can do.
If that is not enough for
juma, then to hell with him.
I've got your passports
and itinerary in hand.
Meet me at our usual spot in
half an hour. I'll bring them.
No, we'll meet in the lobby of
the roosevelt continental hotel.
That's not a good idea. It'll
be crowded there at this hour.
I know. I want the meeting earlier.
I'll see you in 15 minutes.
Go.
- I can't get it to boot. Hard drive must be fried.
- Damn it.
Let's search the bodies. Start with him.
- yeah.
- Renee, it's me.
Bill buchanan just briefed
me on your situation.
What's henry taylor's status?
They've got him in an ambulance en
route to west arlington hospital.
I don't know his current condition.
Buchanan told me you and
bauer were in a firefight.
Yeah, we took down six of dubaku's men,
but dubaku was gone before we got there.
You all right?
I've been in worse.
******
- I'm fine, larry.
- Really? I'm not so sure about that.
And what is that supposed to mean?
I'm looking at a report
faxed to me from metro police.
A mrs. Carol vossler is
claiming an unidentified woman
held her and her child
hostage at gunpoint.
She says the woman
threatened to kill her son.
Larry, we discussed this.
We needed to get vossler to tell
us where taylor was being held.
It was the only leverage we had.
Yeah, right, whatever's necessary.
Jack bauer's rationalization for
every unethical action he takes.
It worked, larry. Doesn't
that count for something?
Renee, jack bauer is about to be sung up by a senate
subcommittee, and you are following his playbook.
You already got the ag's office looking into that
thing you pulled with tanner's respirator, and now this.
No one was actually hurt.
No one...? Renee, bauer
killed the woman's husband!
Renee, I swear to you, I am
scared of what is happening to you.
You put these people through
hell and it doesn't bother you.
I didn't say that it doesn't bother
me, larry. I said that it worked.
Of course it bothers me.
I can see that woman's face.
She and her child
staring at me with such...
she had no idea that her husband was
a killer, a traitor to his country,
and she looked at me
like I was the monster.
- Agent walker.
- Hold on.
I cross-referenced the
information on these pdas.
I came across some banking transactions.
All from a series of accounts
registered to the same address.
- You think it's a safe house?
- It's worth a shot.
Larry, we may have an address on dubaku.
21917 euclid street. Apartment six.
21917 euclid street, unit
six. We're moving out now.
Can you provide sat surveillance?
Yeah, bill buchanan's sending somebody over
to run th, but until she's up and running,
you're gonna have to go in blind.
Okay. We'll be in touch.
- You sure you're okay?
- I'm fine.
Let's go.
Federal investigations continue into the terrorist
acts that have gripped the nation's capital,
as well as the people of kidron, ohio.
Despite assurances by president taylor in her
national address that the threat has passed
Sources at the white house will not confirm that
all those responsible have been accounted for.
Now, are you sure you're
not gonna need my help?
I'm just running fbi ops
temporarily until they catch dubaku.
Once they find him, hopefully he'll tell us
the names of all the people on his payroll
that are inside our government.
And then, we can go home?
Then, we can go home.
Well, just be careful. All right?
'Cause if buchanan's right and dubaku
has someone working inside the bureau...
I'll watch my back.
You just watch prescott.
Okay, sweetheart, mommy has to
go to work. You be good, okay?
Bye, mommy.
- You be good, too.
- I will.
And if you get all jammed
up, you know where to find me.
I need you to cross-reference
our deployments with homeland.
Make sure the requisition
numbers match up.
After that, you can
catch up on the hourlies.
Are you joking? That is busy work,
administrative crap you're handing me.
Janis... I don't have the time or the inclination
right now to explain my assignments to you.
Just get it done.
Agent moss, chloe o'brian just
cleared security. She's on her way up.
All right, thank you.
Janis, set up a secure vpn socket.
Port it to the conference room.
Why do you need a vpn socket?
I'm bringing in a consultant from homeland to confirm
there are no lingering gaps in the cip firewall.
That's fine. Take that downstairs.
Ms.O'brian, larry moss.
Welcome to the fbi.
- You can call me chloe.
- All right, we're right in here.
Buchanan said you'd be up to speed.
- I'm up.
- Good.
Agent walker and bauer are
pursuing a potential lead on dubaku.
They're en route to this address
in the mount pleasant district.
Agent walker's requesting
satellite support.
What's the matter? Is something wrong?
I'm feeling a little exposed here.
If someone out there is working for dubaku,
shouldn't we be doing this more covertly?
As far as anyone knows, you're
working on shoring up our firewall.
Besides, this is the only space available
where you'll have full access to our server.
Our network doesn't
support remote modules.
That's inefficient.
Whoever set your network up that
way didn't know what they were doing.
I set our network up that way.
Okay.
Something else?
You worked with bauer for
a long time, didn't you?
Seven years, on and off.
That's impressive.
That you survived the experience.
What are you talking about?
Only that a lot of people didn'T.
Curtis manning, ryan
chapelle. His own wife.
Are you saying it's jack's
fault his wife was killed?
You tell me.
Jack bauer is the most trustworthy,
honorable man I know, and he'sy iend.
Maybe you should worry less about him and more
about the mole in your office working for dubaku.
- Is that chloe o'brian?
- What?
In the conference room. Chloe
o'brian-- she was senior analyst at ctu.
I once took a seminar she
gave. What's she doing here?
Larry said homeland sent her over to check
for residual breaches from the firewall attack.
What?
It just doesn't sound
like her area of expertise.
Besides, as far as I know, she's been
inactive since ctu was decommissioned.
Your passports and travel itinerary.
A hawker-siddley 748 is
fueling at taft airfield.
Be ready to fly within a half
hour, get you to the cayman islands.
You shouldn't have any trouble
getting to belize from there.
I need a car to the
airfield and a driver.
I assumed you had your
own transportation.
It's not for me.
I see. It's for the girl.
Well, I'm not sure I can find
someone I trust on such short notice.
Really?
What about your man at the bar?
Excuse me?
Or one of the two on the
balcony watching us now?
Or the two in the black town
car waiting for me to leave?
Do you think I am a fool, mr. Burnett?
I know you people see
me as a liability now.
These men are here to guarantee your
safety, colonel, not to threaten it.
Guarantee my safety. How nice.
And said with such sincerity.
I want you to take this
message back with you.
If anything should happen to me
on my way out of the country--
an accident or an assassination
attempt, anything--
if the plane that you were so
generous to donate decides to explode,
a data file with all the names and
bank transactions of all those involved
will be sent to the justice department.
That is completely uecessary.
The same holds true if anything
should happen to marika donoso.
I swear to you, she
knows nothing of this.
She is no threat to you.
Make sure your driver knows
this before he brings her to me.
Do you understand what I am saying?
I want you to tell me that you understand what
I am saying to you, so there will be no mistakes.
- I understand.
- Good.
The one thing I have learned in the
company of mercenaries, mr. Burnett,
is that ultimately, they care about
nothing but their own survival. Good day.
I was right.
Dubaku suspected we
were gonna take him out,
and apparently, he's assembled
evidence to use as an insurance policy.
We need to make sure he gets out of
the country and safely into exile.
Otherwise, we're all compromised.
I'll make the calls.
What are you doing?
Rosa.
Where are you going?
Rosa, listen to me. We're
going away from here. All of us.
Well, what do you mean, all?
Samuel told me the truth.
He's an illegal, just like you thought.
He has to leave the country,
and I've agreed to go with him.
You're leaving me?
No, no, only for a short
time. You're gonna come, too.
Samuel's made plans. We're gonna
live with him in his home in belize.
Marika... he's lying to you.
- He's not.
- I won't let you do this!
My god, rosa.
I have taken care of you my entire life.
I've sacrificed everything for you.
Why can't you let me have this?
I don't trust him.
Oh, well, you never liked any man
who's ever shown an interest in me.
Every chance I've ever had at happiness, you
found some way of ruining it. But not this time.
- Marika, I'm begging you, listen to me.
- No.
Marika, please. Stop.
Move!
Marika, please. Listen to
me. I'm begging you, marik...
fbi--
don't move!
Get on your knees now! On your knees!
Both of you, put your hands behind
your head, interlock your fingers. Now!
Do not move.
We're clear.
- Where is dubaku?
- Who?
Don't play games with me!
Ike dubaku-- we traced bank
accounts to this address.
Now, where is he?
We don't know who you're talking about.
Let me make try and
make this easier for you.
You know this man?
No.
You're lying to me.
Why are you lying to me?
Let me see.
That's him--
we know him.
- He calls himself aboa, samuel aboa.
- Rosa, shut up!
She was going to meet him to leave me.
Where were you gonna meet
him? Where were you going?
I don't know.
- How do you know him? You work for him?
- No.
- Do you work for him?
You know what he's doing
here in this country?
Do you have any idea...
what this man is?
He's everything to me.
- Nurse...
- Mitchell.
Nurse mitchell,I'd
like to see my husband.
Uh,ma'am,I...I don't
know if that's possible.
I was told that dr. Schulman
will be doing the surgery.
Where is he?
Excuse me,madame president.
I'm lee schulman,your husband's surgeon.
If you come with me,you can see him
now,but you'll need to keep it brief.
Thank you.
You should know that mr. Taylor's looking
at a minimum of five hours in surgery.
The bullet lacerated his pulmonary
artery and lodged in his thoracic region.
He's also suffered
massive internal bleeding.
Can you offer any kind of prognosis?
I'm a blunt woman,dr. Schulman.
I appreciates bluntness.
His chances aren't good,ma'am.
But I'll do everything I can.
If you'll excuse me.
I need to scrub up now.
Henry?
Darling,can you hear me?
Ally.
Yes,sweetheart.
I'm here.
I'm so sorry I didn't
listen to you about roger.
You were right.
It wasn't suicide.
I know that now. You were always right.
He was a hero.
Yes.
He was,and so are you.
I'm sorry,madame president,but
the anesthesiologist is ready now.
Mr. Buchanan?
Yes,madame president?
Ere's something I need you to do for me.
Have someone find my daughter
olivia and bring her to me.
Have you had a chance to tell her?
My daughter and I haven't spoken
for some time,mr. Buchanan.
She'd never get on the phone with me.
She works for a consulting
firm-- martling/norris.
Do have someone
trustworthy you can send?
Yes,ma'am.
I believe I do.
And here he is again in the uniform of the presidential
guard at the gates of the notorious mukatu prison.
And here,inside the soccer
stadium after the barakar massacre.
The event that earned him the
nickname the butcher of sangala.
Oh,please. No more.
what did you say his
real name was again?
Dubaku.
Ike dubaku.
I've seen firsthand
what he's capable of.
I was in africa a few months ago.
He was responsible for
murdering a friend of mine.
I know this is a shock.
and I'm sorry.
I really am.But here's the situation.
We need your help,and we need it now.
what kind of help?
We need to put this man in custody
before he can leave the country.
Well,she already told you.
She doesn't know where he is.
Yeah,but you said earlier that
you were going to meet him.
Where?
He didn't say.
Just told me to go home and
pack and wait for his call.
Give me your phone.
Why?
When he calls,I want you to answer it.
No. No,no. I can'T. I can'T.
Yes,you can.
listen to me.
Just...just-just listen to me.
It's-it's over.
The man you thought you knew,the man
you had feelings for-- he doesn't exist.
All you've been left with
are his lies and his betrayal.
is that him?
Marika,please.
All I want you to do is answer
the phone and talk to him
so that we can find out
where he wants to meet you.
Please. You can do this.
Please just try.
hello.
Marika?
Yes.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
What took you so long
to answer the phone?
I was in the bedroom packing.
Where are you?
What's wrong?
You sound strange.
It'S...it was rosa.
She caught me packing,and we argued.
Is she going to be a problem for us?
No.
I'm sorry,samuel.
I had to tell her everything.
It was the only way.
But,uh...but she understands now.
Are you certain?
Yeah. Yeah,she's fine.
Now that she knows she and I will
be together again in a few days.
She should thank heaven she
has such an angel for a sister.
Are you ready to go?
Almost.
Hurry up then.
I've had a car sent for you.
It should be there very shortly.
Go downstairs and wait for it.
Where is it taking me?
Don't worry. The driver will know.
I just want the woman I love to
get downstairs as quickly possible.
Okay.
It's all right. It's all right.
You did great.
Did we get the rendezvous point?
No. He's sending a car with a driver.
Come here.
there's no one on the street yet.
We could grab the driver,get
him to tell us dubaku's location.
There's no guarantee
we can get him to talk.
And if we take too long,dubaku's
not gonna wait around.
So then what do we do?
We can get her to go meet with him.
What?
We could track her. We could use
her cell phone as a transponder.
You want to send that girl to dubaku?
We don't have another choice.
Jack.
You want to get dubaku,this is our shot.
Marika?
I have a favor to ask of you.
We can't make you do this.
But when the car arrives,we would
like you to go with the driver
so that we could follow
you back to dubaku.
Oh,what-what are you talking about?
You want her to go to him and face him?
It's the only chance we have of finding
him before he disappears forever.
I'll do it.
- I'll do it.
- No!
I'm your older sister,and
I won't allow it.
It's not your decision to make,rosa.
It's mine.
And it's the right thing to do.
Let me see your phone.
What are you doing?
Getting your sid number.
It's how we're going to track you.
You're not gonna be out there alone.
Agent walker and i
will be following you.
We'll never be more than a mile behind.
As soon as you reach the destination--
that's when we'll move in.
Marika.
A mile!
Are you crazy?
Rosa,enough.
You heard what he said.
He's a murderer! He could hurt you.
He won'T.
Rosa,I should have listened to you.
Sweetheart.
You warned me about him.
Listen,the only reason why I said
those things was because I was jealous.
And I didn't want to lose you.
Larry,it's jack.
Renee said you had someone
running operations support?
Yeah. She's right here.
I'll put you on speaker.
jack,it's chloe.
Chloe.
What do you need?
How long's it gonna take you to set
up a sat beacon for a mobile line?
Usually a few seconds,but with the
backward way they have the system set up,
it's gonna take at least a few minutes.
Okay,well,let me give
you the sid number.
1-c-4-8-6-8-9.
You got it?
Got it.
Jack,who are you tracking?
A woman who's involved with dubaku.
He's sending a car to take her to him.
She's one of his operatives?
No. It's-it's more
complicated than that.
Arthur,you're not going
to find another firm
that's done more high-level consulting work  for a
relatively small pharmaceutical company like yours.
Remember,my firm helped the governor craft a plan to swap
property taxes for sales taxes in his last budget reform.
Tell me that didn't save
dexter-carr a bundle.
Oh,it did,olivia.
But since I'm specifically looking to hire
you,I need to know what you yourself can do.
Whatever you need.
You know my accomplishments,you've
seen my resume.
I mean white house influence.
Considering your family.
We're not lobbyists,arthur.
It states that clearly in the contract.
I just thought,since you
had the president's ear...
I don'T.
Is that going to be a problem?
Excuse me,ms.Taylor?
Do I know you?
My name is aaron pierce.
Your office told me you'd be here.
I've been dispatched at
the request the president.
Your credentials say
you've retired,mr. Pierce.
Perhaps no one informed you I refused
secret service protection months ago.
I'm aware of that,ma'am.
This ia special circumstance.
Well,as you can see,I'm
a little busy right now.
This isn't a good time.
I'm sorry,but I have to insist.
It's really...it's all right.
No. No,it's not all right.
What is it that's so important for my mother to
steal me away while I'm trying to do business?
I'm not at liberty to say,ma'am.
That informationis confidential.
Olivia,we can pick
this up at a later time.
Arthur,wait...
we'll be in touch.
Ma'am,please?
I'm not going anywhere with you
until you tell me what this is about.
It's your father,ms.Taylor.
He's been shot.
He's in surgery at
west arlington hospital.
Your mother's there now.
None of this is public knowledge.
My god,I...
my car is just outside.
Excuse me,sean.
Can I please get the digital
beta key for the server?
Why?
Larry asked for it.
Something to do with
the firewall assessment.
If larry wants it,why
doesn't he come to me?
I don't know.
Maybe I ought to go ask him.
No.
Okay.
I think that larry brought in this
woman,chloe o'brian,to replace me.
And I just want to get a bead
on what they're working on.
That's all.
That's all? That's enough
toose us both our jobs.
Well,maybe I should
stop covering for you.
What are you talking about?
Erika and you,and your
little sexual indiscretions.
I've said nothing to larry or your wife.
I'm sure you'd like
me to keep it that way.
You're a little bitch,you know that?
You're a little bitch.
Okay,jack. The link's
up,I've got the signal.
Copy that. I'll get back to you.
We're on.
Marika...
we got to go.
You--
fbi.
You keep her safe,you hear me?
We will.
I'm really scared.
You're going to be fine.
Just remember,we're right behind you.
Move up here.
Now,listen,if you get into trouble,you
can signal us by dialing one-zero...
no. No,I don't want you to do that.
Don't do anything that's going to
raise the suspicion of the driver.
Okay.
You ready?
I'm ready.
Yeah.
What the hell are you doing?
She was scared.
I wanted her to know there was another
option than waiting for us to swoop in.
If we're going to find dubaku,there
are no other options,you understand?
Come on,you've run operations like this.
Not without full tactical support,and
at least two backup units on the scene.
She's naked out there,jack.
I don't like it.
This isn't about you.
This is about her and dubaku.
Listen,life gets ugly,innocent
people get hurt-- that's a reality.
At least she got to make a choice
to be involved,to do the right thing.
Which is a lot more than I can
say for dubaku's other victims.
We have one job here--
that's to get dubaku.
Outside of that don't get involved.
Chloe,the car's here.
Copy that.
She's getting in the car.
Copy.
She's moving. Are you cked in?
Yeah,I've got them
heading south on 14th.
Can you upload the tracking
grid to agent walker's pda?
No,I'll have to direct you.
Just keep us close.
Understood. Head towards
14th,make a right.
Copy that.
How much further?
Continuing west on r
street,crossing hampshire avenue.
You're less than a mile
behind the target car.
Copy that.
Target car is turning,left
on connecticut.
Okay,rounding dupont circle.
Agent moss,is there anything
in the northern quad of the grid
that would indicate where dubaku
can hide a plane or a helicopter?
No. Nothing definitive.
Could be any number of launch sites.
Whoa! Whoa! What was it?
What happened?
Jack,we've got a problem.
Chloe,what's wrong?
- We just lost the tracking grid.
- What?
I-I don't know. It just
suddenly glitched out.
We can't afford to lose them.
Jack,I gave this woman
my word we'd protect her.
I know.
Chloe,get it back up.
We're doing our best,here,jack.
Wait.
It's back up.
What the hell happened?
I don't know,I'm running
a diagnostic right now.
Jack,they're moving southeast
on massachusetts avenue.
You've closed the gap
to about a half mile.
You may want to back off a little bit.
Okay,copy that.
Oh,no.
What?
Somebody was in the system.
What? What are you talking about?
I'm saying someone in this
office was mirroring my terminal.
Whoever it was knows
exactly what we were doing.
Can you backtrace the breach?
No.
The link was severed.
It could have come from anywhere.
Jack,you getting this?
It looks like we might
have a security breach.
Someone is mirroring our comm.
Jack,they're coming from all sides.
Larry,we got a situation here.
what's going on?
I got metro pds Trying to
build a roadblock around us.
What?
Why would they be doing that?
I don't know. Just get 'em off us!
larry,do something!
This is agent moss.
Connect me with metro district command.
Hands in the air! Hands in the air!
My name is jack bauer
Get out of the car right now!
my passenger is a federal agent.
She's a federal agent!
Put your hands behind your back,sir.
Come on,larry,do something!
Captain,you've got to release
these people immediately!
No. No,that is a mistake.
No federal warrants have
been issued for them!
Yes,they have.
A warrant was called in for the vehicle.
"Occupants armed and dangerous,to
be apprehended with decisive force."
Issued by whom?
Fbi. This office.
There's no attribution,but
the routing code's real.
This was definitely
done by someone here.
Marika's car just turned
east onto n street.
Captain,listen carefully.
I'm the special agent in charge of this operation,and
I am revoking these warrants immediately.
No. No,I don't have time to
deal with your chain of command.
You need to release
these people right now!
Thank you.
So is o'brian here to replace you?
I don't know.
No.
Larry's using her for some kind of
covert operation with jack bauer.
They're tracking a car to dubaku.
Why would he keep us in the
dark about something like that?
I don't know.
I don't know,but I don't like it.
Hey,I took care of bauer and walker.
They're pinned down.
Why am I being brought
in on this so last minute?
Moss is running this op on his own.
It took me some time to
tap into his phone line.
He's on with metro right now.
Can you at least disable the tracking
signal they're using to follow the girl?
No,not from my console.
But judging by the frequency,they're
using her cell as the tracker.
All right.
Good work.
You told me that once dubaku served
his purpose,you'd take him out.
Why are we still helping him?
He's threatening to expose us using the database he's
kept with names and accounts of everyone involved.
Including mine?
I mean,everyone.
We don't know where the file is,so
you just better pray that he gets away.
Yes,it has to do with the terrorist
threats that happened this morning.
hello?
You got a problem.
What is it?
Your girlfriend's
been turned by the fbi.
I don't believe you.
They met with her a half hour
ago,told her who you really are.
That's impossible.
Marika would never do this.
I got it from our source inside
the bureau,it is definite.
She agreed to lead them to you,using
her cell phone as a tracker.
Look,my source managed to stall
their surveillance team for a while,
but you need to get to
the airfield immediately.
I'll call my driver,have
him take care of her.
No.
I'll do it.
Colonel,I told you,they
are tracking her.
If you let her come to you,you're
risking your chances of escape.
I said,I'll take care of her!
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
proudly presents
sync:»‚»‚&∏‚∏‚
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
Season 07 Episode 09