... ::: www.SubCentral.de ::: ...
&
Bierdopje.com
proudly present
24 - Season 7
Episode 15
Previously on 24 ...
Ken Dellao, CNB.
I'm wondering if you can
confirm some information.
I'm gonna be reporting
in this evening's
broadcast
that a rogue ex-federal
agent named Jack Bauer
is the prime suspect
in the murder of Ryan Burnett.
You leaked this story
of Burnett's murder
and my involvement
to the press.
So another one of your errors in
judgment bites you on the ass.
You've gone too far this time.
Renee, it's Jack.
Don't hang up the phone, please.
Whatever they told you,
I did not kill Burnett.
I sent you a photo
of the man who did.
All I want you to do
is make an ID.
John Quinn,
Black Ops combat vet.
He works for Starkwood.
Starkwood work with Juma?
If they did,
it wasn't on the books.
You know, if anyone knows,
it's Senator Mayer.
Renee, where's Bauer?
I don't know.
Don't you lie
to me.
We know you accessed
a classified
government database
and sent someone's name
and address to Bauer.
Tell me where he is.
I can't.
Put her in holding.
Mirandize her.
If Bauer connects us to Juma,
it could seriously impede
this operation.
Yes, it could.
Is the shipment on time?
Yes. Due into port
in the next hour.
Once the weapons are deployed,
then it doesn't matter
what Mr. Bauer
or anyone else knows.
I didn't kill Burnett.
This man did.
His name is John Quinn.
He works for Starkwood.
And what does Starkwood have
to do with this?
Your informant claims
that Starkwood was trying
to acquire a bioweapon, and
that's your connection to Juma.
You've been trying
to dismantle Starkwood
for the last six months.
If they have
a weapon like this,
you better believe
they intend to use it.
No!
Just tell me where the
weapons are coming in.
You're too late.
They're already here.
The following takes place
between 10:00 P.M. and 11:00 P.M.
Sir?
Preliminary sweep
of the immediate area's done.
There's no sign of Bauer.
All right,
widen the grid.
And run down security cameras
around the perimeter, witnesses.
Somebody must
have seen him.
Yes, sir.
Mr. Kanin.
Yes?
Larry Moss is on the line.
Agent Moss,
please tell me
you have Jack Bauer in custody.
I wish that were the case,
Mr. Kanin, but the truth is...
Sir, it's
Senator Mayer.
He's dead.
What?!
He was murdered at his house.
We only found out
that Bauer was on his way
over here a short time ago.
Unfortunately, we
got here too late.
Wait a minute.
Are you telling me
that Jack Bauer just killed
a United States Senator?
That's the assumption that
we're working under, yes, sir.
How could you have
let this happen, Agent Moss?!
He had us all
fooled, sir.
I released Jack Bauer
into your custody!
I ordered you to keep him
on a short leash!
No, no. Mr. Kanin, you are not
gonna lay this one at my feet.
It was your decision
to give Bauer access to Burnett.
I advised you against it.
Mr. Kanin?
I'm sorry. Uh,
what did you say?
I said, I advised you
against it.
Yes, you did.
Sir, I have teams
sweeping the area.
Just find him, Agent Moss.
Yeah, I will.
Starkwood was involved with
everything that happened today.
They were the ones that
helped Juma and his men
bring down those planes
and attack the White House.
In exchange, they
were allowed to develop
and manufacture
a WMD in Sangala.
It's a bioweapon.
Apparently, it's already here
in the US.
Who else knows about this?
No one.
Senator Mayer and I
were piecing together
the information
right before
he was killed.
You said the weapon's
already here.
Are they in
possession of it?
I don't think so.
The text message I got
off their agent's cell phone
said, "Port of Alexandria,
Lot C, 10:15 p.m."
Why don't we just call the FBI
and lock the whole place down?
Because we're
fugitives, Tony.
No one's going
to believe us.
We need to know exactly
where that weapon is
before we call
anyone else in.
Tony, I need to know
if you're with me on this.
Yeah, I'm with you.
Okay. Meet me
at the north end of the port.
There's an access road
right before the main entrance.
All right, I'll be there.
It's over.
Dubaku and Juma are dead.
Everyone responsible
for the terrorist attacks...
responsible for Roger.
Thank God for that.
And there's...
there's something else.
Something good
that's come out of all of this.
Olivia
is here at the White House.
Olivia?
She's come home, Henry.
This crisis--
it brought us together.
I've asked her to stay on
as Special Advisor, and...
she's agreed.
Ally...
I can't begin to tell you
how happy that makes me.
Me, too.
Sweetheart, I know
that you're tired.
You should get
some rest.
Olivia and I will come
to the hospital
just as soon as we can.
When you can.
I'm not going anywhere.
Give Olivia my love.
Love you.
We love you, too.
The doctors expect him
to make a full recovery.
Henry's a lot tougher
than anyone thought.
Oh, maybe, maybe, maybe,
just maybe,
this day will end
on a positive note.
What is it, Ethan? What's wrong?
I'm sorry to have to tell you
this, Madam President,
but Senator Mayer is dead.
What happened?
All evidence points to the fact
that he was murdered
by Jack Bauer.
Bauer?
It's hard to believe, I know.
It-It doesn't make any sense.
After everything
he has done today,
why on earth would he do this?
We'll know more
when we find him.
My God.
Madam President,
in light of what's happened,
and for the sake
of your administration,
I'm afraid I have no choice
but to resign
as your Chief of Staff.
Ethan!
Madam President, please,
you need to hear this.
Inevitably, it'll come to light
that I sanctioned
Bauer's release
from custody.
Unless I step down immediately,
the damage to your office,
and you personally,
will be extensive.
Ethan, Olivia has already killed
this story once today.
We can control the damage.
No.
No, not even Olivia
can control it now.
Not after the senator's murder.
The truth is, Madam President,
I didn't do enough
to protect you.
The truth is, I failed you.
And I should
shoulder the blame
for what's happened.
Ethan, really, you're...
you're taking
this too far.
Am I?
I'm not so sure.
As your daughter has made
abundantly clear,
I have a lot
to answer for.
You have done nothing but be
an invaluable advisor to me
and an even
better friend.
I appreciate
you saying that,
Madam President,
but Olivia's right.
The political knives
will be out.
Every decision
I've made will be scrutinized.
There will be calls
for a special
prosecutor.
You're a great woman, Allison.
You have great work yet to do.
I'm a liability
to you now.
Don't let me compromise
your next three years in office.
Don't let me sink
your agenda.
Our agenda, Ethan.
Yes.
Our agenda.
Trust me, Madam President,
it's the right thing to do.
Accept my resignation.
I'll have a letter on your desk
in the morning.
They're gonna be
here any minute.
We need to narrow
down the search.
If they offloaded it today,
it should still be
on the storage dock.
That's still a needle
in a haystack, Jack.
There must be over
a thousand containers in there.
We need to access
the yard's manifest.
What's the security?
I've spotted one Port Authority officer.
That's it?
That's it.
There's got to be more.
Come on, let's go.
Honey, it'll be fine.
I get relieved in a few hours.
Carl, you know I don't like you
working double shifts.
Well, it was my choice.
And we could use the overtime.
How are the girls?
Kicking like a
chorus line tonight.
They miss their daddy.
What'd the doctor say?
That I'm lucky
it's not triplets.
Honey, let me call you back.
Don't even think about
going for your weapon.
I need the port's manifest.
Where is it?
I'm just a PA cop.
Customs House.
That way.
Let's go.
We on schedule?
We're at the staging area
near the port, sir, but we're
still waiting on Quinn.
He should have
been there by now.
Have you heard from him?
We've tried his cell,
but he's not answering.
If Bauer took out Quinn,
he might have knowledge
of the operation.
Mightn't he?
Should we stand down, sir?
No. Give Quinn
five more minutes,
then go in.
Do so with extreme caution
then contact me the minute
that you've secured
the container.
Yes, sir.
Everybody on the board
is here, sir.
You have a worried look, Greg.
It's very tense
in there, sir.
They're six-year-olds, Greg.
And they need
to eat their carrots.
It's been a rough day for
the United States of America.
The White House under siege,
the President taken hostage...
It's especially painful
because we know
this didn't have to be.
Fact: the United States military
is strained
to the breaking point.
Fact: reinstatement
of the draft
is off the table
for political reasons.
Fact: the people in this room,
you all control
the largest private army
in the Western hemisphere.
Now, could we have been
of help today?
You bet your ass
we could've been of help!
But they didn't
call us, did they?
No. Instead,
we sit here,
our contracts are canceled,
our soldiers vilified,
our corporate sovereignty
is threatened
by congressional fiat.
Doug, you brokered the deal
with this government.
You were short-sighted
and they don't understand
that the global war
on terror can
only be won
by forces like ours.
So as of this
minute, we sit
for no more depositions.
We volunteer
no more documents.
I don't even want us to take
any phone calls.
Is that what this is about?
With the security of our country, ...
we cannot afford to let
them take us down.
Is that what
this is about then?
You came here
to ask the board to risk
a federal indictment?
It won't work, Jonas.
We got a deal.
It's a good deal and
we're lucky to have it.
With an administration
that wants to destroy us.
Wants to take us
out of business.
No, it's all different now.
Today was
a game-changer.
No, institutionally,
we are in compliance
with the subpoena.
Documents have
been filed,
depositions taken.
Not anymore.
Jonas, we have to stay
engaged with this
administration.
No, we don't, Doug.
So look, you and I
can talk this out.
If you guys
have any questions,
any further questions,
Greg, you will
stick around
and you'll answer them.
Thank you for coming everyone.
Thank you.
Your way was
a mistake, Doug.
You have to
acknowledge that.
Maybe. But you
and I both know
that Starkwood cannot survive
an all-out war
against the subcommittee.
Let me worry
about that.
No, you should worry
about Senator Mayer.
He's not going
to let go of this.
He's got his teeth in it.
Senator Mayer's dead.
He was killed
by a rogue federal agent
not one hour ago, tragically.
Jonas.
Tell me you had
nothing to do with this.
Are you accusing me
of complicity
in the murder
of Senator Mayer?
I want a personal assurance.
Starkwood is not
in the business
of political
assassination, Doug.
Though maybe we should
look into it.
I hear it's a growth market.
Jack, you finding anything?
12 ships were unloaded
here today.
Any from Sangala?
There's no deepwater port in
that area of West Africa.
If the weapon
originated from there,
it would've had to overland
into Pointe-Noire.
Where...
two of the 12 ships acquired
cargo from that port
within the last four weeks.
Come on.
Come on. Damn it!
What is it?
I can't access
their manifests; their database
is password protected.
What's your name, officer?
Gadsen.
Carl Gadsen.
I don't have any information
about a password.
Carl, I want you to listen
to me very carefully.
The same terrorists who took down
two planes earlier today
and attacked
the White House are trying
to acquire a weapon
of mass destruction.
They're coming here
to pick up that weapon.
It's somewhere
out there
in your yard in one
of those canisters.
Look, I understand
this might be hard
for you to believe.
No, actually, it's not.
You don't have a lot of time.
What do you mean?
They are coming.
In fact, they should
be here already.
Keep talking, Carl.
They told me they
were smuggling in
electronics from South Korea.
I swear.
I had no idea they
were terrorists.
What'd you agree to do for them?
Open the front gate.
Look the other way.
Is that it?
Disable the security cameras.
A yard this size should
have more police officers.
Where are they?
I'm the supervisor.
I do the shift schedules.
I made sure
I'd be the only one here.
That's enough
confirmation for me.
I'm making the call.
Untie him.
Who's he calling?
The FBI.
Now that we're confident
the weapon's here, we're calling
in the authorities.
Tony? My cell is down,
so is the landline.
Someone's jamming
communications.
Carl ...
It's them.
They gave me that radio;
told me they'd be
contacting me.
Answer the call. Just play along.
Carl ...
Answer the call.
Hello?
Where are you?
I didn't think you were coming.
You're late.
Well, we're here now
and we're waiting.
Okay.
They're at the front gate.
Put your belt back on.
I want you
to resume your post.
Pretend like
everything's normal.
Just let them in.
And then what?
We're going to follow them
as soon as they pick up
their container;
once we're past
the jamming grid, we'll make our call.
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
You're a part
of this, Carl,
whether you want
to be or not.
You became a part of it this
the second you said
"yes" to these people.
Jack!
What do you got?
I got three vehicles.
Eight hostiles,
heavily armed; got to assume
there's more inside the trucks.
Carl, if you don't
open that gate, they're going
to come in here looking
you, you understand me?
Let me put it to you this way.
These men have killed
over 300 people today.
If they get ahold
of that weapon,
they're going to make that
look like child's play.
You've only got one choice here.
I just open the gate
and let them in.
That's all you've got to do.
And you guys got my back, right?
Yeah.
Promise me.
I promise you.
Okay.
Tony, get
the surveillance package.
Don't worry.
It's just so we can hear
what's going on.
Turn around.
I need to put
this on your back.
Listen, the money--
it wasn't about
greed or anything.
It's my wife, Linda.
She's having twins.
They say it's the most natural
thing in the world, right?
Getting pregnant?
Well, it took us three years,
cost an arm and a leg.
No excuses, but insurance
doesn't cover a dime.
I just always wanted
to have a family.
You know what I mean?
Put this in your pocket.
You got him?
Yeah.
Remember, it's just another
day at the office.
You're going
to be fine.
Let's go.
What took you
so long, Carl?
You got the routing
documents?
Sure.
I need to see them in order
to locate the container.
Relax, Carl.
They're right here.
Okay.
Center section.
Row 36, Q-block.
It's that fourth stack
on your left.
I know where
the container is, Carl.
Did you disable
the security cameras?
They've been off
since 10:00,
just like you said.
How's your wife?
She's fine.
You didn't tell her anything
about this, did you?
No, of course not.
Did you tell anybody else?
No, no, why would I?
You tell me, Carl.
Why are you so nervous?
Okay, um, you want
to know the truth, Mr. Stokes?
Uh... I was expecting
a simple pickup,
but you show up
with a small army here, and, um...
And what?
It's just... not what-what I
was expecting, that's all.
I just don't want
to get caught.
Nobody's gonna
get caught, Carl.
Let's go,
we're moving.
You too, Carl,
take a ride.
I told you, it's the
fourth stack on your left.
Q-block, row 36.
I'd feel better
if you showed us.
I really should stay here,
Mr. Stokes.
I got to finish
my patrol.
Why, Carl?
You expecting
somebody?
No.
Then get in.
Okay.
Damn it.
Forget about him, Jack.
He was dead the minute
he stepped out that door.
You and I
both know that.
Ethan, I just came
to say how sorry I am.
Well, I appreciate the courtesy
if not the sincerity.
As much as I may feel this
is what's best for my mother,
on a personal level
I'm sorry you have
to go through this...
and for some
of the harsher things
I said to you
in anger.
Well, I suppose I owe
you an apology, too,
for accusing you
of leaking my role
in this Bauer fiasco
to the press.
I really believed you were
trying to blindside me.
Considering the impression I
gave you, I'm not surprised.
Olivia,
as someone who's known you
most of your life,
I'd like to offer
some advice.
Of course.
Ambition can be
a valuable quality
here in Washington
as well as in life,
but unchecked, it can be
unhealthy, if not dangerous.
What I'm trying
to say is...
you got yourself a seat
at the president's table.
She listens
to you.
But running a country
is not like running
a campaign.
It's not about doing
whatever it takes to win.
It's about doing what's right
for the American people.
Sometimes those things
aren't mutually exclusive.
Well...
good-bye, Olivia.
Good-bye.
Hello.
It's Olivia.
You can go with that story now,
Ken, and it just got better.
Tell me.
Ethan Kanin's resigning.
What happened?
I thought the plan was
to let him twist
in the wind
for a while.
His hand was forced.
Thank you.
It seems Jack Bauer
just murdered
Senator Mayer.
What?
You're kidding me.
Anybody else have this yet?
Not yet, it's all yours
in time for the 11:00.
Told you I'd take
care of you, didn't I?
You are too good
to me, Olivia.
You just hold
up your end.
Make sure Kanin's
the fall guy.
My mother is nowhere near this,
understand?
No problem.
She really doesn't have any idea
that you're the leak?
No, and it'd better stay
that way.
She won't hear it from me.
When are we having that dinner
you promised?
Maybe next week.
It's always
next week.
You'd better get to work
if you're going to make
that broadcast.
Preliminary ballistics.
So these files on the computer--
presumably
Senator Mayer was looking
at 'em before
he was killed?
Someone was, sir.
They were opened
and viewed
within the last hour.
So if the sen...
if the senator was killed
point-blank
in the entry hall,
how are we explaining the slugs
in the door frame
and the railing?
I don't know, sir.
Get the crime lab guys on it.
Yes, sir.
Agent Walker,
it's Larry Moss for you.
Hello.
Senator Mayer is dead.
Where's Jack?
Don't know;
we don't have him.
Okay, but what, you think
that he did this, Larry?
First Burnett
and now Mayer?
Well...
it looks that way.
What do you mean
"looks that way"?
Well, that's why I'm calling.
Senator Mayer
was killed with a UMP
40 submachine gun.
If Bauer was on the run,
where'd he get ahold
of a weapon like that?
Also, there's evidence
to suggest that the, uh--
there was a third party
in the house
when the senator was killed.
What kind of evidence?
Unexplained slugs...
...a broken set
of French doors,
a chair where it doesn't belong.
Okay, so are you saying that
this third party killed Mayer?
Well, you know, Renee,
I might be saying that
if I knew what the hell
Bauer was doing here
in the first place.
All right, Renee, listen.
I want to meet you
halfway, I do,
but if you expect me
to even entertain
Bauer's innocence,
you have got to help me here.
I can't, Larry.
If Jack is still underground,
he is underground for a reason.
There were files open
on Mayer's computer--
documents relating to his
investigation into Starkwood.
All right, so just tell
me that, tell me that.
Did Starkwood ever come up in
your conversation with Bauer?
Renee.
Look, maybe, maybe I should
have trusted you before, okay,
but you have got
to trust me now.
What role does Starkwood play
in all this?
The man who framed Jack
for Burnett's murder was John
Quinn, a Starkwood contractor.
Jack believes that
they were behind Juma
and all of the
terrorist attacks today.
He went to Mayer to get
the evidence to prove it.
I have to assume that
Quinn followed him there.
That's all that I
know, Larry, I swear.
Okay, I believe you.
Thank you.
Just sit tight,
I'll be in touch soon.
Well, let me help, Larry.
I mean, Jack could still be
out there.
He may be in trouble.
No, no, I can't release you,
not yet.
Reese, what's the status?
Just getting the chassis on,
sir, I'll be a minute.
Hurry it up.
Hold up, hold up,
I don't have my truck.
Put it down there,
I want it there.
Mitch, get up there.
Let's run a diagnostic now.
I want to be
ready to roll
as soon as Reese gets
here with that flatbed.
Yes, sir.
All right, there's the package.
We should get back to the car.
We want to be in position
to follow that container
once they move out.
Jack.
Just give me one second.
Cooper.
Now's as good a time
as any
to settle up with Carl.
Yes, sir.
Thanks, Carl.
Good luck.
Let's go.
Where we going?
Your money's in my truck,
just one aisle over.
Come On.
Jack, we should
get going.
No.
What are you doing?
I thought you said
the money was
in the truck.
What the hell's going on?
Just keep moving.
Listen, I don't know
what Stokes told you,
but I didn't tell a soul.
Damn it, Jack,
what the hell are you doing?
Don't do it.
You're gonna turn a surveillance
job into a firefight.
It'll be two against ten.
Two against nine.
Right, and we lose
our best chance
at getting
this weapon.
Don't break
your own rules.
You may save
one man,
but what about the thousands
of people
who could die
in a biological attack?
Is this about you,
Jack, or about them?
You want to prevent
another disaster
or ensure that it's going
to happen?
That's far enough.
Turn around.
You're going to kill me,
you're going to have
to look me in the eye.
Okay.
Damn it.
Thank you, thank you.
We've got about 30 seconds
before they figure out
what happened.
Okay, what's our fallback?
Steal the truck.
Strong?
I'll make the direct assault,
you cover the east flank.
All we need is
a big enough firefight
to get one of us
behind the wheel.
You ready?
Yeah.
Go.
How do we look?
Diagnostics check out, sir.
The package is stable.
Good.
All right,
let's get her on the chassis!
Cooper, come on.
Let's roll.
Cooper, do you copy?
Dolen.
Check the next
aisle over.
Find Cooper.
Hold your position.
Wait for my signal.
Cooper's down, Cooper's down.
Code red, code red!
Let's move out... Greer.
Engage... engage.
Reese, get the truck
out of here now!
Go, go, go!
Tony!
The truck-- I'm going after it.
Cover me now!
Two shooters--
fan out and find them.
Tony, this is Jack--
do you copy?
Drop it.
Tony?
I know you.
You're on Emerson's crew.
You're Almeida, right?
I know Bauer's with you.
Now, where is he?
Larry Moss.
- Larry, it's Jack.
- Jack, where the hell have you been?
I need you
to scramble multiple teams
to a weigh station on
Highway 236, exit 29.
I'm in a big rig about
ten miles south.
What's going on?
You also need to send
a CDC recovery unit.
Why?
I'm in possession of
a biological weapon
interdicted at the
Port of Alexandria.
A biological weapon?
Larry, just listen to me.
I don't care if you arrest me.
I don't care if you shoot me.
Just get your teams
out here.
I fully expect
to be pursued by hostiles.
Starkwood?
How do you know
about Starkwood?
I talked to Renee.
And I saw what was
on Mayer's computer.
Larry, they're coming
after this weapon.
You can count on it.
Now, be advised, I believe
that Tony Almeida
is being held hostage.
All right, I'll call out
an interagency alert.
We'll secure both locations.
Larry, hurry.
Damn it!
Sir, this is Stokes.
What's your status?
The package is secure--
we're inbound.
What about Bauer?
He's at the scene, sir,
but he sought cover nearby.
Well, we have to assume
that he contacted
the authorities,
so we better be on
an accelerated timetable.
Get over here.
It will be there
in ten minutes.
We're right behind.
Good.
I've got teams on the ground
prepping for your arrival.
Larry Moss.
Larry, it's Jack.
I'm still on Route 236,
but I had to stop
approximately seven miles
before the weigh station.
Jack, I got two units
moving to you right now.
Yeah, well, you're gonna
have to redirect them.
Why?
Starkwood reacquired
the bioweapon.
They managed
to access
one of the dock's
freight helicopters.
While they had me pinned down,
they airlifted the freight
right out of here.
They were headed due west
from my current position.
West... they got
a large military facility
in that area.
Okay, good--
redirect the teams there.
Jack, I can't assault
a private compound
unless I have proof
that a weapon exists.
Okay, where's the CDC?
They're scrambling a team
right now.
Send them to me.
You'll have
all the proof you need.
Jack, what happened?
One of the canisters
was breached
during the interdiction.
Some of the bio-agent
was released.
I...
I was exposed.
Okay.
Jack, just sit tight.
CDC's on the way.
They're going to be there soon.
presented by:
... ::: www.SubCentral.de ::: ...
&
Bierdopje.com