Everything that's happened today, from
the infected body to Salazar's prison break,
has been part of an elaborate sting operation.
Some Ukrainian scientists were trying to sell
a weaponized virus on the open market.
I suggested the Salazars as potential buyers.
Our goal was to remove
the virus stockpile from the marketplace.
But all of this hinged on me convincing
the Salazars that I had switched sides.
Tell me how the man who betrayed us
is now our friend.
Bauer came to me with an opportunity to
make more money than we ever dreamed of.
- What's in it for you, Jack?
- 15 million dollars.
I would never have thought
that Jack Bauer was for sale.
You said you'd take me away from here.
Do you remember, Jack?
Yes, I remember.
There was one small thing
you forgot to mention - you were a cop.
Even that wouldn't matter
if you'd meant what you said to me.
I meant everything I ever said to you.
For the next few hours, all of our resources
are dedicated to helping Jack get this virus.
Tony, I spoke to Chase.
He's not coming back to CTU.
- He still thinks my father was captured.
- And he thinks he's going in to rescue Jack.
Dammit, he'll blow Jack's cover
and we'll lose this virus.
I know this man. He's Bauer's partner.
- What the hell's going on, Jack?
- Shut up. You shouldn't have followed me.
- You're with them?
- Yes, I'm with them.
- Jack?
- Shut up, Chase.
You wanna get through this, just shut up!
- The transponder on Jack's watch went dead.
- Dammit!
By the time the assault teams are in position,
we'll have no idea where he is.
The president will make a brief statement.
There will be no questions at this time.
My fellow Americans, good evening.
A few hours ago
I had to terminate a presidential debate
in order to handle what was at the time
a national security threat.
I can't reveal to you at this time
the details surrounding the situation.
Those will be forthcoming
in the next few hours.
Let me assure you that the danger
that existed a few hours ago has passed.
America is safe.
The American people are safe.
I apologize to my opponent, Senator Keeler,
and to the millions of you expecting
to see the two of us engage in the issues.
The debate will be rescheduled.
I'd like to thank you all for your patience
and understanding. Good night.
Mr President...
There are rumors that this crisis was
manufactured to protect Dr Anne Packard.
How do you respond to that, sir?
Those allegations were false.
Senator Keeler's charges were unfounded
and we have proof.
Proof that comes directly
from Anne Packard's ex-husband.
In fact, in the next few weeks, Senator Keeler
will have his own explaining to do.
Anne Packard
is an individual of the utmost integrity.
- She didn't deserve this.
- Mr President...
Thank you, ladies and gentlemen.
That's it. No more questions.
Bauer's with the Salazar brothers in Mexico.
His transponder signal stopped working.
We're doing all we can to re-establish contact.
Tell the Delta units to hold their position.
All right, thanks.
- Let's try an amplification module.
- I cycled through it three times.
- It's not a weak signal, there's no signal.
- What do we think happened here?
Jack's cover might have been blown.
There's no indication his transponder's
been found or his cover blown.
Maybe he can't get a signal
or the transponder's broken.
Damage might have knocked it
to another frequency.
- Let's run a scan.
- I am.
I'm a third of the way through the spectrum,
but so far no luck.
All right, I'll get you some help.
- Kim?
- Yes, Tony?
- Do you know how to do a frequency scan?
- Yeah.
We want to pick up
your father's transponder signal.
Michelle's begun it. Coordinate with her.
- What's the signature?
- I already told you, 30 over five.
You didn't tell me.
Look, Kim, I know this is hard on you,
your father's life being at stake.
- But I need you to focus, OK?
- Sorry.
All right, good. Call me if anything changes.
Why are we stopping?
Tomás says there's no sign
of anyone following.
Until we know more,
we're better off staying here.
Could he have come here on his own,
without backup?
Maybe he came by himself to rescue you.
How sad.
Does it bother you that your partner's
going to die trying to save you?
It breaks me up.
This man Amador should have called
to set up the meeting.
He's gonna call.
Make sure you've got your money ready.
The money's ready.
- Yeah?
- It's Amador.
- We're ready.
- Where?
Put Bauer on the phone.
I only deal with him.
- This is Jack.
- Hello, Jack.
Five kilometers north of town,
a trail splits off the road into the woods.
- Take it for two kilometers, 15 minutes.
- Got it.
The meeting's north of here. 15 minutes.
Hey, wait. The phone.
- What if he calls back?
- I'll take a message.
Look at you, Jack. You are a mess.
- We gotta get you straight.
- I'm not gonna fix.
Take them. You'll feel better.
I need to use the bathroom.
They're in the back.
- I want you to get some sleep.
- I'm not tired.
I'll wake you when it's time to leave.
- Where's Hector?
- He's busy.
You'll see him tomorrow morning.
Go to sleep.
I love you.
Claudia, stay down, stay down.
I need you to listen to me.
Hector and Ramón are trying to buy a virus
to use as a weapon.
Millions of people could die.
I've set up this deal so my government
can destroy the virus. Do you understand?
- You're still with CTU?
- Yes, I'm still with CTU.
But you broke Ramón out of prison.
So I could gain his trust,
to make the deal happen.
I cannot allow this virus
to get into the wrong hands.
You betrayed us once.
Now you'll betray us again?
- No, them, not you.
- I was a fool to believe any of it.
"I'm going to protect you,
get your family somewhere safe." All lies.
I wanted to come back for you earlier.
When I heard about this virus,
I had to deal with it.
Millions of lives are at stake.
You have to understand that.
But I can get you out now.
You, Sergio and your father.
- How?
- American soldiers are not far from here.
They're waiting for my signal. I can't reach
them because my transmitter's destroyed.
Claudia, I have nothing to gain
from telling you this if it's not the truth.
One word from you and I'm a dead man.
What do you want me to do?
First I need a cellphone.
I need to let CTU know where I am.
Then I need you to do whatever you can
to help my partner Chase. Keep him alive.
- When Hector realizes, he's gonna kill me.
- You'll be gone by then.
Chase can help you get out. I promise.
But if I can't contact CTU, this is all
for nothing. You've gotta get me that phone.
- Please.
- I'll do what I can.
I have to go.
They're waiting for me.
If you're lying to me again, I'll kill you myself.
Help Chase.
Jack Bauer broke Ramón out of prison.
Your people are sending forces
to bring them back.
When are they coming?
When?
And where?
Get Ramón.
Aargh!
He was your partner.
You must be feeling something.
I got a 15-million-dollar payday
when this deal goes down. He's on his own.
Is he as tough as you?
He still believes in the lie.
- What lie?
- That what he's doing has purpose.
Belief is a beautiful thing.
Hello.
- Where are you going?
- Please.
- No, don't leave.
- No.
- Mi amor.
- Sit down for a minute.
Ramón is waiting, OK?
All right. All right.
Claudia.
- I left my phone inside.
- I'll get it.
Let's go.
- Chloe, have you heard from Chase?
- No.
Are there alternate frequencies
he might use to contact you?
Yeah, and they're on autoscan.
He hasn't checked in.
I know you're busy.
Maybe we can reach him by satellite.
Satellite. I didn't think of that
I'll get right on that.
You don't have to be sarcastic with me.
This is someone I care about.
Get a grip.
I have to update the president.
I don't wanna tell him
we're still in the same place - nowhere.
I don't want excuses.
Just get me the answer, all right?
- I need to finalize the com file.
- It should have been done.
I need the format code.
You said you'd download it.
- Delta-733-Golf.
- That's the code from the previous file.
Delta-723-Bravo.
- Thank you.
- All right.
- Did you get it?
- Yeah, I got it.
Eight minutes shot to hell on an invalid code.
Access granted.
That could have been a disaster. Without
those files, we can't track the rescue teams.
Come.
Bad news. CTU lost track of Jack Bauer.
- Is he in trouble?
- We don't know.
- Does he have the virus yet?
- We don't know that either.
Come.
Mr President,
I have Alan Milliken on the line for you.
I'll take it.
- Alan?
- David.
- You angry with me?
- Of course I'm not angry with you.
Your first time in LA in three years
and you don't even call.
- It's been a bad day, Alan.
- I know. I've been watching the news.
I don't want to add to your burdens,
but I'd like to come by and see you.
- See me?
- David, I wouldn't ask if it weren't important.
I know you're busy. After all,
you are the President of the United States.
In large part, thanks to you.
I'll come to you, Alan.
I'll be there in 15 minutes.
Thank you, David. And one more thing.
As a personal favor to me,
I'm asking you not to bring Wayne.
- May I ask why?
- It's something I'd rather explain in person.
All right.
Where are we?
So far we've been unable to pick up Jack
on any of our imagery.
How long we been out of contact?
His tracking beacon went dead
27 minutes ago.
- Last known location?
- Here.
He can't be much farther
than 30 miles in any direction.
- Unless he was choppered out.
- No way. Air Tactical's watching the skies.
Where's Bauer?
We don't know yet.
That's great.
This entire operation, which hinges on Jack
being on site when they deliver the virus,
is going down the tubes
because we don't know where he is.
- How does that happen?
- Ryan, you want to chew us out, do it later.
- We're trying to get this back on track.
- I will.
You better find Bauer
and make this thing work.
Otherwise, the two of you and Jack,
assuming he's still alive,
are gonna take the fall for everything today.
From the prison riot to Salazar's escape
and every dead body in between.
So what happens
if Jack goes to this meeting without backup?
The Salazars get the virus.
What happens from there?
I don't know.
Feeling better?
I'm fine.
Amador.
Hello, Jack. So these must be the buyers
you're representing.
This is Hector and Ramón Salazar.
There's 100 million dollars in escrow
accounts in Geneva and Hong Kong.
We'll give instructions
to have the money transferred
when we have confirmation
that the virus has been delivered.
There's been a complication.
Another buyer's interested in the virus.
- What? We have a deal.
- What's going on, Jack?
I had nothing to do with it.
This is a new development
that's surfaced in the last few hours.
We'll auction the virus to the highest bidder.
- You son of a bitch!
- No!
Mr Salazar,
I merely represent the wishes of my client.
- May we have a moment?
- Of course.
Hector, this does not need to be a problem.
- It's a huge problem.
- Think it through.
Add 50 million dollars to this price tag
and you're still looking
at over an 800-million-dollar profit.
You said you could move the virus
for a billion dollars, right?
- Something like that.
- You've come this far. Don't stop.
Let it play out.
The other buyer's here.
You know her?
What the hell is he doing here?
- That man is a federal agent.
- I know who he is, Nina.
- Everything's fine.
- It's not. He's setting us up.
You have to kill him. Kill him!
The first man who fires gets cut down.
That's a promise.
- Why is he here?
- He represents a buyer, Nina, just like you.
No, he doesn't. Believe me, I know him.
Whatever's he's told you, he's lying.
I don't work for CTU any more, Nina.
I work for myself.
- I'm out of here.
- Nina, please.
Let her go and honor the original agreement.
Nina, I don't think
your client's gonna be too happy
if you walk out
and let the virus go to another buyer.
We gotta close this deal.
We have a wide perimeter
and we're monitoring every frequency.
There's no law or military
within 25 kilometers.
You know how I work.
This area's completely secure.
If I had the slightest doubt, I wouldn't be here.
I suggest we all take a few minutes
to calm ourselves.
And I'll explain the ground rules
and we'll proceed with the bids.
Agreed?
Agreed.
-  Fine.
- Good.
- David.
- Alan, it's good to see you.
- Thanks for finding the time to fit me in.
- You've always made time for me, Alan.
Even when there was
no obvious reason to do so.
Your potential was always obvious, David.
- How are you doing?
- I could use a few new body parts.
- But besides that...
- You look well.
I know you're wondering what could be
so important that I'd ask you here.
So I'll be brief and I'll be blunt.
I want your brother off the team.
I don't understand.
You were supportive of Wayne.
I was. I'm not any more.
What's this all about, Alan?
- Yes, sir?
- Tell my wife to come in here.
Right away, sir.
- Julia.
- Mr President.
David is wondering
why I want him to fire Wayne.
And I thought you should explain.
As you know,
I've known Wayne for some time.
Three years ago,
when he was president of Alan's company,
we began to spend
quite a bit of time together.
Get to it, Julia.
Wayne and I became involved.
They had an affair
while I was recuperating from the stroke.
That's how your brother thanked me.
Go on.
We saw each other for a year, before
you asked him to join your administration.
- Then we broke it off.
- Hold on.
- If you knew, why didn't you say something?
- I didn't.
I just found out recently.
Did you know, David?
Did you keep it from me too?
Of course not.
- I can hardly even believe it's true.
- It's true.
- I've told you how sorry I am.
- You can go.
I waited for you to come to Los Angeles
so I could do this face to face.
I gave your brother my company
and he took my wife.
Now I'm taking away his job.
Wayne is my chief of staff, my closest friend.
- I trust him.
- I don't. Neither should you. He's dishonest.
I think you'll agree, David,
that you wouldn't be where you are
without my support over the years.
I've never asked you for anything in return,
but I'm asking you now.
Fire Wayne.
I'm sorry, Alan, I can't do that.
I'm disappointed, but not surprised.
You know me well enough
not to be surprised by repercussions.
I hope you're not threatening me.
I don't make threats, David.
I just tell it like it is.
You let me know if you change your mind.
Have them open up the field search
to these coordinates. Tell them it's priority.
Sorry, I don't mean to interrupt,
but can I see you for a minute?
Do you have enough to go on?
I'll let you know
if the satellite guys give me trouble.
- What is it?
- It's actually about Tony.
Look, I don't know if he's...
You don't know if he's what?
I don't know if he's well enough to do his job.
He was shot a few hours ago.
He's not gonna be working at full capacity.
I know,
but what if he misses something important?
- I mean, he's running things.
- What happened?
He asked me to finalize the com files,
but he forgot to give me the format codes.
And he chewed me out for forgetting
something he thought he told me,
except he never told me.
He's under a lot of stress. We all are.
That's my point.
Michelle, you're his wife,
but you're also second in command.
If Tony can't do the job,
somebody has to tell Chappelle,
and I think that someone should be you.
- What are you doing?
- Taking a rest.
There's oil under Hector's truck.
It needs to be fixed before Hector gets back.
Now!
OK, I'll check it out.
Here. I have a message from Jack.
Can you hear me?
Things aren't what they seem.
Jack isn't really with Ramón and Hector.
Everything he's done
has been to earn their trust.
The virus they're going to buy, Jack is going
to take it from them. Do you understand?
There are soldiers from your country nearby.
- They'll come when Jack calls for them.
- Claudia?
Jack promised to get me and my family
out of here if I help you.
- Then help me.
- I can't now. There are too many men around.
Don't give up. I'll figure out a way, all right?
Each party will make one final bid in writing.
Amador wants to start
in the next ten minutes.
You have to come up with a number.
We are offering 100. She must have
made him an offer to make this worthwhile.
- Say another 50.
- So we go 175.
More. If we do this, we do it to win.
At least 200.
Make the calls.
Who is she?
- I told you, she worked for me at CTU.
- No.
There's more between you and this woman.
She killed my wife.
Is this going to be a problem, Jack?
No.
No problem.
- Where are we going?
- We'll be together.
We're together now.
Is Hector coming?
- Sergio, just be ready to leave.
- What about Hector...
Sergio, forget about Hector!
Just do what I'm telling you!
What are you going to do?
Jack said if I help his partner
he'll get us out of here, Papa.
These people - Ramón, Hector, Jack Bauer -
you can't trust any of them.
Jack's not like Ramón and Hector.
Papa, please,
this is our chance to get out of here.
Then go.
No.
No, we're all going.
No, I'm not going without you.
What about Landsat Alpha-39?
Yeah. That's about it, right? Thanks.
I checked the NSA logs. There's no satellites
in the area we think Jack's in.
I'll check the flight paths just in case.
Just in case what? I just checked it.
There have been other mistakes today, Tony.
Mistakes? That you think I made?
Sweetheart,
you should still be in the hospital.
- You should step down.
- I'm fine.
- After what you've been through...
- I just said I'm fine.
End of discussion, please.
Tony, I've got something. NSA has
a satellite we may be able to reposition.
We just have to ask for access.
- All right, thanks.
- Yeah.
... also I'd like to redo that email
and determine how best to use
these resources for this compressed divert.
As for the information packets,
they have online synoptic...
- Yes?
- I need to talk to you, Ryan.
- I think it's best...
- Hold on.
I don't think Tony should be here.
My understanding is
he's not in imminent danger.
No, it's not that.
I've had reports he's been forgetful.
Missing things.
- Like what?
- Key information. Format codes.
Things that are causing delays.
On any other day I wouldn't be worried about
this, but I'm not sure if he's up to it today.
If I pull him now, that sets us back too.
No one can replace what he does.
He, Gael and Jack
have been working this from the beginning.
- If you think his mistakes are significant...
- I do.
Or else I wouldn't be bringing this to you.
All right. Just let me wrap up this call
and I'll get into it.
Thank you.
- You need to make it happen.
- We're working on it, sir.
All right. Thanks.
I just got back from seeing Alan.
- What did he want?
- I think you know.
- Know what, David?
- He wants me to fire you.
What the hell were you thinking,
carrying on an affair with a married woman?
- The wife of my biggest supporter.
- Listen, I am sorry.
- But it was a mistake and I corrected it.
- Not in Alan's mind.
For him, this is fresh.
He just found out
and he wants to make you pay.
We both know you can't afford
to make an enemy out of Alan.
He wields too much power, so I'll resign.
You'll leave only if I decide
it's the right thing to do, not Alan Milliken.
David, Alan is a very dirty fighter, trust me.
Sure you want to get down
in the gutter with him?
You haven't left me much choice, have you?
- You want to see me, Ryan?
- Yeah.
What's going on?
I asked you here because your competency
has been brought into question.
By whom?
By me.
- An employee had some concerns...
- An employee?
Kim Bauer.
I felt I needed to address them.
With Ryan? You didn't come to me first?
- I tried to talk to you.
- That's enough.
The point is, Ryan, that they're wrong.
I am fit for duty, completely.
All right. When you entered the room,
the monitor was on.
Tell me what it showed.
On the left side
was a C-TAN schematic of the country,
indicating an ongoing investigation
in Florida, New York and Montana.
On the right side was an all-clear report
from the Austin branch.
That's correct. But it still doesn't ease
my mind considering the slips you made.
- What slips?
- Michelle?
You thought you gave Kim the signature
on the frequency scans. You didn't.
Not verbally, no.
I put them on her in-screen
15 minutes before I talked to her.
Anything else?
She said you didn't load the format codes
onto the grid in time.
No, I didn't load the format codes
onto her grid.
I put them in the shared volume, on time.
Check it.
It's there.
All right. I'm sorry, Tony.
- We're done here.
- Good.
You've wasted time we don't have.
Are you ready with your bids?
- Yes.
Let me see them.
The banks will verify
the presence of these funds?
Yes, that is correct.
The bank will verify those as well.
Your bid is 225 million dollars.
Hers is 240.
Nina, you win.
You are a dead man.
My people will escort you out.
The transfer will take place in two hours.
You said would deliver the virus
and you didn't.
Not now, Hector. Come on.
I'll be contacting you with the details.
Excellent. We'll be waiting for your call.
Let's go.
You can't let Nina Myers just walk away.
Put a man on her.
- Shut up.
- Ramón, listen to me.
If Nina gets away she'll disappear.
You'll never find her again.
You had your chance, Jack.
All right. This is good enough.
- Ramón, please. You're making a mistake.
- Get out.
- Look, I can explain. I didn't know that...
- Get out!
You're of no use to us any more! You failed!
Hector, don't do this!
Ramón, think this through.
What about your buyers around the world
that you promised the virus to?
They'll know you were double-crossed and
did nothing about it. What will you tell them?
"I'm sorry,
we'll try and get it right next time?"
The Salazar name will be a joke.
You can't let that happen.
Come on!
Five hours ago you were in prison.
Now you're free because I broke you out!
Then I brought you the deal of a lifetime.
What do I have to do
to prove to you I'm on your side?
This deal can still happen.
We can get the virus.
- How do you get the virus?
- I told you.
- The woman, Nina.
- The woman? She's the problem.
- She outbid us.
- I know her. I trained her. I can get to her.
- You don't even know how to find her!
- I'll find her!
Please, Ramón. You can't lose here.
If I fail, you get to kill me. Fine.
But if I succeed, the deal will go forward.
We'll be back on track. We'll all get paid!
Please.
Hector, let's play this out a little longer.
The man has more lives than a cat.