-=http://sfile.ydy.com=-
proudly presents
sync:ßÇÈâÈâ »ğ¼ı¼ı
Season07 Episode07
Previously on 24...
That was bob cornell at nsa.
They've detected
another firewall breach.
There's been another attack?
Not yet, but they believe the
cip device is being utilized.
We have to assume dubaku is
initiating another attack.
Madam president.
What is it, tim?
I've just been forwarded
a scrambled call.
It's from colonel dubaku he's
demanding to speak with you.
The deadline for your forces to
begin their withdrawal has passed.
Go to the window. See
what you have done.
Comply with my demands within the
hour, or 10,000 more americans will die.
She's on her way up.
I'll call you when it's done.
Mr. Taylor, are you okay?
audio forensics cleaned
up the recording.
Walker is extraneous.
Kill her before you get here.
Larry, I don't think it's
worth it. There's nothing here.
All righT. Fine, help
janis coordinate with nsa.
I'm sorry about renee.
She was a good agent.
We don't know that she's dead yet!
I've devoted my life to the bureau
and you just expect me to believe that
the entire government's been corrupted.
Not all of them.
But until we find out
who, we can't trust anyone.
And the four of you really
think you can stop this?
We have to. It's as simple as that.
Dubaku wants you and your
wife. That's the deal.
You're asking us to risk our lives
to be delivered into dubaku's hands.
Listen to him, ule.
But how can we trust this man?
Because he has no reason to lie.
How are you doing, tony?
All right. Where's emerson?
He's dead.
You want matobo or not?
you got what you came for.
Now, get the hell out of here.
Did everything go smoothly?
We have the matobos,
that's what matters.
I heard about the planes on the radio.
The white house still has not complied.
What do you intend to do?
Exactly what we promised.
We're ready, sir.
Where's the target located?
Kidron, ohio.
Population?
Begin.
********
Larry.
We think this is the truck
the matobos were abducted in.
Where was this image taken?
Near northwoods airfield.
Were you able to track it?
Not beyond this sector. But they
were heading east on mckinley avenue.
All right. Make sure the vehicle I.D.Is
disseminated to all search teams and local agencies.
Yes, sir.
- Larry, I think I found something.
- Yeah?
I've been working nsa, trying to back-trace
the cip attack that took down the two planes.
And I found a code fragment which I think
could be residue from the cip intrusion.
I'm running a pattern match right now.
With any luck at all, we may be able to anticipate
where in the infrastructure they're targeting next.
And I need sean.
Janis, I don't want to waste
personnel on some wild-goose chase.
Dubaku's threatened to kill 10,000
more americans in the next 30 minutes.
I understand that, and I will
drop it the minute it feels cold.
All right, I'm going to brief the
white house. Keep me in the loop.
Sean.
Are you sure he's up to
running this operation?
- Larry's fine.
- Is he?
You're the one who told
me about him and renee.
This has got to be
hitting him pretty hard.
If I don't think larry can do his
job, I'll let you know, all right?
In the meantime, I need you
to open up a fresh socket.
You've reached agent brian gedge.
Please leave a message
and I'll get bk to you.
agent gedge, I expected
to hear from you by now.
It's urgent that I speak with the
first gentleman as soon as possible.
call me back, agent gedge.
This is extremely important.
Yes?
Larry moss with the fbi.
Where are we, larry?
We've I.D.'D a vehicle that we believe
was used in the matobos' abduction.
We're still trying to track it down.
And how long is that going to take?
I wish I could tell you, sir.
I don't have a time frame.
That's not good enough, larry.
Unless you get some results,
we're going to get hit again.
A lot of people are going to
die if you don't find dubaku.
With all respect, sir, I don't
need to be told what's at stake.
We're giving everything we can.
One of our agents has given her life.
Yes, I was told about
that. I'M... I'm sorry.
- I'll call you the minute we have something.
- We'll be waiting.
God...
The matobos have been
taken into a building.
546 adams.
- Okay, pull up the stats on that address.
- On it.
It's the ritter building,
four stories high.
The building is two years old.
- Give me the security specs.
- Give me a minute.
We're coming up on it.
I'm going to need your help.
I see you've chosen a target.
The boyd chemical
plant near kidron, ohio.
The cip device has enabled us
to take control of the main tank.
We're about to cause the
primary safety valves to fail.
Do you remember the last
time we saw each other, ule?
It was at a state
dinner in your residence.
We shared an excellent bottle of wine.
I offered my hand in
friendship and you...
slapped it away.
You gave me an ultimatum-- to
be the puppet for your military.
You could have had a long and
prosperous career as prime minister.
But now you're going back to
sangala as a traitor to your people.
I am prime minister.
I was elected by the people.
It's you and juma who are the traitors.
No.We brought order to sangala,
but you are trying to destroy
everything that we've built.
You'll be taken back to sangala, ule,
and you will give general juma the
names of all your fellow traitors.
I will never do that. Never.
believe me, you will.
Take them.
Any response from the president?
Not yet.
But once she sees dead americans lying
in the street, she will be less stubborn.
I'm inside, jack,
approaching the front desk.
Copy that.
Are the motobos still
on the third floor?
Affirmative, jack. They're being
moved. I'm just not sure where yet.
Copy that.
Good afternoon.
I'm agent walker with the fbi.
I don't have an appointment, but I'm here
to see mr. Roane of roane and associates.
- I'll let them know you're here.
- Actually, I don't want to be announced.
I'm here on official business.
All right.
So as far as you're concerned,
I was never here, understand?
Yes, ma'am.
Past security. Heading
toward the elevator.
We're on our way to
the service entrance.
Chloe, I'm on the third floor.
Law firm is on your left.
On your right is a suite of
offices where matobo's being held.
I see it.
Stairwell's down the
hallway to your left.
agent walker, we're at the door.
There's one guard outside
the suite, probably armed.
Bill, take the third
floor. Wait for my signal.
Go on.
Chloe, we're on the fourth floor in what
used to be the computer room. What now?
In the center of the room
there are two removable panels.
This should give you
access to the crawlspace.
Copy that.
Okay, we're clear. Let's go.
We're in.
I should never have
allowed you to come with me.
It was a mistake.
It was not your decision, ule.
We will be all right.
Jack bauer will be here soon.
Okay. We're at the heating unit.
Okay, jack, there's an airduct
leading off that unit; do you see it?
Yeah.
Follow that for about 30 yards
until you see an electrical junction.
Make a left, then another 20
yards you'll come to the vent.
This will give you a
view of the entire floor.
And the matobos?
They've been moved into a adjacent
room just off the main area.
Okay, copy that. Come on.
The entire nsa has been combing the firewall
searching for the next cip device breach.
If this were something, don't you
think they'd already know about it?
I can live without your
negativity today, sean.
There it is again,
that same code fragment.
"Kidron, ohio." What's in kidron,
ohio? Any sensitive instaltions?
Something dubaku might want to hit?
I don't know. Homeland has a high-value
target database; I'm cross-checking it now.
Okay. Okay, nothing in kidron itself,
but in the neighboring county there'S...
- boyd chemical.
- Boyd chemical. What do they make?
Insecticide. Please get me that number.
Hello? This is janis gold at fbi.
I need to speak to your plant
manager immediately, please.
Ma'am, as I just
stated I'm with the fbi.
Does that sound vaguely
important to you?
Now, connect me to john brunner.
Fbi? Uh, yeah, put her on.
This is john brunner.
Hello. Mr. Brunner, this is
janis gold, fbi, D.C.Bureau.
What can I do for you?
We've been tracking some possible
breaches in the government firewall.
The firewall's designed to
protect installations like yours...
I know what it does, honey.
Um, we have tracked and isolated one
of these breaches in the kidron area.
I need to know are you
experiencing any problems right now?
As a matter of fact, we're
dealing with one right now.
What is it?
Three of our safety valves just
failed on the primary storage tank.
We're having trouble resetting them.
What's in that tank?
Methyl isocyanate.
It's concentrated
insecticide, highly toxic.
Can you-- what the
hell is this all about?
Mr. Brunner, I have reason to believe that
this is a terrorist attack on your facility.
Terrorist attack?
Yes, sir, I need you to initiate on-site
emergency procedures and stay on this line.
Shut down the tank.
- What's going on?
- Do it! Do it! My authority.
Damn. What is it?
- It's not responding.
- What do you mean? Try it again.
Nothing.
Pressure in the primary tank is rising.
Son of a bitch.
Mr. Brunner?
We cannot shut down the primary
tank and the pressure is building.
If we cannot stop this, we are
looking at atmospheric release.
Okay.
Get larry. Dubaku has targeted that
facility. We need to alert the president.
Mr. Brunner, you need to begin
evacuating people right now.
All right, agent moss, keep me
apprised. I'll speak to the president.
I just received an interagency alert.
The fbi just discovered
dubaku's next target.
A chemical plant, yeah. I just
got off the phone with larry moss.
I need to brief the president.
Has the first gentleman
spoken with the president?
Not yet. I talked to
agent gedge 40 minutes ago.
Mr. Taylor is the only person who can talk the
president into withdrawing our troops in sangala.
And that is our best way
to prevent this attack.
I know we need him. I'm
waiting for a call back.
The middle section's still
bothering me; read it again.
"Colonel dubaku and the juma regime have
killed "countless thousands of their own people,
"and now hundreds of
our fellow citizens.
They deserve your
prayers and your outrage."
I think the word "outrage" might be too strong
if you're trying to convey calm authority.
"Outrage" is the only word
to describe how I'm feeling,
and how every person in
this country will be feeling.
The american people deserve the truth.
Dubaku's already killed 300 americans.
God knows what else he has planned.
come in.
Could you excuse us, angela?
What is it?
The fbi believes they've detected
where the next attack will take place.
Dubaku's infiltrated a chemical
plant just outside of kidron, ohio.
He's causing the pressure on the
facility's primary tank to go critical.
If the tank erupts, over 3,000 gallons of methyl
isocyanate will be released into the atmosphere.
Given the prevailing winds, a very large,
very toxic cloud will sweep into town.
Methyl isocyanate is a
concentrated insecticide.
Even brief exposure causes severe lung
damage and chemical burns of the skin.
What's our time frame?
The tank could rupture
in less than 15 minutes.
They've begun evacuating?
We've already contacted emergency
responders on the ground in kidron.
It's just not enough
time to get everyone out.
Kidron's population's just over 30,000.
This projection says that
we could lose over 50%?
Oh, dear lord...
Right now, our only chance of stopping
this is finding dubaku and the cip device.
- You ready?
- Yeah.
Quietly.
Jack, I just intercepted an fbi alert
identifying dubaku's next target.
A chemical plant near kidron, ohio,
12 minutes from going critical.
There are 30,000 people in that
town, jack. We have to hurry.
Copy that.*****
Give me the scope out of the bag.
turning scope over to night-vision.
I don't see dubaku.
We've got nichols.
Three men with automatic weapons.
Three more over at the control
station, most likely armed.
Copy that.
That's dubaku.
We got dubaku. Chloe,
are you seeing this?
Yes. The control station looks like an
s-dart. 'S a reallypowerful processor.
It could be driving the cip device.
Copy.
Nsa's classified infrastructure team
is trying to plug the firewall breach.
Any luck so far?
None so far, but they're staying on it.
They have less than ten minutes left.
They're aware of that, sir,
but they're doing what they can.
Not now. What's going on at the plant?
I'm on with them now.
John? Did yotry flashing
the memory cards?
Three times, honey.
We're not in control
of the computer system.
I've already told my people
to get the hell out of here.
Normally, I don't allow people to call
me "honey," but we can disss thalater.
Yeah, well, it sounds like
you need to lighten up.
good, good. I'm heading
to the primary tank room.
I'm going to try to manually
release some of the pressure.
That's not going to stop it.
No, but it might buy us a few more
minutes so people can evacuate.
I've got a thousand
workers at this facility.
And I am responsible for their safety.
now look, I need you
to stay on the phone.
- I'm going to need some help.
- Absolutely. What c i do?
I don't have access to
the override schematics.
See if you can pull up the
operating procedures for tank one.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I got
it. I got it right here.
All right. Now look for the
emergency valve release sequence.
Okay. Uh, valve release.
I have it right here.
******
This, wait, this procedure is
going to release the chemical
right into the primary tank
room where you are right now.
I know that. I have respiratory gear on.
I'll be okay, just give me the sequence.
But how long will that protect you?
Don't worry about it, honey.
Uh, okay.
- Are you looking at the routing board?
- I am. Go ahead.
Set the bus switches to this
sequence from left to right:
Two.
Eight.
Seven.
Four.
Three.
Done.
The secondary flow valve should
be behind you and to your right.
I need you to turn
that clockwise please.
all right. All right, I got it.
Okay, that's one valve
down, three more to go.
Pressure inside the tank is approaching 400 psi.
How long before the tank ruptures?
Seven minutes.
We've got a problem.
What is it?
An alert.
Our hidden surveillance camera on the roof.
Almeida and bauer.
When was this taken?
20 minutes ago.
I thought you killed almeida and bauer?
Damn it!
You said this location was kept secret from everyone!
It was.
Then what are they doing here?
I don't know.
How did they find us?
I don't know!
600 psi and rising.
disengage the cip module.
Begin the offload.
What are you doing?
We're almost there.
We will continue this attack from another location.
Let's finish this.
We can handle them.
We need to get out of here now.
The cip module's disengaged,starting off load.
Hey,what the hell is that?
What the hell is that?
What's the matter?
The firewall breach just closed.
What?
What are you talking about?
No cip intrusion,the firewall is secure.
How?
Nsa?
I don't know.
Bring the cip module.
Get motobo and his wife!
Bill,we should go with the second option on the assault.
Two-prong attack.
You and tony come through the main entrance.
We'll go in from here.
Copy.
Give me the c4 out of the bag.
Go!
Move.
Move!
get the cip device!
Clear!
All clear over here!
Get dubaku?
Negative!
Jack,I've got the cip device.
It's been destroyed.
Jack,it's renee.
The motobos are safe.
I'm taking them to the van.
Copy that.
I want you and bill to do a sweep.
See if you can find dubaku.
I'll cover the south side.
John?
John,are you still there?
yeah.
John,listen to me.
The terrorists are out of the system.
Please tell me what is happening right now.
automatic shutdown mode has kicked in.
Pressure's dropping.
I think we're gonna be all right.
Okay,that's great.
Now you-you gotta get out of there right now.
john?
I can't make the door...
I'm sending the rescue team.
A rescue team is on its way.
John,please stay with me.
Stay with me.
have they found dubaku?
Still searching.
First responders are five minutes away,jack.
Copy that.
Get up.
I said get up!
They're coming.
Please don't make me do this.
I will go to your home,michael.
I'll make you wife watch as I kill your daughter,and then I will kill her.
So do as I ask.
Save your family.
Let me see your hands!
It's latham.
Where's dubaku?
I'm sorry.
cover!
Tony!
Bill!
Yeah!You all right?
Jack?
Jack,can you hear me?
Yeah,yeah,we're okay.
What happened?
Latham was wired with explosives.
We still don't have dubaku.
What?
The cip device has been destroyed.
I want you to stay with the motobos.
Make sure they're safe.
jack the police are almost here.
If you get arrested,this entire operation goes out the window.
You have to get out of there.
Copy that.
He's gone.
We need to get back to the safe house.
Let's go.
sean,this stays both nsa and homeland have no idea why the breach at the kidron plant was stopped.
They're still looking.
We're working on it here also.
Janis is coordinating with a digital forensics team that she sent over to the plant.
This doesn't make any sense.
Why...
why would dubaku suddenly stop an attack when he was minutes away from causing mass casualties?
Maybe there was a malfunction in the cip device.
No,no,I don't want maybes,all right?
I want answers.
We're doing everything we can,sir.
That's not good enough right now,is it?
I don't know what else to tell you,sir.
I know you're upset about renee,but getting angry at me is not going to make it go any faster.
If you think I'm yelling at you because of my history with agent walker,you are mistaken.
There are thousands of lives at stake here.
That's what concerns me.
Sorry,sir.
I want you and janis to work with nsa.
Find out where that cip device is being used.
If we find the device,weind dubaku.
I appreciate the call.
Thanks a lot.
Janis,larry wants you to interface with nsa.
See if you can back-trace that cip code fragment to its source.
I'll try.
Who were you talking to?
The head of the response team at the plant.
What did he say?
Facility's clean.
A trace amount of the chemical was released,but not enough to do any damage,
and the site has been secured.
That's good.
What about the plant manager?
John brunner.
Is he okay?
No.
Will you do me a favor?
It depends.
I'd like to track down mr. Brunner's family.
I was the last one to speak with him,and I feel they should know how brave he was.
I'll see what I can find.
Thank you.
Janis,before you start sending flowers,you need to find out where that cip device was being used.
I know.
I'm on it.
Cleanup crews are already on site and we're continuing our evacuation of a one-mile radius around the chemical plant.
Casualties?
There was,in fact,one casualty,the plant manager.
13 other workers are being treated for chemical burns and inhalation of toxic fumes.
And there haven't been any other intrusions in the firewall?
No,ma'am.
It appears the crisis has been averted.
Except that no one's been able to explain how the firewall break disengaged.
Not yet.
The fbi has no idea how it happened...
it just happened.
And that's not an explanation.
Perhaps dubaku was firing another warning shot.
No,dubaku's already down two planes.
He's not afraid to take more lives.
In any event,we should be grateful.
I'm not one to accept good news unless I know where it comes from.
Until we have more answers,I want to maintain alert levels.
yes?
Madam president,I have admiral smith on line two.
Put him through.
Thank you,tim.
Admiral?
I've been trying to reach agent gedge,and he hasn't picked up.
Yes,I'm sure I have the right number.
I just spoke to him over an hour ago.
He said he was outside samantha roth's apartment waiting for the first gentleman.
just find him.
I don't care who you have to pull off shift.
Still can't reach gedge.
The secret service doesn't know where he is either.
I need to tell the president.
Maybe you should hold off.
The domestic threat's been lifted for now and she's on the phone with admiral smith.
I can't authorize the air strikes until our post-invasion plans are in place.
Finding a politically viable replacent,until that happens,
you need to keep your forces at full readiness.
The joint chiefs are getting impatient.
Madam president,we need to talk about your husband.
His theory about your son's death,he hasn't let it go.
What are you talking about?
He's been harassing roger's girlfriend,accusing her of complicity in the death of roger.
Henry and I went over it again and again with the fbi,and he swore to me he was past all that.
Well,he's found a private investigator who's feeding his conspiracy theory; taking advantage of him.
Please get henry on the phone.
I'm afraid I can't do that.
Henry's unreachable.
I don't understand.
Agent gedge hasn't been answering his phone.
Now,I wouldn't get too worried yet.
You're telling me my husband's gone missing?
Secret service has put out an apb.
They're going to ms.Roth's apartment.
Whatever's going on,i will find out soon enough.
Secret service dispatcher: This is a priority order code charlie zero charlie.
We need an immediate 20 on agent gedge.
All available field agents proceed to his last known location: 404 wilkinson drive.
you're making a mistake.
Think about it.
Shut up!
You haven't killed anybody yet.
You don't need to do this.
Gedge's plan to frame me is already blown.
If you kill me,they'll know it was murder,and they'll trace it back to you.
go ahead.
Where's agent gedge?
I can't reach him.
Gedge is dead.
What happened?
Everything was going according to plan...
but something went wrong.
Taylor killed gedge; I don't know how.
Where's mr. Taylor now?
He's right here.
Don't kill h,bring him to me.
Yes,sir.
Prime minister matobo,ma'am,please come with me.
Chloe,pull up the ritter building on a satellite grid.
Look for any sign of dubaku leaving the site.
We've got to find him.
It's going to take me 20 minutes to task the satellite.
Then don't waste time talking about it.
Pull up satellite and traffic cams,street corners and metro stations.
What's the priority?
I can only do one thing at timE.
Satellite!
Fine.
Bill,we need to rethink this.
What do you mean?
You were set up to surveil an undercover operation.
Your cover's been blown.
The police are after us.
We are not equipped to look for one man in a city of millions.
We neeadditional resources.
What are you suggesting?
It's time to contact outside agencies.
The government?
Yes.
I thought you said the government couldn't be trusted.
Right now,we don't have a choice.
It can't be trusted.
We can't trust anybody,that's why we're working on the outside.
President taylor can be trusted.
I'm not questioning that,prime minister.
It's the people around her who can't be trusted.
Mr. Buchanan,jack's right.
We need help.
It's too dangerous.
We can limit the flow of information.
Prime minister matobo can get us past the president's outer circle--
that way,we can at least explain to her why and what we're doing.
I think jack's right.
We left a lot of clues in that building.
We're vulnerable; we can't do this on our own anymore.
Am I supposed to remain in hiding with you,pretend that my wife and i are still being held hostage or dead?
I need to return to the white house and help the president save what's left of my country.
Let my husband do this.
Let him call president taylor.
She will listen to him.
Bill,you want to find dubaku,make the call.
All right.
Get me the white house.
Representatives from boyd chemical have assured local authorities that the immediate crisis s passed.
However,this has done little to calm the nerves of the citizens of kidron,ohio,
many of whom have taken shelter in neighboring communities.
Again,we have confirmed one fatality inside the plant itself.
13 others,all boyd employees,are being treated at local medical centers...
- Madame president,- yes?
I have prime minister matobo callg foyoU.
Matobo?
Yes,ma'am.
You're tracing it?
We tried,madame president,but it's a secure line.
Put him through.
Prime minister?
Yes,madame president.
Are you all right?
Thank god my wife and i are both fine.
We were rescued.
By whom?
Where are you?
In a safe place.
Madame president,you need to listen to me.
The people who rescued us,they have acquired the cip device.
It has been destroyed,and your country is no longer under immediate threat.
Who are these people,and tell me how this happened.
I will tell you everything in person,but,uh,this must happen privately.
I must speak to you alone.
Why alone?
They will bring me to you,madame president.
We will arrive in ten minutes.
I'll be waiting for you.
They tried to trace the call,but the line held.
Ethan,I need to see you right now.
Yes,madame president?
I just spoke to prime minister matobo.
What?
He's safe.
How?
What happened?
He'll let us know when he gets here.
He's on his way now.
He wants a private meeting.
Bring him in through the south entrance,and keep this to as few people as possible.
All right.
Jack,I've mapped a route for you to the white house.
It's mostly side streets,but there will be fewer traffic cams.
Okay,good.Send it to my phone.
We're ready.
Let's go.
As soon as we set the vehicle in front of the building,agent walker will move mr. Matobo.
Jack...
jack!
What?
I'm not going.
What are you talking about?
If the government gets their hands on tony,they'll arrest him.
I already told you-- I did some pretty bad things before I teamed up with bill.
Tony,take it from me...
you need to deal with the consequences.
And believe me,I will.
But not yet.
Not till we get dubaku.
I'm working on a lead.
I've got a guy on emerson's crew who might have some intel we can use.
Let him do this,jack.
He's the reason we got this far.
Fine.
But you give me your word as soon as this as over,you turn yourself in.
We'll stand behind you.
All right,you have my word.
Good luck.
Be careful.
I was on my way to work,so I thought I'd stop in and see you.
I tried calling you earlier.
I'm sorry; I've been busy.
Are you all right?
You look exhausted.
It's just been a long day.
Well,I hope you're still coming over for dinner.
I'm making lasagna.
And my sister promises not to give you any more dirty looks.
You haven't forgotten,have you?
No.
It's just that I've got some business to attend to.
Samuel,you work too much.
Every time you come into the diner,you're always on the phone.
I have to,maria,so that,one day,
I can finally take you away from that awful place that you work in.
Well,we met in that awful place.
Don't forget that.
I'll see you later.
Okay.
Go ahead.
Have you got mr. Taylor?
Yes.
I'm about three minutes away.
There's a korean grocer opposite my building.
One of my men will meet you out back.
Bring taylor inside.
What are you gonna do to him?
Just make sure you weren't followed.
-=www.ydy.com/bbs=-
sync: ßÇÈâÈâ »ğ¼ı¼ı
proudly presents