- Wayne said you wanted to see me.
- Keeler.
He's bringing your ex-husband
into this debate.
The SEC's investigation into his company.
Ted served his sentence.
You know that.
All Ted Packard wants is money.
If we pay him off,
he'll recant before this debate.
- It's blackmail.
- We can have the money within the hour.
- I thought you were with my dad.
- Your dad's sidelining me. Making me sit out.
Look, I know my dad can be hard.
But he will come around.
We shouldn't have told him.
The only other option
is for us to stop seeing each other.
- Chase, what do you want?
- I wanna be able to do my job.
Linda! I need your help. These guys...
they'll kill me if I don't get 'em something.
- Where are you?
- I'm at the mall.
CTU knows the powder's not real.
They're going after Singer.
- What do you want me to do?
- Take him to containment.
Done.
We believe your son was infected
with the virus in Mexico early this morning.
We have three hours to find him
before he becomes contagious.
Got him. He's at Los Feliz Mall
between Vermont and Sunset.
- I can land a team there in ten minutes.
- OK, fine.
- Kyle.
- Who are you?
My name's Tony Almeida.
I'm a federal agent. I'm here to help you.
- I don't believe you.
- Come with me, I'll prove it to you.
We have an officer down.
Kyle Singer is not in custody.
Clear the way here, please.
Jack isn't picking up. Isn't Tony there?
I can't get through to him.
I'm trying Micah.
What's going on?
- There's been gunshots at the mall.
- When?
Two minutes ago. I can't get in touch
with my dad or Tony.
- Micah said someone's down.
- Who?
It's either Tony or Jack, he's not sure.
He's about to find out.
Hold on.
It's Jack. He wants to talk to you.
What's going on? Where's Tony?
- He's been shot.
- How bad?
He was hit in the neck. He's alive.
They're getting him to the hospital.
Oh, God.
I know how difficult this must be for you.
But you need to make a decision.
- What?
- With Tony down, you're in command.
If you wanna be by his side,
you have to hand CTU over to someone else.
No one will fault what you choose to do.
But if you choose to stay,
we need you at full capacity.
- I understand.
- Michelle, I'm sorry.
Is Tony all right?
They don't know yet. He was shot in the neck.
We're overloading the network.
When the virus threat came in
we stole cycles from the main CPU.
- Chloe, now is not a good time.
- What? Are you out of your mind?
- Just deal with it, OK?
- Michelle?
Send the archives to Division.
That should free up the network.
Fine. That's all I needed to know.
I have to get to the hospital.
The second call from
Hector Salazar's people just came in.
I can't deal with this now.
Who else is there?
You're the ranking agent on site.
Find out what hospital they took Tony to.
The second anyone knows anything
you have them patched through to me.
Deliver Ramón Salazar to the
Van Nuys dam, adjacent to the 101 freeway.
Provide him with a full-spectrum bandwidth
radio adjusted to frequency XQ2137.
Do not attempt aerial or ground surveillance.
You have two hours from receipt
of this message to comply.
If you violate any one of these conditions
we will release the virus.
- Does the encoding match the first message?
- Yeah.
- Can you find out where it came from?
- I can scan the frequency.
Maybe we'll get lucky.
Whoever sent this message
is controlling Kyle Singer's movements.
We have two hours to find him
before they release the virus.
- Kyle?
- Linda, where are you?
I'm trying to park but they're putting up
barricades. Something's going on.
No, don't go to the garage.
Meet me outside the east entrance.
- On Vermont?
- Yeah, go there now. I'll be there in a second.
I've found him!
Move over. Go!
- Get over!
- What's going on?
I don't know.
- Where are we going?
- We just gotta get outta here.
This is our contact frequency. If he shows up,
please let me know as soon as possible.
- Got it.
- Excuse me.
What's up?
Just heard about Tony. How's he doing?
He's on his way to the hospital.
- Why isn't Michelle with him?
- It'll set us back if they're both gone.
- Tell Michelle I'm heading over to Downey.
- To see Salazar?
- Yeah.
- Dad said questioning him is a waste of time.
Sitting around here is a waste of time.
Don't you think you should
clear it with Michelle first?
We lost the kid who's infected. If anyone
knows where he's going, it's Salazar.
- At least run it by her before you go.
- I'll call her from Downey.
Chase.
- Dessler.
- I'm looking for Tony Almeida's wife.
- Yes, this is Michelle.
- Michelle, this is Dr Linzer.
- How is he?
- The wound to your husband's neck
is going to require some vascular repair.
We're just about to go into surgery.
- Can I talk to him?
- No, we've medicated him.
That's why I'm calling you.
We need your consent to operate.
- Yes, of course. Whatever you have to do.
- Great. Thanks.
- Are you sure he's gonna be OK?
- We can't be 100% certain till we get in there.
- But he'll be in good hands.
- Please let me know the second you finish.
I'll find you in the waiting room
when we're out of surgery.
Doctor Linzer,
I will do my best to be there, but...
- you may have to reach me at this number.
- OK. We'll find you.
- Thank you, Doctor.
- Sure.
I just spoke with Anne's ex-husband.
I'm meeting him in half an hour.
Unless you're changing your mind.
I've never given in to blackmail in my life.
Considering everything
you're up against, we decided...
I decided, Wayne.
- It's my choice.
- And, David, you're making the right one.
Give this guy some money, he crawls back
under his rock and life will be a lot simpler.
For Anne too.
I hope so.
- Yes?
-  I have Jack Bauer on the line, sir.
- Put him through.
- The president's on the line, Mr Bauer.
- Mr President? This is Jack Bauer.
- Hello, Jack.
I was told Hector Salazar has given your
office instructions on delivering his brother.
Yes, sir.
I've also been told you might be able
to pre-empt that demand.
We identified the person carrying the virus.
It was a young man named Kyle Singer.
- Then you know where he is.
- No, sir. Unfortunately we lost him.
Can you find him?
Not in the time frame
that Hector Salazar has given us.
So either I hand over Ramón Salazar,
or risk that his brother will release the virus.
Mr President, I understand
that this is an impossible choice.
It's not a choice, Jack. Not really.
This nation's policy of non-negotiation
with terrorists has been a proven deterrent.
Capitulating to Salazar
would destroy that policy.
Hundreds of thousands of innocent people
may die within the week.
More would die in the long run
if I release Salazar.
I would be declaring open season
on the American people.
- This is your final answer, sir?
- I don't negotiate with terrorists, Jack.
I won't negotiate with terrorists.
I understand, Mr President. Thank you.
Conference in CDC and Health Services.
I want a full briefing on quarantine
and evacuation procedures.
Yes, Mr President.
Can you tell me where we're going?
I just gotta get outta town for a second,
figure this whole thing out.
- I thought you had to meet with those guys.
- Things have changed, all right?
What are you into, Kyle?
You ask me to steal money so these guys
won't hurt you over losing their drugs.
I don't think it was drugs.
What do you mean? What is it about?
These cops came to my apartment today
and they were saying something about...
using me to bring some
weird disease into the country.
A disease?
This cop, he was saying
that it was inside of me.
In your body?
I know. It sounds ridiculous, right?
Right?
Man, this whole thing is so surreal, Linda.
- Pull over.
- What?
- I said pull over!
- What are you doing? What are you doing?
Take the car, take the money.
I don't want any part of it.
Hey, Linda, chill out, OK?
Stay away. If you've got some disease, I don't
want it. You shouldn't have done any of this.
- Don't you think I know that?
- Kyle, please.
All right, fine. Fine, baby. You're right.
I'll stay away, OK?
The money's under the front seat.
Come on, Linda. Please.
Kyle, I really don't want anything
to happen to you, but I can't do this.
God, how stupid am I? Come on!
I'm sorry.
Go! Run! Run, Linda!
Go!
No, I have it, OK?
I have it!
Kyle!
We have a monitoring plan for everyone
inside the quarantine zone.
- Define the quarantine zone.
- Everyone within two miles of ground zero.
Ground zero being the shopping center
where Kyle Singer was last seen.
This is Dr Nicole Duncan with
Health Services. Medical teams are in place
and ready to start screening and releasing
people from quarantine over a 72-hour period.
If we move quickly, we believe we can lower
the prior casualty estimate.
- Lower it to what?
- Between 60 and 90 thousand.
All right, thank you. Miss Dessler, Dr Duncan.
Mr President.
We're about to set in motion a chain of events
that will create panic throughout the country
that will take some time to control.
If anyone here sees an option that
I'm overlooking, now's the time to offer it up.
It's Jack Bauer.
He needs to talk to you in private.
He says it's urgent.
Would you all excuse me for a moment?
In the meantime, I want everyone
to contact their key personnel.
Make sure they're ready to go.
- What is it, Jack?
- Mr President, is this line secure?
Yes. What do you need to tell me, Jack?
For what it's worth, sir, I agree with
your policy to not negotiate with terrorists.
You didn't call me to express your approval.
- I have another option for you.
- Another option?
Yes. One that I believe will protect
the integrity of this nation's policy.
- And stop this outbreak.
- And how would I do this?
- By simply doing nothing, sir.
- Nothing?
Yes, sir.
Hector Salazar will view that
as noncompliance.
- Not if he gets his brother back.
- How?
Ramón Salazar would be broken out
and delivered to him.
The public, and other terrorist groups,
would view this as a prison break
as opposed to a capitulation
to terrorist demands.
Sounds like quite a plan, Jack.
Who'll break Salazar out?
I will, sir.
- By yourself?
- I know the prison and the prisoner.
Because of the nature of my involvement
I could break him out and deliver him.
CTU would believe that I switched sides.
The cover story would stay clean.
- This doesn't sound like a one-man job.
- In order to protect you, it has to be.
I don't know, Jack.
There has to be some other way.
Not in the time that we've got. The Salazars
are gonna release the virus within two hours.
Regardless of how you contain
the initial outbreak,
the resulting civil unrest would far outreach
any quarantine zones established.
The damage to this country, sir,
would be catastrophic.
Mr President, I need your OK on this.
Even if you succeed, I won't be able to correct
your legal status. You'll be a fugitive.
I understand.
- This would be my last assignment.
- I don't know what to say.
If you don't say anything, Mr President,
I will accept that as a go for this mission.
Good luck, Mr President.
I want the information from Dr Duncan
sent directly to my office. My eyes only.
- Wayne? Where are you going?
- Excuse me.
- Wait.
- I have an appointment and I'm running late.
An appointment? The debate starts
in 30 minutes. Who are you meeting?
I'm sorry, but that's confidential.
It's government business.
Does this have anything
to do with my ex-husband?
Like I said, it's government business.
Surgery. Nurses' station.
This is Tony Almeida's wife.
I was wondering if he'd gone into surgery.
Yes, he has.
I wanted Dr Linzer to know
that he's allergic to penicillin.
He's aware. The allergy card was in his wallet.
Is there any way to know how he's doing?
No, but the doctor will contact you
as soon as he's out of surgery.
OK.
Thank you.
- Yeah?
- The site profiles are done.
- You've sent these to my system.
- I know. I wanted to come down here anyway.
- Why?
- Because of earlier.
What is it, Chloe?
I want you to know that I didn't know Tony
had been shot when I was insensitive earlier.
And had I known that I would have been
more careful about my choice of words, OK?
That's fine, Chloe.
- I do try to be aware of other people.
- I said it's fine.
OK.
- Gael?
- What?
We should be careful with Michelle today.
She's really sensitive.
- About Tony being shot. In the neck.
- Of course.
So make sure everyone
in your department knows.
I've gotta take this.
A personal cell? Those are prohibited.
They can't be monitored.
I'm using it for inner agency.
They'll monitor at the other end.
I've really gotta take this call.
Hello.
- When did you make the second call?
- 20 minutes ago.
- Are they letting Ramón go or not?
- They're still deciding.
- What are they waiting for?
- I'll let you know as soon as I hear anything.
I'm sorry.
It's not good to touch what's not yours.
- Does your sister know you're here?
- No.
Did you know it was loaded?
It is a nice gun, huh?
Take it, Sergio. It's OK.
You like the way it feels?
Want to pull the trigger?
Hear the noise it makes?
That is what power feels like, Sergio.
It feels like a gun.
Can I?
Sure.
Sure. Come on.
Do you see that vase down there?
OK, now, I want you to aim.
And squeeze the trigger very slowly.
Bueno.
What are you doing?
Get out of here! Go, now!
How many times do I have to tell you?
He's just a boy.
- Your boy needs to become a man.
- No, you're not his father.
What you gonna do, huh?
You gonna shoot me?
Come on. Pull the trigger.
Right here. Come on.
Get in there!
Hey, what is this?
What are you gonna do to us?
What is this? What are you gonna do to us?
Come.
We never really finished our conversation.
I was wondering what you had decided.
- Decided about what?
- The debate.
What to do about my ex-husband.
I ran into Wayne a few minutes ago.
I know he's never liked me, but this was
different. He was avoiding me, and...
I had a feeling I wasn't able to shake.
- What kind of feeling?
- That you're paying Ted to keep quiet.
Is that what you're doing, David?
Sometimes you have to do the wrong thing
for the right reason.
How can you reward someone
for threatening you with a lie? It's wrong.
There are political realities I have to consider
if I want to stay in office.
- Tell yourself that if it makes you feel better.
- It doesn't make me feel better.
It just happens to be the truth.
Anne, I have been in this job
for nearly four years,
and I have learned the hard way
that there are no absolutes.
- Sometimes you have to make compromises.
- Politically, yes.
But when it comes to morality...
David, you have to draw the line.
I have drawn the line.
We're just standing on different sides.
You're running scared.
I'm fighting to stay in office
and serve the people that put me here.
Then face Keeler's lie with the truth and
trust that the people can tell the difference.
- It's not that easy.
- You've never been about what's easy.
You've been about what's right.
That's who you are.
That's who the people elected to lead them.
For what it's worth...
that's who I fell in love with.
I was...
- I was trying to protect you.
- Protect me?
This won't end with Keeler's allegation.
You're gonna be in the media's cross hairs.
- I'm used to public scrutiny.
- Not like this.
This will be different.
And much uglier than you can imagine.
I can defend myself.
- David.
- Have you made contact with Packard?
- He just got here.
- Are you with him now?
He's coming over now. Why?
Walk away.
- What?
- You heard me.
We've been through this.
You decided to bury this, remember?
- I've changed my mind.
- Anne talked to you, didn't she?
Wayne.
Walk away.
- You wanted to see me?
- I've spoken to Chloe and Adam.
We'll cover for you
if you want to be with Tony.
- Cover for me?
- We know you've got a lot on your mind.
I'm fine, Gael.
I've been taking 30% of Chloe's load since the
biothreat. I can handle half of Comms as well.
We'll just need a route user password so
we won't be slowed down by authorizations.
It's Joe Tomasello's area. He put a 24-hour
delay on user mods for security.
- What if I called Joe?
- I tried that. He's unreachable.
Is there any other way to do this?
More bodies. We need at least four more
system-ready analysts to take on the work.
- I can make some calls, get the next shift in.
- I've already tried that.
By the time they got here it would be too late.
I appreciate this, but it's not gonna happen.
So let's get back to work.
Michelle.
Listen, I agree. We can't run this place
by committee. Let me step in for you.
- Adam and Chloe stay at their posts.
- What about yours?
At Langley I filled in for my bureau chief
a couple of times.
Was there a biothreat?
President in town? All in one day?
Thank you anyway, Gael.
- CTU. Bauer.
- Kim, what are you doing right now?
Trying to locate the origin of
that phone call from Salazar's people.
- I need you to do something for me first.
- What?
I need you to generate
a prisoner transfer document.
Look in File Form under the heading
"Federal Transit Authorization".
What's this about?
- I need to move Ramón Salazar.
- Why are you gonna move him?
Kim, this has priority clearance.
No one at CTU's supposed to know.
That's why you're the only person I can trust
to do this for me. So please, help.
OK. It's asking for a clearance code.
Hit *99.
Now it wants a password.
Lincoln65fga.
- OK, it's cycling. It's gonna take a minute.
- OK, good.
Look, Kim.
I know you came up to my office earlier
to talk about something important to you.
- I wasn't very supportive. I wanted to...
- You don't have to do this.
Sweetheart, I do. I need to tell you I'm sorry.
I know that I'm overly protective of you.
I've watched so many things
happen to you, I...
I don't want you to get hurt any more.
But the fact is, I trust you.
I trust your judgment.
I need you to know that anything you ever
chose to do, I would support you in. OK?
Thanks. That means a lot to me.
Good.
I love you so much, Kim.
I love you too, Dad.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, I'm all right. Is the document up yet?
- Yeah.
- Send it to Warden Mitchell, over at Downey.
- Done.
- OK, good. Let me speak to Chase.
- He's not here.
- What are you talking about? Where is he?
Where is Chase?
- He went to interrogate Salazar.
- Chase is at the prison now?
He left about 15 minutes ago.
He's gonna be there soon.
I'm gonna have to get back to you.
Son of a bitch!
- Yeah?
- Chase, what are you doing?
- I'm going to talk to Salazar.
- Get back to CTU now!
- And do what? Filing? Maybe some dusting?
- No, work with Michelle and find Kyle Singer.
She's got a dozen IT people on that right now.
- Listen to me.
- No, listen to me, Jack.
I know you're angry about me and Kim, but
I won't let you stop me from doing my job.
Your job is to follow my orders!
You're in no condition to give me orders.
Chase, I'm warning you. Don't go against me.
Jack, look. You know I respect you,
but you also know I've been covering for you.
I've been keeping the fact that you're a junkie
from Kim and everybody else.
I'm not doing it any more.
I'm done.
Chase! Chase!
Dammit!
Get this guy processed
and get him outta here.
Agent Edmunds.
- Warden. I need to see Salazar.
- I've got a lot going on right now.
I'll follow up with authorization,
but I need to see Salazar now.
Salazar's been behind two murders today.
No one gets close.
You don't know what's happening today.
Salazar has information that I need.
- What information?
- Classified.
This is my facility. I need to know.
We're dealing with a major terrorist threat.
Salazar's brother is behind it.
Confirm it with Division if you want to.
But hundreds of thousands
of lives are at stake.
Jack and I have been here twice a week
for the last three months.
Salazar has prevented us from doing our job
with his lawyers and his due process.
We don't have time for that.
I need to go one-on-one with him. Right now.
He's in an isolation cell in B block.
Come on, I'll take you.
- Cameras?
- There are three.
- Need 'em turned off.
- It's against regulations.
- There won't be any marks. I promise.
- You've got 30 minutes.
This is Warden Mitchell.
I need you to go black on Isolation B.
-  For how long, sir?
- Until further notice.
You are a tough guy, huh?
You are not worried what may happen
if you lay a finger on me?
OK.
If you're not worried, neither am I.
Let me know when you start to worry.
- Where's Kyle Singer?
- I told you, I don't know.
You're gonna tell me who does.
Chase!
Put him in his cell.
- What are you doing here?
- We ran out of options.
We can't find Singer.
Salazar's our only hope. You were right.
He's tougher than I thought.
Maybe two of us can...
Look, Jack. About what I said before...
- Forget about it.
- So we're OK? You and me?
Yeah, we're OK.
- Tell me about the security cameras.
- They're disabled.
Good. Get him out of his cell.
Are you gonna kill me now, Jack?
I'd love to. But I can't.
If you play this cool,
you're walking out of here now.
You'll be with your brother in the next
couple of hours. Now grab his feet.
Turn and face the wall.
How are you gonna feel, Anne,
if David loses this election because of you?
I don't think that's very likely.
Then you really don't know
what you're talking about.
This allegation may cost him this debate.
David needs this debate to win this election.
- It was blackmail.
- And David made a decision to pay.
It wasn't up to you to change his mind.
If he believed the decision was right,
he wouldn't have changed his mind.
The problem is you can't stand the fact
that your brother wants me in his life.
Because you're a distraction, Anne.
And you're a liability.
Compared to whom? Sherry?
I'm not gonna defend Sherry. She went off the
rails. But at least she understood the game.
She understood David.
She was with him over 20 years.
- I know the kind of man he is.
- You don't know anything about him.
Or what it takes to survive
in the world he lives in.
We disagree, Wayne. We always have.
Anne, I will not stand by and watch you
jeopardize everything he's worked for.
I won't do it.
I don't scare easily.
After all you went through to put me here,
I can't believe you'd let me out.
Shut up.
I don't believe you sold out. It's not your
nature. But then, why knock out the kid?
Did your government cave, but can't admit it?
Is that what happened?
You don't look so good, Jack. That's a bitch.
You wanna get outta here? You keep your
mouth shut and do what I say, understand?
We've been cleared to pass.
The warden wants to see you first.
He'll be here in a minute.
OK.
Don't you move.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Jack.
- What's the problem?
- The codes on this transfer order.
They don't correspond to the ones assigned.
Division superseded those access codes.
CTU has a mandated prefix.
- This is yesterday's prefix.
- Son of a bitch.
Someone in my office screwed up.
We'll get you the proper prefix retroactively.
Look, I know about the terrorist threat.
Agent Edmunds told me.
That's why we need to move
the prisoner now.
It's classified. Priority one.
I couldn't tell you.
But I can't afford to lose time
over some technical detail.
- Come on, Kevin, help me out.
- Where's Agent Edmunds?
He's searching the prisoner's cell,
trying to find information.
He'll be right behind me.
He can help you out with the paperwork.
All right. Pick up your badge
and gun at Receiving.
Thanks. I owe you.
Move.
Turn on Isolation 3, please.
What the hell...?
Someone turned the camera. The angle's
wrong. Get Benjamin to meet me in Isolation.
Door.
Face the wall.
Agent Bauer.
Here to get my gun and my badge.
Open it.
Door!
- Kinda hot today.
- Yeah, buddy.
Whatever Bauer told you, he's lying!
Come on!
- One minute, I'll check you out.
- OK.
Daniel, I'm back on post.
- Move!
-  Code 4. We have full lockdown.
Code 4. Full lockdown.
Security breach.
We have lock on all blocks.
Lock on all blocks.
- Open the cell blocks now.
- I can't do it from here.
Is it worth losing your life over?
Do it now!
- Hey, this is what I'm talking about!
- Yeah!
- Come on!
Full lockdown.
Code 4. We have full lockdown.