Here are all the access codes
to CTU and Division.
- Thanks.
- I'm probably gonna be gone for a while.
If you need anything,
you can always call me at home.
Sir,
Ms Driscoll's replacement arrived.
Tony, thank you for filling in.
And I'd like you to stick around
and assist Ms Dessler.
- Who?
- Michelle Dessler. Do you know her?
I used to be married to her.
- I have to go to McLennan-Forster.
- Why there?
Turns out the man
we're looking for works there.
- Need to get into their computer system?
- Yeah.
OK. I'll go with you.
So how can I help CTU?
One of your employees,
Harris Barnes, is actually Habib Marwan,
a terrorist responsible for today's
attack and theft of the override.
We need you to take your IT systems offline
so Paul can look into his directory.
CTU will subpoena those files.
They will find out the truth.
- Dammit!
- What's he doing?
He's trying to rebuild the files I deleted.
Look at this.
Son of a bitch, it's encrypted.
That's it. Print it out, now. Now!
He's gonna find evidence
we sold arms to terrorists.
The pulse bomb. We have to use it now.
We're dealing with an EMP.
Once it goes off, everything
within its radius that's electrical gets fried.
I'm gonna try and stop it.
If I don't, take the hard copy,
meet me in front of the building.
CTU agent's heading down near you.
Don't let him near it.
Oh, my God.
Are any electronic devices working?
Only the basic battery-powered devices.
- How many square miles are affected?
- 80, including southeast downtown.
OK. Hold your position
until the readings stabilise.
- Any word from Jack or Paul?
- No.
Once the bomb went off
we lost communication.
- What was the last we heard from them?
- Jack and Paul found something.
It must be incriminating
to McLennan-Forster.
So they set off the EMP
to destroy the evidence.
That's my guess.
The fact that McLennan-Forster
is taking action is evidence against them.
Yeah, but it's not proof.
Curtis.
- Could Jack or Paul have been injured?
- No. An EMP only damages electronics.
But it doesn't mean they're safe.
We know you printed a document
before the EMP detonated.
Where is it?
It's up to you.
You decide when the pain stops.
- Call me when he talks.
- Yes, sir.
No!
Drop your gun or I'll kill him.
I said drop it!
Paul, where's the data printout?
I hid it in an office down the hallway.
I know you're hurt, but we've gotta get it
and get out of here. Let's go.
Let's go.
It's in here.
Take a seat.
- Where is it?
- Bottom drawer, under some folders.
I hid it because I thought I might be captured.
- Is this it?
- Yeah, it's in code.
I couldn't make any sense out of it.
We need to get it back to CTU.
- I couldn't have held out much longer.
- You did great.
Let's go.
For those who don't know,
this is Michelle Dessler.
She'll be taking over as acting director of CTU
effective immediately.
Tony, I appreciate you carrying the ball
until she got here.
Why don't you
bring everyone up to speed?
Yes, sir.
Less than an hour ago, we discovered that the
man responsible for planning today's attacks,
Habib Marwan, has been a long-term
employee of McLennan-Forster,
the third-largest defence contractor
in the country.
We know that Marwan's
been using the alias "Harris Barnes".
What we don't know
is how he evaded their security checks.
He knows we're after him
so he's probably gone dark.
His association with McLennan-Forster
is our main focus.
Jack and Paul Raines
went to inspect his computer files,
but as they were doing so,
an EMP bomb was detonated,
wiping out the company's database.
It fried every electrical device
in an eight-mile radius -
streetlights, computers,
cars, cellphones, everything.
Did they find anything before detonation?
Yeah, but we haven't
been able to contact them.
But we have to assume
whoever detonated the EMP
wants Jack and Paul eliminated.
- Have rescue teams been sent into the area?
- Not yet.
Once the effects subside we'll send
two teams in with functioning electronics.
The problem is until we find Jack
and Paul, they won't be able to do much.
We want to do everything we can
to find Jack Bauer and Paul Raines,
but the priority is to retrieve any information
they found at McLennan-Forster.
That's all.
Tony.
I need the access codes for CTU and Division.
- Thank you.
- What do you want me to do?
Division's sending over a supplemental list
of terrorists who've had contact with Marwan.
Check any names that have been flagged
by other agencies, including overseas.
Given what's happening right now,
doesn't seem like the best use of my time.
It has to be done and I'd like you to do it.
Michelle, Jack and Paul have information
that could end this crisis.
I should be helping us find them. Michelle!
When I last saw you,
you couldn't stay sober to keep a job.
That was six months ago.
This is what I need you to do.
If you don't like it, you can resign.
I'm gonna need a security clearance.
I'll make sure you get a level three.
Level three? I used to have a six.
Right now, all you need is three.
Is there a problem with Agent Almeida?
Not at all.
It's just that Secretary Heller is very sensitive
to personal conflicts on the job.
I know your history,
I know you were married
and that he sacrificed his career
to save your life.
- But if this is gonna be a problem, I...
- His being here will not affect my work.
Now, if Secretary Heller wants to speak to me
about it, I'll be more than glad to.
We are receiving reports from LAPD
indicating that there is widespread looting
going on in the blacked-out zone.
A number of cars have been set on fire
and stores ransacked.
Witnesses report shots were heard.
There may be casualties.
We just don't know at this time.
That could be the same people
that were after Jack.
I don't get it. What could be worth
setting off a pulse bomb?
Something implicating McLennan-Forster.
Anything they're doing now is insignificant
if they helped Marwan today.
- This is Anderson.
-  It's time for you to go.
Marwan, your face is all over the news.
Don't worry about it.
Things will proceed as planned.
- Are you ready?
- Yes, of course.
- How long will it take you to get there?
- Less than 30 minutes.
I'll inform the others.
It's heading to McLennan-Forster.
It's not responding to any of our ID requests.
- You're sure?
- Yeah, I'm positive.
Michelle.
Excuse me.
There's a chopper in the dead zone,
not one of ours.
- Police?
- Not one of theirs either. I checked.
We picked it up by its electronic signature.
- Where's it going?
- Straight to McLennan-Forster.
Could it be some sort of
corporate rescue chopper?
- They'd give the police a call sign.
- It's a search-and-destroy mission.
A chopper that size
carries 20 men, fully armed.
- Who would have sent it?
- Whoever set off the EMP, they're after Jack.
McLennan-Forster's been training
mercenaries for years.
Contact our field teams in the air.
Let them know about the intruding chopper.
I'll be right back.
- Jack, I can't do this.
- You don't have a choice. Come on.
Get me some gear!
These are the men we're looking for.
They have an encoded computer print-out.
We need to erase these two men
and recover the document.
Just be aware,
one of them is a CTU field agent.
- You want us to kill a federal agent?
- I'll take care of him.
He went bad, helped the terrorists,
dragged the company into it.
LAPD is responding to this area.
We'll have to do this quickly if we want to
stay off their radar. Use that to keep in touch.
We spotted two men
headed east on Addison.
Deploy your men in a flanking position
a mile down the road and then move in.
- We'll fan out and come in from behind.
- You got it.
Get me that chopper
back in the northwest corner.
Let's move.
Come on.
Come on, this way.
This way.
- Why are we going here?
- Weapons and ammunition.
Get away from here!
- Paul, get down!
Get out of here!
The next one won't miss!
- I'm a federal agent.
Sure you are. Get away from here.
Look, we need your help.
Go! Now!
Hey, just relax. I'm leaving.
OK? I'm leaving.
Drop the weapon! Now!
Kick the gun over to me.
- Paul!
- Yeah?
Get in here.
Pick up that gun.
My name is Jack Bauer. I am a federal agent.
You should have helped stop the looting.
You still have any rifles
or did they get them too?
- Behind the counter, yeah.
- Show me.
Look, we're the first to be hit
because we're Arabs.
- We had nothing to do with what happened...
- Quiet. He doesn't care.
Take what you need, but leave two guns. We
chased the looters once, but they'll be back.
Just stay there.
Give me the keys.
What are you guys doing here?
- We needed to take cover.
- What do you mean? Who's after you?
It has to do with the terrorist attacks.
I have evidence
that I need to get to the authorities.
The men chasing us caused this blackout.
They detonated a device
called an electromagnetic pulse bomb.
It destroys electrical activity
within eight miles.
So everything that's happened, the looting,
the blackout, it's all because of the terrorists?
Yes, and the evidence that I have
can help prevent further attacks.
Jack, the commandos
will be here any minute.
- Commandos?
- He's right. You need to leave this store.
Right now we're their target.
You're not safe here.
- Why don't you leave? It's our store.
- If I had a choice, I would,
but you have weapons and shelter.
Right now there's no other place for us to be.
Can I talk to my brother for a second?
Stay where I can see you.
What's the plan?
CTU knows that we can't contact them. They
can view this area with satellite and infrared.
McLennan-Forster's commandos
arrived in a military helicopter.
CTU had to see that on satellite.
If we can initiate a large-enough firefight,
we can force their commandos
to communicate their positions.
- And CTU will pick up the signal?
- Yes.
So you want to engage the
McLennan-Forster army, just the two of us?
We have a positional advantage.
And we only have to hold down
till CTU gets here.
...nothing, all right?
- All right.
My brother and I talked about this.
We're staying.
I can't force you to leave your own property,
but this is not just a bunch of looters.
This is a very dangerous situation.
I cannot guarantee your safety.
You don't understand. For years we've been
blamed for the attacks by these terrorists.
We grew up in this neighbourhood.
This country is our home.
If you're fighting the people who caused
today's bloodshed, then we'll help you.
The president should stay in the air
at least another hour, if not longer.
If he wants to speak to the nation,
he should do it from Air Force One.
- Keep me informed.
-  Yes, sir.
I have an update from the San Gabriel Island
meltdown. It's not as bad as we had feared.
How you doing?
Sit down.
Any word from Jack or Paul?
No.
I can't imagine how hard this must be for you.
There's something else, isn't there?
A couple hours ago,
when we thought that Paul was involved
with the attacks, Jack questioned him.
And Paul has his pride, so he resisted, but...
Jack was pretty rough?
Very.
That's his job.
He had to make sure.
You have to believe that Jack had no choice.
I know. I guess it was just a shock to see it.
Somehow he seemed like a different person.
We need people like that, Audrey.
Jack is an incredible man. I just...
But you're not sure you feel
the same way as before, is that it?
Something like that.
Can I speak to you for a moment?
It's important.
OK. I don't have much time.
You're aware I was falsely accused
of leaking information.
- Yes, I saw the report.
- Erin Driscoll didn't talk to you about it?
Her daughter died.
I think she has other things on her mind.
I understand, but there are some things
that still need to be handled.
What things?
She promised that it would be expunged
from my record,
and I'd be bumped up two pay grades,
so I want to make sure that will still happen.
I'll look into it, but not today.
What happened to me was an outrage.
If you don't do something to resolve it
right now, I'll go directly to Secretary Heller.
Secretary Heller doesn't run CTU.
I do. And I am ordering you
to go back to work.
Not until you assure me the false accusation
will be expunged and my pay grade changed.
- I need security to station one.
- Security?
What for?
I need people whose minds are on their jobs.
Yours isn't.
So you're firing me? You can't.
You need me. I'm juggling active protocols.
We'll manage.
Please escort Ms Gavin out of the building.
Make sure you get her access card.
You'll be sorry for this.
I promise you will.
- Back entrance locked?
- Yeah.
Put these in each window.
Have ammunition ready.
And I want you to get two hunting vests.
Fill all the pockets with empty clips. Go.
Ms Gavin won't be working with us any more.
I'll need you two to divide her workload.
We're stretched pretty thin. Everyone is up to
their necks, or not qualified to replace Sarah.
- You may want to reconsider.
- No. I don't trust her.
Then what about Agent Almeida?
Michelle, we could use the help,
and he's already proved himself useful today.
Agent Almeida, please come to station six.
Yeah.
Work with Stiles and Manning
for the rest of the day.
Edgar, call up Sarah's protocols. Check
the configuration, make sure they're accurate.
- I'll advise internal stations of the change.
Give me an update.
It's quiet except for emergency-vehicle
chatter. There's no sign of Jack or Paul.
CTU teams are ready. All we can do is spread
them around the perimeter and wait for Jack.
I think that's a mistake.
We should consolidate our teams,
meet strength with strength.
- Where would you place them?
- At McLennan-Forster.
Jack won't be far from there.
Look, he knows we won't be able
to find him without help.
He's gonna help us by starting a firefight.
I know the way he thinks.
The hostiles will break radio silence
when they attack. We can follow the signal.
He's gonna engage
an entire team of commandos?
It's the most efficient way to be found.
And he's gonna expect us to be ready for it.
Stick with the plan. Cover the perimeter.
Michelle.
If we send all our teams to one location and
you're wrong, Jack and Paul won't survive.
But if we cover the perimeter,
we may have a chance to save them.
Do it.
Castle, go ahead as planned.
Be ready to move.
There's one of them.
It's time.
No one fires until I give the order.
- OK.
- All right.
Team leader, this is Spectre.
I was just shot at.
I'm on the northwest corner of Stringer,
between Flower and Third.
Copy that.
- He's not returning fire.
- Because he's alone.
He's calling for backup now.
- And what do we do?
- Wait for them to come full force.
Just stay ready.
- Audrey.
- Yes?
Let DOD know we're using law-enforcement
channels in the blackout zone.
- I told them we might need their feeds.
- You don't need them?
- No.
- All right, no problem.
I didn't mean to be confrontational before.
Just, when you walk into a hailstorm
you have to be decisive.
I understand,
and I know where you're coming from.
I think that you're making
the right decisions, but...
But what?
I think that you should
re-evaluate your opinion of Tony.
- Why is that?
- This morning Jack had nowhere to turn.
He went to the one person
he knew would come through for him - Tony.
Tony saved our lives.
- I didn't know.
- We had to spend a couple hours with him.
It's true, Tony has a lot of issues,
but he is good at what he does.
And I think that we could use him
on a day like today.
Fair enough.
And business aside,
he still cares about you.
I got those perimeter teams
you asked for ready to go.
Thanks.
Tony, look, I just want you to know that just
because I overruled you a few minutes ago
doesn't mean that I don't value your input.
Don't patronise me, Michelle.
I'm not.
Look, you ran CTU for two years.
Anything that you have to say
I will consider seriously.
Don't worry. I'm gonna tell you what I think
whether you want to hear it or not, all right?
Good.
You scared?
- You sure you both want to do this?
- Yeah.
My brother and I are more angry
about these attacks than you are.
So we're gonna stand up and we're gonna
try to be part of the solution.
- I'm sorry this had to happen in your store.
- Yeah.
Our father left us this business
when he died.
And he worked his whole life to make
a good name for himself in the community.
This store is his legacy,
but if he were here right now,
he'd be standing next to you,
just as we are.
Just stay low and do what I tell you.
Thank you...
for saving my life.
Yeah.
They're here.
Tony, Michelle said that you were doing
a search on ties to Marwan. May I help?
- Do you have a sign-on for the SYKY server?
- In Washington?
- Yeah, it would save me time on this search.
- Yeah.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
- Anything else?
- It should kick off a few names.
You can help me write them down
once it's done searching.
So... did you tell Michelle
what happened today?
- I said that Jack called you.
- Anything else?
I didn't say that you were living
with anyone, if that's what you mean.
She probably already knows that,
and I'm sure she couldn't care less.
So how are you and Jack faring
with him out in the field today?
It's different.
- A lot different than Washington.
- Yeah.
It is different.
To tell the truth, I couldn't believe it when
I heard that Jack had taken a desk job in DC.
He said he was happier this way.
Uh-huh.
Well, you've gotten a chance
to see him in both worlds today.
Think he'll go back to wearing a suit?
After the hell Jack's been through today,
you think he'd want to come back to this?
Some people are more comfortable in hell.
Are you talking about Jack...
or yourself?
I think we found them.
Each signal is a radio,
all using the same frequency.
They're planning an attack.
They're at Flower and Third,
a quarter mile from McLennan-Forster.
You were right.
He's actually drawing them in.
Go, go!
A sporting goods store, across the street.
Let's move.
Bravo One, move in.
The spread's picking up
automatic-weapon fire.
- When will our teams get there?
- The ground teams will arrive first.
- When?
- At least five or six minutes.
- Who's helping them?
- I don't know. They gotta be civilians.
We need to end this and get that document.
Understood?
- Yeah, I understand.
- Let's go.
Hey, Naji! Hey!
Hey, are you hit? Hey?
You OK? Naji!
It hit the clip.
Naji.
Fall back!
All right! Now! Now!
Move forward!
Hurry! Take my shotgun.
Because of their night goggles,
if they get within ten feet,
shine your flashlight in their eyes,
it'll blind them.
Jack?
The gunfire's stopped.
- Are the teams on site?
- Not yet.
The commandos could have
taken over the location.
They might have taken the information back.
Try to get in touch with our teams.
I'll update Division.
If McLennan-Forster won the firefight,
what about Jack and Paul?
There's no way to tell.
- CTU personnel are approaching the location.
- It's Castle. We're about to engage.
- How many hostiles?
- Six down outside. Unknown inside.
- Lee, it's Tony. Are Jack and Paul alive?
- Unknown at this point.
The hostiles cannot leave
with the information from McLennan-Forster.
- You understand?
- We'll do our best.
No. Listen. Failure is not an option. That
information is what this whole thing's about.
Roger that.
Jack!
- Yeah? I'm here.
- You safe?
- Yeah.
- All hostiles are down. We're clear.
- OK.
Go ahead.
This way.
- This is Castle. Get me CTU.
-  Stand by.
- Curtis.
- It's Castle.
- Lee, what's your status?
- Location secured. Jack and Raines are safe.
- What about their information?
- Unknown at this point.
Keep this line open.
Jack's OK. The team secured the store.
- What about Paul?
- He's with him.
- Has he anything from McLennan-Forster?
- We don't know yet.
Stay in touch.
Whatever they get, be ready to work up.
You got it.
Yeah?
-  You want us to help process?
- No. We'll do it when we sift the data.
-  Sure that's not a problem?
- Yeah.
- All right. We'll wait for your confirmation.
- Yeah. OK.
- Jack and Paul are OK.
- What about the information?
We don't know. Even if Jack has it, we don't
know that it'll bring us any closer to Marwan.
McLennan-Forster's involvement
should yield some leads.
That will have to be worked up here. Their
computers were knocked out by the EMP.
You want to head that up?
No. You know what?
You should probably let Curtis handle that.
All right, I will.
I shouldn't have said that earlier
about your drinking. I was out of line.
I'm sorry.
You don't owe me an apology.
My life right now...
Let's just say that I've been better.
Quite frankly, seeing you here today
has only made things worse.
Look, I'm gonna leave, get out of your hair
and let you do your job, all right?
No.
We can't afford to lose you.
Not today.
You're sure?
Yes.
Yes, I'm sure.
All right.
I'll make sure you get help
putting the store together.
I appreciate that.
Thank you.
Lee, I need you to get this to CTU.
It needs to get decoded immediately.
Set up a detail, five of your best men.
Nothing happens to this store. Understand?
Jack, look out!
Paul?
Paul? Paul! Medic!
Come on. Just stay with me.
Come on, Paul, stay with me.
No, no. Paul! Paul, stay with me.
Come on, look at me. Look at me.
There you go. Look at me.
I owed you.
You don't owe me anything.
Just stay with me.
Jack, it's OK. The medic's here.
Jack, let the medics do their work.
- Any problems?
- No, I'm here.
- Are we on schedule?
- Yes.
- What about you?
- I'm leaving now.
The President of the United States
is on a tight schedule. We can't be late.
Visiontext Subtitles: Sarah Johnston
ENGLISH SDH