I just spoke to my source
at Keeler's headquarters.
Sherry was there,
meeting privately with Keeler.
- Meeting Keeler about what?
-
I came here because I can guarantee you
a win in November.
David Palmer is an accessory to murder.
David lied to the chief of police last night
in order to provide an alibi for me.
- Why are you lying to me?
- I screwed up earlier.
The SAT transmission on my system
was forged by own people.
Making a mistake is one thing.
Covering it up is another.
I can't let you stay in place.
I am taking over command of CTU.
- I made a mistake, Jack.
- No, Tony. You made two.
I'm going to let you speak to your husband.
Tell him you're OK and being treated well.
-  Are you all right?
- I'm fine. Don't let them do this...
If Jane is not released when I order it,
your wife dies.
That's all you need to know. Are we clear?
From this point on, I am assuming control
of CTU. Tony Almeida has stepped down.
I'm taking Jane Saunders to Division.
Here's the order.
We're leaving right now.
We're going out this way right here.
- Where are all the guards?
- We don't need those guards.
Tony locked me in here. Saunders has
Michelle. He's using her to get his daughter.
- This is Almeida. We're out. I've got her.
- I'll give you instructions in 20 minutes.
Exit security, I need a 20 on Tony Almeida.
Chloe, pull up all the surveillance tape
from every exit. Focus on the last 10 minutes.
- Have you linked up with traffic yet?
- I'm working on it.
- I just heard Tony took Jane Saunders.
- That's right.
- Why?
- Saunders has Michelle.
- He wants to trade her.
- Jane is our only leverage.
I know that.
I got him. He left the building
and drove off the premises.
He's in a silver SUV. Prep a tactical team.
Be ready to move as soon as I give the order.
I got him. He's on 5th
about half a mile from here, heading east.
I'll call you from the car.
Son of a bitch.
- Are you OK?
- It's just traffic.
- You've been acting all weird since we left.
- There's a lot going on right now.
You never explained why you wanted
to transfer me to this Division place.
- I told you...
- I know. It doesn't make sense.
I don't have the time
to explain it to you right now.
Almeida got my daughter out of CTU.
Be ready to move the moment I tell you.
When are you calling Almeida
with instructions?
15 minutes. I'll be with Frederick.
At least 800 people are dead or dying
in the Chandler Plaza Hotel
because Saunders released a weaponized
virus into the ventilation system.
What the media is reporting is a cover story.
They're deflecting the truth
to avoid mass panic.
You'll be infected along with everyone else!
No matter what he's paying you,
it's not worth losing your life!
Jack's in pursuit of Tony. We move out
as soon as we get a location on Saunders.
Good.
- Kim, what are you doing?
- I'm on the team monitoring my father.
- I thought you were setting up a tactical unit.
- I am.
We have to wait
until we get a location on Saunders.
Listen. Before I have to go back out there,
I wanna talk to you.
About what?
About us.
I need to know
whether there's gonna be an us.
Look, I've been thinking about it a lot,
and the baby changes everything.
- It doesn't change the way I feel about you.
- Forget about me for a second.
You have a daughter
and a job that won't let you be with her.
Is that you talking or your father?
My dad would be the first one to admit it -
he wasn't the greatest dad.
And it wasn't because he didn't love me.
I know he loved me.
It was because of his job.
If I transferred out of field ops,
would you consider staying with me?
I wanna stay with you,
and I would raise a child with you, Chase.
I just won't raise one for you.
- Adam, is he still on 5th Street?
- No, he turned between Jarvis and Hill.
- Widen the search.
- I am.
Got him. He's going south on Vine, two
blocks below Hill. You could save time...
I got it.
He's hit traffic.
You might be able to intercept on Grant.
Look, I know you're lying to me.
I know you're not taking me to Division.
- You're fine, Jane.
- At least tell me where we're going.
- Where are you taking me?
- Back to your father.
My father? Why?
He's holding my wife hostage.
He'll kill her if I don't take you back to him.
So, basically, you're kidnapping me.
I'm sorry.
After everything he's done,
how can you be sure he'll do what he says?
How do you know
he won't kill your wife anyway?
I don't have a choice. I wish I did, but I don't.
Tony, put the gun on the dash!
Put the gun on the dash now!
Slowly get out of the car.
Jane, stay where you are.
Everything's gonna be fine.
- Saunders has Michelle.
- I know.
- He wants to make a trade.
- I know. I can't let that happen.
I almost lost her once today.
I understand exactly how you're feeling.
I've been there.
- And you handled it just like me!
- Millions of lives are at stake.
- Rules apply to other people, but not to you?
- Tony, just calm down, OK? Come on.
You help me make this trade,
I'll turn myself in, go to prison, whatever.
I can't do it.
We need Jane to lure her father in.
- Even if Michelle's gotta die?
- Michelle doesn't have to die.
We can string Saunders along.
Start working with me.
- Chase has already got a strike team.
- No!
- Saunders sees CTU, he kills Michelle.
- He's not gonna know we're there.
Where are you meeting him?
Tony, you don't have a choice. You've gotta
work with me on this. Where is the meeting?
Come on. Where are you meeting him?
He wants me to be at a payphone at the
corner of Taylor and Vine in five minutes.
He'll give me further instructions from there.
Thank you. You're doing the right thing.
The quarantined areas are in red.
As far as we know, we have containment.
- We're still not certain?
- We can't be certain for hours, maybe days.
The press is breathing
down Gerry's neck pretty hard.
- He thinks we should release a statement.
- I already have.
I've closed down public transportation
and told people to stay in their homes.
We have F-18s patrolling the skies.
But we haven't revealed the exact nature of
this threat, and the press is picking up on it.
We have 10 million people spread out
over a 4,000 square-mile area.
If even a small percentage
decide to leave at the same time,
it will ignite a public panic
beyond anything we could control.
The right thing to do is to withhold the truth
until we're sure the virus is contained.
I'll tell Gerry to hold off on the press
as long as he can.
Mr President.
- Yes, Jeannie?
- Senator Keeler's here to see you.
- Have him brought in.
- Yes, sir.
Thank you.
- Hello, John.
- Mr President.
- Please, take a seat.
- Thank you, I'll stand.
You can imagine my surprise
when I was told that you wanted to see me.
Are you withdrawing from the race?
Mr President, with respect to the death
of Alan Milliken, I know you lied to the police.
Excuse me?
You obstructed the investigation
of a capital crime.
That's a baseless charge. Though I've come
to expect this kind of recklessness from you.
No, sir, it is neither baseless nor reckless.
This is a photograph of the nitroglycerin
medicine that would have saved his life...
if it hadn't been kept from him.
You told the police Sherry was with you
at the time of Milliken's death.
Her fingerprints on this prescription bottle
prove otherwise.
Now, the last thing this country needs is to
have its president dragged through the mud
for complicity in a murder.
Why are you showing me this, John?
What do you want?
Your resignation.
Not immediately, of course.
But once this crisis
you're dealing with is over,
you can resign with whatever
face-saving reason you wanna give.
Get out of here.
I'm offering you the chance
to leave office with honor,
to control how your legacy is written.
It's a good deal, David.
You should take it.
I should go to the phone.
As soon as he tells you where he wants
the exchange to take place, reject the location.
We need him to pick a secondary location
so Chase has time to embed his teams.
If I don't go where he wants,
he's gonna kill Michelle.
Not as long as we have his daughter.
- What if he doesn't go for it?
- You've got some leverage here. Use it.
I need to go.
My father kidnapped his wife because of me?
Something like that.
And now you wanna use me
as bait to get to him.
We're gonna do whatever we have to
to stop your father from releasing this virus.
Stay here. We'll be right back.
- Where are we meeting?
- First let me speak with my daughter.
No, you can talk to her
when we make the exchange.
All right.
Bring her to an industrial park three miles
north of where you are on Morton Road.
A car will be waiting at loading dock 22.
Choose a new place. That doesn't work.
Make it work. You've got 10 minutes to get
to the industrial park or your wife will die.
- If we meet there, we all die.
- Really?
CTU has satellite surveillance of that area.
They're dedicating all their resources
to finding me right now. Pick a new spot.
I am not negotiating terms. I've planned
too long and too hard for this day.
I will do whatever it takes
to make sure nothing interferes,
even... even if it means
sacrificing my daughter.
You need to understand my commitment.
- What the hell you doing?
- He's testing you. He'll phone back.
- How do you know?
- He thinks I'm gonna kill his daughter.
He exposed himself
to make sure she's still safe.
That's what you'd do,
but you're not Saunders.
No matter how well you think
you know this guy, you're not him.
This isn't a game. She's my wife.
Michelle's got a chance if we control
the ground where the exchange takes place.
But protecting her is not your priority, is it?
If she were to get killed, that would be
an acceptable loss, wouldn't it?
My God, Jack. Didn't you learn anything
from what happened to Teri?
Shut up, Tony. Shut up!
Tony!
Just because you sacrificed your wife for this
job doesn't mean I'm gonna sacrifice mine!
I'm here.
Make no mistake, this is your first
and your last accommodation.
Just tell me where
you wanna make the exchange.
Downtown, under the 6th Street Bridge.
- Under the 6th Street Bridge.
- Be there in 30 minutes.
But if I see that you've brought anyone else
into this, I will kill your wife.
You did great.
Tony'll make the exchange, but until we know
that Saunders is on site, we stay invisible.
I'll assign positions on the way out. Let's go.
- What is it?
- Satellite pictures of 6th Street Bridge.
- I asked for real-time feed.
- We'll have it to you when you're on site.
- What about air support?
- We're coordinating with the marines.
Look, Chase...
please be careful.
Don't worry about me. I'll be fine.
Chloe, how much time before you can set up
a real-time satellite feed for 6th Street Bridge?
Do you really think Chase is gonna
quit field ops to start a family?
- He won't.
- It's none of your business.
I've known Chase for three years.
You've been dating for three months.
- Your point being?
- He's a great guy, but he's like your father.
They're the same, so if you're expecting him
to leave for the suburbs,
you should revise your expectations.
- When can you uplink a satellite feed?
- 10 minutes.
- Then do it.
- I'm just trying to be a friend, that's all.
- Hello?
- You've gone too far this time, Sherry.
I thought I might be hearing from you, David.
You sent Keeler over here to blackmail me
into giving up my presidency!
Whoa, whoa, slow down.
You mean Keeler paid you a visit?
You know damn well he did,
and you know why.
Only you could have given him
that prescription bottle.
OK, supposing that was true. What then?
- You could go to jail for murder.
- You could go to jail, too.
You lied to the police.
You told them that I was with you.
Withholding evidence, obstruction of justice.
Those are serious crimes.
I knew you wanted to go down in
the history books, but I'm not certain like this.
- What did Keeler offer you?
- What you should have offered me.
Respect, and a seat at the table.
But you called me up when you needed me,
and then after I did your little dirty work,
you threw me out like an old pair of shoes.
You know me, Sherry. Better than anyone.
You know I won't be bullied.
So before this goes too far,
you better ask yourself a question.
- Are you willing to go to jail?
- I've asked myself that a million times.
And the answer is yes,
I am willing to go to jail.
The question is, are you?
I didn't think so.
I want the strike team in two groups.
Group A can take cover here, group B here.
I want them ready to go when we get there.
If Saunders sees anyone,
he's not gonna make the approach.
- What's the response time for air support?
- 30 seconds.
- I'll relay the coordinates.
- See you at the bridge.
I know my father released the virus
in the hotel, that people died,
but do you really think
he'll do what he's saying?
Release it all over the country?
If we don't stop him, yes.
Why?
There has to be a reason he's doing all of this.
When I worked with him, he was dedicated
to saving the lives of innocent people.
Something's happened to him,
I don't know what,
but now he believes
our government's betrayed him.
Is he right?
There's no easy answer to that.
The work your father did often demanded
that he make seemingly impossible sacrifices.
Whatever happened to your father in Bosnia
was a sacrifice he wasn't willing to make.
I'm sorry.
-  No!
- Shut up! No one can hear you.
Shut up now!
No!
- No! Oh, God!
- I said stop. Stop screaming.
Look at me. I've been infected.
Help me. Help me.
Oh, God!
No.
- We got a problem here.
- What's going on?
- She has it. She has the virus.
- What are you talking about?
She's bleeding.
She must have caught it at the hotel.
They wouldn't release her
without testing her. It's a trick.
She did it to herself.
Kevin, are you there? Kevin!
Take the east corridor. Stop her from getting
above ground, but do not shoot to kill.
O'Brian.
-  Chloe, it's me. It's Michelle.
- Hello?
Can you hear me?
Whoever this is,
I have a really bad connection.
Chloe!
So what did Keeler want?
My job.
He has proof that Sherry
was at Alan Milliken's tonight.
What? What proof?
Alan Milliken's prescription bottle turned up
with Sherry's fingerprints on it.
- How did he get ahold of this?
- How do you think?
Sherry?
I talked to her a few minutes ago.
She didn't even bother to deny it.
She's gotta be bluffing.
If this gets out, she goes to jail.
So will I.
She figures I have more to lose than she does.
- And she's right.
- What does Keeler want you to do?
Withdraw from the race...
for whatever reason I choose.
The party gets thrown into chaos.
Whoever takes my place
won't have a prayer in the election.
And Keeler becomes president.
Oh, my God.
This is all my fault.
Hey, look.
We both made mistakes.
I'm the one who called Sherry.
- There may be a way out of this.
- How?
Without this, Sherry's got nothing, right?
- What are you suggesting?
- We take away the only leverage she has.
You mean steal evidence?
- My God, Wayne.
- Before you say no, you just think about this.
I can call Foxton
and he can make this disappear.
All you have to do is give me the OK.
You stay with her.
- Is your team in place?
- Two minutes, they'll be ready.
- They'll be out of sight?
- They'll be invisible.
- I'm gonna back Tony up here.
- We should get into position.
- Priority call from Kim.
- This is Jack.
- I got Michelle on the line.
- Is she with Saunders?
No, she said she got away from him.
- Patch her through.
- Hold on.
- Michelle, go ahead.
- I got away from Saunders, but he's after me.
Michelle, it's me. Where are you?
Wilshire. A block east of Olive.
- Send your strike team in now.
- Don't.
- What are you talking about?
- Michelle, listen.
- Let Saunders catch you again.
- Are you crazy?
We have to let the exchange go down.
It's the only way to catch him.
- You want me to give myself up?
- Yes. The exchange site is secure.
- I'll send our people in when he's there.
- Redirect your people now!
- Chase, don't!
- Jack, stay out of this!
You are not in command here.
Get him out of here now! Now!
That's my wife, Jack, you son of a bitch!
My wife! Jack!
We need this exchange to go through.
Everything depends on it. Understand?
If he doesn't have you to trade,
he's not gonna go through with this meeting.
We're not gonna get another chance at this.
Do you understand, Michelle?
Yes.
We're gonna do everything to make sure you
come out of this OK, but we gotta move now.
Let's get our teams into position.
I thought your brother was a politician
who would never lower himself to my level.
I need to recover something
that could cause him a lot of trouble.
- What is it?
- A bottle of medicine from a crime scene.
- Has it been admitted into evidence?
- No.
It's in the possession of Sherry Palmer,
the president's ex-wife.
I have a pretty good idea where she is and
can partially reconstruct where she's been.
- What time frame are we looking at?
- Hours, Foxton, not days.
Has this... operation been authorized
by the president?
What difference does that make?
You'll get your money.
I'm not worried about that.
I just need to know who I'm working for.
My brother knows what you're doing.
Not that I don't trust you, but...
I'd like to hear it from him.
Fine.
That's proof enough.
Let's go.
Do Chase's men have Saunders yet?
No one's coming yet.
Look, Jack, promise me you won't make
a move on Saunders until Michelle is safe.
We move as soon as we've got a visual
on Saunders. That's how it's gotta go.
I know. I'm... I'm just asking you
just to do what you can.
You know I will.
We've got three cars headed in from the west.
- Tony, they're coming. Are you ready?
- Yeah.
Windows are tinted. I can't see inside.
-  Give her the phone.
My preference is to turn you over
to your husband unharmed.
But I will kill you if anything goes wrong.
Yeah.
When I see my daughter,
you get your wife.
Right.
Jane, I need you to get out of the car.
Everything's gonna be OK.
- I want you to walk over to your father's men.
- Where's my father?
We don't know.
Listen, we have to do this, Jane. I'm sorry.
Look, Jane, you gotta trust me on this.
Please, go. Come on.
- Jack, send your men in now.
- We don't have a visual on Saunders.
- I can't.
- Come here!
- Turn around!
- Jane, it's OK! Come here!
Teams A and B move.
We've got a visual on Saunders. Move now!
Stephen!
I'm pinned down! Saunders has a helicopter.
Call in air support now!
- I repeat, call in air support!
- I need air support!
I've got two US marine F-18s just off
the marina, call sign Guardian Angel.
Copy that! Guardian Angel,
this is Watchtower!
We got a hostile at vector Bravo Tango!
Jack, marines are coming in.
Take cover.
Let's go! Let's go!
Chopper's been taken out!
- You OK?
- Yeah.
Don't move!
11 vials of the virus are unaccounted for.
Where are they?
- It's not gonna be that simple, Jack.
- Stephen, it's over.
No, it's not, Jack. It's just beginning.
Where are the vials?
You can waste time trying to break me
and kill millions of people.
Or you can give me what I want.
This is Jack Bauer. Saunders is in custody.