Transcript by Addic7ed.com
Cole, he's dead.
Just go. Nobody knows you had
anything to do with this.
I don't want you involved.
I'm already involved.
We're cleaning this up,
and no one's never gonna
know what happened.
They're scum, Dana,
and no one's gonna miss 'em.
Kayla may be in danger.
She's run away.
With Tarin.
She's somewhere in the city
with no idea that a
nuclear threat exists.
And, Omar, what about you?
Don't worry about me.
Just help me find our daughter.
Come inside.
They have the rods
you are looking for.
I thought you had the rods.
They turned against me.
I can help you find them.
Just get me out of here.
You find Farhad?
Still looking.
He won't get far.
Medic! Come on! Medic!
I need you to identify the men
who stole the nuclear
rods from you.
Can you do that for us? Yes.
Blood pressure's dropping.
We got a rapid heartbeat.
We lost him. Farhad's dead.
Damn it!
Whoever shot Farhad
couldn't confirm
that he was killed.
I'm saying that we use
Farhad as dead bait.
Leak it to the press
that we've got him in custody,
and he survived,
and they'll have to make
a move on him.
Tell the support teams
it is imperative that
we take these terrorists alive.
Go! Go!
It's all right.
We just want to talk to you.
No. No!
He's still moving.
Notify the perimeter.
It was a trap.
Farhad was already dead.
I locked myself in some
kind of oxygen chamber.
They can't get in here.
You know what you must do.
I can't. They scrambled
the arming code.
You need to set it off manually.
You cannot let them take you alive.
Can you hear me?
What's the status?
The hyperbaric chamber is
one-inch steel all around.
Hermetically sealed,
air and power systems are internal.
Also, its atmosphere is
most likely oxygen-enriched.
Anything we use to blow the
door could ignite a fire inside.
How long will it take to cut in?
We need to use a low-speed
drill to avoid sparks.
How long?
Best estimate- 40 minutes,
unless you want us
to push the risk.
I can't take the chance.
We need him alive.
Agent Bauer, the techs have got
the internal cameras online.
We have eyes on him.
What about the intercom?
The intercom's still down
from when he shorted out
the locking mechanism.
And the bomb techs say we
have a bigger problem. What?
They assumed that once we jammed
the signal to the detonator,
it'd be impossible for the
suspect to explode the vest.
Turns out that may not be the case.
He's reconfiguring the circuits.
Yeah. The detonator's
German military,
so our guys are familiar with it.
The end-around he's
sketched out here will work.
What's the timeframe?
Well, it depends on
how fast he works.
He needs to reset four circuits.
That LED light indicates
he's already completed one.
When he wires the other three,
he'll be able to explode
the device at will.
The only upside is the chamber
will contain the blast.
No one else will be hurt.
He's not trying to hurt anybody.
He's trying to make sure
we don't take him alive.
Get that intercom up and running.
I need to talk to him as
soon as possible. Sir.
This is Bauer.
Let me speak to Hastings.
So, what have you got, Jack?
It looks like our suspect
might be able to get
the detonator working
before we can get to him.
Owen will fill you
in on the details.
Right now, I need to know
everything you've got on him.
I'm just pulling up the
information now, Jack.
It took a while to get it from
Hassan's intelligence people.
Just give me the overview.
Okay, Marcos Al-Zacar
was born here,
raised in East Harlem.
Mother's American,
father was from the IRK-
that's where Al-Zacar
got his politics from.
His father was a professor
known to be highly critical
of American foreign policies,
suspected of connections
with extremists.
He was imprisoned by Wayne
Palmer's administration
for four months.
Although the charges
were eventually dropped,
he was unhireable after that.
Almost a year later,
he committed suicide.
That must have been
what triggered Al-Zacar.
He started spying
on America for the IRK
two months after that.
What about the mother?
Checking current records.
According to motor vehicle
and utility records
she's still in East Harlem.
4211 East 117th Street.
Find her and get her
here as soon as possible.
We're on it, Jack. Keep us posted.
Copy that.
We have to assume the people
building this dirty bomb
want to hit a high-value
target here in Manhattan.
But first, they've got
to get it on the island.
We should shut down the city? No.
We want them to make the attempt
to move the radiological materials.
It's our best chance
of catching them.
First, we have to make sure
that all of our radiation
sensors are strictly monitored
at all crossings.
Arlo, that goes for the
drone sensors, too.
Yes, sir.
That's all.
Cole?
We went over this.
All we have to do is act natural.
Keep our heads.
You'll be okay.
I am not worried about me.
You can't really be this calm
after what just happened.
You've never broken
a law in your life.
Cole.
What do you want me to say?
I don't know! Anything.
Tell me you hate me.
Tell me that you'll never
forgive me for lying to you.
We're not doing this now.
I told you to walk away... Not now!
We're in the middle
of a radiological threat.
We got jobs to do.
When it's over, then we'll talk.
Look, I can't promise things are
going back to the way they were.
But I wouldn't have done what I
did if I didn't still love you.
You two have holy
hell to answer for.
Sir, I'm sorry.
I can explain... Save it.
If you were following up a lead,
you should have been
updating me every 20 minutes.
You broke protocol.
The lead didn't pan out.
Witness proved to be unreliable.
But you're right, sir,
there's no excuse.
I should have called in.
And you were supposed
to be servicing
a faulty relay station.
Yet I see you found time
to change your clothes.
Look.
I don't know what's
going on with you two
and, frankly, I don't care.
If we weren't at high alert,
and you weren't the
best at what you do,
you'd both be out on
your asses for this.
I'm going to ask you once.
Whatever it is, are you finished?
Yes, sir. Good.
Walsh, until further notice,
you will answer to Chloe O'Brian.
She will fill you in on
what she needs from you.
Bauer has a situation at St.
Julian's Hospital.
I need you to assemble
a team, pick up
an Elaine Al-Zacar from East 117th
and take her to him.
Is she a hostile? Unclear.
Arlo will fill you
in on the details.
Yes, sir. How you perform
from this point will
determine whether or not
you salvage your careers.
Now, get to work.
Yes?
I'm in place.
I've managed to tap into the
hospital's security cameras.
But we can only pick up audio
in the hallway outside the room.
CTU has set up a
command center there.
Can you see Marcos?
Yes. He's still working
on the detonator.
Are you able to gauge his progress?
He already has one of the
four circuits reconfigured.
We're arriving at the landing now.
Soon we'll be able to transport
the rods into Manhattan.
Are CTU's radiation sensors down?
Not yet. But we'll be ready.
Call me when Marcos is dead.
Port Authority's reporting no hits
on the radiation
sensors at the Holland,
Midtown and Lincoln Tunnels.
I don't see any stream
updates for the GW,
Brooklyn or Queens crossings.
What the problem?
MTA's providing that feed
on a dedicated sublink to
prevent a server overload.
You can access it yourself on
the system's Ethernet port.
So there's really no problem.
There's no way I
could have known that
since you didn't put
that in your hourlies.
Right. I will do that next time.
I know this must be hard for you,
having to report to me
since you've been demoted.
It's okay, Chloe, I deserved it.
Yeah, you did.
I just want you to know I'm
actually glad you didn't get
fired or anything and...
Hang in there.
Thank you. I appreciate that.
Where are we on aerial detection?
I've got drones covering
every inch of the waterfront
with their radiation
detectors cranked up.
If they try to bring the fuel rods
into the city by boat,
we'll spot them.
Easily.
Look, I know you probably
hate my guts right now,
but I just wanted you
to know that I'm sorry.
For telling Cole about
you and that other guy.
I mean, you were definitely
messing up, and with the threat
of those rods out there...
Don't worry about it, Arlo.
So is he gone?
Who?
You know.
The other guy.
Yeah.
Yeah, he's gone.
So, you and the Boy Scout are okay?
We'll get through it.
I'm glad.
But if for some reason
that changes... I know.
Meaning, if you ever decide
you want to trade up...
I got it.
Sir, we got the intercom
to the chamber working.
You should be able to
talk to the suspect.
Good. Tell CTU I'll keep my
comm up so they can monitor.
Yes, sir.
Marcos, my name is Jack Bauer.
I'm working with CTU.
I know the original plan was
to smuggle the fuel rods back
to the IRK to reconstitute
their nuclear program.
So I'm just guessing
that helping to deliver a
dirty bomb to New York City
which will cost the lives
of tens of thousands
of innocent people isn't
exactly what you signed on for.
But the truth is if you do this,
you'll be killing the IRK.
By bombing New York City,
you're going to force
President Taylor to retaliate,
and she will, hard.
You can't possibly want that.
It doesn't matter what I want.
This so-called peace agreement,
it's just Hassan
signing away my country's
ability to defend itself,
its independence.
He's surrendering without a fight.
But there are a lot of
people in his own government
who are not willing to do that.
Marcos, you can't win this fight.
The IRK will sustain massive
casualties because of this.
Because of you.
Not because of me.
America will be the one
dropping all the bombs.
No, son.
The eyes of the world
will hold you responsible
for the innocent lives
taken in New York City.
No, don't think you can take
the moral high ground with me.
The arrogance of this country.
That it feels it can dictate
to the rest of the world
who gets... who gets to
have nuclear weapons,
while it insists on keeping
my people in the Dark Ages.
You keep saying "your people,
your country."
Marcos, I read your file.
You were born here.
You're an American citizen.
Your father is from the IRK.
You leave my father out of this!
What happened to your father
was unfair and tragic,
but this is no way
to honor his memory.
Please, you can still
do the right thing here.
You can help me stop
this from happening.
All you have to do
is open the door.
Please, I'm begging you.
You're not going to get
me to change my mind.
I came here prepared to die.
And that's what's going to happen.
Marcos.
Please, just talk to me.
Marcos!
Yes, of course. I understand.
We'll see you soon.
Thank you.
Your friend at the
State Department-
you trust he can do what he says,
give us asylum?
Yes.
He says with what your
father has been doing-
ordering unlawful
arrest and torture-
U.S. law will consider
us political refugees.
But you have to understand,
asylum will not be
granted overnight.
Well, how long are
we talking about?
A year, maybe 18 months.
But as soon as we
file the application,
we are protected by the law.
Your father cannot touch us.
You know that I will not be
able to work here legally
until asylum has been granted.
I have some savings.
But I will not be able
to give you the life that
you have been used to.
Oh, you know I don't
care about any of that.
One minute.
Oh... my mother again.
I really should answer it. Kayla.
No, she deserves to
know I'm all right.
Give that back to me!
Please. You know what?
You can call her
when the lawyer has
filed the application.
We must wait until then.
Bye-bye.
Kayla, it's me again.
Darling, I need to talk to you.
Your father told me
something terrible
may be happening here in New York.
Please, call me back as soon as you
get this message.
I still can't reach her.
Thank you for coming back.
Our daughter is missing.
I'm not leaving until I
know she's all right.
We'll find her, Dalia.
Nabeel told me you
had Tarin arrested.
I didn't know who I could trust.
So you started arresting people
from inside your own delegation?
What possible evidence could
you have gathered so quickly?
I had to do something. But Tarin?
He's one of your most loyal men.
So was my brother.
Or so I thought.
Until he tried
to have me killed and
destroy my government.
If you continue to act
the way you have been,
you will have done the job for him.
Have you told the police?
I've been trying to
deal with it on my own.
But it's time to get them involved.
Dalia, I'm sorry.
As you should be!
This city is under attack!
Our daughter is god knows where!
You drove her away
with your suspicion
and your paranoia!
How could you, Omar?
How could you have lost your way?
Dalia.
You're right.
I have.
I have. I see that now.
And I'll make changes.
I'll do everything in my power
to find her.
And get her safe.
You have my word.
I am sorry.
Dalia, I'm sorry.
Who is it?
Elaine Al-Zacar?
What do you want?
My name is Cole Ortiz.
I'm an agent with CTU.
I need you to open
that door, ma'am.
I don't understand.
What's this about?
Your son, Marcos.
Marcos?
Ma'am, you're either
going to open that door
or I'm gonna break it down. Now!
Go!
Mrs. Al-Zacar, are you aware
of where your son is right now?
Not at the moment.
How much do you know
about his activities on behalf
of the IRK? Uh...
I know that he
communicates with family there,
if that's what you mean.
You going somewhere?
I was just about to leave
to my sister's house.
You do that a lot, take trips
to visit relatives at 2:
30 in the morning?
No, I don't. I can explain.
Marcos called me about an hour ago.
He told me to leave the city.
He said he needed me to meet him
at my sister's house
in Pennsylvania.
He didn't tell you
anything else? No.
I swear.
Ma'am, right now your son's
barricaded himself at St.
Julian's Hospital,
trying to blow himself
up with a suicide vest.
Oh, my God. No!
I need you to come with me to St.
Julian's- ma'am.
We don't know how much longer we
have till your son can activate
the explosives; we have to go.
Yes?
Sir, Cole just checked in.
He's got Al-Zacar's
mother and he's en route
to St. Julian's now.
What's his ETA?
Less than ten minutes.
All right, then. Thank you.
Sir, I would like
to apologize again
for leaving my post.
I know that I let you down.
Yes, you did.
I brought you in and
gave you this promotion
because I saw something in you,
not just your skill,
which is considerable.
But an ability to adapt
to any situation,
drive to be better,
attributes that make
you a good leader.
Or did I misread that?
No, sir.
So we can chalk up the
last several hours
to a serious lapse in judgment?
What I was... Look.
I don't want to lose you or Cole.
You're both valuable,
but everyone is replaceable.
I screwed up and I'm willing
to accept the consequences.
I know that Cole
feels the same way.
Thank you, sir.
Hello?
Can I ask who I'm speaking with?
Excuse me?
Would you mind telling
me your name, please?
This is Dana Walsh. Who is this?
Forgive me, Miss Walsh,
for calling at this ungodly hour.
I actually expected
to leave a message.
I'm sorry if I woke you.
No, no, that's okay.
I'm actually at work.
What is this regarding?
Well, my name's Prady.
I'm with the Department of Corrections
down in Little Rock.
I'm trying to locate an individual
by the name of Kevin Wade.
I- I'm sorry.
Who did you say
that you were again?
Bill Prady.
I'm a probation officer.
Mr. Wade is one of my charges.
Do you know him?
No, no. I don't think that I do.
Well, that's peculiar since
he dialed this number
a few days ago from a
motel room in Queens.
Probably just a misdial.
No. Dialed this
number more than once,
and some of the calls lasted
more than a couple of minutes.
Look, Mr. Prady,
I am really busy right now.
I work for CTU and we are
in the middle of a crisis.
Well, I completely understand.
I've heard the news.
But since we're both awake,
I wonder if I could
meet with you in person.
You mean now?
Well, I got an early flight
to Little Rock in the morning,
so, yeah, it'd pretty much
have to be now, ma'am.
I'm sorry. I-
I don't really understand
why this is so pressing.
Well, Miss Walsh,
I've grown kind of fond
of young Kevin, and the longer
it takes me to find him,
the harder it'll be for me
to keep him from going
back into prison.
I don't really see how
I can be of any help.
Yeah, well, maybe not.
But we can determine
that when we speak.
Like I said, it won't take long.
Look, if it'll smooth things over,
I could call your supervisor.
No, no. That won't be necessary.
I'm sure that I could spare
a few minutes for you.
Thank you, ma'am.
That would be super.
Tell you what.
Let me just pull over,
and I'll get your address.
All right?
Of course.
Sir, according to the bomb techs,
he's close.
Getting that third circuit
active was the toughest part.
The fourth is only a matter of
rerouting the firing circuits.
What's the time frame?
Ten minutes, maybe less.
How much longer is it going
to take them to drill through?
Too long. They're not
going to make it.
Get her some water.
Take care of that.
Did she resist?
Not once I told her
her boy had explosives
strapped to him and was
going to blow himself up.
She had a packed suitcase, Jack.
So he cares enough about her
to make sure she got out of town.
What else does she know?
Nothing, as far as I can tell.
And I didn't tell
her anything more.
Okay, good.
Mrs. Al-Zacar,
my name is Jack Bauer.
I'm in charge of field
operations here.
Where is he? I'm going
to take you to him.
I want to see him.
I'm going to take you to him.
Please sit down. I need you to
fully understand the situation.
Please.
This is Ortiz.
Cole, it's me.
Kevin's probation
officer just called me.
He's in New York,
trying to track down Kevin.
I can't talk to you about this now.
We're in the middle here.
Listen to me. I told him I
didn't know who Kevin was,
but... he caught me in the lie.
He has records that show him
calling my cell several times.
Cole, this probation
officer is on his way here.
Look, you're going to have
to figure out a reason
why he had your number.
I don't know if I can do this.
What, lie? Come on,
we both know you're good at it.
Sorry.
Look, you just have
to handle this. Okay?
All right?
Yeah.
Let me know what happens.
I got to go.
I can't believe this is happening.
You need to believe it.
The men your son is working with
intend on detonating
a radiological bomb
somewhere in Manhattan.
That's why your son tried
to get you out of the city.
Marcos has been an
agent for the IRK,
spying on this country
since your husband died.
We have proof of that.
And now he's going to kill himself
in order to protect this plot
unless you can
convince him otherwise.
What do-what do I say to him?
Whatever you have to,
to get him to stop rearming that vest,
and open the door.
We need him to open the door.
Do you understand?
If he does that,
then what happens to him?
He'll be alive.
If he cooperates with us,
I promise you,
I will do everything
I can to help him.
I give you my word.
Ma'am, I'm sorry,
but we need to do this now.
We need the room.
Now.
It's definitely her.
Marcos's mother.
You recruited him, Ali.
You know him better than anyone.
Will she be able to talk him down?
He's loyal to our country.
I don't think so.
ELAINE Marcos?
Marcos, it's me.
Mom, what are you doing here?
Marcos, you have to stop this.
This is crazy.
You son of a bitch!
Leave us alone!
You leave us alone!
Marcos, talk to me.
Oh, my God, Mom. I told you
to get out of the city.
I told you to go to Aunt Shelley's.
Why didn't you listen to me?
I'm listening now.
You told me that you were
going to meet me there.
I believed you.
I was trying to protect you.
From a terrorist attack?
That's what they say that
you're involved in here.
Something that's going to
kill many, many people.
Marcos, tell me that's not true!
Tell me!
Marcos, why?
You ask me that?
After what this country did to Dad?
Marcos, I loved your father.
You know I did.
But he was a complicated man,
and especially when it
came to his politics.
But he never condoned
violence of any kind, Marcos.
Never.
He would agree with
what we're doing.
You really think that?
He hated America.
And yet he came to America.
He married an American.
He had an American son.
Honey, nothing is as simple
as you're making it out to be.
Mr. Hastings.
I've registered a 12%
degradation in the hospital's
security feed.
Can you boost the signal?
You're missing the point.
The indications are someone's
tapped into the feed.
They can see everything we can.
I wish I'd done more.
I wish I'd helped you
deal with your grief
and with your anger.
No, don't put this on yourself.
You couldn't have done any more
or been a better mother.
She's almost got him.
CHLOE Jack, do you copy?
Yeah, Chloe. Go ahead.
The video feed has
been compromised.
You're being surveilled.
Copy that. I'll take
care of it from here.
Owen, how long will it take to
disconnect the video system?
30 seconds.
Get on it. What's going on, Jack?
Someone else is watching.
Mom...
I know what they want you to do.
But it's too late for that.
Don't say that.
You can still turn yourself in.
We'll hire the best lawyers,
whatever it takes.
I'll be with you every
step of the way.
I promise that.
I'm sorry.
Marcos, I'm-I'm begging you.
Mom, listen to me.
You got to be strong now.
Damn it. No. Marcos.
Marcos,
please. You're all I have.
Please don't do this.
I love you so much.
I'm sorry. It's over.
Get her out of there.
I'm sorry. Now! Move!
Marcos, No! No!
No! Marcos, no!
No! No!
Samir, I just lost picture.
Is his mother still in the room?
No, but he's still in there
with one of the agents.
You detonate that vest,
your mother dies, too.
What did you say?
You heard me.
I'm going to make sure
your mother's in Manhattan
when that dirty bomb goes off.
You don't even know
what the target is.
I'm not talking about her
dying during the explosion.
I'm going to personally
escort her to the blast site,
so she's exposed to the radiation.
I don't believe you.
you wouldn't do that.
You're a federal agent.
Truth is, I'm not, really.
Well, not anymore.
I'm more of a specialist that
they brought in for today.
If you knew who I was,
and things I've done
before in my life,
you would know that
I'm not bluffing.
So, go ahead.
Blow yourself up into
a million pieces.
First thing I'm going
to do is I'm going
to make your mother come
in here and clean it up.
And then I'm going to take
her to the blast site.
Do you know how long
it takes a human body
to absorb a lethal
dose of cesium 137?
Five seconds.
Followed by 12 days of pain
that's so agonizing,
morphine can't even touch it.
You got a decision to make.
Make it carefully.
You're not gonna hurt my mother.
I am done playing with you.
You look into my eyes.
Look in my eyes!
You think I'm joking.
What happens to your
mother is because of you.
Only you.
If I open the door and I come out,
you promise you won't hurt her?
You promise you'll leave her alone?
I give you my word.
Cole, I've got some
action on the door.
Put your hands up now!
Walk towards me! Move!
Down on your knees!
Put your hands behind your head
and interlock your fingers!
Don't you move!
Cole, I got four lights on.
Damn it!
Cole, I got four lights on!
We need bomb techs now.
The suspect's come
out of the chamber,
but he's managed to arm the vest.
I repeat: he has armed the vest.
We need bomb techs
here to disable it now!
Samir, Marcos is
out of the chamber.
What?! They must have
talked him out it,
but he's rearmed the vest.
You're sure? He's still wearing it?
Yes, I think so.
Hang up right now and
transmit the fail-safe.
Let's move!
Keep you men back!
I know the circuit pattern!
I'm looking for four common leads
before I can disarm it.
What's happening?! What is that?!
Cole, they must have
triggerd a fail-safe.
Get you men back now.
Move! Move! Move!
Get this off of me!
I'm gonna try! Just stay calm!
Mom!
Get her out of here now!
Marcos, I might not be
able to do this in time.
I need to know what the target is.
I don't know. How are they
gonna smuggle the fuel
rods into the city
past the radiological detectors?
I don't know, I swear!
Who does?!
Give me a name.
Damn it, Marcos, give me a name!
President Hassan's head
of security Tarin Faroush!
Tarin Faroush.
Did you get that, Cole?
Copy! Come on.
Come on. Come on.
One more.
I'm not gonna be able
to do this in time.
You tell my mother I'm sorry.
Jack? Jack, do you copy?
CTU, this is Jack.
Marcos is dead.
I'm gonna need to speak
to President Hassan.
Commissioner, I appreciate
that your NYPD's overburdened,
but I would ask you
to do whatever you can
to have my daughter's
picture circulated.
Please keep me posted
if you get any information
regarding her whereabouts.
Yes.
Thank you.
Sir, CTU is routing a call to you.
From whom?
Jack Bauer.
Yes, Mr. Bauer?
This is President Hassan.
Mr. President,
I was told you were briefed
on the situation at St.
Julian's Hospital.
I was.
Sir, the suicide bomber is dead.
His explosive vest was
remotely detonated.
Then you have no leads.
No, sir, we actually do.
Before the suspect was killed,
he identified your
head of security,
Tarin Faroush, as a co-conspirator.
Tarin?
Are you sure about this?
Yes, sir. Right now you
need to call UN security
and have them take Mr.
Faroush into custody until we get there.
That won't be possible, Mr. Bauer.
Tarin's not here.
Where is he?
I don't know.
Somewhere with my daughter.
Excuse me?
They are in love...
so I've learned.
Mr. Bauer, I suspected
Tarin hours ago,
and had him arrested
for questioning.
He escaped while being
transported to our embassy.
Kayla believed he was innocent,
and has, apparently,
run away with him.
Do you have any idea
where they might be?
None. Can you contact
your daughter?
My wife has made several attempts,
but she isn't answering her phone.
Sir, you need to keep trying.
Right now Mr.
Faroush is our only lead.
I'm going to jump in the shower.
Hello, Mother.
Kayla?
I have her.
Mr. Bauer, Darling,
are you all right?
we have Kayla on
line with her mother.
Oh, I'm fine, Mother. Mr.
President, you need to get me an address.
I'm sorry I've been
ignoring your calls,
but I know Father has
put you up to this.
Where are you? You know
I can't tell you that.
Is Tarin with you?
Not at the moment, no.
He doesn't want me
to speak to anyone.
Kayla, listen to me,
you are in danger.
Tarin is working with
your father's enemies.
That's not true.
It's Father's paranoid delusions.
It isn't.
CTU just called to confirm.
They're on the line
with your father now.
I don't believe you.
Kayla, please.
You know I loathed
your father's behavior
and the way that he's
handled everything.
I wouldn't be telling you this
unless I believed it, too.
Not Tarin.
It has to be a mistake.
Then we'll sort it out together.
But you must tell me where you are.
Kayla!
The Teodore Hotel, suite 514.
The Teodore, suite 514.
Mr. Bauer. Kayla, darling,
just stay where you are.
The police will be there shortly.
They are at the Teodore Hotel,
suite 514.
Thank you, sir.
I promise I'll call you once
the Americans give us asylum.
Please don't tell Father we spoke.
Kayla? I love you, too. Hello?
I thought we agreed
you weren't gonna take
your mother's call.
I'm sorry, my love.
I just didn't want her to worry.
Did you tell her where we are?
Did you?
Of course not.
Do you think I'm stupid?
You know I could never
think such a thing.
You are perfection.
Now come on. We must get dressed.
Where are we going?
Where do you think?
To formally request our asylum.
At this hour?
My friend at
the State Department
made the arrangements.
But I'm exhausted.
We haven't even slept.
I suppose you blame
me for that, huh?
Well, then... can't we have
a little more time together?
No. Come on.
You must get dressed.
Why don't you just
get dressed here?
I'm just gonna clean up first.
He's in the Teodore Hotel,
suite 514.
And Kayla's... Kayla's with him.
Our men are clearing out now.
It's all yours.
Where are we?
I could have a Tac team at
the Teodore in 20 minutes.
No, NYPD can get there faster.
I want your men to
set up a perimeter
and wait until we get there.
If any of your men
happen to come in contact
with the suspect,
it is imperative that they know
we need to take him alive.
Let's go.