I need to know about my brother.
He's alive.
Get out now.
It can't be long
before they realize it's you.
I need you to get
back in the car.
Ah!
Your brother was involved
with the attack.
He's the insider
we've been looking for.
What's going on?
The body triggered
a Hazmat alarm.
It's highly
enriched uranium.
You mean it's weapons-grade?
How the hell did he come
into contact with that?
I think I know the answer.
Someone approached my brother
with weapons-grade uranium.
Who?
Someone who had access
to decommissioned
Soviet stockpile.
You must find the Russians
before they can get
the uranium to my brother.
I want proof
that the rods exist,
or you will not be paid.
You want proof, huh?
Come with me.
My younger son,
he was transporting the rods,
and he was careless.
There, you have your proof.
You were undercover
for nearly two years
with the Russian mob.
Your cover is still intact.
Are you asking me
to go back in?
Agent Walker hasn't been
undercover for over six years.
I think you're making
a mistake by putting her in.
You must have other options.
She's our only way in.
Fine, then I want
to go with her.
I assume your plan is
trying to set up
a competing buy?
I'll act as a buyer.
I'm looking for Vladimir.
Vlad disappeared.
But you can find him.
They know where I am 24/7.
I'm still in prison.
Parole bracelet?
I can get this off.
You can't cut bracelet.
I'm not gonna cut the bracelet.
What the hell have you done?!
That's it,
this is over.
Maybe for you, Jack, but
I'm just getting started.
I thought you were
dead or captured.
Where have you been?
It took me this long
to get clear.
I'm with Bazhaev.
To hell with Bazhaev!
Everything we have worked for,
it's all over because of him.
It's not over, General.
Of course it is!
Your brother
is still alive,
and your plan to replace him
as head of state is finished.
Now his security forces
are rounding up our people
all over the city.
General Amiri was just pulled
from his home five minutes ago,
in front of his wife
and children.
Look, the Americans
won't let him continue.
They'll accuse him
of human rights violations
and threaten to pull out
of the peace talks.
Once we have the uranium,
my brother will become
irrelevant anyway.
You are being hunted
like an animal.
How do you expect
to get the uranium?
Bazhaev can deliver it to us,
but first I need payment
wired to his account.
It's all right.
Mm. Thank you.
Papa, there's a clinic
in Mt. Vernon.
I found a doctor
who can treat him.
We have been through this.
No doctors.
Yes, but this one
has a family.
I know where they are,
I know their names.
I'll make sure
he keeps his mouth shut.
And you can guarantee
no one else in this clinic
will find out?
Another doctor, a nurse, no one?
The authorities know
about the nuclear material
or they will soon enough,
and they'll be
looking everywhere.
Putting Oleg in a clinic
would lead them right to us.
He's going to die if
we don't get him help.
Then he's going to die.
But alone like this?
In a cold room
behind the kitchen?
He's my brother, Papa,
and he's your son.
All right.
Take him to the country house.
Ulana will look after him.
Thank you, Papa.
What is it?
Farhad is asking for you.
You have news for me?
Yes.
The money will be transferred
to your account shortly.
When can I take
possession of the rods?
As soon as we have the money.
Five hours.
Good.
I'll help you pass the time.
You have a preference?
No.
Then take both.
He's still bleeding out.
This should cauterize the wound.
Okay, it's working.
Who are you calling?
Hastings.
Why?
Because I'm shutting
this operation down.
You shouldn't be in the
field, and this proves it.
This was the only play, Jack.
You would've done
the same thing.
The play was to get him
to cooperate.
He will cooperate.
How do you figure?
Look, I know these guys, Jack.
The only thing that Ziya likes
more than 13-year-old girls
is money.
í  He'd have butchered himself
for a score like this.
Yeah, well, Hastings still
needs to know the truth.
The truth?
That you're unstable!
Look... I don't blame you
after everything
you've been through,
but you are not fit
for this mission.
I went through
a rough patch, yeah,
but I came out
on the other side.
And I don't think you have.
The bottom line is,
I'm still the best chance
that anyone has of
intercepting that uranium,
and I can do it now.
So, what's it going to be, you
making that phone call or what?
He's waking up, Jack.
Better make up your mind.
Fine.
You see what you can
get out of him.
But don't forget, I'm listening.
Renee!
Shut up, Ziya.
You'll get your painkillers
as soon as we get out of here.
What did you do?!
I got the bracelet off,
all right, I did you a favor.
You crazy bitch!
You cut off thumb!
Look, what's done is done.
You can either stay here
and whine about it like a baby,
or you can come with me
and be a rich man.
Look, I'm willing to give you a
point on this deal off the top.
It's a lot of money, Ziya.
How much?
Two-and-a-half million.
Maybe three when it's all done.
Two million?
You're serious?
You tell me.
I take this deal to Vladimir,
and it's not real,
you know what happens?!
Why would I be here
if this wasn't real?!
Fine, forget it, Ziya.
I'll find Vladimir my own way.
No, wait!
I don't know
where he is exactly,
but where he might be.
Tell me.
No, I'll take you there myself.
You have a car?
I have truck;
it's parked out back.
All right, I'll drive.
Come on!
Yeah?
Jack, I just found out in my
background check that Ziya
has a probation officer.
How do you want
to handle this?
You don't need to.
He has a tracking bracelet.
Not anymore.
I don't understand.
Those things have
anti-tamper mechanisms.
You can't cut them off him
without triggering an alarm.
Yeah, well, trust me,
it's been taken care of.
Jack, what happened in there?
Renee got the result
she wanted.
Ziya's taking her to Vladimir.
Dana's still working
on your cover profile.
Okay, they're moving.
I'll call you when it's ready.
Jack's still waiting
on the rest of that profile.
I'm still working the timeline.
Tell him I'm almost finished.
Okay.
Aren't you going to get that?
Yeah, probably should.
Hello?
I'm in the middle of something.
Hold on a second.
Chloe, I will send that profile
to you as soon as I'm done.
Okay.
I told you not to call.
Yeah, I know what you told me.
But now that I'm here
in your apartment,
I just can't help but miss you.
My shift is over in the morning.
I will see you then.
Yeah, well, that's just not
going to work now, is it?
I'm right in the middle
of something, Kevin.
Turn on the news
if you don't believe me.
Hey, that's not my problem.
Okay, I need to see you.
You have 15 minutes.
That's not possible.
Okay, you got 30.
Who said I can't be reasonable?
Kevin...
Don't make me call that
little boyfriend of yours.
Rock his perfect little world.
"Hey, pal, congratulations
on the engagement."
By the way, her name's not
Dana Walsh, it's Jenny Scott.
Oh, did I mention
that she's an ex-con?
No, no, no,
nothing too serious.
"Just accessory to murder
is all."
You still there?
Yeah, I'm here.
See you soon.
Arlo, can I ask you something?
Yes, I'm available
Saturday night,
and I can change my plans
for Friday if you want.
Also, I'm free on Thursday.
Look, Arlo, I'm sorry.
It's just,
a situation's come up,
and I have to go home
for a while.
Dana, we're in the middle
of a major protocol.
I understand that,
and I won't be long, I promise.
But I need you
to cover for me.
Put the finishing touches
on the profile
for Renee Walker and Jack Bauer.
And if I ask what this is about,
you'll tell me...
That it's none
of your business.
Right.
I thought so.
Send it to Chloe's screen
as soon as you're finished.
Okay.
Thank you, Arlo.
I owe you one.
One what?
I look forward to
seeing you tomorrow.
They're concerned,
but they're all still
planning to attend
the signing ceremony tomorrow.
Well, I've got some bad news.
Apparently, killing
President Hassan
was only part
of his brother's plan.
CTU now believes
he's also trying to acquire
weapons-grade uranium.
From whom?
A Russian crime syndicate
here in New York.
Half of them are
ex-Soviet Army or KGB.
If anyone had access
to unsecured stockpiles...
It's what we've been afraid of
since the Wall came down.
Is President Hassan
aware of this?
He's the one
who told CTU about it.
Director Hastings
has already initiated
an undercover operation
to try to recover the uranium
before it's smuggled
out of the country.
The nuclear materials
are here on U.S. soil?
Are they sure?
Afraid so.
Ethan, you asked
if President Hassan
was aware
of this. Why?
Helps explain what's been going
on in the Islamic Republic.
I just spoke
with our ambassador
in the I.R.K.
Hassan's security forces are
sweeping through the capital,
arresting opposition leaders,
shuttering news organizations.
Has he declared martial law?
Not officially, but effectively,
that's exactly
what he's been doing.
Who can blame him?
I mean, his brother can't
have been acting alone.
We want Hassan cracking down
on hardliners in
his own government.
Except that he's defying
his country's laws,
as well as his international
human rights obligations.
And if he continues, it may
delegitimize the peace accord.
Is President Hassan
back yet from CTU?
He'll be here in ten minutes.
I want to speak to him... alone.
I'll take care of it.
That's enough.
What's your problem?
I need you thinking clearly.
You tell me you'd get me
real painkiller.
Put it away.
I'm surprised.
I'm surprised you take
deal to him again
after what he did to you.
How much further?
Okay.
You don't want to
talk about Vladimir.
I understand.
I don't blame you.
After all, what is there
to say about such a man?
Nothing good,
nothing very...
Just tell me
how much further.
Ten minute.
Touchy, touchy.
Yeah?
Arlo just locked
your cover profile.
I'm uplinking it to you now.
Okay, hold on one sec.
Okay, I got it.
Hey, you're taking me out
of Renee's comm
when you call, right?
Yes.
Okay, I want you to go
into her undercover file
with regards
to Vladimir Laitanan.
I need to know everything
that happened between them.
I'll call you
right back.
Okay, thanks.
Mr. President.
Your chief of staff said
it was urgent.
It is, but first,
I want to say again how thankful
we are that you're all right.
If this is
about my security forces
and the necessary steps
I'm taking back home,
I'm afraid I can't help you.
Are you so sure
they're necessary?
What happened today
was nothing short of a coup.
These same people are trying
to restart my country's
nuclear weapons' program.
I understand, but...
No, I don't think you do.
Yours is an open society,
Madam President,
governed by the rule of law.
Mine is closed.
The only real law is power.
Any perceived
weakness on my part,
and I'm finished.
I'm aware of the complexities
of your situation,
Mr. President.
My brother tried to kill me,
helped by elements
within my own government.
Those elements
must now be purged.
Purged?
You mean, executed?
It is the only thing
my people understand.
I can't vouch for you
as a reformer, Mr. President,
if you renege on your
human rights obligations.
The world is trusting you
because I trust you.
You're asking me to show mercy
to enemies
who are trying to destroy me.
I am asking you
to find a middle way,
in the name of bringing peace
to a region that hasn't
known peace for generations.
I need to see my family now.
I found a doctor.
A doctor?
Someone who can help you,
someone we can control,
but Papa says
it's too risky.
Papa's right.
Condemning
you to death?
I don't believe that.
What happened...
was my own fault.
The family shouldn't have
to pay for my mistake.
You know, all these years,
I thought it was an act.
But you really are the good son,
aren't you?
I'm no better or worse
than you, Josef.
You're my older brother.
You've always
looked out for me.
What are you doing?
Joseph? Joseph,
what are you doing?!
I'm taking you
to the doctor.
But Papa said
we can't.
I don't care what Papa said!
I'm not letting you die
without a fight.
You are old enough
to make your own decisions.
I've decided to stay.
As you wish.
You should stay, too.
I can't.
Why not?
You think that
your father is one way, but
he's not what
you think.
Stop doing that.
You always
do that.
What?
Imply things, but you never
actually tell me what you mean.
It is better that way, Kayla,
believe me.
I don't want to poison you
against your father.
There.
You're doing it again.
You can't help yourself.
Doing what again?
Father!
Oh, are you all right?
I'm fine.
We thought that...
I know, I know.
Kayla, I need to speak
to your mother now alone.
Okay.
Dalia?
We have nothing
to say to each other.
Dalia, please.
Do you love her?
It's over.
I ended it.
You didn't answer
the question.
Be honest for once.
Show me a little respect.
I'm your wife, damn it.
Do you love her?
Maybe I thought I did.
Then say it.
What does it matter now?
It matters to me.
The truth is...
...I'm just glad I could
still feel something, anything.
And that's my fault somehow?
How dare you!
Our fault.
There's enough blame
to go around.
Dalia, please don't go.
What?
I don't want you to leave.
Don't worry.
I won't make a scene.
You should know me better
than that by now.
My brother's
a traitor.
My highest officers are
conspiring against me.
And now President Taylor
is threatening to pull
out of the peace talks.
It has been a long time
since you've asked my advice
about anything.
You were the one who always
gave me the best counsel.
Thank you for remembering that.
Then you'll stay?
It's too late for that, Omar.
Too much has happened
between us.
Dalia...
I'm sorry.
Vlad operates
t of here?
Sometimes.
He moved around a lot.
That's why cops
don't find him inside here.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, Ziya?
Hmm?
You know, Vladimir was
never fond of surprises,
so I was thinking...
maybe you could go in first?
Get him used to the
idea of me again.
Whet his appetite?
Exactly.
Okay.
Is our cover in place?
Yeah. Chloe got me everything.
Good. Let's start going over
what happened in Mexico City.
How we met, who we dealt with.
First tell me about Vladimir.
What do you want to know?
What he did to you?
I heard what Ziya said.
Ziya?
Come on, Jack,
he's a drama queen.
Damn it, Renee,
I am running this!
Stop messing with me!
I'm responsible for your safety.
So, when I ask you
a straight queution,
you give me a straight answer.
Look, it was nothing, all right?
I handled him six years ago,
I can handle him today.
The only thing that
I am worried about
is locking down this cover,
so, please,
let's not waste another minute
on Vladimir.
I'm a Munich-based arms dealer
named Ernst Meier.
We met in Mexico City.
You became my liaison
to the locals.
Lugo.
Long time.
It's me, Ziya.
I know who you are.
Now what the hell
are you doing here?
I've got business.
Business?
Yeah.
With Vladimir.
You've got business with me?
Vlad!
I should kill you for even
thinking of coming here.
What?
Let me go, please!
No, I...
Five years
I've been living
underground.
Five years! And now you walk
into my place of business?
You're on probation!
No. Not anymore, Vlad.
Look.
She get bracelet off.
What are you talking about?
Who did?
It's what I'm trying
to tell you. Renee.
Renee Zadan.
She come to my place
looking for you.
Yeah, she say
she have buyer that
you'd want to hear about.
That it'd be good for all of us.
It'd be worth it for all of us.
Renee.
Dah.
She say where she'd been
these last five years?
Uh, where everybody else was.
In jail.
Then she go to Mexico City.
She say she got
the opportunity there.
Mexico City, huh?
Dah.
What do you think, Lugo?
You believe this
piece of dirt?
Sure I believe him.
He's too stupid to make up
a story like that.
It's her I don't believe.
I never did.
I told you, Lugo, it wasn't her.
She's not the one
who sold us out.
She shows up out of the blue,
then 16 months later,
the feds are down our throats.
I'm just saying, Vlad.
You were just saying.
Where's Renee now?
Outside.
Clean yourself up.
Bring her to me.
Arlo, where's Dana?
She isn't at her desk.
She went home.
Home?
Yeah.
Who is it?
It's me.
You have my key.
Nice of you to drop by.
It's not funny.
What the hell?! Who's he?
That's Nick.
It's a buddy of mine
from Beaumont.
Get him the hell out of here.
You know I can't do that, Jen.
I already told him
he could stay.
It'd be impolite.
Here.
What's this?
It's $500.
It's all I could get out
of the cash machine.
I'll get you another
500 in the morning.
You think you're smart,
and the whole world's stupid.
That's just not how it is, Jen.
I don't think you're stupid.
No? But you think you can buy me
off with $1,000?
I'm not trying
to buy you off.
No, no.
What do you want from me?
You know what I want?
What I really want
is for you to stop treating me
like some dumbass,
19-year-old stickup artist
with a fast car!
You're not the only one
who's grown up.
Easy, Kevin, easy.
I've been waiting
for this moment.
Dreaming about it.
You owe me.
If you think that I testified
against you, I didn't.
Don't lie to me!
I'm not lying to you!
I got out of jail
before you did, yeah, but only
because I went in as a minor.
No other reason.
The truth is,
it doesn't change things,
one way or another.
See, I've done
my homework.
I know what your job is.
I'm a data analyst,
nothing more.
Yeah, but you're a data analyst
for CTU.
You got access to all sorts
of good stuff--
bank codes,
port authority manifests,
stock exchange.
Access, yeah, but not
unrestricted access.
You'll figure something out.
You always do.
But whatever it is,
the payout's got to be at least
six figures, okay?
Please, Kevin.
Okay, here's the deal.
You do this one thing for me,
and I'm gone.
I'll never bother you again.
I can't.
You can.
And you will.
Since last August, we've
been living and operating
out of a hotel called
Bella Noche on Avenida Juarez.
Can't they check that?
Yeah, it's been set up
as a safe haven
for high-end criminal activity.
They don't keep records.
Have you got the name?
Bella Noche. I got it.
Okay, I'm going to be monitoring
you, filling in the details.
Just listen to my voice.
I'll get you all
the information you need.
He's coming.
Come on. Let's go.
Yeah?
It's not pretty, Jack.
She had a real problem
on her hands.
Talk to me.
According to the
responsible agent,
Vladimir Laitanan was completely
obsessed with her.
It turned violent.
How violent?
Broken ribs, a busted cheekbone.
A couple of trips
to the emergency room.
Did he rape her?
Not according
to these files,
but it looks like he
tried a couple of times.
Did she say anything about this
to you or Hastings?
No.
What's this about, Jack?
Jack?
The FBI tried to cover this up
as much as they could.
But after she left the bureau,
Renee went into a tailspin.
She tried to kill herself at
least once that I know about.
She says she's past it,
but I know she's not.
I can see it in her eyes.
You think she's purposely
putting herself in harm's way?
I don't think she cares
what happens to her either way.
Where is she now?
She's going in.
I'm going to put you on speaker.
Hands up.
Turn around.
Go.
Hello, Vlad.
Renee.
You changed your face.
I had it done in Caracas.
What do you think?
Makes you look younger.
I should get the name
of that doctor.
He's not practicing anymore.
A sad story.
Our little friend here
says you were
in Mexico City.
For what?
Had some business.
Good for you. I have
some contacts there myself.
Yeah, I know you do.
So...
give me names.
The Peralta-Rodriguez...
Family.
Uh...
The Peralta-Rodriguez family.
Castorenas
in Guadalajara.
Ramon Jimenez.
I know Ramon. Is his brother
Luiz still running
their heroin operations?
He was killed nine months ago
by the Federales.
Not since he was killed by
the Federales nine months ago.
You know, Renee,
now that you mention it,
there is something different
about you, too.
How do you mean?
Your eyes.
Your skin.
You look like hell.
Well, it's hard to look your
best with a gun in your face.
No, that's not it.
Something else.
Have you been sick?
No.
Maybe you picked
up a little
Hepatitis C
on your travels?
Where were you staying
in Mexico City?
The Bella.
Bella Noche Hotel.
Bella Noche, naturally.
Then, of course,
you must know
the government
official who allows it
to operate without
police interference.
Chloe, the hotel
in Mexico City--
was there a local
politician on the take?
I don't have it here.
Neither do I.
Checking DEA database.
Come on.
Chloe.
Give me a minute.
She doesn't
have a minute.
Waiting for a name!
Go ahead, tell him.
Really getting tired
of this, Vlad.
His name!
Got it-- Raul Castillo.
Castillo,
Raul Castillo.
Raul Castillo,
all right?
Are we done playing
20 questions now?
Yes, I believe
we are.
You know, Renee, I
had almost forgotten
how much fun
you are.
You're not like
other women.
You have balls.
Hmm, you always did say
the nicest things.
Can we talk
about this deal now?
I wish it were
that simple.
Tie her up.
What?
Vlad, what are you doing?
You gave me all the
right answers, Renee,
but you're not
telling the truth.
You're making
a mistake.
This is the chance
of a lifetime.
Him, too.
Vlad, wait.
Put them in the trunk.
Vladimir, Vladimir, no!
No, Vladimir,
please don't do this!
Listen to me!
She come to me!
She come to my place,
the bitch!
I swear!
Vladimir, I don't know
anything about this!
No!
Chloe, what the hell
just happened?
They put her in the trunk,
I lost audio.
Boosting the signal now.
Renee?
Try it again.
Renee, can you hear me?
Say something.
Chloe, I don't have her.
Then the car must be armored.
Either that
or her comm shorted out.
Are you seeing this?
I am.
Okay, I'm following north
through an alley
towards Woodward.
I think this operation
just blew up.
Jack, are you planning
to intercept?
Not if the car is armored.
I'm gonna need tactical support.
I'm alerting Hastings
to scramble a team now.
Tell him I see four men
in the car,
and we're going
to have to assume
they're taking Renee somewhere
to kill her.
Copy that.
Damn it!
Don't work too late, hon.
Call me when you're on the road.
Will do.
Dr. Levine.
How did you get in here?
My brother is sick.
I'm not seeing patients
right now.
He needs your help.
I'm gonna call you an ambulance.
No.
No one else can know
about this.
My men are outside your house
in New Rochelle.
I don't believe you.
I just spoke to my wife.
We're outside the gate.
The address is
1614 Brook Street.
The light in your
little daughter's room
just went out
about ten minutes ago,
so I want you
to put the phone down
because you're not
going to try
to warn anybody
about this.
Do you understand?
I understand.
My brother has
radiation poisoning.
He needs
treatment.
His symptoms seem
quite advanced.
I'm not sure what it is
I can do for him.
Well, you'd better be able
to do something,
for your family's sake.
I, um... I need to know
what kind of materials
he came in contact with.
It was uranium.
Do you know what variant,
the isotope?
Weapons-grade 235.
Jack, this is Hastings.
TAC teams are
three minutes away.
All of them aware
that Renee is in the trunk?
The instructions are
to engage only on my command.
Any indication
where they're taking her?
None.
Any percentage
in letting this play out?
No. As soon as she's
out of the vehicle,
she becomes that
much more vulnerable.
If we engage now, it means
ending the operation.
This operation's over.
Vladimir didn't take the bait.
Target just turned
south on Flushing.
Jack, that's a feeder
onto the BQE in 2.6 miles.
Mr. Hastings, if we don't engage
on these surface streets,
we lose our tactical advantage.
Chloe, get me an ETA.
Intercept in...
two minutes, ten seconds.
Sir, you need
to make the call now.
All right, I'm
authorizing engagement.
Stand by
for intercept protocols.
This is good. Pull over.
Open it.
Vladimir.
Take them out
of the trunk.
Lugo, please, you tell him,
tell Vladimir...
Chloe, I've got
a signal again.
Please, Vladimir, Vlad...
Something's wrong--
they definitely sound stopped,
but the vehicle
I'm following
is still going south
on Flushing.
She told me to come to you!
Shut up, shut up, Ziya.
It's not going to do any good.
Confirming that, Jack,
the target is still moving.
Chloe, we're following a decoy.
They must have left
in another vehicle. Find it!
Okay, pulling up
a satellite footage.
All right, TAC teams,
hold your positions,
stand by.
Jack,
another car drove out of the
back of the auto parts building
five minutes
after the first one.
Are you kidding me?!
I'm sorry, we were focusing
everything on your follow.
Just tell me where they are!
Take them down to the water.
Okay, I've got a GPS lock
on Renee.
They're pulled off
at Newtown Creek,
just south
of Bryne Memorial Bridge.
Where are the TAC teams?
I'm redirecting them now.
How far out are they?
At least ten minutes.
Tell them to move it.
Put me back on to Renee's comm.
Damn it!
Renee, it's Jack.
I know you can hear me.
Vladimir had us
following a decoy.
TAC teams are
ten minutes out.
I'm on my way now.
Do whatever you have to
to buy time.
On your knees,
both of you.
Please listen to me,
I don't know anything.
Shut your mouth.
I'm going to give you
one last chance
to tell me what is going on.
Vladimir,
I swear on my life,
she come to my place.
I don't know
anything.
No!
Renee.
Renee?!
Amazing.
You didn't even blink.
Go ahead.
Just get it over with.
Renee, what the
hell are you doing?
Not yet.
For God's sake,
don't make me grovel.
Just pull
the damn trigger.
First I want
to hear the truth.
I want to know
who you really are.
Who I really am?
Yeah, who you are,
not a game, Renee...
or whatever your name is.
Fine, you want the truth?
I'll tell you the truth.
You were right.
You were right, I am sick.
I am so sick
of living like this.
The truth is...
even if you let me walk
right now...
I have nowhere to go
and no one to go to.
You don't want to do this deal,
fine.
Then you might as well
just kill me
because this deal is
the only thing that I have.
Renee, please don't
do this, please.
Besides, you wouldn't
be doing anything
that I haven't already
tried myself.
Do it.
Do it!
Pull the trigger!
I had to be sure.
You understand,
right?
Yes.
Good... good.
Dump him in the river.
Jack, TAC teams are
almost there.
I need a status update.
Jack, are you there?
Do you copy?
You tell the TAC teams
to stand down.
What's going on?
She's in.
They bought her cover.
www.tvsubtitles.net