Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com
Our security police have
completed their initial sweep
of the capital city.
65 known members of the
opposition have been arrested
and are being
questioned.
Have you learned anything?
Were any of them
working with my brother?
It's too early to tell.
Kayla, your father
is a great man,
but Farhad's betrayal
has changed him.
What can we do?
The president says
you may be involved
with his brother.
He's ordered me
to detain you.
I'll talk to him.
President Hassan's
crackdown
isn't just a response
to the attempt on his life.
There are unsecured
nuclear materials in play.
CTU is running
an undercover operation
to retrieve them as we speak.
I've got something.
It's an NYPD evidence lockup.
A local vice group
just impounded
$120,000.
I help you do this and
you never call me again.
That's beautiful, man.
Absolutely beautiful.
It's a cop.
You're going to have
to slip past him.
I'm at the warehouse...
Nick!
Kevin, stop him!
I hear there are materials
for sale.
Talk straight.
What materials?
Nuclear rods.
Nobody deals
in nuclear rods, nobody.
We have a problem.
Vladimir Laitanan knows
about the fuel rods.
Come on, Vladimir,
push them harder.
Somebody knows something.
No one knows,
there's no one left to call.
Look, it's over!
What is wrong
with you?!
Renee.
Stop, stop.
They're Russian.
What are you doing?
I need to let them take me.
When CTU gets here, you tell them
to start tracking me from the air.
These people are gonna lead us
to everything we're looking for.
I'm unarmed, don't shoot.
We can do business.
Where's Jack?
The Russians took him.
He said that you'd be
monitoring him from the air.
We haven't seen anything.
Where is he?
Yeah?
Where the hell are you?
Hey, Jenny girl!
You said you would call me
as soon as the two of you
got clear.
I'm sorry, sweetheart,
I forgot.
We-we got- hold on-
we got caught up
celebrating our score.
Celebrating?
You put a police officer
in the hospital.
Hey, that wasn't
me, that was Nick.
A- And look, why do, why do you
got to focus on the negative?
We're flush 120 grand.
Why don't you just
come down here,
have a drink,
celebrate with us?
We're at a club in Jersey
City called Starlight.
We'll work
out your cut.
What cut?
I don't want anything from you,
Kevin.
We're done.
I want you
to put my key
in my mailbox
and get the hell out of my life
like you promised.
Yeah, that-that's not going
to happen.
What does that mean?
This is a sweet operation that
we got going here, you know?
You getting the access codes
and-and us
pulling the jobs.
W- W-Wait...
We had a deal, Kevin.
You promised me
I do this one thing for you
and then you leave me alone.
I- I know and I, and I, and
I meant that, all right,
but things change,
okay, an-an-and...
We can get rich
off of this, Jenny.
You can't do this
to me, Kevin.
Jenny, please...
Look, bitch,
you're in this
up to your neck.
You want your boss and want
your boyfriend finding out
you're not who
you say you are?
You're gonna be our
golden goose, okay?
Hello?
Dana.
What are you doing?
We got a situation;
you need to be
on the floor.
Dana...
I heard you, I will
be right there.
Who was that
on the phone just now?
That's none of your business.
Actually, it is.
When you start
sneaking away
to make phone calls
or leave the office,
making me cover for you,
it becomes my business.
Now, who was that?
Kevin?
How the hell would you...?
Are you spying on me?
Look, you want to step out
on your fiancé,
it's fine with me.
God knows I've got
no love for the guy.
You have no idea what
you are talking about.
I am not cheating
on Cole.
Okay, whatever you
want to call it,
you'd better start telling
your boyfriend what's going on
or I will.
Now, come on.
Our undercover operation
just went south.
What's happened?
Jack Bauer was grabbed
by an unknown group
of armed Russians.
We think they're the ones
in control of the nuclear rods.
Are we tracking them?
We can't.
They took Bauer
through an underground access
behind the building.
Without aerial support, the best
my people could do
was track them
to a drainage junction
near Avenue Y and Ocean.
They must have had a
vehicle standing by.
Jack's cell phone was
trashed at the scene.
Well, there has to be
something at the site
to help us I.D.
the vehicle.
Tire treads,
transmission fluid,
oil residue?
No, there's nothing, sir,
the trail's gone cold.
Well, what about Walker?
Did she get a good look
at these people?
I don't know, sir.
Frankly, she's pretty
messed up right now.
Blaming herself
for Jack's circumstances.
Well, she should.
She crippled this operation
when she murdered her contact.
Without Vladimir Laitanan, we
have no lead to finding Bauer
or the nuclear
materials.
You get her back to CTU
for debriefing.
I want to know
what the hell happened.
Yes, sir.
You might want
to consider
running a psych eval
on her when we arrive.
Count on it.
You were supposed
to be coordinating
with NSA,
monitoring chatter.
I know, something came up,
I had to take care of it.
What was so important?
It's my fault, Mr. Hastings.
I asked Dana to
recover a datalog
I accidentally deleted
from archives.
I didn't have clearance.
I'm uplinking to
NSA servers now.
All right.
Just get on it.
Roll back any chatter
within the last 20 minutes.
Right now
that's all we've got.
Let me know
if something turns up.
I need to brief
President Taylor.
Thank you.
You can thank me
by putting aside
whatever it is
that's bothering you
and helping me
find Jack.
He's my friend
and he's in trouble.
Take him down the hall.
Where is Vladimir?
Dead.
So are his men.
The German said
they tried to rip him off.
Did he also say how he knows
about the fuel rods?
Who are you?
Ernst Meier.
I've been looking for you
to make you an offer.
You know who I am?
No.
All I know is that there's
a very powerful man
in the Russian syndicate
who's been trafficking
weapons-grade uranium,
specifically U-235
fuel rods.
After the nasty business
with Laitanan,
these men brought me here,
so I'm just assuming
you're that man.
Where did you get
this information?
I represent a consortium
of private interests.
They intercepted communiqués
within the Islamic republic.
From whom?
Farhad Hassan...
or someone
in his camp.
In either case, you're doing
business with the wrong people.
And who are these people-
the ones you work for?
I'm sure you can understand
I'm not at liberty to say.
Aah!
You should be less concerned
about who I work for
and more concerned
about the deal
that they're willing
to offer you.
I'm not interested
in your offer.
$250 million,
half of which is ready to be
wired to you immediately.
The other half you will receive
upon final acquisition
of the fuel rods.
You pose
a very difficult problem for me.
You show up
out of nowhere,
knowing far too much
of my business,
yet I've never
heard of you.
You've never heard of me
because I'm good at what I do.
What I'm concerned about...
is that you're a cop.
I just killed three people
back at that garage.
Vladimir Laitanan-
I stabbed in the eye.
You really think I'm a cop?
As a child,
I saw KGB throw
an entire family
off the roof of a building,
two of them small children.
I know what cops are capable of.
So I ask you again:
Who do you work for?
I'm sorry,
I can't tell you that.
Dimitri, work on him
until he's ready
to tell us everything.
No, we can make a deal.
We can still make a deal!
No! No!
No!
You have buried
your brother's body?
It's Oleg's necklace.
You gave it to him
at his confirmation.
You keep it.
To remind you of him.
I'm glad you're back.
We may have
a problem.
What is it?
There is a man down the hall
who claims to be an arms broker.
He knows about the nuclear rods.
How could he?
He says there was a leak from
Farhad's people, but I wonder.
Until I know for certain
who and what this man is,
I've stopped the transport
of the rods.
They've been redirected
to our weigh station
off the Wantagh Parkway.
I'm sure Farhad can't
be happy about that.
I haven't told him yet.
Perhaps we should
tell him together.
How long do you plan
to hold him off?
That depends.
On what?
On how long it takes Dimitri
to break this guy.
Okay, Mr. Policeman.
I'm not a cop.
I swear to you.
Please, don't do this.
Tell me what you know.
We are exhausting all efforts
to ascertain who took Bauer
and where,
but until any progress is made,
we just have to hope
that Jack can find some way
of salvaging the operation
on his end.
What even makes you think
he's still alive?
Only the fact
that he wasn't killed
at the point of abduction.
Mr. Hastings,
I need a realistic assessment.
What are the odds of
finding and securing
these nuclear weapons
within the next few hours?
I can't answer that, ma'am,
but the longer
we're out of touch
with Bauer,
the less likely our chances.
All right, Mr. Hastings.
Continue to coordinate
with my office.
I want updates every 30 minutes.
Yes, ma'am.
I just spoke to General Wasim.
He's very worried.
Your brother's crackdowns
back home are intensifying.
Everyone
is being arrested.
Our window of opportunity
is closing.
And why didn't the general
call me himself?
Perhaps he's losing confidence
in your ability
to complete our mission.
This is my mission.
My plan!
Of course.
But we're running
out of time.
If your brother dismantles
our opposition forces,
we will no
longer be able
to reconstitute our
nuclear program.
He won't succeed.
At this rate, he will.
How much longer
must we wait
for the delivery
of the uranium?
Not long.
The rods should be arriving
to you within the hour.
Have your men ready.
I'll call you back.
Yes? What is it?
There is a man downstairs
who's shown up
to outbid you for
the fuel rods.
Is this some feeble attempt
to renegotiate terms?
Not at all. This man, Meier,
claims someone in
your organization
tipped him off to our deal.
That's not possible. He's lying.
At any rate, in light of
his sudden appearance,
I'm halting delivery of the rods
for the time being.
What? You can't do that.
It's already done.
I cannot take the risk
that we may be exposed.
The longer you delay,
the more time
my brother has
to crush his enemies.
If he manages to purge everyone
in the military
who opposes him,
the uranium is worthless to me.
That's your concern.
Mine is to make
certain this Meier
is not a policeman.
One of my men
is interrogating him now.
That could take hours,
even days.
Not days.
I can promise you that.
You promised
to assassinate my brother, too.
Your failure
to eliminate him
has put me under
enormous pressure, and now,
because of your people's
inability to maintain secrecy,
you break our agreed timetable
to suit your needs.
Don't speak
to my father that way.
We've honored
every agreement
we made with you,
and shed a lot
of blood for it.
My father's allowed you
to stay here
and hide from the Feds
at great personal risk
to our family.
Tell him to put the gun down.
No.
We're not taking any
more of your demands.
Throw him out
of here.
Let his own people shelter him
if he thinks we're such fools.
I'll drive him
there myself
if that's what
it takes.
It would seem you have used up
our hospitality here.
Perhaps it's best
you join your men
at the rendezvous point
to wait for delivery.
And when will that be?
When I think it's safe.
Not a moment before.
Make sure he gets
where he's going.
Still got men
back at the scene
in case we missed something.
In the meantime,
I'll work out
the aerial sweep
protocols with Arlo.
What are you doing to find Jack?
Everything we can, Ms. Walker.
Come with me.
Have you checked
all the... the traffic cams,
subway routes?
You have all this technology
working for you-
comm surveillance,
satellite tracking.
We're using everything
at our disposal.
Then how come
you haven't found him yet?
Why don't you have any leads?
The best lead we had is dead.
I know about
your suicide attempt.
You should have been honest
with me.
O'Brian will take
your statement.
I want to know every detail
about every event
leading up to the death
of Vladimir Laitanan.
When she's done,
take her to medical.
I've ordered a full
psych evaluation.
Yes, sir.
Uh,
you can write
your statement here.
Hastings blames me
for what happened to Jack.
And he's right.
No, he's not.
He shouldn't have said that.
The only reason
that Jack was even
part of this operation
was because of me.
So whatever they're doing
to him right now,
it's because of me.
I have to find him, Chloe.
Renee, I know how you must feel.
Just... just take
one thing at a time.
We have to deal
with what you did.
So write your
statement.
Ill check back with you.
Cole.
Hey.
Do you have some time?
I need to talk to you.
Can it wait?
I need to review these protocols
before Arlo distributes them.
I've got it covered.
Go talk to your girlfriend.
What's up?
You all right?
No, I'm not.
I have a big problem.
And it's the reason why
I've been acting kind of weird
the past few days.
Okay.
Listen, if you're
calling off the engagement,
you couldn't have
picked a worse day.
No.
No, I would never do that.
Good.
So what's bothering you?
There are things about my past
that I haven't told you.
I'm listening.
Hey.
I'm sure I haven't told you
everything about
my past either.
I don't care what happened
before I met you.
All that matters is now
and what we have
to look forward to.
I think that's all
that matters, too.
So what are you
so worried about?
I don't want to lose you.
I'm not going anywhere.
Excuse me.
Agent Ortiz, Mr. Hastings
needs to see you in his office.
Uh, tell him I'll be
there as soon as I can.
No. Go.
Hastings can wait.
So can this.
Talking to you has helped.
I think I know
what I need to do now.
You sure?
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Maybe later you tell me
what this is all about.
Who do you
work for?
Who else knows
about the fuel rods?
Everybody
has a limit.
Don't worry,
I'll find yours.
You're working with the police.
Admit it!
Tell me and the
pain will stop.
Who else knows?
I told you... I'm not a cop.
Please.
I'm just a businessman.
Who do you work for?
I'm an independent contractor.
I couldn't even tell you
if I wanted.
Please.
We'll see.
Wake up.
I said, wake up.
I told you
I didn't want to be disturbed.
Your daughter is still demanding
to see you, Mr. President.
She refuses to leave.
Very well. Send her in.
Kayla, my love,
I'm in the middle of a crisis,
so unless it's an emergency...
It is an emergency.
We need to talk about you
having Tarin arrested.
Tarin has been taken
to the embassy
to help clarify a few questions,
strictly routine.
I know you believe
he's been working against you.
What I don't understand is why.
He refused to follow my orders.
You asked him to
arrest the family
of one of
your delegates.
A man you considered
a friend.
Kayla, this is a matter of
state; it doesn't concern you.
It doesn't make sense.
Tarin was in the car with you-
if the assassination
attempt was successful,
he would've been killed, too.
The world is full of men willing
to die for their cause.
I know you consider
Tarin a friend.
And your loyalty
is commendable.
But trust me, I have my reasons.
We are more than friends.
We're in love,
and have been for almost a year.
You've been carrying on
with this man
behind my back?
You say that to me,
after driving mother away
with your infidelity.
Please, Father.
Don't let Uncle Farhad's
betrayal
turn you against everyone
who cares about you.
I can't think of a better way
to completely infiltrate my life
and influence my judgment
than getting close
to my daughter.
It's not like that.
You're not to see that man
again, ever.
Father...
I'm done with
this conversation.
I need to get back to my work.
What's happening to you?
Come on.
Damn it!
I am holding the rods
until Meier comes clean
about how he knew
of the transfer.
If what Meier said is true about
the leak in Farhad's team,
it will be dangerous for us.
So we must unload the
rods, finish this.
Let them be someone
else's problem...
And we erase any evidence.
Once Dimitri is finished,
and I'm satisfied
the German is telling the truth,
I'm going to want
to hand off the rods
to Farhad tonight.
Keep your men out of sight
along the perimeter.
Mikhail and his men will stay
with the cargo.
Check to see if the rest
of the street lost power.
Just us.
It's Meier.
Cover the exits.
Check the fuse box.
Come on.
CTU. O'Brian.
Chloe. It's Jack.
Jack, everyone's
been looking for you.
Where are you?
I need you to trace this call
and send
a Tac team immediately.
Jack? Chloe, just
trace the call.
Jack!
*
We're sure NYPD's got
the perimeter locked down?
The restaurant and everything
in a block radius is secure.
Our response team
will be there soon.
Where's Dana?
She logged out of the building
about 15 minutes ago.
Something about
fixing a faulty relay
at our 17th Street station.
Why didn't she just have
IP maintenance take care of it?
Good question.
She had to manually reboot
the firmware herself.
That's what she said anyway.
Where are we
with this man Bazhaev?
It's coming
through right now.
I've cross-accessed
interagency servers,
also Interpol and FSB.
I'm relaying intel
as it comes in
to our response team
and to Jack.
Good. Put it up on screen.
Okay, people.
We've ID'd the suspect
we have in custody.
His name
is Sergei Petrovich Bazhaev,
Ukrainian national,
61 years of age.
Now, we believe
he knows the location
of the unsecured nuclear rods.
Now, tactical is on its way
to transport him back here
for interrogation.
Agent Ortiz will coordinate
operations from here.
Is it true?
You found Jack?
Yeah. He's okay.
If you're finished
with your statement,
I need to take you
to medical.
No. No. I want to be here
when Jack gets back.
I'll let him know
where to find you.
Come on.
Mr. Bauer, this should
hold you for now.
But you're going to have
to go to the hospital.
Okay.
Excuse me, sir.
They uploaded
the suspect's file right now.
How far out is CTU?
They're about five
minutes out.
It's all right.
I got it. Thanks.
Sergeant?
I need to speak
with this man alone.
I knew you were a cop.
I should have
trusted my instincts
and killed you on the spot.
Well, you can add it
to your list of regrets.
CTU's already acquired a
great deal of intel on you,
Mr. Bazhaev.
It's over. You
know that, right?
You're finished.
I mean, at the very
least, we've got you
on kidnapping and murder,
and that's before
CTU rips this place apart
and uncovers the rest
of your criminal activity.
Lucky for you, though, I'm
only interested in one thing,
and that's the acquisition
of those fuel rods.
So, if you were
to cooperate,
help me out there,
that would go a
long way to reducing
what is clearly going to be
a very long prison sentence.
That offer extends to
both of your sons, too-
Josef and Oleg.
Oleg is dead.
He was exposed
to the rods.
Became ill with
radiation poisoning.
He was suffering,
and I shot him,
as if he was
just a sick dog.
I murdered my own son.
For nothing.
You want to know
where the rods are?
I will tell you.
But I want full immunity.
Not just for me,
but for my other son, Josef.
I don't think
I can make that happen.
Then we have nothing
to talk about.
I'll see what I can do.
CTU. O'Brian.
Chloe, it's Jack.
I need to speak
with Hastings.
I think he's in the middle of a
briefing with President Taylor.
Even better. See if you
can patch me in, okay?
Okay.
Mr. Hastings, it's Farhad Hassan
I'm worried about.
How do we know
he hasn't acquired
the rods already?
Based on the intel we have,
the transfer hasn't
taken place yet.
Madam President,
excuse the interruption.
Jack Bauer is on the line.
He wishes to be conferenced in.
Put him through.
Jack, it's President Taylor.
You're on with Mr. Hastings
and my chief of staff.
CTU's been keeping me apprised
of your involvement in this.
I'm sorry that it's taken
this long for us to speak.
I understand, and
please forgive me
for getting straight
to the point,
but the man that
we have in custody,
Sergei Bazhaev, is
willing to cooperate.
He said he would hand
over the fuel rods
in exchange for full
immunity for him and his son.
Is that all?
Why don't me give him a parade
down Broadway, too?
Jack, you've been dealing
with this man.
Is there no other way
to get the location
of the nuclear
materials out of him?
It says in his files
that he did 12 years
in a Russian labor camp.
In the time frame
that we have,
we're not gonna break him,
Madam President.
I can see it in his eyes.
Mr. Hastings, what
is your assessment?
Well, at first blush, I'd say
an immunity deal is premature,
but under the circumstances,
I'll defer
to Jack's judgment on this.
Gentlemen, I have a peace deal
that's going to fall apart
at any moment unless I
can show President Hassan
that we have
stopped his brother
from smuggling those fuel
rods out of the country.
Make the deal, Jack.
Madam President, he's going
to want this in writing.
He'll get it.
But in the interests
of expediency,
put him on the phone with me.
Yes, ma'am.
The President
of the United States
wants to talk to you.
You want to tell me
what's going on?
What are you talking about?
You were implying something
about Dana,
and I want to know what it is.
When she came over before
and said
she had to talk to you,
what did she tell you?
Nothing.
She said she had a problem,
and she'd handle it.
That's it?
Arlo, if you know something...
Okay, look,
it's none of my business,
and I didn't want to be the one
to tell you this,
but I think she went
to meet some guy.
You're out of your mind.
Take a look at this.
Who is he?
I checked with the gate.
They said his name
is Kevin Wade.
Identified himself as a friend.
Okay, so he's a friend.
Cole?
Bazhaev's given up the location
of the nuclear rods.
I've already scrambled
a NEST team.
Meet your tactical unit
at the helipad.
The coordinates will be relayed
to you en route.
Yes, sir.
You think you can find her?
I could if all the drones
weren't already committed.
What about a cell trace?
Just do it.
I don't know where you are
or what you're doing, Dana,
but I need you to call me
as soon as you get this.
It's important.
I love you.
Thank you, sir.
Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Miss Kayla, no.
Get out of my way, Nabeel.
I want to see him.
Your father forbids it.
I'm sorry.
I'm just doing my job.
A job that Tarin gave you.
He brought you
into my father's
security detail,
and this is how you repay him?
You're his friend, Nabeel.
You know he's innocent.
What would you have me do?
Just let me speak to him.
A few minutes is all I ask.
I can't let you in now.
Tarin's going to be readied
for transport
to our embassy in an hour.
I will find a moment
you can see him before then.
Thank you, Nabeel.
Now go before we're both
in trouble.
Cole, the NEST team's ETA is
two minutes from target site.
Now the HAZMAT crew will wait
for your signal to move in.
Be advised the truck with
the fuel rods is being guarded
by two armed hostiles.
Command, we have an immunity
deal with their boss.
Why haven't they been ordered
to stand down?
Well, Jack's understanding is
that these men are hard cases.
They won't roll over easily.
We cannot take the risk that
they'll flee with the rods.
Understood.
Now, when you secure
the nuclear materials,
you'll transport them
to Fort Hamilton.
We're clearing that air corridor
as we speak.
Command, we
see the truck,
but there's no
sign of hostiles.
Approaching the weigh
station now. Stand by.
Set us down there.
Picking up trace radiation.
30 millirads. It's safe.
Go, go. Move in.
We're clear.
Command, are you seeing this?
I am.
Where the hell are the rods?
We picked up trace
radiation signatures.
The rods were here.
Right now all we have
are two bodies, both shot.
Hey, Agent Ortiz.
Come on, man,
you can have a good time.
It's okay. It's okay to laugh
once in a while.
You can be a happy person.
This is Bauer.
It's Hastings.
Our team's at the truck stop.
The nuclear rods are not there.
What? H-Hold on. Say that again.
I said the rods
are not there.
That's not possible.
Did your men go
to the right place?
They went exactly where
you sent them.
Now stop playing games
and tell us where the rods are.
I told you, they were there.
I had two
of my men guarding them.
We found their bodies,
both shot.
And there was something else.
Some kind
of necklace hanging
on the inside
of the truck's door.
Like someone wanted
to send a message.
What kind of a necklace?
A gold cross.
What does that mean?
Josef.
I have the fuel rods.
Really?
I wasn't sure I believed, Josef,
that you would betray
your father.
You were upset that he was
holding up delivery
of the rods;
now I've gotten them for you.
It won't take him long
to realize what's happened,
so let's get
this done fast.
You're worried
he'll discover
you've replaced him
as our partner.
No, I want my father to know.
In fact,
I made sure he will.
When will you get here?
Less than five minutes.
Just have my money ready.
Transcrypt by www.addic7ed.com