We authenticated the data. Omicron made
the Sentox for the military. Who's Henderson?
- Someone I worked for.
- Where?
CTU. He was the man who recruited me.
Things ended badly between us.
Are you accusing me
of being in bed with terrorists?
I need access
to Omicron's Sentox programme.
I gotta merge files, find out who was working
on this project. We need IT. They're next door.
I listened to everything Bauer had to say. CTU
does not have enough information to hurt us.
- What about Bauer?
- In about one minute, he'll be dead.
Oh, my God!
How could I be so stupid?
There might be an attack
on Suvarov's motorcade.
My people are not gonna chase that white
elephant. They're trying to locate Sentox gas.
Let people focus on their work
or I will have you escorted out of here.
Lynn is mentally incapable of running CTU.
- What?
- Section one-twelve.
Take Mr. Stiles and Miss O'Brian.
Put 'em in holding.
And then escort Audrey Raines out of CTU.
I'm relieving you of your command
under section one-twelve.
- . Logan is with the Suvarovs.
- Get my wife on the phone.
The terrorists were specific.
If I don't allow them to attack the motorcade,
they're going to release canisters of gas
in multiple locations. You need to get out.
We're under attack. We need backup now!
We had an understanding.
It happened outside of my authority.
I told no one.
If Russia isn't going to pay
with the life of its president,
then its new ally, the United States,
will pay with the lives of its citizens.
Mr. President, this is our final conversation.
Goodbye.
No. Wait!
- How long has he been conscious?
- Ten minutes.
Before you go in, you should be aware of
something. Tony's been asking for his wife.
- He doesn't remember.
- The explosion, but that's all.
- We have to tell him Michelle's dead.
- No. He's undergone severe trauma.
Stress will raise his blood pressure
and make vascular damage worse.
Please, just hold off on telling him
till his condition is stabilised.
Could you excuse us, please?
Tony.
- How are you feeling?
- They told me they took Michelle to Cedars.
Yes, they couldn't treat her here.
Why? How badly was she hurt?
Is she gonna be OK?
As far as I know, yes.
What's going on? They killed Palmer
and they tried to kill Michelle and me.
David Palmer was the target. They killed him
because he was going to expose someone
inside Logan's administration.
They set Jack up to take the fall.
- Did they get Jack?
- No. He's alive.
He's working with us on a provisional basis.
- Bill, I need to talk to Jack.
- You need to rest.
No, I don't need to rest.
I need to talk to Jack. Now.
- I'll tell him.
- Thanks.
Could you do me a favour? Could you get
a message to Michelle? Tell her I'm OK.
I will.
Tony.
We need you to get better.
This is Black Top One.
We're one minute out.
Copy, Black Top One. We're standing by.
Roger that.
The navy helicopter is on its way, ma'am.
It'll take us back to the retreat.
He...
didn't warn the motorcade.
Ma'am?
Charles.
He knew about the attack, and...
he just let it happen, Aaron.
That can't be true.
He didn’t just let it happen. He...
He gave the terrorists
the Suvarovs' motorcade route.
Ma'am, why would he do that?
- How soon before you're ready?
- A couple of minutes.
I need to finish the arming mechanism.
Make sure you place the canister
to maximise casualties.
It must look as if this is a primary target.
It'll be taken care of.
- Yes.
- Do you have the key card?
I'll have it within the hour.
There can be no miscues. I'm using up
one of my canisters to create this diversion.
Without the key card, it's all for nothing.
Call me when you have it.
I will.
- Hello?
- I'm going to be there soon.
- Make sure you bring the money.
- You'll have it.
And you'll have your precious card.
Careful. It's all we've got left.
Don't worry about it. In a little while,
we'll be able to buy all you want.
Navy transport has arrived on site.
I'll advise...
Mrs. Logan and the Suvarovs
have been treated.
The chopper's picking them up now.
- What do I say to my wife?
- She put you in an impossible situation.
It's my job to handle impossible situations
and I failed, and not for the first time.
I should never have given in.
I should have ordered back the motorcade.
Sir, with all due respect, you don't have time
for self-recrimination. The attack failed.
We have to assume they'll make good their
threat to use the Sentox on American soil.
Has CTU made progress? Or are they waiting
for the other shoe to drop?
They're looking for a lead, working the scene
where the motorcade was ambushed.
Bill. They're airlifting the bodies
of the terrorists to CTU.
- When will they be here?
- Any minute.
- Let me know what you find.
- You got it.
- Jack's calling in.
- Put him on speaker.
We're in an emergency briefing.
Bill wants to put you on speaker.
- I thought Lynn took Bill off the roster.
- Lynn's been relieved of duty.
- OK, fine. Put me on.
- All right.
- All right, you're on.
- Jack, what did you find at Omicron?
Henderson set up the deal that allowed
the terrorists to gain control of the Sentox.
He tried to kill me by blowing up a bunker
Sentox was developed in.
I managed to survive, but the servers were
destroyed. Henderson managed to escape.
- Chloe, are you there?
- Go ahead, Jack.
- Can you hack Henderson's computer?
- I did. Henderson's work station is clean.
He wiped his hard drive,
but there's an active socket.
- What does that mean?
- He's exchanging data with a link.
Can you locate it?
Yeah, the registry listing
is 5714 Tarrowood Drive, Toluca Lake.
- Tarrowood Drive? That's his home address.
- I'll send a tac team.
- No, Bill. I need to go in alone.
- Why?
Henderson's good.
He'll detect a tac team moving in.
- How do you wanna play this?
- I'm the last person he expects to see.
I should be able to walk up to his front door.
All right, but I want you in constant contact.
Henderson is our primary link
to finding this nerve gas.
I know. I'll get back to you.
You've reached Banco Buenos Aires.
Enter your party's extension, or press
the star button for immediate assistance.
- Your identification code, please.
- 8477C, as in Charlie.
Yes, how can I help you?
I'd like after-hours access
to my personal safety deposit box.
Yes, sir.
- Buchanan.
- Bill.
We found a schematic of some kind of
ventilation system on one of the terrorists.
Since that's the way to deliver Sentox,
this could be their next target.
- Do we know what building it's from?
- Not yet.
Building and safety
are running it against their archive.
Upload it to Chloe and Edgar.
I want them on this.
Better make it fast. There's a number
handwritten in the margin. 1800 hours.
- The attack could happen in the next hour.
- Yeah.
That was Curtis. He's going to upload
schematics to our server.
This is the likely target of their next attack.
There was a time on it.
- It could occur in the next hour.
- Where is it?
We don't know.
The only thing Curtis could tell
is it's the ventilation in an industrial building.
- How big?
- Enough to hold several thousand. Find it.
- How are you doing, Tony?
- Fine.
Have you heard anything else
on my wife's condition?
I haven't heard anything new.
Sorry.
- Tony.
- You have to get back to recovery.
- Get away from me.
- Almeida, please.
I said get away from me.
Tony, come on.
My God!
Michelle.
- Thank God that you're all right.
- Let go of me.
Sorry. I made a mistake.
I didn't think I had any choice.
Charles.
It isn’t just that you...
You didn't stand up to them.
You should've stood up to them.
Martha.
Yuri, Anya, I can't tell you how glad I am
that you're both all right.
Thank you. It was awful.
I'm deeply embarrassed
this could happen on US soil,
but I promise you whoever did this
will be brought to justice.
- Excuse me, Mr. President.
- Of course.
We both know who is responsible for this.
We believe it was the group who attacked the
airport, but we thought they were all killed.
Obviously you were wrong.
The situation is more serious than you know.
The terrorists have possession
of a military nerve agent.
They've threatened to use it
against the population of LA.
- How long have you known?
- We just found out.
But given this change of circumstances, I'm
asking you to honour the terms of our treaty.
Allow my law enforcement agencies access
to whatever intelligence your security people
have on these separatists.
- You will have our help.
- Thank you.
I hope you won't find this offensive, but
there's something that's been troubling me.
- What is it?
- . Logan, her behaviour.
She has not been herself.
I'm sure she's very upset by what happened.
Yes, I imagine she would be,
but I noticed this before the attack,
from the time she entered the car
with Anya and me.
The truth is my wife
has been under a doctor's care for a while.
She suffers from depression and anxiety.
It's been very difficult for both of us.
- I'm sorry to hear that.
- Thank you.
- The guard said you wanted to see me.
- How long are you gonna keep me?
You're not going out there any time today.
The district marshal's reviewing your case.
I need to ask you a favour, Bill. I know
I don't deserve it. I was unfair to you earlier.
- What is it?
- I need to make a phone call.
If you think you can get out of this
with a few phone calls, you're mistaken.
It's not that, I swear. I'll give you the number.
You can clear it yourself.
What's this about?
My sister.
I need to talk to her about a personal matter.
- It can't wait a few hours?
- No, it can't.
Bill, please. She's in a little bit of trouble
and I'm the only one who can help her.
I don't need to clear it.
Get Mr. McGill a phone
and give him some privacy.
Thank you.
- Hello?
- Jenny, it's me.
Listen, I don't care that you took my wallet.
You can keep everything that's in it.
- I just need to get my key card back.
- What key card?
My CTU access card. It's of no value to you,
it just lets me in this building.
Can't you get them to give you a new one?
I mean, that's what I did
when I lost the key to my laundry room.
Dammit, Jenny. This isn't a laundry room.
This is a secure government building.
If you don't want me to call the police,
you'll get me back the key card today.
- You hear me?
- Yeah, I do.
Listen, I gotta go.
- Where's that card from Lynn's wallet?
- Why?
- I wanna give him his card. We don't need it.
- That's how I'm getting us all this money.
You told me we were gonna take his cash
and a credit card.
Yeah. I'm taking a credit card.
A $20,000 line of credit right here.
$20,000?
Who's gonna pay you that kind of money?
- Yes, Mr. President.
- I'd like to speak with my wife.
- I'm sorry, sir. She asked to be left alone.
- I wanna see my wife now. Move away.
Sir, she ordered me not to let anyone in.
I'm not "anyone", Evelyn.
I know, sir,
but she specifically mentioned you.
I have to get to a meeting. Would you tell
my wife I would like to speak with her?
Of course, Mr. President.
Thank you.
I'd like you to find Aaron Pierce right now.
I want to know how he's doing.
- Is there a message you want to get to him?
- If he's all right, tell him I'd like to see him.
Chloe, come here.
- I think I got a match.
- There's a discrepancy.
They're from different layers. Curtis's was
structural. This is an electrical blueprint.
You're right. Mr. Buchanan, Edgar matched
the schematics we got from Curtis.
- Where is it?
- Tyler Memorial, Westwood.
A hospital. Tell Curtis to activate a tac team.
I'll call Tyler Memorial, tell them to evacuate.
- Operations.
- Put me through to Tyler Memorial.
This is Bauer. I'm on site
at the Henderson house. Do you copy?
We found intel on the body of a dead terrorist.
There is going to be an attack.
- Where?
- Tyler Memorial, we think within the hour.
OK, I copy. I'm moving in now.
- Miriam.
- Who?
Christopher's wife. He's not here.
- Tell Chloe I'm gonna get back to her.
- All right. We're on it.
This is Manning with CTU.
I need to speak to the security officer.
- You're talking to him. Tom Wegman.
- I'm heading to you now with a tactical team.
The gas will most likely be released
into a ventilation unit. Seal the subbasement.
- I've called in a second security shift.
- How long before the hospital's evacuated?
- An hour, maybe two.
- This attack could occur within 30 minutes.
This is a large facility, Agent Manning.
We have 600 patients,
many of whom need assistance.
Mr. Wegman, if this nerve agent is released
into the ventilation system,
everyone inside that building will die.
Do what you have to do,
but get those people out of that building.
Right.
Hello, Miriam.
My God!
We thought you were dead.
Where is he?
What are you doing, Jack?
Miriam, where's Christopher?
He's still at work.
- Did he call you?
- You're scaring me, Jack.
- In the last hour, has he called you?
- No!
Now tell me what the hell is going on.
I need to see his computer.
- What are you doing?
- Where is his computer?
I'm not gonna tell you anything
until you tell me what is going on.
Christopher developed a chemical weapon
system called Sentox nerve gas for Omicron.
He enabled terrorists to gain control of it.
Now it's being used in Los Angeles.
So where is his computer?
Miriam, I am telling you the truth.
- We have proof that he brokered the deal.
- That's impossible.
Less than an hour ago, he tried to kill me.
Move towards the living room.
Keep walking towards the den.
I want you to take a seat on the couch.
Look, why don't we just call him?
I'm sure there's an explanation.
Miriam, take a seat.
You don't need the gun, Jack.
You're not gonna shoot me.
Chloe, I need access to Henderson's
hard drive. I need you to talk me through it.
OK, Jack.
Yes?
- You wanted to see me, ma'am?
- Oh, yes, Aaron. Come in.
I didn't really get a chance
to say thank you before.
You saved my life. I know that
you'll say it was all just in the line of duty.
Well, you're welcome.
The country's lucky to have men like you.
I'm lucky.
I hope you'll allow me to say that.
Mrs. Logan.
Would you excuse us, Aaron?
What is it, Mike?
- The president's been trying to reach you.
- I know.
I don't want to see him.
Would you like me to convey that to him?
You can convey whatever you want, Mike.
Mike.
Mike, I want you to know
nothing happened in there.
Whatever didn't happen,
make sure it doesn't happen again.
- Clark, cover the north. Blake, you're with me.
- Manning?
- Yeah.
- Wegman, hospital security.
Thanks. Have you uplinked to CTU yet?
We're doing it now. We've doubled security
at subbasement ingress points.
- Nobody's getting down there.
- Good.
The bad news is we have 26 patients in ICU
that can't be moved.
Seven are high-dependency newborns.
We can't relocate them without
specialised transport, which we don't have.
- What about nearby hospitals?
- All neonatal units are in service.
Thanks. I want a visual sweep
of high-probability targets in the hospital.
Team A, start at the north end,
team B, take south. Move.
It's Viktor. I'm at the hospital.
- Then why are you calling me?
- They must have found out.
The hospital's being evacuated.
The elevators and stairs are guarded.
Calm down, Viktor.
Bring up the schematics of the hospital.
There's an entrance to the subbasement -
an electrical conduit.
- There's a good chance it isn't guarded.
- How do I find it?
In the radiology wing. Call us
when you're there. We'll talk you through it.
- I'll call you in a few minutes.
- And, Viktor, I need you to finish this task.
Even if it means you don't get out.
I won't fail you.
DOD concluded a briefing with
Russian intelligence. We were given a name.
Vladimir Bierko. He made billions in
the post-Soviet economy in weapons and oil.
He bankrolled publications
promoting the separatist cause.
- It's believed he was more than a sympathiser.
- They think he's financing these attacks?
- They think he's directing the attacks.
- Based on what?
Communiqués intercepted
by the Russian security force,
supported by the fact
that Bierko vanished three months ago.
We posted Bierko's profile
to interagency servers.
Homeland Security has issued
an emergency brief to local law enforcement.
Any hope of finding him before the attack?
The most promising lead is a man named
Henderson. Unfortunately, he escaped.
Jack believes that files on Henderson's
computer could lead to Bierko.
He's trying to acquire those files now, sir.
Let's hope he succeeds. The country's
suffered three devastating attacks today.
- We need to stop this madman.
- Yes, Mr. President.
- Chloe, have you found anything yet?
- The only thing on it is domestic stuff.
Bill-paying programs, music.
He isn't trading music files with his office.
There's something else.
- I'm doing the best I can.
- Why don't you face it?
Christopher is innocent. He was when
you forced him out of CTU, and he is now.
- Maybe you didn't hear. He tried to kill me.
- If he did, he was defending himself.
No, he blew up the server room
while I was still inside.
He was destroying evidence
that would've implicated him in this.
This is familiar - you accusing him of being
a criminal. Why do you hate him so much?
I want you to know something.
Chris never hated you,
not even after what you did to him.
When he thought you were dead,
he looked in on Kim. He cared about her,
just like he cared about you.
We both did. You know that.
- I found something.
- What is it?
- It's a shadow drive. It was partitioned.
- What's on the shadow drive?
A log. It contains data for every satellite call
Henderson has made in the last year.
Can you cross-reference those
with numbers the terrorists used?
I got into the log,
but the lists are password protected.
Hold on. He had a secret file in his computer.
- There's a list of numbers.
- And that implicates him?
- We need access. You know the password?
- No, I don't.
We believe there's gonna be another attack
within 30 minutes.
Thousands of lives are at stake. Please.
If you know that password, I need it now.
I can't help you.
- Chloe, try and hack in.
- I'll see what I can do.
Hurry.
Let me show this to Manning. Good work.
Agent Manning?
One of our guards caught this.
This guy's dressed as an orderly,
but I've never seen him before.
An orderly has no business being where he is.
That was five minutes ago.
- Where is this?
- Subbasement.
Team A, southeast stairwell.
Team B, form a perimeter.
- We have a suspect. CTU, copy?
- We copy.
Edgar, uplink the video surveillance
for facial recognition.
- See if you can get a match.
- Got it.
Curtis has a suspect.
We're running facial recognition.
We're halfway through the database.
- Got something.
- Print it.
Curtis, we have a suspect. His name
is Viktor Grigorin, a Russian national.
Served time for drug smuggling
and weapons trafficking.
Copy that.
All teams, suspect is a confirmed hostile.
Repeat, a confirmed hostile.
Freeze!
Don't move!
Agent Manning,
you need to come look at this.
Search him.
Don't! It might be set to go off if it's moved.
- Chemical response team, we need you here.
- Copy that. On the way.
All teams, we've located the canister
and it is armed. Repeat, the canister is armed.
CTU,
the chemical response team is on the way.
Evacuation is in progress,
but there are a lot of people in here.
Copy that, Curtis.
Edgar, notify LAPD and all relevant agencies.
- I want a mandatory evacuation downtown.
- Yes, sir.
- Henderson's using interlaced encryption.
- What does that mean?
- It'll take me half a day to crack it.
- We don't have that kind of time.
Sorry. It's tougher than it looked
at first glance, OK?
All right.
Jack, Curtis and his team
intercepted a terrorist at the hospital.
- Did they take him into custody?
- No, he's dead. But they found a gas canister.
They're trying to disarm it now. There
are patients there that can't be evacuated.
Chloe, there's nothing you can do
about the hospital.
There are still 18 canisters out there.
Stay focused.
- I know.
- If I got more personnel, would that help?
I've already got three analysts on it.
Miriam.
Miri...
Honey, I want you to pack a bag. I want you...
Don't you move.
Miriam, sit back down.
Put your hands behind your head,
get back up on you knees. Now!
I want you to handcuff yourself
behind your back.
Get up.
Take a seat next to Miriam on the couch.
- Are you OK, honey?
- I'm OK.
- How do I find the nerve gas?
- I have no idea.
- Where is it?
- Start with my knee, just like I taught you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
- Where is it?
- He doesn't know, Jack. He doesn't know!
For God's sake, leave him alone.
Christopher, CTU found one of the canisters
at Tyler Memorial Hospital.
It's armed. People are gonna start dying.
How do I find the nerve gas?
Jack, leave him alone!
He doesn't know anything.
Do you really trust him?
Ask him what's in the briefcase.
Unlock it!
Ask him what he's doing with all the money.
Ask him!
Christopher? Is this true?
- Have you been lying to me?
- I've been protecting you.
- By lying?
- It's not that simple.
- I defended you.
- I defended you too, because I love you.
There's not one thing I've done out of greed.
Even when they fired me -
framed me - I served my country.
I don't care how you justify it.
I am out of time.
You are gonna tell me now
how to find the rest of the gas.
Go ahead and do it, Jack.
Get it done. Shoot me.
Kneecap me. Go ahead, do it. Do it!
- Oh, you son of a bitch!
- I shot her above the knee. She can still walk.
If you make me shoot her again, she'll be
in a wheelchair. How do I find the nerve gas?
Dammit!
- Where is it?
- Please. Please!
- Don't you make me do this.
- Tell him what he wants to know.
I can't.
Forgive me, Miriam.
You son of a bitch.
You don't care about anybody.
Not even her.
Chloe, it's Jack. I need an ambulance on site.
I repeat, I need an ambulance on site.
Miriam Henderson's been shot. I'm bringing
Christopher Henderson into CTU.
I need an interrogation room prepped,
and a medic with hyoscine pentothal.
- It'll be ready. Are you OK?
- Yeah, I'm fine, just get the ambulance here.
- The team's on its way.
- Put Buchanan on.
Mr. Buchanan, Jack's on line one.
- Jack.
- What's happening at the hospital?
There's a CRT team on site. Stand by, Jack.
- Curtis, what's your status?
- We're still trying to defuse the detonator.
- Look what we found.
- Is the evacuation on track?
Hold on, Bill.
- It's a remote timing display.
- Can you defuse the detonator?
- Not in 60 seconds.
- Then we're gonna have to get it out of here.
- It could detonate if you move it.
That's a chance we'll have to take.
All teams, we're moving the canister
to the containment unit. All right, go, go!
Go, go, go, go, go! Come on, let's go!
All teams, clear the halls. Clear the halls,
we're coming through. Go, go, go, go!
Make sure the door's open.
Go! Come on! We're coming upstairs.
We're coming upstairs.
Go! Go! Move! Move! Move!
Go, go, go! Clear the hall!
Get out of the way! Get out of the way!
Keep the halls clear! Coming through!
- Go!
I need to clear this hall.
Get them out of the way.
Go! Move! The hall's clear.
Move! Move!
I need to clear this area.
Move back!
Step aside, please.
- Get the door open!
Come on!
All right, get it in there.
We have negative pressure.
Clear!
CTU, the canister detonated
inside a containment unit.
- The hospital's safe.
- Good work.
- I have the key card.
- How long will it take you to reprogram it?
Five minutes.
Then we will be able to use it to access CTU.
Good.