Tony, we have a problem. We determined
a man who was exposed to the virus got out.
Son of a bitch! How'd that happen?
Got out before we reinforced the perimeter.
Probably didn't know he'd been exposed.
If we don't find this guy before he becomes
symptomatic, we might have an outbreak.
- What do you want?
- To give you your next assignment.
There's a man named Ryan Chappelle,
regional director of CTU. I want him killed.
Saunders has proven he will use this virus
to inflict mass casualties
if you don't do what he says.
How long am I supposed
to let him hold this country hostage?
Until we catch him.
- Saunders has another demand.
- What does he want now?
He wants you killed.
He's threatened to release the virus into
the population unless we deliver you by 7am.
My God, Jack.
He'll use the virus.
The president had no choice.
Ryan, I think we've found Saunders.
45 minutes ago he called from an apartment
near here. Chase is leading a team there now.
Good, Jack.
- No one's here.
- Why are you doing this?
Even if I told you, you wouldn't understand.
A van will be arriving shortly.
Leave Chappelle's body with the driver.
I'm sorry, Ryan, we gotta do this.
Get on your knees.
I'm sorry we let you down.
God forgive me.
He's clean. There's no tracker.
If you try to follow us,
Saunders will release the virus.
- Wayne Palmer.
- This is Jack Bauer.
Chappelle's body's just been picked up
by Saunders' people.
Thanks, Jack.
Ryan Chappelle is dead.
I ordered the death of one of our agents.
One of our finest.
As unthinkable as that was, I had to buy
some time in order to protect civilian lives.
I will not cave in to any more
of this terrorist's demands.
We're vulnerable as long as Saunders
has this virus and is willing to release it.
So far over 700 people have been infected,
and they're all gonna die.
Unless you're willing to accept more loss
of life, I don't know what else we can do.
He has us in a corner, David.
Convene the Cabinet.
Yes, sir.
- What'd you find?
- We worked up the money trails.
Saunders sends $10,000 a month
to his daughter Jane.
- He has a daughter?
- Right here on the screen.
She's 19, lives in Santa Barbara
and goes to school there.
Find out where she is now. Call Santa Barbara
PD and make sure they're on standby.
- Almeida.
- Tony, it's Jack.
- Jack, what happened?
- Chappelle's dead.
Saunders' people picked up his body.
Four men, all wearing hoods.
- Black van, no plates.
- I'll see if we can sat-track it.
I already put Adam on it.
Do we have any idea
why Saunders wanted Chappelle dead?
I was just about to call you. We found
a thread that Chappelle was working up.
- Looks like Saunders has a daughter.
- A daughter?
The money trail leads to a Jane Saunders.
- What do we know about her?
- She's 19, goes to school in Santa Barbara.
- Is she still there?
- I was just about to have her picked up.
Wait. Tony, Tony.
Don't. That's not the right play.
- Why not?
- We don't know anything about her.
We don't even know if she knows who her
father really is, and Saunders'll protect her.
So someone's watching her. If you wanna
grab her, do it without him knowing.
Which means we have to switch her out
with one of our own agents.
I don't know that we have the time.
We're gonna have to find an agent
in the next half-hour.
Saunders is calling all the shots. If we don't
do something, we're gonna be paralyzed.
I'll get started.
Chloe, we need to find
a Jane Saunders lookalike.
Get a description. Cross-reference it
with CTU agents in regions two and three.
- When do you need it?
- Right now.
- I just started the file on her.
- Chloe, just do it for me, please.
- Dessler.
- Hey, it's me. Did you get the test results?
I won't know if I'm infected for another hour.
What's taking so long?
They couldn't interpret the results here.
They had to send everything back to the lab.
How are you feeling?
I'm... I think I'm OK.
No nose bleeds? Nothing on your skin?
No. NHS has everything under control here.
I wanna keep busy. How can I help?
Adam's working on citywide containment.
I'll have him split off some of his workload.
Open up a socket.
You can help with NHS deployment.
I'll call you later, OK?
Yeah. OK.
Michelle's still at the hotel. I told her you'd
send over some of your system updates.
OK. I'll send 'em right over.
Where are we on this guy who escaped?
His name is Bill Cole.
He's an insurance sales rep.
His wife wasn't being very cooperative.
We did manage to get from her that Cole
came home unusually late and left early.
- For work?
- His office doesn't open for a half-hour.
We're looking for him now.
NHS just arrived.
They'll quarantine the house and test the wife.
- Who are we sending?
- Chase. He'll be there soon.
- Agent Bauer, I have the president for you.
- Patch him through.
- Jack.
- Mr President.
Stephen Saunders, the man who's in control
of the virus. You know him?
I worked with him on a mission that you
sanctioned, the Drazen mission in Kosovo.
The last conversation I had with him,
he said there would be other demands.
His exact words: "The main event to come."
- Any idea what he means?
- I wish I could tell you, sir.
Right now Stephen Saunders
is in a vengeful state of mind.
Any demands that he makes will be
detrimental to American security.
What I'm asking, Jack,
is what will he do if I say no to him?
When I worked with Saunders, I never
thought he was capable of mass murder.
Today we know he is. He still has the virus.
If you don't meet his demands, sir,
I believe that he will continue to release it.
- Thank you, Jack.
- Yes, Mr President.
Here's the list you wanted of the top ten
agents that could double as Jane Saunders.
- None of these are in Los Angeles.
- The closest is CTU, San Francisco.
Did you put together a second-tier list?
Yeah.
- You sure this is right?
- I double-checked when I saw the results.
- Kim Bauer.
- Could you come up to my office, please?
- Sure.
- Thanks.
- You're not gonna use her?
- We don't have a choice.
- Shouldn't you talk to Jack first?
- I'll take care of it, all right? Thank you.
Hi.
- Why don't you sit down?
- OK.
Kim, we need to question Jane Saunders
without her father knowing about it.
But we're pretty sure
he has somebody watching her.
Fine. What do you need me to do?
You're the same age, similar body types.
Your faces are not so different
that we couldn't disguise it from a distance.
You want me to pose as Jane Saunders?
We have better matches,
but they're too far away from this office.
So the bottom line is...
you're our best chance.
We don't have much time, we're still in
the early stages of planning this mission,
but if all goes according to plan,
it shouldn't be too dangerous.
Now, I'm not gonna order you to do this.
I know, and I know
what's been going on today,
and if you had a better option,
I know you'd take it.
I'm fine and I'll do it.
- You sure?
- Positive.
Chloe, I'm leaving for Santa Barbara.
Transfer all my stuff onto your system.
- I know. I already pulled your data.
- Good.
It's only fair I tell you,
I told Tony I didn't think you should do this.
- Field work isn't learn as you go.
- I'm not doing this to be a field agent.
- There's no one else.
- That's why I didn't fight Tony harder.
Not that he would listen to me anyway.
I know he doesn't respect my opinions.
- OK, look, I have to go.
- I just wanted to let you know how I felt.
I want you to know that I'm behind you 110%.
I really hope nothing bad happens to you.
Chloe, are you coordinating
this operation from inside?
- Of course.
- You should start prepping.
I bet there's two dozen agents
still waiting for comm codes.
I like your energy, Kim. Use it.
Adam, could you send me a list of personnel
on the Jane Saunders operation?
- I can't. I'm monitoring Chase.
- Did he find Bill Cole?
- Not yet. He's interrogating Cole's wife.
- This thing is out of control.
- I said on the phone that Bill isn't here.
-  I know.
But when he was here, did you notice
anything out of the ordinary?
- Was he bleeding from the nose?
- Not that I saw.
- What about rashes, skin irritation?
- No. Why would you think that he'd be sick?
He came in contact with some people
who were sick at the Chandler Plaza Hotel.
- When was he at the Chandler Plaza?
- Earlier this morning.
No, he wasn't.
He was with a client at the office.
He did it again, didn't he?
The bastard did it again.
- Ma'am...
- Then...
I hope he did get something.
I hope that he dies.
- Please, Mrs Cole, I need you...
- Get out of my way!
- Mrs Cole!
You need to stay calm
because I can't let you leave.
- Agent Edmunds.
- Yeah.
One of my men just found this.
- Where?
- Waste basket in the bathroom.
- Blood's tacky, which means it's fresh.
- Then Bill Cole's symptomatic.
I need you to contact every ER
and urgent-care facility in a 30-mile radius.
Excuse me. I've had a nose bleed
for an hour. I can't seem to stop it.
- Did you put ice on it?
- Yeah.
- Try an ER. Get it cauterized.
- I gotta go to work.
We don't have anything here that'll stop that.
All right. Thanks.
Excuse me.
The swap'll take place at the library.
She works there in the mornings.
- This is a file of relevant personal data.
- All right.
- Chloe, where's Tony?
- In the teleconference room with Kim.
Why isn't she working the satellite track?
You might wanna ask Tony about that.
Once you get into position, just act naturally.
Try not to look out of place.
- Jack.
- What are you doing with Kim?
Chloe came up with matches
for Jane Saunders.
- Good, so we've got one.
- You're not gonna like it.
It's Kim.
- My Kim?
- I'm not crazy about it, either.
But she's the only one that matched
physically and geographically.
- You're sending her out?
- She can handle it.
- Plus she has a safety net.
- Find someone else.
We need to get Saunders' daughter
without him knowing.
- Kim's our best shot at doing that.
- She's not doing it.
It's not up to you. It's her decision.
Fine. I'll order her not to do it.
Jack...
She doesn't work for you, Jack!
She works for me!
Don't.
- Dad, please don't do this.
- Get out of here.
Get out of here now,
or I'll throw you out myself! Move!
Jack!
Talk it over with your father.
If we have to abort this, I wanna know now.
I'll be outside.
- This is not going to happen!
- Somebody has to do it!
- Someone will. Not you!
- I'm the best match!
- You're not a field operative!
- I have weapons training.
- Saunders' people won't even come close.
- Kim, it's not a chance I'm willing to take!
You're not taking it! I am!
The reason why I gave you this job
is so that I could make sure you'd be safe!
I took this job because I wanted it.
Not because you wanted me here.
I know that this is hard for you.
But this is not your decision.
This is my job. Better yet, my duty.
I'm gonna be safe.
But I'm doing it.
- They ready to go?
- All set.
When we get there,
they'll do your hair and make-up.
We'll set you in a position where Saunders'
people can only view you from a distance.
- Are you getting a clear signal?
- It's fine.
- Kim.
- Yeah?
This is a gun I got for you. I don't think you'll
have to use it, but if you do, don't hesitate.
- OK.
- Come on. Let's go.
Please be seated.
Thank you for assembling on short notice.
You've already been briefed on the Cordilla
virus that is now threatening our cities.
What you don't know is
we have two new developments.
Wayne.
First, a vial of that virus
has already been released.
The Chandler Plaza Hotel here in Los Angeles
was the site of the first attack.
That situation is being addressed.
We have the identity of the perpetrator.
His name is Stephen Saunders
and he's a former Ml6 agent.
Apparently, Mr Saunders
has at least 11 more vials
and is threatening to release them
unless we meet his demands.
- What are those demands?
- So far there have been two.
One was for the president to use the phrase,
"The sky is falling" in a press conference.
He then demanded
we terminate one of our agents.
- One of our agents? Why?
- We're still looking into that.
What was his response
when you didn't comply?
It devastates me to tell you
that I had no choice but to comply.
A half-hour ago we delivered this agent's
body to one of Saunders' representatives.
My God.
Millions of lives are at stake.
I need each of your departments
to open your files to CTU, Los Angeles.
Give them whatever they need.
I'm trying to get into some DOD files.
I need authorization from Chappelle.
- When's he gonna be back?
- He's not.
What do you mean?
Could I have everybody's attention, please?
I'm sorry to have to tell you that...
Ryan Chappelle was killed
in the line of duty about a half an hour ago.
I can't give you any more details...
but I'll be assuming Ryan's responsibilities
until we hear from
Brad Hammond at Division.
There'll be an opportunity to pay proper
respects to Ryan, but now's not the time.
- Tony, it's Chase on line five.
- Thanks.
- Almeida.
- It's me. I'm at Cole's house.
We found evidence
he's almost certainly symptomatic.
How many people
did he come in contact with?
Just his wife.
NHS is moving her into isolation.
- I'll let the teams know.
- Transfer me to Kim.
- She was running a simulation for me.
- I gave that to Adam.
- Kim's out on assignment right now.
- What kind of assignment?
Saunders has his daughter
under surveillance,
so Kim's gonna take her place
when we grab her.
What the hell is she doing out there?
I don't wanna hear about it.
Kim was the only match we had.
There's gotta be other agents
you can use for this.
No, there aren't! Back off, Chase!
Where is she now?
She's on her way to Santa Barbara with Jack.
- Jack signed off on this?
- First of all, it's my call.
Secondly, yes, Jack did. But, most
importantly, Kim accepted the assignment.
I'm gonna transfer you over to Adam.
Fine.
I'm sorry about what happened earlier.
I didn't mean to scare you.
I just don't think what you're doing is right.
But I need you to understand something.
In the field I am in command.
You do what I tell you to do.
Do you understand me?
- Do you understand me?
- Yes.
OK, good.
... attempted to reach hotel officials,
the police, even the FBI.
My nose has been bleeding
for almost an hour. I can't get it to stop.
- Have a seat and fill this out.
- How long will that take?
There are a couple of patients ahead of you.
Not too long.
Thanks.
... contracted some illness. As to how
serious this illness is, we have no information.
We cannot verify this, but we are hearing that
whatever is infecting the people of this hotel,
it is very serious and possibly deadly.
Body bags have been spotted and rescue
workers are around the Chandler Plaza.
Authorities are not giving any information...
- Hey!
- One minute, sir.
No, now! I need to see a doctor now!
I was at that hotel.
- There is something wrong with me.
- Oh, my God. You're him.
Hold on. Dr Joyner. The man
we're supposed to isolate, he's here.
- Yes?
- We've just ID'd the body.
- And it's Chappelle?
- It's confirmed.
The thumb print matched the one in his file.
Good. Dump the body.
Yes, sir.
Did you take care of your problem?
Yes. Chappelle's dead. But CTU's still gonna
try to find out what he was working up.
So tell Lennox to stay alert.
Make sure he doesn't let Jane out of his sight.
- Yeah?
- Any problems over there?
No. She's leaving her apartment now.
She's going to work.
All right. Stay with her.
The next few hours are crucial.
I'll be here.
Mr President, we've started down
a slippery slope here, and unless we're...
Cut the euphemisms, Joseph.
What are you trying to say?
We're concerned about the fact that
you ordered the death of a high-ranking...
We're not here to second-guess
actions that have already been taken.
No one's more aware than I am
of the moral ambiguity of my decision.
I did it to buy CTU more time
to find Saunders
and to delay for as long as possible
the slaughter of millions.
I made the decision to protect their future.
Not mine.
Saunders.
I have to take this.
Yes.
I've confirmed the identity
of Chappelle's body.
It will be disposed of respectfully.
We know who you are, Mr Saunders.
Whatever you want to accomplish,
you'll fail.
Your only chance is to relinquish the virus
and hope we don't find you.
That's not going to happen.
What is it you want?
To make America clean again.
You see, Mr President, the world
hates America, and for good reason.
I won't bother going into the details.
You know better than I
the atrocities your nation commits.
But we're gonna change all that.
You and I, together, are going to dismantle
the military machine that exports
its ugliness across the globe.
- And how are "we" going to do that?
- We'll start where the work gets dirtiest.
Something I know a little about.
Covert foreign nationals.
In 32 countries your government employs
grade A through H intelligence consultants.
They are citizens of their countries.
They're spies working against those countries
at the behest of
the American military machine.
In 45 minutes I want a list of their identities
sent to me by way of a website:
sylviaimports.com.
If you fail to comply, I will release
two vials of the virus in major cities.
And this time, they won't be in hotels
where they can be contained.
- Agent Bauer. Rachel Forrester.
- Agent Kim Bauer.
- She's gonna double for Jane Saunders.
- We're set up a staging area by the library.
- Is it a safe distance away?
- We won't be detected.
- Is she there yet?
- She will be in a few minutes. Let's go.
Make sure nobody leaves their house.
Sheriff's department is sending officers.
Until they get here, use your men.
Excuse me.
- Edmunds.
- We found Bill Cole.
- Where?
- An urgent-care center not far from you.
- Laurel Canyon and Moorpark.
- I know it.
Get over there and get as much as you can
off of Cole. He's pretty agitated.
Tony, is Kim in play yet?
- She just landed at Santa Barbara.
- I'll call you.
- Where's Jane now?
- In the library, behind the reference desk.
- How crowded?
- 10, 20 people.
One belongs to Saunders, and their orders
are not to let her out of their sight.
We've taken over the surveillance cameras
and narrowed it down to five probables.
Get that intel over to Tony Almeida at CTU.
OK, let's see her.
You're not gonna fool anyone
who knows Jane up close.
- I know.
- Stay at least 10 feet behind the counter.
I want you to keep your head down
as much as possible.
The wig looks darker than Jane's hair.
It's the best we could do at short notice.
You're gonna have to match every detail
as closely as possible. Her life depends on it.
Mr Cole, when you were inside the store,
who did you come in contact with?
- What do you mean, contact?
- Who did you talk to?
Just the pharmacist behind the counter.
How many others? Customers?
Yeah, there were some other people there.
How many other people were there?
Bill, if we do not identify and track down
everyone you have come in contact with,
we are gonna have a citywide epidemic,
so how many people?
I don't know.
Think!
That's it.
We're now patched in to campus security.
We're all up.
Nothing on B.
Go ahead. Try six.
On your screen, go ahead
and isolate the front desk.
-  Five is good.
- Top screen set.
- No.
- That's all we can get from it?
Let's see if we can activate it.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Hi, Jane.
- I am so sorry.
- You're not supposed to have drinks in here.
- I'm sorry. I'll throw it away.
- It's OK.
Start tracking that man in the red shirt.
I wanna know everything that he does.
Got subject on camera four right now.
I was just about to replace those.
Here you go.
There you go. Clear.
- No activity.
- What camera are you on?
- The main screen.
- What the hell is taking her so long?
Checking all screens now.
- Where's subject?
- Nothing on one.
- Come on.
- Nothing on two.
- Still on four?
- Negative.
She's coming out on four.
Kim, there's a man heading
from the bookcase at your three o'clock.
Red shirt. He might be one of Saunders'men.
I want you to angle away from him slowly.
- Good.
- We still have subject Red Shirt on camera.
We just got off the phone with Chase,
who's with Cole right now.
After Cole left the hotel,
he went to his house in Burbank.
He stopped at a gas station
on Riverside Drive, self-service.
His wife confirmed he didn't become
symptomatic until after he got home.
- The nose bleeds and sweating?
- Right.
Here's where the ripple effect starts.
At 7.20 he stopped at a pharmacy
and asked the pharmacist, Sam Tyler,
for medication to stop the bleeding.
There were three other people
inside that pharmacy.
Anne Schwartz has been going to the
pharmacy for years, so they had her address.
We've sent NHS people to her house.
She has a husband and three children.
- And the other two customers?
- IDs unknown.
They could be anywhere, spreading the
disease to anybody they're in contact with.
It gets worse. At the urgent-care facility
there were six patients when Cole came in
who left before the quarantine
was put in place.
We're tracking them down,
but between them and the staff at the facility,
we could be looking at up to 75 people
just in their families.
If any of these people are in a supermarket
or a mall when they become symptomatic,
it's gonna be impossible to contain.
We need to identify 'em and find them now.
Coordinate with NHS and Hazmat.
We have to set up a quarantine in two
neighborhoods in the Studio City area.
Department heads report to Adam.
If Wally has time,
have him get on the exterior cams.
Good work, everybody.
It looks like this worked.
Maintain monitoring
and come get me if anything happens.
Thank you. Good work.
What's going on?
- Who are you?
- My name is Jack Bauer.
I'm a federal agent.
You're not in any danger.
What do you want?
We need your help.
We need to get in touch with your father.
- What do you need me for?
- We don't know where he is.
And we think you do.
What's this about?
You don't know who your father really is.
First of all, I hardly know my father,
and whatever this is, I know it's illegal.
You have no right to keep me here. Release
me now. I haven't done anything wrong.
Listen to me very carefully, Jane.
Your father is engaged in terrorist activity
against the United States.
He's killed hundreds of people
and has threatened to kill thousands more.
I can only imagine how difficult
this must be for you to believe,
but you're going to cooperate with us.
There's a lot at stake
and there's not a lot of time.
I'm not gonna do anything.
I wanna talk to a lawyer.
There's no lawyer. There's just you and me.
I don't know anything about my father.
He comes into town twice a year.
I don't even know where he lives.
- How do you contact him?
- I don't. He calls me.
- You're lying to me, Jane.
- I'm not.
Don't try protecting him.
You'll get in trouble.
You're the one in trouble.
You're breaking the law!
You think I'm playing a game here with you?
Hundreds of thousands of lives
are on the line.
You have no idea how far I'm willing to go
to acquire your cooperation.
- What are you threatening?
- Where is he?
I don't know! Please somebody help me!
- Where is your father?
- Jack. Red Shirt is approaching the desk.
Please.
- What's going on?
- He's at the desk.
Kim, don't turn around.
Just stay where you are.
- Where the hell's the librarian?
- Get someone to the reference desk now.
- Excuse me.
- Just a minute.
- I need some help with finding a book.
- Just one second.
You're doing great.
Just stay calm until we check this guy out.
Give me a close-up of the gentlemen.
- Can I get some help here?
- I'll be with you in a minute.
OK, Kim, I want you to slowly get up and try
and make your way to the bookshelves.
Stay out of his eye line
until we find out who this guy is.
Maintain a constant visual on her.
- Get camera three on Kim.
- Coming over to camera three.
- Get me another angle.
- There is no other angle.
- What's going on?
- Camera three should pan back on her.
- You work here, don't you?
- Yeah.
- Could you help me find something?
- Yeah. What is it that you need?
Call for help and I'll kill you right now.
- What?
- Who has Jane Saunders?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
Let's go. Come on.
Back in range in three seconds.
Where the hell is she? Kim?
- Dammit!
- Team two! Go! Go!
Get down! Get down!
Kim!
Kim, step back. Step back!
Radio back. Tell them subject is down.
- Are you OK?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
Saunders is gonna know
we have his daughter.