Previously on 24:
- Almeida.
- Tony, it's me. Gael's dead.
He was suffering so badly. No one
should have to go through what he did.
There are children upstairs
who are going to die in agony.
Unfortunately,
there's nothing we can do for them.
Actually, there is.
Suicide capsules.
For the people down at the hotel.
- It's against every regulation in the book.
- Yeah.
Do it.
Get down!
Saunders' computer file.
What server did you store it on?
A 5.
Chase. We got a bomb.
- How much time?
- None.
I got it. Go! Go!
Chappelle.
Ryan, it's Jack. Almost the entire Ml6 office
has been wiped out.
One of the things Saunders was trying to
destroy was the information Ml6 had on him.
I retrieved the hard drive.
Got anything yet?
I'm following the money trail.
- What do you want?
- To give you your next assignment.
There's a man named Ryan Chappelle,
regional director of CTU.
- I want him killed.
- It's out of the question.
Before you decide,
you might want to drop by the Chandler
Plaza Hotel, look at what's happening.
Then imagine the same taking place
at hundreds of locations all over the country.
You're insane.
The following takes place
between 6am and 7am.
This office isn't above the law. How can
I authorize the murder of an innocent man?
David, we're fighting a war.
Ryan Chappelle is not a civilian.
I still can't order him to be killed.
So what's the alternative?
Yes, David, I know it's extreme, I realize that.
But it's the only move we have. Look at
what's happening at the Chandler Plaza.
Saunders has proven he will use this virus
to inflict mass casualties
if you don't do what he says.
How long am I supposed
to let Saunders dictate my actions?
- How long does he hold us hostage?
- Until we catch him.
- And what if we don't?
- We will.
But until we do your only
option is to sacrifice Chappelle.
The hard drive from Ml6 is at the IT lab.
They're sorting the data now.
- London wants you to debrief them on Ml6.
- Are we any closer to finding Saunders?
He's using a scrambler
to contact the president.
- It could take 24 hours to trace.
- That's the only search we've got going?
Saunders transferred money
to Amador using a server in Los Angeles.
I'm following Amador's money
to see if it leads to Saunders.
- You haven't turned up anything.
- No.
The computer we confiscated
from the "Go" club is a dead end.
I'm back-tracing Saunders' offshore accounts.
- OK, fine.
- Jack, the president's holding.
- Transfer it here.
- He has to speak to you in private.
He's on the line at station seven.
Excuse me.
- This is Bauer.
- Agent Bauer, please hold for the president.
Mr President, I have Jack Bauer for you.
- Jack?
- Mr President?
- Are you alone right now?
- Yes, sir.
Saunders called. He's made another demand.
What is it?
This is a hard one, Jack.
So I'm gonna be as direct as I can be.
- He wants Ryan Chappelle dead.
- I'm sorry, I don't understand.
- He wants his body at the train yard.
- Why would Saunders want Chappelle dead?
He wouldn't say. But he was emphatic about
the consequences if his demand wasn't met.
Jack, I feel as though I'm crossing a line
that I will never be able to step back from.
So then you've made your decision, sir.
Unless you can suggest a way to handle this.
- What time is this supposed to happen?
- Seven o'clock.
- We need to find Saunders before then.
- That's in less than an hour.
- Yes, I know, sir. I should get going.
- Jack.
I'm sorry to put this on you,
but I didn't know who else to call.
I understand, sir. I'll get back to you.
Chloe, what are you doing
right now to help find Saunders?
- We're relaying our data streams to Division.
- Why there?
They're the hub now.
They gather information for us...
- Forget that. Search from here.
- What kind of search?
What's the largest base
of knowledge on Saunders?
- Financial.
- Follow the banks.
- I'll have to clear it with Chappelle.
- No, you can't do that.
He gave the order. He outranks you.
Do what I ask you.
And don't let Chappelle know, you got it?
No, I don't. He's mad at me already. I'm not...
Chloe!
Chloe, I wouldn't ask you to do it
like this if it wasn't very important.
OK? So please, just do this for me.
- Fine.
- Thank you.
Nearly a third are symptomatic,
and it's getting worse.
They should have the choice
to end their own lives.
The capsules should be there soon.
Tony?
Yeah?
I realize we've both been
talking around this, but...
- if my test comes back positive...
- Michelle, don't go there.
Sweetheart, we both know
my chances of survival are low.
You still have a chance, and while there's
still a chance, I don't want to talk about this.
OK. Just...
No matter what, I just want you to know...
the last three years
have been the best years of my life.
I should be there with you.
- You are.
- No. It's not the same.
The best thing you can do for me right now
is to make sure those capsules get here.
I'll do my best.
I know you will.
Tony, I need to speak to you.
- Michelle?
- Yeah.
- Did she get her test results back yet?
- No, they won't be back for another hour yet.
What's going on?
Do you know if Saunders and Chappelle had
any history, if their paths had ever crossed?
Not that I'm aware.
What kind of connection you looking for?
The kind that would make
Saunders want Chappelle killed.
Cos that's what he just
ordered the president to do.
By 7am he wants Ryan Chappelle dead.
- Why?
- That's what I'm trying to figure out.
And the president put this on you?
I don't know what I'm gonna do
if we don't find Saunders by seven.
Have you told Ryan about this?
No, not yet.
I should change his clearance before you do.
- You think he's a flight risk?
- We can't take a chance now.
I'll get Chappelle to send his data to Chloe.
Prep her and whoever you can spare to sort it.
- They'll want to know what's going on.
- They don't need to know.
- I'll take care of it.
- Thank you.
- Field Ops. O'Brian.
- Chloe.
- Put all protocols on hold for the next hour.
- Got it.
- OK.
- All right.
What did the president
want to talk to you about?
You.
Me? What about me?
Ryan, come with me.
Just take a seat.
- What's going on here?
- Saunders has another demand.
What does he want now?
Jack.
He wants you killed.
- Is this some kind of a joke?
- It's no joke.
He's threatened to release the virus into
the population unless we deliver you by 7am.
Did Palmer actually go along with this?
My God, Jack.
He'll use the virus.
The president had no choice.
- He sent you to kill me?
- Not if we can find Saunders by 7am.
Ah, great.
That gives us a lot of time, doesn't it?
- I don't understand. Why me?
- We don't know.
Think hard. Do you have any connection
with Saunders we don't know about?
No. The first time I heard
the name Stephen Saunders was today.
The transactions
you investigated triggered this.
I haven't traced them to Saunders yet.
The fact that he wants you dead
proves that they lead back to him.
And you expect
to figure this out by seven o'clock?
Finding Saunders in time
is the only way to keep you alive.
And I will use everything
at my disposal to do that.
Ryan, I need your help.
I need all your files, everything, sent over
to Chloe so she can start going through it.
I'm sorry, Ryan.
Let's find this guy.
- What have you got?
- I've found Saunders' offshore bank account.
I accessed his account off their network,
but it's encrypted. Another brick wall.
Send it to Chloe.
If anyone can break it, she can.
- Not in the time we have.
- You don't know that.
It has to be now, Jack, now.
This is it. Don't you understand?
Oh, of course you understand.
You're the one who's gonna kill me.
We're doing everything we can.
Don't you realize the possibility
that this might not even be relevant?
Saunders knows killing me
doesn't kill the investigation.
It might be something else I know,
- that I haven't made a connection with yet.
- Then, think, Ryan, think.
But don't give in to this bastard. With all of us
working together, we're gonna find this guy.
Send the encrypted account over
to Chloe's desk. I'll explain it to her. Come on.
Chloe. Ryan's forwarding a file to you.
Please let me... let me call my wife.
We're under orders to keep this secret,
so we don't create a panic.
Yeah, I won't tell her anything,
and your people can listen in.
That order comes directly from the president.
I have done everything
I can do to help you. Please.
I just want to... I just want to hear her voice.
Please.
I'm sorry.
- Sir?
- I'm so sorry.
There you go.
Can I have your attention, please?
What I'm about to tell you
will be difficult to hear.
But it's important
you have all the information,
so you can each make your own decision.
First, I want all of you to know that...
once symptoms of infection appear,
there is no chance of recovery.
As the virus progresses, it attacks
the body's organs and major blood vessels.
This process is extremely painful.
The estimated time of death
is within six hours.
I'm telling you all of this
as directly as possible because...
we can offer each of you an alternative.
Some pills that you can take that will
make you feel like you're going to sleep.
It will be up to each
one of you to decide when,
and if, you want to use these drugs.
They will be available shortly.
Thank you.
Michelle, we have a situation.
A woman told us she can't find the man she
was here with. She hasn't seen him for hours.
- Sure he's not in isolation?
- Yeah, we let her look.
- What's his name?
- That's the problem. She doesn't know.
- I'm Agent Michelle Dessler.
- I'm Kathy, Kathy McCartney.
You realize how important
it is we account for everyone?
- Yes. That's why I came forward.
- We need you to be completely honest.
I am. All I know is that his name is Bill,
and I'm not even sure if that's real.
What do you mean?
We met tonight at a club on Hill, and we really
connected, so we decided to come here.
- Who booked the room?
- I did.
When was the last time you saw him?
We fell asleep in the room, and when
the fire alarm woke me up, he was gone.
- Do you remember what time you fell asleep?
- I know, I looked at the clock. It was 4.02.
Stay here, please.
Sunny.
If she's right, then this man was
in the hotel when the virus was released,
and he got out of the building
before it was locked down.
Is it possible he's in the hotel?
No. No. We've accounted
for everyone in the guest rooms,
and we've done an infrared
sweep of all the public areas.
Ed. Get a forensic team up to her room.
Dust for prints.
- There'll be dozens of prints.
- Do it.
This is Miller. We need a forensic team.
- Kathy. I need you to come with me.
- Why?
You need to show me every surface
that Bill may have touched. Come on.
Thanks.
Chloe needs processing power. I need you to
open up another socket in the network for her.
How's he doing?
He's scared.
Chase has a strike team ready to go
as soon as we get a location.
I ordered a helicopter from Air Tactical.
Train yard's across town.
- We can't be slowed down by traffic.
- OK, good.
- I'll get the socket open for Chloe.
- Thanks.
Jack. The bank used deep encryption.
We'll have to use a password crack.
- How long?
- It could take 90 minutes.
- We don't have time.
- I'm doing my best.
Maybe if you told us why
this overrides our protocol...
All you need to know is,
I need these files now.
I'm doing my best.
Your tone is not a morale booster.
Chloe, please, just do it.
- Let me help with the parallel processing.
- Good idea.
Send it to my station.
Ryan.
I'm sorry, Mr Chappelle.
We can't let you leave.
- What?
- Please return to CTU, sir.
- Who the hell do...
- We have orders.
From who? I'm regional director,
I countermand any order given.
-  Ryan.
- What the hell's going on here, Jack?
Why aren't I being allowed
to leave the building?
You think I'm trying to run?
I'm going out to smoke a cigarette. I wouldn't
condemn millions to death so I could live.
Let me see the cigarettes.
These men will escort you back to holding.
- I don't think so.
- I'm not asking, Ryan.
Under the authority given to me by the
President of the United States, I order you.
Tony, we have a problem. We determined
a man who was exposed to the virus got out.
Son of a bitch! How'd that happen?
Got out before we reinforced the perimeter.
Probably didn't know he'd been exposed.
Have you notified Health Services?
They're aware.
The problem is, we don't know who he is.
- He wasn't a registered guest.
- What was he doing inside the hotel?
Having a one-night stand.
The woman he was with came forward.
Any sign of him on the cameras?
Nothing at the front desk,
and no one saw him come or go.
- What are we doing to find him?
- Our best shot is prints.
We've pulled dozens from
the light switches, bathroom fixtures.
Send the prints to us.
See what else you can get from this woman.
Got it.
- Sorry I can't be more helpful.
- You're doing great.
Let's just go over this one more time.
The two of you came into the room.
I had the key,
so I'm the one who opened the door.
- We didn't turn the lights on or off.
- Did he go to the window, draw the blinds?
No, we just started kissing right away.
- And where were you standing?
- I was here, by the bed.
- And then what happened?
- He started taking my clothes off.
- The clothes you're wearing now?
- Yeah. He pulled my shirt over my head,
- and then my pants, and then...
- I need your belt.
Miller, try the buckle.
Couple of prints look like hers.
- Hold it. I got a partial thumb.
- It's not hers?
Checking.
No. She's got inverse swirls.
This print doesn't.
Upload it to CTU. Now.
If we don't find this guy before he becomes
symptomatic, we might have an outbreak.
Where have you been?
I had a client meeting. I told you that I
wouldn't come home if it went too late.
That's right. Kinda wish
you would have called, I was worried.
I didn't want to wake you up.
Jack, I think I'm getting something.
Applying last layer keywords.
We cracked it.
We have access to Saunders' bank account.
- Tell me what address they've got on him.
- Several, one in Los Angeles.
- An apartment five minutes away.
- How do we know it's real?
When money is moved,
the location of the call is confirmed.
Saunders called 45 minutes ago,
from that address.
- I'll call Chase.
- He can't let Saunders see us.
Good work. Great work. Thank you.
Open it.
- Ryan, I think we've found Saunders.
- Through his bank account?
45 minutes ago he called from an apartment
near here. Chase is leading a team there now.
Good, Jack. Thank God.
Ryan.
- We still need to go to the train yard.
- Now? What are you talking about?
We have to be in place,
in case the strike team isn't successful.
But you said they know
he was there 45 minutes ago.
This is just a precaution. We have to do it
until we have him in custody, you know that.
I've got a helicopter waiting for us,
but we should go now.
- All right, Jack.
- OK.
- We'll be in touch as soon as we're airborne.
- All right.
Mr Chappelle, Division confirmed
your three o'clock briefing. That OK?
Sure.
Mr President. Helen Stoopen
from the LA Timesjust called my office.
She was asking about some kind of toxic
accident at the Chandler Plaza Hotel,
- and if it was connected to the red alert.
- What exactly did she say?
Not much. She was fishing.
I appreciate you need to keep things
from me, but this story will get out,
- and when it does I'll need to have answers.
- Jerry's right, David.
The sooner we bring him into the loop,
the better he can handle the press.
A weaponized virus was released
into that hotel's ventilation system.
Oh, my God.
When will you go public with this?
Once we're sure the virus has been contained,
and there's no longer a threat.
- Are you certain that it will be contained?
- We're doing everything possible.
Yes, sir.
Jack. Tony said you're not
coming with me to get Saunders.
- You and Baker head up the strike team.
- I don't understand. Saunders is the priority.
I've ordered Jack downtown
to answer a few more questions.
You know what, Ryan?
All you do is put obstacles in our way.
We need our best people.
You tie us down with your bureaucratic BS.
Chase.
Those are the orders.
- What's going on, Jack?
- Just take care of the strike team.
-  Any sign that he's in there?
-  I can't get a visual inside.
- Three men outside the building.
- We can take 'em out with a sniper.
No, we can't. If we miss, Saunders will
know we're here. I want to do this up close.
- It's in the open. They'll see us a block away.
- That's why he picked the place.
I don't see how we get to them
before they can warn Saunders.
I do.
- They're grounding flights from LAX.
- Did the couriers get out with their vials?
New York, Washington, San Francisco
made it through. They're on their way.
I rerouted Las Vegas, our man is driving there
now. But we missed Chicago and Cleveland.
Did you revise the casualty projections?
- Of course. Here they...
- Just give me the number.
- Two to five million dead within 48 hours.
- Good enough.
There is a chance the outbreak
will spread beyond the Americas.
We'll be fine, don't worry.
Tony. We got results back
on the fingerprint from the hotel.
- What you got?
- For a complete print, there'd be one match.
But it's a partial, so we get results from
anyone whose prints match that quadrant.
How many potential matches
we talking about?
The FBI database gave
us almost 300 possibilities.
Upload the pictures to the hotel,
have that woman check 'em.
- OK, I'm on it.
- Tony. Ryan Chappelle on line three.
Ryan?
What's taking Edmunds so long?
Has he called in yet?
He's moving into position
around the building.
Why are they waiting?
Why haven't they gone in?
They're preparing a covert entry. Takes time.
Well, get on 'em, Tony.
Get them into that building.
Chase is running this operation.
He needs to make this call.
Ryan, Chase knows what's at stake here.
He's gonna go in when it's safe.
Just try and relax.
- Ryan, you still there?
- I'm here.
- I'll hook you up to the real-time com feed.
- Good.
- Tony, I've got a visual on the train yard.
- Copy that.
No one in the lobby.
Baker and I are moving up the stairs.
Grahams and Martinez
are coming down from the roof.
The guard at the top of the stairs has been
taken out. Proceeding down the hall.
You got one man by the door.
We're gonna have to move fast. My lead.
Set.
- Clear.
- No one's here.
It's a switching node.
He's been relaying calls
from this location. Dammit!
- This is Bauer.
- You underestimate me, Jack.
Why are you doing this?
Even if I told you, you wouldn't understand.
Try me.
Tell your people not to bother tracing
that relay. I've switched to another node.
- Stephen.
- A van will be arriving shortly.
Leave Chappelle's body with the driver.
Do not attempt to follow the van.
If you don't follow my directions,
I will release the virus immediately.
Can I have everyone's attention, please?
These are the drugs
Agent Dessler told you about earlier.
Anyone who wants to exercise
this option can step forward.
Thank you.
- Michelle.
- Did you find a match?
Partial print gave us a few hundred possibles,
which we narrowed down to a dozen men.
Ms McCartney's looking at 'em now.
That's not him.
No.
- This one. I think that's him.
- Are you sure?
Yeah. I'm sure.
Find him.
Are you OK, William?
You've been in there for a while.
- Uh, I have some kind of bug.
- Do you want me to make some tea?
No, I'm fine.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah.
Yeah, I gotta go to the office.
- I have a staff meeting.
- OK.
Kaufman.
This is Jack.
Have you got satellite coverage?
- Not yet, I'll reposition.
- Black van, no plates.
Do everything you can to follow it.
OK.
- We have to go, Ryan.
- Yeah.
- My legs are shaking.
- I've got you.
Ryan, is there anyone you want to talk to?
What do you mean, to say goodbye?
To say whatever you have to.
I have a brother I haven't spoken to in years.
I don't have that many friends.
Just the people at work.
So, no. There's no one.
I'm sorry, Ryan, we gotta do this.
Get on your knees.
All right, there's no way around this,
right, Jack? We don't have any outs here.
Not that I can see.
Wait.
I...
Let me do this myself.
At least give me the dignity of taking
my own life. That's something you can do.
- No, Ryan, I can't do that.
- Yes, you can.
You were right, back at CTU, to put me under
watch. I wasn't going out for a cigarette.
I was trying to bolt.
But I know this has to happen.
I can't take that chance.
I'm giving you my word, Jack.
I won't run. I swear.
I-I'd be lying if I said I wasn't scared,
but I'm not gonna run.
I couldn't live with myself, knowing I was
responsible for the deaths of all those people.
You've gotta believe me.
I can't. I can't.
It's all right.
I'm sorry we let you down, Ryan.
God forgive me.