You've already been briefed on the Cordilla
virus that is now threatening our cities.
A vial of that virus has been released.
We have the identity of the perpetrator.
His name is Stephen Saunders
and he's a former Ml6 agent.
In 32 countries your government employs
intelligence consultants. They're spies.
In 45 minutes I want a list of their identities.
If you fail to comply, I will release
two vials of the virus in major cities.
- Looks like Saunders has a daughter.
-  A daughter?
She's 19,
goes to school in Santa Barbara.
I was just about to have her picked up.
Tony, that's not the right play. If you wanna
grab her, do it without him knowing.
Which means we have to switch her out
with one of our own agents.
OK, let's see her.
You're not gonna fool anyone
who knows Jane up close.
I know.
Clear.
You think I'm playing a game?
Hundreds of thousands of lives
are on the line.
You have no idea how far I'm willing to go
to acquire your cooperation.
- Where is your father?
- I don't know!
- Could you help me find something?
- Yeah.
Call for help and I'll kill you.
Kim? Dammit!
Saunders is gonna know
we have his daughter.
These quarantine zones
were set up an hour ago.
Since then two new patients
were discovered at an ER in Silver Lake
and one at Hancock Park.
Those two cases engendered
five new quarantine areas.
That's three per cent of the city.
If containment isn't total,
it'll grow exponentially.
All right. Thanks, Adam.
We're all tired. I know that.
And some of you have been working
for 24 hours straight.
So I don't have to tell you
how serious this situation is.
But we can't drift.
If there ever was a worse-case scenario,
this is it. We're in it.
Everyone has to stay on point.
We've switched from prevention
to containment. The virus is out.
- You all right?
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I'm sorry it had to go down like this.
The man I shot, is he dead?
Yeah.
What's gonna happen now?
Saunders is gonna know we got Jane.
- This is Jack.
- The Saunders girl's calmed down.
- You can try talking to her again.
- Thanks, Rachel.
We'll see what we can get from the daughter.
- I understand.
- You'll tell him?
I'll tell him.
- I want every precaution taken.
- I'll get back to you.
- What's going on with Jack Bauer?
- The operation wasn't completely successful.
They have Saunders' daughter
but didn't remain covert.
- So Saunders knows we have her?
- Not yet.
But CTU is estimating
he'll find out within the hour.
- What's Jack's plan?
- Use Saunders' daughter.
Try to locate him.
David, listen, the deadline for his next
demand is gonna be up in about 15 minutes.
Giving this guy a list of every foreign
operative on our payroll's an act of treason.
I know that, but he'll release
more of the virus if we don't.
So what do you wanna do?
I wanna see what Bauer
gets out of the daughter first.
You know what just happened?
A man who your father hired to protect you
just tried to kill one of my agents.
So you killed him, right?
A man that worked for my father.
You're a smart girl, Jane.
Look out at that room.
Everyone here is a federal agent whose job
it is to protect the lives of American citizens.
I know how hard it must be
to believe everything
that everybody's been telling you
about your father.
But I'm gonna show you some things
that'll change your mind.
The sooner you stop resisting me,
the sooner you can help us start saving lives.
Why are you putting all this on me?
Because you're Stephen Saunders' daughter,
and, unfortunately,
you're the only leverage we have against him.
You can't just say these outrageous things
and expect me to believe you.
I know.
Truth is, I knew your father.
I worked with him.
He was a good man. He was a brave man.
But something's happened to him.
All I care about now is stopping him
from doing what he's doing.
I can't do that without you. I need your help.
- Palmer still hasn't sent the list yet.
- He has 15 more minutes.
CTU is trying to use IP locators
to get at you through the domain name.
- We're protected, though, right?
- Yes, it's a dead end.
Good.
Thank you.
I'm gonna show you who your father really is.
These photographs were taken
over eight years ago.
Your father said he was going
on a fact-finding mission,
but we were both part of a unit dispatched
to Kosovo to kill a man named Victor Drazen.
This was where the mission ended,
Drazen's hide-out.
When I left, I believed
your father had died in the blast.
The government told your mother
that's where he died.
But recently we discovered that your father
contacted you four years ago. Is that right?
Yes.
A couple of months after my mother died,
I got a call from him.
He said he was living under an assumed
name and that nobody knew he was alive.
And, for his protection, I couldn't
tell anyone that I had spoken to him.
Did he ever tell you why he had
contacted you after so many years?
Yes.
He missed me.
I understand that.
Over the last three to four hours
we've been pulling data from Interpol.
Here are some more recent images.
This is your father with Sayid Kolobe,
a known weapons dealer in the Middle East.
Here he's with a biologist who's now
spending the rest of his life in prison
for the manufacturing
of illegal biological weapons.
He could have been meeting with them
for any number of reasons.
I'll play you an audio file, one of three
that we got from your father earlier today.
This is your father talking to the president.
... working against those countries at the
behest of the American military machine.
In 45 minutes I want a list of their identities
sent to me by way of a website:
sylviaimports.com.
If you fail to comply, I will release
two vials of the virus in major cities.
Two more vials.
He's already released one.
This is a live feed from
the Chandler Plaza Hotel in Los Angeles
where your father ordered the release
of the virus into the ventilation system.
These people will all be dead
within two to three hours.
Almost 800 of them are infected, Jane.
This is how they'll die.
- I don't wanna see any more.
- I don't wanna see any more, either.
You can help us stop this, Jane, please.
Please.
I have a phone number.
He told me to call it, day or night,
if I ever got in trouble.
Have you ever used it before?
No.
We need it.
No! No!
It's a mistake! I'm OK!
I don't have any infection!
No!
Don't take me in there with those people!
I don't wanna die!
Michelle, I just got a call.
Your lab results are on the way here.
I'm sorry to interrupt, Mr President.
What is this, Aaron?
Our bureau chief just informed me that
NHS believes Los Angeles is no longer safe.
We would like to move you out of the state.
I appreciate your concern.
Tell Chief Kurtzman
I'd rather manage matters from here.
Sir, I'm afraid this isn't a request.
- Excuse me?
- Secret Service is invoking Section 32.
For your own protection, we are requiring you
to accompany us to Air Force One.
- You're ordering me?
- Yes, sir.
- It's for your safety.
- Wayne.
I don't know the specifics of the code,
but Secret Service is invoking it.
And, David, here in LA the threat is serious.
It's serious everywhere.
At least here we know what we're facing.
- Who has to sign off on this?
- Chief Kurtzman and myself.
I'd like a word in private with you, Aaron.
Sir, I'm sorry for appearing
to overstep my bounds.
It's my job to protect you.
Listen, Aaron, you've been with me
from the beginning.
You don't have to apologize
for doing your job.
But this crisis will end,
and the people in this city
and this country will be stronger
knowing that their president
stood by them shoulder to shoulder.
I'm asking you as a friend and a fellow citizen,
protect me, but here in Los Angeles.
Can you do that for me?
Yes, sir. For you, I can.
- Thank you.
- Yes, sir.
Mr President,
the conference call is about to begin.
-  Jack, you there?
- Yeah, I'm on.
- Mr President?
- Mr Almeida.
I understand we may have a way
to locate this man, Stephen Saunders.
Yes, sir. However, my technical staff
just informed me that to do so properly
may take 15 minutes, possibly longer.
There's no way to get to him
in the next few minutes?
No, sir, there's not.
OK, gentlemen, the time is upon us.
Having considered all the scenarios, I see no
other choice than to draw our line in the sand.
I will not give in to Saunders' latest demand.
Mr President, that leaves us
with only one option,
to use his daughter as a hostage
and hope that that'll stop him.
I understand.
- All right, gentlemen. Get to it.
- Yes, sir.
David, are you sure
we're doing the right thing?
The only thing I'm sure of is we cannot let
this country be taken over by this madman.
- Jack, how do you wanna do this?
- How long do we need to run a trace?
- About a minute.
- We need to cover our bases.
We'll use Jane to try and keep him on the line.
I'll initiate the trace.
You tell Jane what we need.
I'll get back to you.
Dammit.
- What's happening?
- We've run out of time.
We need you to call your father.
- And tell him what?
- Anything. Just keep him on the line.
- For how long?
- At least a minute.
- Do you think you can do that?
- I need to think about it.
We don't have any more time.
Your father just threatened to release
more of the virus in the next few minutes.
- Is the list up yet?
- No.
Well, his time is up.
- Yeah.
- It's me.
- Yes, Stephen.
- Release San Francisco.
I understand.
That's my daughter's line. Lan, wait.
- I'll call you right back.
- All right.
Find out where this is coming from.
- Jane?
- Yeah.
Hi, Dad.
What's wrong? I told you only to use
this number in an emergency.
I wanna see you. I'm scared.
The airports are shut down and they're talking
about the alert level being raised.
Just stay where you are, honey. You'll be fine.
- Someone is monitoring the call.
- Hang on a second, honey.
- Are you sure?
- Yes. The signal's splitting.
They've got her.
We just got hit on the trace route.
He knows we're on the phone.
- What do I do?
- You're doing great. Just keep talking.
- Jane.
- Yes, Dad.
There's a man named Jack Bauer
with you, isn't there?
- What, Dad?
- Hand the phone to him.
- Dad...
- You heard me.
- I'm on the line, Stephen.
- Jack.
You know how many vials I have
and what I'm capable of.
You know what I'm capable of, too.
- Did you get a lock on the signal?
- Negative.
- Tony, did you get him?
- We're working on it. Adam?
I've got the longitude,
but I don't have the latitude.
Here, try this.
- Adam?
- I'm trying, Tony. I'm working on it.
- OK, here it is. 21904 Collins.
- We've got him. We'll send teams from here.
Pass the location through to the chopper.
Get me Chase.
They got a location.
Tell the chopper to come in.
Assemble a team. Take Jane back to CTU.
I want her fully protected.
What are you gonna do to my father?
We're gonna stop him.
I want you to go with her.
We have to make sure these stats are updated
and sent to CTU.
Michelle, the test results, they just came in.
Thank you.
- Almeida.
-  Hi, it's me.
What's going on?
I'm OK. I'm not infected.
- Are you sure?
- Yeah, they did a swab and a blood test.
I'm gonna be fine. I'm gonna be fine.
My God. Oh, my God, sweetheart.
That's fantastic.
I want you to get outta there,
away from anybody who's infected.
No, no. No, sweetheart. They said those of us
that didn't come down with the infection,
we have an immunity to the virus.
Where are they taking you?
Downtown. To NHS.
They wanna keep us under watch for
18 hours, but they said it's just a formality.
Look, I'll get there as soon as I can, all right?
No, no. Stay where you are.
They need you at CTU.
- I can work from downtown.
- Honey, you don't have to work.
- We can handle it from here.
- I wanna help, Tony.
OK.
- Michelle...
- Yeah?
I can't believe I almost lost you.
I almost lost you, too.
- But we're still here.
- Yeah.
I have to go. I'll call you from NHS.
Hey...
I love you.
I love you so much.
Excuse me, can I have your attention, please?
The president has asked you to this
informal setting without recording devices
to tell you what relationship the outbreak at
the Chandler Plaza has with airport closures.
Was the Chandler Plaza
why the alert level was raised?
The president will deal with that
in his statement.
- Saunders knows we have his daughter?
- He found out about five minutes ago.
- How did he react?
- He broke off communication.
The good news is
CTU has a position on Saunders,
and they're sending in teams now.
- What's our confidence level?
- This man knows our system, our protocols.
- He's gonna be tough to corner.
- Stay on top of our response teams.
The abduction of his daughter
may have made things worse.
- The President of the United States.
- Please be seated.
As you know, this morning
our alert level was raised to red.
We do have information regarding
a possible biological attack on American soil.
We have maximized
our preparedness across the nation.
Now, the best way for our citizens
to ensure their own safety is to stay home.
If you're at work, go home. That's
the message I hope the media can convey.
Mr President, we've heard reports that the
local British intelligence office was attacked.
- Is that related?
- I can't release any details on that right now.
I'm sorry, Mr President. The people of the city
of Los Angeles are starting to panic,
and information is not flowing
from this office.
We've had outbreaks, quarantines
and now a hint of biological terror...
- Carol, please...
- The president has to be more forthcoming.
The president has to be in control,
and so do you.
If you wanna help the public
and do your jobs best,
sit quietly and listen to what I have to say.
Biological agents do their worst damage
where large groups of people congregate.
The best defence we have right now
is to encourage everyone to go home
and stay home and await further instruction.
- Chase, this is Jack. Are you en route?
- I'm a little more than ten minutes out.
- Will Saunders know we have his location?
- Not likely.
He'll think he had 90 more seconds
before we could lock on to his location.
Move into position and remind local
law enforcement to stay out of sight.
- We cannot tip him off.
- Done.
Adam, keep an eye on the satellite.
Track anyone coming in and out of that
building and feed it to local law enforcement.
- Do you copy?
- I'm watching the data now.
- Plug Chloe into it, too.
- Yeah.
Listen, everybody, this is our time.
Get it right.
- Stephen, we have to leave.
- We're not leaving.
Why not? You said
they'd probably know our location.
- Not probably. They do.
- I don't understand.
They've got us on satellite.
They'll pick us up if we try to leave.
So we sit around
and wait till they surround us?
Exactly. The more bodies they send,
the easier it'll be for us to disappear.
No, I'm not waiting around to get caught.
- Osterlind!
- I'm leaving, Stephen.
- Yeah?
- Has she left yet?
No.
She will. Stay on her.
I'm gonna need to do this soon.
OK.
- Where are we going?
- Los Angeles.
- I thought there was an outbreak there.
- Where we're going it'll be safe. Don't worry.
- Where in Los Angeles are they taking me?
- A place called CTU.
- CTU?
- Yeah, Counter Terrorist Unit.
I still can't believe this.
That my father is a terrorist.
Four years ago when I found out he was alive
after all that time... I was so happy.
I had a father.
I let myself believe all that he wanted me to.
That he was this wonderful man.
How often did you see him?
A couple of times a year.
Sometimes he'd surprise me,
and he'd always bring me something.
And it was always perfect. Like he knew.
- Maybe he did know.
- What do you mean?
He had people watching you, Jane.
He knew more about your life
than you're probably aware of.
What am I supposed to do
with all these feelings for him?
The person I love doesn't even exist.
What's gonna happen to him?
My dad's gonna try and bring him in.
Adam, what's the status
of Saunders' location?
No one's left the building.
- Who's working with us?
- LAPD have surrounded the area.
- They're hidden from view.
- Good work.
- I'll be there in a few minutes.
- All right.
- That information's correct.
- You're absolutely sure?
- I checked myself.
- Thank you very much.
What's the status of the simulation?
- Tony, I need to talk to you.
- Just a second.
- Put those simulations on my system.
- I need to talk to you right now.
I'll catch you up. Go ahead.
- What is it?
- I've been working on the quarantine areas.
And?
I've been over the list of people who have
been isolated and found a familiar name.
And?
One of them is Sarah Kaufman.
- Who's Sarah Kaufman?
- Adam's sister.
- You sure it's Adam's sister?
- Yeah. She tested positive.
In the medical sense. She's gonna die.
- Thanks.
- You're not gonna tell him?
- Yeah, I have to.
- We still have a lot of work to do.
How can he concentrate knowing that
his sister's gonna die in a couple of hours?
Chloe, I'm getting real tired
of your personality.
- I'm just trying to help.
- You wanna help? Get back to work.
Adam, could you come with me for a second?
I'm sitting on these satellite feeds.
Can it wait?
No, it can't. Chloe'll watch it.
Fine. What is it?
Tony, I really have to stay on this.
- It's personal. Just come with me.
- Just tell me. Did I do something wrong?
No.
I'm afraid I have some bad news for you.
Your sister Sarah's
in one of the quarantine zones.
- What?
- You have a sister named Sarah, right?
Yeah, but how can they be sure it's her?
There have to be a hundred
Sarah Kaufman in Los Angeles.
Chloe confirmed it.
Have they kept her away
from the people that are infected?
She's infected.
What are you saying, Tony?
Are you telling me that Sarah's gonna die?
It looks that way, yeah. I'm sorry.
Oh, my God.
Look, Adam, I'm gonna give you a chance
to talk to your sister,
but then I'm gonna need you to stay on
until the crisis passes.
You think you can do that?
Adam?
Cos we need you here.
- Yeah.
- All right.
- No other way out?
- No.
- I'm completely surrounded.
- How do you know?
A security guard across the street
made his rounds every 15 minutes.
He missed his last rotation, which means
CTU has taken over that building.
What are you gonna do?
I'm gonna wait until Bauer gets here.
Baker and his team are behind the building.
They'll move when we say.
LAPD's set up a perimeter here,
here, here and here.
We got SWAT teams moving in this way
and from over here. Snipers on the roof.
- Nobody goes until we give the word.
- What's the situation?
We've taken over buildings on either side.
We've got snipers on the roof ready to go.
- Phones?
- We didn't jam the area. You said he'd know.
- What about infrared?
- We can't get through the walls, Jack.
- He knows we're here.
- What makes you say that?
- Cos I would.
- You think he's still in there?
- Yeah.
- Why wouldn't he try to escape?
I don't know. On my signal, move
into position, minimum three men per exit.
No one goes in till I give the order.
Assume Saunders has taken
defensive measures.
Everybody ready? Let's go.
All teams move into first position.
This is a go.
- In position. All set.
- OK. Let's go.
Stephen Saunders, this is Jack Bauer.
You're completely surrounded.
The president has refused
to capitulate to any further demands.
I need to remind you
that we still have your daughter.
Stephen, it's over. The only way
you're getting out of this thing alive
is coming through the front door
with your hands on your head.
That's not exactly true, Jack.
- Adam.
- Not now, Chloe.
I'm running comm on the Saunders pick-up.
I know what you're doing. Robin, take over
Adam's screen for a minute. Come here.
Why? Chloe, this is really not a good time.
- Tony, you need to hear this.
- What?
I have to report some bad news.
We lost two satellite feeds because
Adam forgot to segregate the channels.
- What?
- I checked your system.
- I had to reinitiate everything.
- You touched my system?
Adam shouldn't be here. He's under duress
because his sister's gonna die.
- I did not forget to separate those channels.
- Yes, you did.
We don't have time for this.
Teams on the ground are depending on us.
- Did you back up the satellite data?
- Yes. We lost about 30 seconds.
We didn't lose it, Chloe.
I can prove it to you right now.
I thought that I...
Chloe's right. I forgot to separate them.
All right, look, you made a mistake.
I need to know if you can get through the rest
of the day without making another one.
Adam?
I'm fine, Tony.
OK.
I don't agree with Tony's decision.
I'm gonna double-check your logs every
ten minutes, in case you screw up again.
Jack, what do you wanna do? If he's not
in there, we're wasting time we don't have.
Just have the men maintain their position.
- This is Bauer.
- Congratulations, Jack.
- You found me.
- Stephen, it's over. Come on out.
It would suit me better
if you came in here and got me.
I'd hate to be in the cross hairs
of all those unstable CTU snipers.
Come out the front door with your hands
on your head. You'll be fine.
11 more vials, millions dead.
That doesn't affect your nerves a little bit?
The president's made himself clear.
He's not following orders from you any more.
I work for him.
If that's the case, you won't mind
if I take a few minutes to think things over.
While you're thinking things over,
you might wanna think about your daughter.
Tony just confirmed that he's in the building.
All teams hold your position.
We got confirmation.
- Is it done?
- Yes.
All right. Stay on the line.
- Almeida.
- Listen to me very carefully, Agent Almeida.
- Who is this?
- It's Stephen Saunders.
Before you make any tactical errors,
here's an update on the situation.
I'm listening.
Move to a private area that has direct comm
with your teams on site here.
Why would I do that?
Open a web socket to IP 257-211-16-5
and you'll find out.
That's IP 257-211-16-5.
Just trust me. Do it.
By the way,
I'd like to offer you congratulations
on your wife eluding infection from the virus.
How do you know about my wife?
Get on that site.
I did instruct them to leave her barely
functional so that we can return her to you.
I'll kill you, you son of a bitch.
I'll rip your damn throat out, you hear me?
I'm low on time.
Sorry if I brush past that remark.
In 15 seconds Michelle will be dead
if you don't do what I say.
There are five agents watching
the northeast exit of this building,
four on the ground
and a sniper on the rooftop.
I assume they're operating as a unit.
I want you to give them a code nine,
send them to the front entrance now.
Jack Bauer's running the operation.
I don't have the authority.
No authority. Really?
- Kevin, is Michelle still conscious?
- Yes.
Take an eye out.
No, wait! Stop!
Kevin, hold for a second.
It's gonna take me some time.
You have 30 seconds.
Gerry, we're talking about mass hysteria
spreading out all over the place.
- We're not in any position to mobilize...
- Our position is to let the public know.
- This is Baker.
- This is Tony Almeida.
Switch to channel three.
- Go ahead.
- We need you to code nine your team.
I want you to use a controlled channel.
- What are we doing?
- Move everyone to the front now.
- There's nothing going on at the front.
- We got a sat feed Jack doesn't have yet.
Saunders is on the move in a blind spot.
Get there now.
Four CTU personnel diverting to new mark.
No, Baker, not just CTU personnel. Everyone,
police control included. Get there now!
We have a code nine.
Everyone to the front of the building now!
Get in your car and move to the front
of the building. Down, down!