Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net
- We're going to...
- (woman) Get Medical right away!
Wayne Palmer won't be able to
continue his duties as Commander in Chief.
I have the fate of the West,
the lives of millions hanging in the balance
and I can't stop thinking about you.
Bill Buchanan had Fayed in custody
and he let him go.
Karen Hayes put it in a blue file
over at Homeland.
Someone will have to go down.
The farther from the president, the better.
- Are you asking me to resign?
- No, Bill. I have to fire you.
- Work with Milo, get cosy.
- Don't be such ajealous jerk.
The day I'm jealous is the day I kill myself.
Anything else?
How about, "Don't arm
nuclear bombs for terrorists"?
Sorry. That's not how I feel.
Yeah, it is.
No, it's not. Itjust slipped out my mouth.
Morris!
- You shouldn't have trouble running CTU.
- I'm not the right choice to take over.
You are the right choice.
Nothing will change operationally.
Your objective remains the same.
Bring in Jack Bauer before he can hand over
the component to the Chinese.
Mr Bauer. Let's do this.
Audrey walks out of here alone.
As soon as I see she gets down near
the bridge, I'll give you the component.
This is going down now, Nadia.
Jack is about to hand it over.
Mike, don't let that happen.
(man) Cheng and his men escaped.
They're in three Hummers heading north.
- (man) Agent Bauer, get down!
- Weapon is down!
- On the ground now!
- Who is your commanding officer?
I am, Jack.
I gotta take you into custody.
Where's the board?
Cheng's got it. I was set to destroy the
component till you engaged us in a firefight.
I had this handled.
Audrey, it's over. You're safe.
Help me. Don't let them do this to me.
Audrey!
They've done something to her.
You gotta help her. Please.
My God.
Was this the only C4 in the building?
Yes, that's everything. The building's clean.
Miss Raines, my name is Mike Doyle.
I'm a CTU field agent.
Did you see or hear something while Cheng
held you, something to lead us to him?
You're safe now, Miss Raines.
Jack bought your freedom
with a component
that contains highly sensitive
Russian technology.
Can you understand me, Miss Raines?
Help me, Jack.
Please don't let them do this to me.
I want CHP
to work with Military on roadblocks.
You need to set up three- to five-mile
perimeters from Cheng's last location.
I need satellite scans forwarded to me.
- (man) We're at full capacity. We...
- I understand, but those are your orders.
- You wanted to see me?
- I read your request for transfer out of Comm.
- Mm-hm.
- Is this because you and Chloe had a fight?
Your facts are essentially correct, but the why
I don't see as being anybody's business.
You've had a hard day - we all have -
but I really need you on the floor.
I'm sorry, request for transfer is denied.
I'm trying to protect you
from being caught in the middle
of an awkward professional situation.
You're asking me
to indulge your melodrama
in the middle of an international crisis.
Bill said he'd consider my request.
Bill Buchanan is not running CTU, I am.
I've made my decision.
- Nadia...
- Keep your personal life to yourself.
You can deal with this tomorrow.
We're done here.
(phone rings)
- Anything else you wanna say?
- Oh, yeah.
- Nadia Yassir.
- It's Mike. Do you have a lead on Cheng?
- We're on it. How'd it go with Raines?
- Not good.
She doesn't know anything about Cheng,
where he held her?
She's completely non-responsive.
Whatever they did to her in China,
it left her with a post-traumatic reaction.
District will want a specialist to look at her.
- Any idea what Jack was thinking?
- He had the motel rigged with C4.
- He was gonna take this whole place down.
- He was willing to sacrifice his life.
His plan would've worked
had I not intervened.
- You saved his life.
- But I lost the component.
Jack went against a direct order from the
White House. This was no one's fault but his.
We're on our way back.
Stephenson, you take Miss Raines.
I'll go with Bauer.
Audrey!
- Audrey!
- Jack, stop.
- Where are you taking her?
- CTU, same as you.
- Let me talk to her for a few minutes.
- You saw what condition she's in, Jack.
I know her. I know what she's been through.
I might be the only person
that can get through to her. Please.
You're under arrest. We'll discuss this at CTU.
Put him in the second chopper.
Mike, let me talk to her now!
CTU is pouring its resources
into finding Cheng.
This order gives them authority
to close ports and border crossings.
If we can't stop migrant workers crossing
borders, how can we stop an enemy agent?
I think the point is to slow him down, sir,
so CTU has more time to find him.
But I agree Cheng will find a way to smuggle
out the Russian component eventually.
So then Russia loses its defensive edge
against the Chinese and Moscow blames us.
We will do everything in our power
to prevent that, sir.
Thank you.
- Karen.
- Yes?
Tom told me about you and Bill,
how you had to... fire him from CTU.
How'd he take it?
Not well.
Karen.
Yes.
You and I have had our...
difficulties in the past,
but I want you to know that...
I value your role here,
and that I appreciate your sacrifice.
Thank you.
(knock at door)
- Excuse me, sir.
- What is it?
The Russian president's calling for you.
He's insisting on a face-to-face.
- Did he say what he wants?
- No, but he's on with the heads of military.
I want you both with me on this.
Palmer's in a coma. It looks like Noah's
gonna be acting president for some time.
Good for Noah...
and good for us.
The only thing he cares about
is pushing his foreign agenda.
Any pending legislation on spending...
he'll defer to me.
Now he is acting president,
we must be more careful.
We will be.
- I got half an hour.
- Let's stop talking.
President Suvarov, you're on a secure
conference with Vice President Daniels.
- President Suvarov.
- Mr Vice President.
You know Tom Lennox and Karen Hayes,
my national security advisor.
How can we help you?
Some troubling news
has been brought to my attention.
What would that be?
The nuclear weapons that fell into
terrorist hands contained Russian technology
that, up until now, has only been available
to your government and mine.
- I'm well aware of that, sir.
- Then you are also well aware
that an FB-sub-circuit board
from one of the weapons
is now in the possession
of an agent of the Chinese government.
Do you deny that, sir?
Mr President, all I'm prepared to tell you
is that... we're in control of the situation.
Mr Vice President, my generals
have confirmed that this component
contains information that will
compromise our defensive capabilities.
You must stop the Chinese
from leaving your country with it.
I don't appreciate being dictated to,
Mr President.
It was a Russian general
who allowed those bombs
to enter the US in the first place,
the same Russian general
who conspired to detonate them.
That does not change our grave concerns
about this development.
If you do not intercept this component,
my generals have instructions
to initiate an appropriate response.
- Mr President...
- Good night, sir.
- How did the Russians find out?
- Russian intelligence must've tracked it.
No. The information circle is too tight.
Only select people at the White House
and CTU even knew about this.
- You're saying there's a spy?
- There is no other explanation.
I will start an internal investigation
into White House staff.
I'll do the same at CTU, sir.
What are your reads on Suvarov?
How seriously do we take his threat?
Very. With the Chinese
in possession of the component,
the Russians will need to extend
their defensive line in central Asia.
- We have a military base in the region.
- Which the Russians must target.
- We will have to respond in kind...
- Which will escalate things.
Give CTU whatever they need
to find this man Cheng.
(speaks Chinese)
- (man) Yes?
- I've interfaced the component.
- You should have the schematics.
- Yes, they've downloaded.
I'm running a diagnostic
on the component now.
Good. We'll be there in less than an hour.
Wait. There's a problem.
- What?
- The circuit board is damaged.
- Can you fix it?
- No, not unless I have the security override.
We don't have access to that information.
Without it, this technology is useless to us.
You have to find someone
with the necessary expertise.
(shouts in Chinese)
I'm gonna take a quick shower.
Noah's waiting for me to get back.
(dials phone)
(phone rings)
- Yes?
- We're all set.
- The girl doesn't know you're working for us?
- Not a clue.
Good.
- Morris.
- Yeah.
I saw you arguing with Nadia.
Yeah.
Was that about us?
I asked for a transfer.
It was denied.
Why'd you do that?
Because... working with you
is becoming very uncomfortable.
I told you I was sorry.
You said I should
stop helping terrorists arm nuclear bombs.
We've both said things
that we haven't meant before.
Yeah, I know, but...
there's a line, darling, and...
and you crossed it.
So what are you saying?
I'm saying that...
it's over.
There's no going back. We're done.
Morris, look at me.
- You don't have to do this.
- Shh.
We're done.
Morris...
(sobs softly)
The situation has escalated
with the Russians.
They know the Chinese have the component
and threaten action,
unless we stop them
taking it out of the country.
- How did the Russians find out?
- A leak.
Lennox is looking into it here,
and he wants you to start an investigation.
- I'll let Internal Affairs know.
- What about Raines?
Has she provided any information?
Not yet, but the psychiatric specialist
has just arrived,
so we hope he can get her to talk.
- Do you have any other leads?
- Not at the moment.
That's unfortunate. I cannot emphasise
enough how important it is we stop Cheng.
If you need more resources,
you need to let me know now.
Do you understand?
I will.
One more thing...
To be honest, Karen,
what we need is Bill Buchanan.
There's a rumour flying around
you fired him.
- That's complicated, Nadia.
- Not as far as we're concerned.
You know more than anyone
how good he is at this job.
I don't see how this could happen
in the middle of a crisis.
Look, I'm not at liberty to discuss this.
Just keep me updated
with your progress in finding Cheng.
Doctor Bradley,
I'm Nadia Yassir, acting head of CTU.
We're under a time crunch.
I'd like to get started at once.
She's being prepped.
These men can take you. I'll join you shortly.
- I wanna hear your first impressions.
- Of course.
Nadia, Doyle and Jackjust landed.
OK. Have Doyle secure Bauer
and then have him meet me in Medical.
OK.
Can you leave us alone, please? Thank you.
Miss Raines?
Miss Raines, I'm Doctor Bradley.
I'm here to perform an evaluation to help you
remember whatever you can about Cheng.
Where you were held, what you heard...
It's all right. It's OK.
Come here. Look at this.
Please, you've gotta let me talk to her.
You know CTU's protocol.
You know how they'll interrogate her.
They'll make her retreat inside herself.
Please listen to me!
Sit down.
This will make you more comfortable.
Mike.
Please, I'm begging you. Take care of her.
Are you all right?
Come here. Look at this.
Jack's in holding three. How you doing?
White House is pressuring us to find Cheng.
We have to hope we can
get some information out of her.
This is Agent Doyle.
He was involved in rescuing Miss Raines.
- Do you have a diagnosis?
- She's a type-three catatonic
capable of following commands, repeating
words, but otherwise unresponsive.
Will you be able to get the information?
- Not without intervention.
- What does that mean?
She is suffering from psychological abuse
amplified by pharmacological agents,
as evidenced by over 100 injections
in her arms, feet and groin.
It'll be impossible to communicate in the near
term unless we shock her out of this state.
They used drugs, and you'll give her more?
These are compounds
used for different reasons.
- What are the risks?
- 22% of patients have cardiovascular events,
some of it neurological.
In extreme cases, death occurs.
- We can't do this.
- Doyle.
I am not comfortable
with the high percentage either,
but this is the only way
you're gonna get anything out of her.
Maybe not.
One of our agents has a history with her.
The Chinese put him through
something similar.
See what Jack can draw from her
before we do anything riskier.
- Doctor?
- Yeah, I know who Jack Bauer is.
I've read Miss Raines' file on the way over.
Contact with him will upset her.
But there's no chance of her dying from it.
Let's give Jack a chance with her.
It's not your call, Miss Yassir.
District has placed Miss Raines
in my custody and granted me authority.
I'll begin preparing for treatment shortly.
I'll let you know the results. Good day.
- You can't let him do this...
- He has jurisdiction. There's nothing I can do.
You can do what you know is right.
That's what Buchanan would have done.
- And that was uncalled for.
- Well, I'm sorry.
What I meant to say is, since you're acting
director, you can't be afraid to step on toes.
Does that go down better?
Part of being acting director
is respecting the chain of command.
But thank you for your advice.
(phone rings)
It's him.
- Hi.
- Where are you?
I'm on my way out the door.
Well, get here as quickly as you can.
There's a crisis.
- Has there been another threat?
- Yes, but not from terrorists. I'll fill you in.
I'll be there in less than 15.
Lisa...
I need you.
I need you too.
- I have to go.
- What's going on?
I don't know.
(dials phone)
- (Nikolai) Yes.
- It's me. What's my next move?
- I think I've identified the leak, sir.
- Is it here or at CTU?
It's very much here, sir.
I had NSA run a data sort on all
White House phone calls and emails
over the last two and a half hours.
That's when we found out
the sub-circuit board was in play.
- And?
- During the same time frame,
one of our staffers called a lobbyist,
Mark Bishop, three times.
CIA had flagged this Bishop
two years ago
as having possible-to-likely contact
with Russian intelligence agents.
No further investigation was done
due to lack of resources.
Which staffer are we talking about here, Tom?
Lisa Miller, sir.
I find it hard to believe
she is working for the Russians.
I don't think she did so knowingly, or she
wouldn't have called Bishop from her phone.
Then I... I don't understand.
How's this man getting information from her?
Well, so far,
we have found credit-card records
that show Miss Miller and Bishop staying
at the same hotels on the same nights
several times over the past year.
Now, I think if we dig a little deeper
I'm sure that we will find more evidence
that shows these two are sleeping together.
Then we have
a bigger problem than you think.
Why's that, sir?
Because I'm sleeping with her too.
She... she started working for me
two years after my wife...
after Nancy died.
I didn't think I'd feel anything
for another woman again but...
Lisa and I became close, and then last year
we were working late one night and...
You understand
how these things happen, Tom.
Dammit, what a fool I've been.
What the hell do I do, Tom?
You know, actually, sir...
handled correctly,
we may be able
to turn this situation to our advantage.
(beeping, door unlocking)
Mike, what's happening out there?
Will they let me speak to Audrey?
- I tried, but they're not going for it.
- Why not?
- The shrink doesn't think it's a good idea.
- Let me talk to him.
I wish this guy was interested
in what other people had to say, but he isn't.
Why?
He's got her in Medical. He's about to try
protocol of his own using big doses of drugs.
It could kill her, Jack.
Why did you uncuff me?
Cos I think you need
to do something about it.
Make it look good.
Easy.
- (man) Vitals are strong. She's ready.
- Get her IV started.
Excuse me, sir, you can't be in here.
- Have you started?
- No.
- What have you done to her?!
- Nothing.
Consider yourself lucky.
You're Bauer. I recognise you from her file.
Seeing you will only make things worse.
Shut up!
Audrey, I need you to come with me. I need
you to come with me now. Please, come on.
(alarm)
Just get me anything you can.
- Milo, what's the location of that alarm?
- Room six where Audrey's being treated.
Bring up the video feed.
She's gone. Lock everything down.
Get me holding room three.
If you'd just let Jack talk to Audrey,
none of this would've happened.
OK, thank you. Jack didn't pass through
any of the exits before the lockdown.
He's still here.
No one left sectors A through K. They're clear.
He's on the lower levels.
You checked the video?
- That's what I'm doing. It takes time.
- I know, make it take less time.
Where's Chloe?
- Morris?
- I don't... I'm not sure.
- Doyle.
- Have you found Jack?
No, not yet, but I'd like to know
how he managed to overpower you.
- I made a mistake. I got too close.
- Yeah, see, I don't think it was a mistake.
You wanted Jack
to have a chance with Audrey,
so you went there with the purpose
of letting him overpower you
and then escaping with your key card.
I did what I think is best for this operation,
and for Audrey Raines.
I have him!
He's headed down to the lower level,
but with everything locked down,
he'll only have access to corridors L and M.
I'm on my way.
Let me know if you find anything,
and have Doctor Bradley and Doyle
meet me there.
Hold on.
Let's go.
It's all right. It's all right.
I'm here. I'm here.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm gonna protect you.
I'm gonna take care of you, I promise.
I know you can recognise me.
I see it in your eyes.
It's me - Jack.
The men who hurt you,
they can't touch you now. I won't allow it.
Right now, I need you to try and remember.
I need you to remember who you are.
Your name is Audrey Raines.
You were born Audrey Louise Heller
in Albany, New York.
Your father was the
Secretary of Defence, James Heller.
Your mother's name was Alicia.
She died when you were nine.
Please, Audrey, just try and remember.
Nadia? I've got Jack.
Room 237 was just sealed from the inside.
They have to be in there.
I see the room now.
Dammit, it's disabled.
Get an entry team down here now.
We need an entry team at door 237.
The men holding you, when they called me
they were within an hour of that motel.
When they moved you,
did you take surface streets or the freeway,
anything that can help us find them?
I want them to pay for what they've done.
I know what you've been through.
I know what it's like
to feel like it's never going to end,
to hate them that much, and then need them...
to start blaming yourself
for everything that's happening to you.
But they can't hurt you any more.
You don't need to hide now. It's over.
Please, give me a signal. Anything that lets
me know you understand what I'm saying.
Please, please.
It's all right. I'm... I'm sorry.
It's all right.
I know you're trying.
I love you with all my heart.
I'm not gonna let them hurt you.
They'll take you away from me.
There's nothing I can do to stop them.
We're out of time.
Is there anything you can tell me to help us
find Cheng, or where they were holding you?
Please.
Come here, come on!
- Jack, put your gun down.
- You put your gun down!
Get him out!
I'm not letting him take her back to Medical.
Jack, lower your weapon!
Not until I get a guarantee from you
that Audrey is safe.
Bloomfield.
- What'd you say?
- Bloomfield.
Did you hear that? She said "Bloomfield".
- I asked her where she was being held.
- We don't know if it's communication.
"Bloomfield" could be
a programmed response meaning nothing.
We'll soon find out. Morris, did you get that?
Have Chloe track it down.
- Keep Doyle in the loop.
- All right.
In the meantime, Doctor,
I'd like you to wait for me in my office.
- I'm not going anywhere. She's my patient.
- And she's my witness.
I suggest you go with these men, Doctor.
Listen to me, Jack.
You have my word,
I will not let him touch her.
Please, lower your weapon.
Audrey, please, it's all right.
He's gonna take care of you.
Jack, I need you to go
with these men to Holding.
Thank you.
Yes, of course, General.
I'll review the report with the vice president.
I'll get right back to you.
Suvarov wasn't bluffing?
No, sir. Air Force satellites
confirm the Russian army
is moving large numbers
of troops into central Asia.
- How long till they're in range of our base?
- They'll be in strike range within the hour.
I'm sorry, Mr Vice President.
I got back here as soon as I could.
Forward the report to the Joint Chiefs.
- Let me know their recommendations.
- Yes, sir.
What's going on?
Why is Tom talking to the Joint Chiefs?
Because the Russians
know the Chinese have the component.
- How?
- Someone inside the beltway
has been selling them information -
someone with access.
A man named Mark Bishop.
Do you know him?
I believe he's a lobbyist.
Are you sure it's Bishop?
Yeah. We began monitoring his phone calls
as soon as this came to our attention.
Ten minutes ago he called a known Russian
intelligence agent from his cellphone.
- (Bishop) It's me. What's my next move?
- (Nikolai) You must reach out to her.
Find out if there are any developments
with the component.
(Bishop) I'll call her, access her PDA,
see if she has new email.
(Nikolai) Very good.
So how long have you
known this man Bishop?
He's an acquaintance. He consulted on
a white paper last year on defence spending.
Dammit, don't insult me
any more than you already have.
Bishop's been passing intelligence
to the Russians that he got from you.
I don't know if he read your emails,
or if you talked about it in bed,
but the Russians know about the component.
They're threatening military action
if we don't get it back from the Chinese.
I always knew you were a good liar. I just...
I just didn't think you could lie to me.
- I guess I thought... too highly of myself.
- I swear to you, I didn't know.
It's still treason, which I don't need
to remind you is a capital offence.
You didn'tjust betray me,
you betrayed your country.
What do you want from me?
You're gonna go back to your boyfriend,
and you're gonna make him believe
that we have the component back.
- I can't do that.
- You can and you will
do exactly what Tom Lennox tells you to do.
And don't you even think about
trying to expose our... relationship.
If you go there,
I'll have you declared an enemy combatant,
put you in solitary.
It'll be years before
you speak to anyone about anything.
Noah?
You all right, sir?
I'm better now.
Secret Service is sending over a team
to work with her. We'll get this going soon.
I've made arrangements
to take you away from here.
I'm going to look after you, I promise.
You will get well, and you won't be alone.
I'll be right back, sweetheart.
Before I take my daughter,
I'd like to see Jack Bauer. Where is he?
He's in Holding, sir.
Escort Mr Heller to Holding.
Nadia. Did Audrey speak
when he was with her?
No, I don't think so.
Well, the name she gave us
might be a good lead.
Bloomfield Copper Company used
to have a facility in Jefferson Heights.
Forensics just found
oxidised copper particles on her clothing.
- That's where Cheng was holding her?
- It might be his base of operations.
LAPD's locking down the building.
I told them to stand down till I arrive.
- Good work, Mike.
- Thanks.
Mike.
You were right.
I should've stood up to Doctor Bradley.
You did.
When it counted, you stood up to him.
(beeping, door unlocking)
Mr Secretary.
You've seen Audrey?
I made Audrey a promise. I make the same
promise to you. I will take care of her.
- I will be there for her.
- No, you won't, Jack.
Excuse me?
I don't want you to go anywhere
near my daughter ever again.
Audrey went looking for you,
and this is how she came back.
What's happened to her is your fault.
I accept that responsibility, but I can help her.
Stay away from her.
Mr Secretary, earlier I got through to Audrey.
I can do the same thing again.
I just need some time. Please.
Now, I'm warning you,
stay away.
You're cursed, Jack.
Everything you touch,
one way or another, ends up dead.
(knocks on door)
Ripped by Merah 2010
www.myPortables.net