- What's going on?
- The operation wasn't completely successful.
They have Saunders' daughter,
but didn't remain covert.
- So Saunders knows we have her?
- Not yet.
But CTU is estimating
he'll find out within the hour.
The deadline for his next demand
is up in 15 minutes.
Giving this guy a list of every foreign
operative on our payroll's an act of treason.
I will not give in to Saunders' latest demand.
We're out of time.
We need you to call your father.
- And tell him what?
- Anything. Just keep him on the line.
- Jane?
- Hi, Dad.
I told you only to use
this number in an emergency.
- Someone is monitoring the call.
- They've got her.
There's a man named Jack Bauer with you,
isn't there? Hand the phone to him.
You know how many vials I have
and what I'm capable of.
You know what I'm capable of, too.
Stephen Saunders, this is Jack Bauer.
You're completely surrounded. The president
has refused to capitulate to further demands.
The only way you're getting out alive
is through the front door
with your hands on your head.
That's not exactly true, Jack.
I'd like to offer you congratulations
on your wife eluding infection from the virus.
How do you know about my wife?
I did instruct them to leave her barely
functional so that we can return her to you.
There are five agents watching
the northeast exit of this building.
Send them to the front entrance. Michelle
will be dead if you don't do what I say.
This is Tony Almeida.
Move everyone to the front now.
In your car and move to the front
of the building. Down, down!
Stephen Saunders, this is your final warning.
Come out of the building now.
- Smoke him out.
- Release the tear gas.
We're a go.
- Send them in.
- Perimeter teams move in. Move in!
- All right, boys. Let's go! Let's go!
- Move!
- Baker!
- Move ahead.
- Why aren't you covering the south?
- CTU said you needed us out front.
- Why would they do that?
- They said Saunders was moving.
Clear down there. Check the other room.
All teams respond. Any sign of Saunders?
- Apartment's clear!
- Jack, we're in. Still no sign of him.
- Who gave you that order?
- Tony.
Move your team back to their mark now.
- CTU. Almeida.
- Baker said you pulled him out of position.
- I was working off the information I had.
- You should have cleared it with me.
- Somebody in my team made a mistake.
- That's an unacceptable mistake.
I have tactical command in the field.
If you can't run CTU, get someone who can.
- Chase, check in.
- We've covered the building. He's not here.
Dammit!
- Saunders doesn't seem to be in the building.
- He's gotta be in there.
What were you just telling Jack
about someone making a mistake?
Never mind. Adam, are you sure
we tracked him to the right building?
He was in there
when Jack made that phone call.
- I'm pulling up the imagery now.
- I'll take care of that.
You stay with Chloe and cover the site teams.
Almeida.
I hope you purged
the incriminating satellite frames.
I did what you wanted me to.
Now, where's my wife?
Not so fast. I like to do things in phases.
That was phase one.
Next we have to talk about my daughter.
- What about her?
- I want her back, of course.
- Well, I want my wife back.
- Then there should be no problem.
- Where's Jane now?
- She should be here in about five minutes.
Good. Make sure the men who guard her
will follow your orders without question.
If any harm comes to my daughter,
your wife dies.
If Jane is not released when I order it,
- That's all you need to know. Are we clear?
-  Tony, are you in there?
-  President Palmer's on the line.
- I'll do my part. You do yours.
- That's the spirit.
-  Tony, are you there?
- I'm here.
- Are you OK?
- I'm fine. Put the president through.
- OK, hang on.
- This is Tony Almeida.
- Please hold for the president.
Mr Almeida. I just heard
you lost Stephen Saunders. Is that true?
- Yes, sir, unfortunately it is.
- I thought CTU was certain of his location.
We're looking into it now, sir.
- Does he know we're holding his daughter?
- Yes, sir, he does.
And she's obviously very important to him.
- Is Jane Saunders with you now?
- She's on her way here.
Mr Almeida, I don't have to remind you how
much security we're gonna need around her.
She is the only thing between us
and Saunders controlling the government.
- Yes, Mr President. We're aware of that.
- Good. Keep me posted.
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
As yet, the Keeler campaign
has not issued a comment.
We now go live with the senator.
Senator Keeler, do you feel this is going to do
serious damage to your campaign?
Absolutely not.
My record on labor speaks for itself.
I voted against NAFTA and favored
tax incentives for domestic manufacturing.
What about the other endorsements you lost?
- Who did he lose?
- AFL, CIO and a couple of veteran groups.
They don't like his negative spin
on your withdrawal from the debate.
Now the threat level's been raised to red,
people realize he's the one playing politics.
We can't waste time on the election.
The only thing that matters
is stopping Stephen Saunders.
Would you come with me, please?
Excuse us, Gerry.
We will be scheduling a press conference
shortly to address these issues. Thanks.
No, Adam, we found the room he was using.
I just wanna know how he got out.
- I'll call you when we get something.
- Good.
- What did he say?
- I don't understand.
Saunders disappears and now CTU says
they're having problems with the satellite.
We'll look into it. Baker, this is Jack.
- I want two teams on patrol, two on standby.
- What about us?
We're going to CTU. I wanna be with
Saunders' daughter when he calls us back.
How did Saunders get past us? Could he
have access to our tracking systems?
- CTU. O'Brian.
- Chloe, what are you working on?
We're trying to pick up a thread on Saunders.
I'm analyzing his last call to you.
Is it possible
that he was just routing his calls?
No, he did that earlier at the apartment.
Now he couldn't do that without our knowing.
Get back to me
as soon as you've got anything.
Something's not right here.
- This is CTU?
- Yes.
Your father and Chase are on their way back.
- With Saunders?
- No.
- Why not?
- They're still trying to locate him.
- They haven't captured my father?
- No.
- But he knows you guys have me, right?
- Yes, he does.
- Agent Forrester, Tony Almeida.
- Tony.
- We'll put Miss Saunders in a holding room.
- I was told a white room.
That's changed. If you walk her to the back,
security will take her from there.
You'll be fine, OK?
- How are you doing?
- I can't believe Saunders escaped.
How could this happen?
I thought he was surrounded.
It happened. Rae Plachecki's coming here to
talk to you about the shooting at the library.
OK. Look, I heard the news about Michelle.
What news?
- That she isn't infected.
- Oh. Yeah.
I'm really glad that she's OK. That's great.
Yeah. Thanks.
There's no way to be sure. Some people
don't show symptoms for five or six hours.
- Adam.
- Didn't they talk to you about your options?
They said they could
give me a pill so I won't suffer.
- Adam, I need to talk to you now.
- Sarah, hold on.
- I'm talking to my sister right now.
- The one who got infected with the virus?
I'm not even gonna answer that, Chloe.
I'm sorry. I'll just wait here until you're done.
- Chloe.
- I'm sorry. This is really important.
I just need you to finish up
as quickly as you can.
Sarah, I'm gonna have to call you back
as soon as I can, OK?
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
Satellite navigation said there are missing
frames, and they're certain it's on our end.
- What about the backup?
- Gone, and they cover about 20 seconds.
If Saunders did escape,
it was in that exact interval.
- There was a glitch at the wrong moment?
- Yeah. What are the chances of that?
- Not good.
- So Saunders has access to our system.
- Did you tell Tony yet?
- I want more information before I go to him.
I checked with field ops. Their systems
are accounted for. Do the same in comm.
You really think someone
inside CTU is working for Saunders?
It's the only thing that makes sense, so do
that and then you could call your sister back.
- Hey, Pete. I need a few minutes alone.
- Sure thing.
How you doing?
Why am I being treated
like I've done something wrong?
I apologize for that.
We're just trying to keep you safe.
This is the one place I'm not safe.
I've been thinking about it.
You need me to get to my father.
So threatening to kill me or harm me
is the only tool you have to use against him.
Tell me I'm wrong.
You're right. We need your father
to believe we'll do anything to get him.
But we're not gonna hurt you.
I give you my word.
- Your word?
- Yeah, my word.
I run this office
and I will personally protect you.
What about Kim's father?
They told her that he's on his way back here.
What about him?
He scares me.
I got the feeling he's willing to hurt me.
Nobody's gonna hurt you. All right?
I wish I could believe you.
- Almeida.
- Has Jane arrived?
- Yeah.
- Where is she?
- She's here.
- Put her on.
No. You have my wife.
- I wanna talk to her first.
- You don't give me orders.
You're wrong. I have your daughter,
which means I'm in charge.
If you so much as touch my wife,
I will slit Jane's throat.
Hold on.
Sorry for your discomfort.
Hopefully it's temporary.
Uncuff her.
I'm going to let you speak to your husband.
Tell him you're OK and being treated well.
Nothing more. Understood?
- Tony, it's me.
- Michelle.
- He won't let me say much.
- Are you all right?
I'm fine. I'm being treated well.
Don't let them do this...
Michelle?
Let me speak with my daughter, Mr Almeida.
It's your father. He wants to talk to you.
- Dad?
- Yes, Jane. It's me.
They're saying horrible things about you.
That's what they do. Don't believe any of it.
The virus in the hotel
that's killing all of those people...
Please tell me that you didn't do that.
Listen to me, Jane. The US government
distorts the truth and destroys lives.
Don't listen to any of it. It's all lies.
Then you didn't do it?
I'd never do something without good cause.
You know that. You know that.
That's all. Let's do this.
How long will it take for you
to get her out of the building?
I have to fabricate some clearances.
About 30 to 40 minutes.
Contact me as soon as you're clear of CTU.
Take down this number.
Someone from Tony's group
purged the frames from the feed.
- Do you know who?
- It could have been from here or Division.
I'd better tell Tony
so we can lock down the system.
- CTU, O'Brian.
- This is Sunny Macer from Health Services.
- What can I do for you?
- Have you heard from Michelle Dessler?
No, she was sent to you for observation.
That's why I'm calling. We got a message
that she asked to go to County.
She's not at County and not here.
We can't get ahold of her.
- I'll check on it and get back to you.
- Thanks.
- Davis.
- Get me Mike Redmond. He's with Michelle.
- He's not answering.
- He's active. He has to answer.
- OK, I heard you the first time.
- And you're sure about this?
- Yes, Tony. Of course I'm sure.
There are 79 users, and one of them's been
playing games with the uplink recording.
We're gonna have to
lock everything down, then.
Well, obviously, I agree.
You want me to do it now?
- Yeah.
- OK.
- What is it?
- Something weird's happening with Michelle.
- What do you mean?
- No one can find her or Redmond.
That's because I overrode NHS's order.
I didn't want them to know about it.
I'm putting Michelle in quarantine in one
of our substations so she can still work.
- I need every warm body I can get.
- What am I gonna tell Macer?
I'll call her.
There's something I want you to do.
What is it?
I'm sending you the record of a phone call
between Saunders and myself.
- You spoke to him?
- Strip away the carrier signal.
- See if you can use it to find him.
- What about the voice track?
He scrambled it. It's useless.
Fine.
Chloe. Do it in tech one,
away from everybody.
- I don't want Adam to know about it.
- Why not?
Technically, it's his job, but you're better at it.
- Why did you just say that?
- Because it's true.
You assured me that going on the offensive
against Palmer was the right thing to do.
- Now it's backfired.
- Come on, John. That's not fair.
Palmer leaves the debate after you brought
up the charge against his girlfriend.
Everyone assumed that the national security
excuse was just a cover.
Apparently, it wasn't. The alert level's at red
and the airports are shut down.
I know.
All right.
Palmer still hasn't told the public
any of the details about this threat.
Call Alex at the Pentagon
and see what you can find out.
Depending on what it turns out to be, I may
need to be proactive and issue an apology.
Yeah?
Sherry Palmer will be here in five minutes
to talk to the senator.
- What's this about?
- She says she has a high-value proposition.
All right, hold on.
It's Sherry Palmer.
She wants to come here in five minutes.
- Why?
- She wouldn't say.
Except that it's a high-value proposition
and she wants to present it face to face.
Set it up.
All right. The senator will be here.
This should be interesting.
- I'll offload the systems.
- I'll be right up. Where's Tony?
With Jane Saunders. Kim's waiting
to be debriefed and then working with NHS.
- Why isn't she tracking Saunders?
- Tony put Chloe in charge of that.
- Where's Chloe?
- Tech one.
- Why isn't she in field ops?
- You haven't talked to Tony yet?
It looks like someone from Tony's group
intentionally wiped out those SAT frames.
- That's how he was able to evade us.
- What?
Adam, NHS wants those coordinates now
or they're going to widen the quarantine zone.
OK. That's all I know. I gotta get back on this.
OK, fine.
- We may be moving you in a few minutes.
- Where?
- To Division.
- What's that?
- Yeah.
- It's Jack.
I need to speak with you.
Meet me outside the observation room.
I'll be right back.
Jack. What the hell's going on?
You think someone on the inside's
working with Saunders?
- I have Chloe working on it.
- What's she doing?
She's taking a look at the status logs.
If this is true, we've gotta get
spec ops down here immediately.
I thought about that,
but I don't wanna raise any red flags.
If someone is working with Saunders,
I don't want them to know we're onto them.
OK, we'll work this up together,
but I want Division to pick up Jane Saunders
so they can continue questioning her.
- Good idea.
- I'll call Brad Hammond. See you in tech one.
No, Jack. I have a 30-minute status call
scheduled to Hammond anyway.
Why don't you let me tell him?
You can go up to field ops.
OK, fine.
Adam, is Tony set up for 30-minute
status calls with Brad Hammond?
If he is, it's not in the books.
Thanks.
Thank you very much.
John, hello.
Nice to see you. I don't believe you know
Mark Kaner, my campaign manager.
- No, only by reputation.
- How do you do?
- So what brings you here?
- Well, actually, it's a private matter, John.
Let us have a minute, Mark.
No problem.
Please.
I heard about the endorsements
you lost this morning.
- Daily fluctuation. Doesn't mean a thing.
- Doesn't mean a thing. Pretty optimistic.
No, your campaign is imploding.
By the time the press has a chance to analyse
all the mistakes you made last night,
you'll look like a desperate candidate
gasping his last breath.
- If you just came here to insult me, I'm busy.
- No, John, on the contrary.
Relax. I...
I came here because I can guarantee you
a win in November.
John, what I'm about to tell you, I will deny
to my grave if you try to hold it against me.
So that's clear, right?
John, we are clear on that, right?
Good.
David Palmer is an accessory to murder.
- Whose murder?
- Alan Milliken.
- Alan Milliken died of a heart attack.
- Yes, but he didn't have to.
His nitroglycerin was just an arm's length
away, but someone kept it from him.
How could you possibly know that?
Because that someone was me.
Sherry, I think you had better leave right now.
Really? So you can watch
your entire career leave with me?
If it's true,
I don't want anything to do with you.
Spare me. You haven't gotten this far without
getting a little dirt under your fingernails.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
- Of course not.
But, for the sake of conversation,
just allow me to paint you a picture.
Please. It won't take but a moment.
Just indulge me.
Very well.
David lied to the chief of police last night
in order to provide an alibi for me,
and I can prove that he lied.
No, you think about that.
Proof that the president of the United States
lied to cover a murder.
- What kind of proof?
- Besides my confession?
I have the prescription bottle
he was reaching for. I was holding it.
And I have it in a very safe place.
You are talking about incriminating yourself.
- You would go to prison.
- Yes, I know that.
But so would David.
David lied to the police to save himself.
It's quite simple, John.
All you have to do is go to David
and tell him that you have
this medicine bottle with my fingerprints on it
and, I guarantee you,
David will drop out of the race,
the party will be thrown into turmoil
and nobody, I mean nobody,
will be able to touch you come November.
And for all of this?
You'll put me on the White House staff.
Nothing so high
that it'll raise too many eyebrows, but...
All of this for you to be to a mid-level staffer
in my administration?
You and I both know
that it would be a little more than that.
It's been revised
now the exposure range has changed.
So the casualty estimates
have been projected upward?
- Yes, sir. I'm afraid so.
- By a factor of how many?
Now the virus is not completely contained,
it could be as high as times five, sir.
- All right, thanks, Dan. Keep me posted.
- Yes, sir.
- What is it?
- I just spoke to my source at Keeler's office.
Sherry was there,
meeting privately with Keeler.
- When?
- Just now.
- Meeting Keeler about what?
- He didn't know, David.
So I was hoping you'd have some idea.
I don't know what she's doing,
but we can't worry about that.
- There are people dying here in Los Angeles.
- Yeah, well, I don't like it, David.
So let me put someone on this.
No.
I brought Sherry in to fix a problem
and look what happened.
Just let it be. We'll hear soon enough.
What do you see?
They're trying to use the open
phone switches to find us.
The phone I called in with is shut off.
They can't triangulate me, can they?
Not quickly, but they can use a trial-and-error
process and that could get 'em close.
- Then that's what they're doing.
- It looks like it.
Then we have to stop them.
Come with me.
Your office is using
our last phone conversation to locate us.
How are they doing it?
I'm committed to getting my daughter back.
You kill me and that'll never happen.
That's not the only option.
You're an attractive woman.
I'm guessing your husband would prefer
you returned without disfigurement.
I'm not telling you anything.
I have to talk with Almeida.
Keep the conversation short.
Almeida.
Let me paint you a picture.
I have a sharp knife, the tip of which
is drawing blood from your wife's face...
right now.
If whatever you're doing to trace
these calls doesn't stop in 30 seconds,
she'll be unrecognizable.
- O'Brian.
- Shut down the trace.
- I'm just starting to get something.
- Do it now, Chloe.
Let me at least unscramble the audio.
- I need you to hold off for a few minutes.
- I thought you wanted me to find Saunders.
I do. Just... I'll explain it to you later.
- What are you doing?
- Trying to pick up a thread.
Somebody may be working against us.
I have quarantine zones springing up.
I'm treading water here, Jack.
Why are you lying to me?
- Lying?
- I just got off the phone with Hammond.
You didn't have a status call scheduled.
I screwed up earlier. The SAT transmission
on my system was forged by own people.
I should have noticed it wasn't authentic
before I ordered Baker off his post.
By the time I realized my mistake,
Saunders was gone.
- What about the missing frames?
- Must have been deleted by the same person.
I know this is big and, I promise you,
I'll offer my resignation when this day is over.
Right now we got too much going on.
Making a mistake is one thing.
Covering it up is another.
I can't let you stay in place.
I am taking over command of CTU.
- I made a mistake, Jack.
- No, Tony.
You made two.
Fine. I'll make sure Adam sends over
everything I got to your group.
Tony, I narrowed down the list.
What list?
Of people who can't account for their time
when the SAT frames went missing.
Yeah, right.
It's very likely that someone on this list
is working from within CTU to help Saunders.
Look, Adam, I'm not in charge
of CTU any more.
- What are you talking about?
- Jack decided it was best if he took over.
Why don't you send that list
over to Hammond?
Yes?
- I got a problem.
- What problem?
Jack Bauer just relieved me of my command.
- Why did he do that?
- He found out I deleted those satellite frames.
- Does he know about our communication?
- Not yet.
He thinks I'm covering my mistake,
but he's gonna find out soon.
Then I suggest you get my daughter
out of there before he does.
Look, I might not be able to do this.
I no longer have any authority at CTU.
You don't need authority. You just need
to know that if you don't deliver Jane,
for whatever reason, your wife will die,
just like Ryan Chappelle died,
just like the people
at the Chandler Plaza Hotel died.
- I'm gonna try to get her out, but if I can't...
- If you can't, Michelle dies.
Don't call me again
until you have Jane safely away.
- Dad.
- I need you to help me with something.
Tony wants me to debrief with Rae Plachecki
about what's going on with Jane Saunders.
Tony just stepped down.
I'm acting director of CTU until further notice.
What do you mean, Tony stepped down?
Tony's hiding something.
I need you to help me find out what it is.
- Why me?
- Right now I don't know who to trust.
Maintain surveillance on every station
here at CTU, anyone who checks in or out,
and track communications
flagged higher than a code two.
- Where do you want me to do this?
- Field ops. Come on.
Thanks.
Almeida.
- Good news, Tony.
- What is it?
I found a way to pull the voice track
on the phone call you had with Saunders.
- Have you listened to it?
- The algorithm's running.
Once that's complete, I'll be able to do
an analysis on ambient sound and room tone.
Good work.
Adam, send your volumes
to Kim's computer.
I have her checking something for me.
- Is Chloe still in tech one?
- As far as I know, she is.
- Have her come up to my office.
- I will, Jack.
- Kaufman.
- I'm on the line with Chloe.
- We need the password to 824.
- OK.
- It's BCF19.
- All right, thanks.
Jack needs to see Chloe
in his office right away.
- I'll tell her.
- Thank you.
-  Where is she?
-  She's here.
- Put her on.
- No. You have my wife.
I wanna talk to her first.
You have my wife. I wanna talk to her first.
"You have my wife"?
Hello? Hello?
Dammit.
Help! Somebody help! I'm locked in!
Tech one! I'm locked in!
Everybody, can I have your attention?
Just stop working for a second.
I need your attention.
From this point forward,
I am taking command of CTU.
That includes field ops
and all communications.
Tony Almeida has stepped down.
He is no longer in charge.
I'm taking Jane Saunders to Division.
Here's the order.
I don't have time to go into details.
We have to focus on finding Saunders.
Come on, Pete.
Call Division. Talk to 'em yourself.
Unless you are working directly with NHS,
I need you to get involved.
Your superiors will hand out your
assignments. We need to find this guy now.
We're leaving right now.
We're going out this way right here.
Chloe hasn't refreshed her chron tables.
I thought she was on the main system.
Yeah, she was.
- That's weird. She never forgets to do that.
- What's going on?
- Have you seen Chloe?
- She's in tech one.
- Where are all the guards?
- We don't need those guards.
You were worried
about my father sending men to get me.
We have agents on the streets.
Don't worry about it.
- Why can't I get a feed on tech one?
- Hang on.
- Someone blocked it.
- We have a hostile inside.
- Override the access code now.
- Security, I need a 20 on Chloe O'Brian.
Priority-one sweep of the entire building.
Cover the back entrance.
- Jack.
- Step away from the computer. Now!
Tony locked me in here. Saunders has
Michelle. He's using her to get his daughter.
Don't move.
Security, this is Jack Bauer.
I need a 20 on Tony Almeida.
I repeat, I need a 20 on Tony Almeida.
Negative, Jack.
He's not on any of the monitors.
- When did he lock you in here?
- About 10 minutes ago.
Lock down the entire building. Adam, I wanna
know everything that's exiting this building.
- Who's watching Jane Saunders?
- Both guards are down. She's gone.
Exit security, I need a 20 on Tony Almeida.
This is Almeida. We're out. I've got her.
- How long until satellite finds you?
- About 30 minutes.
I'll give you further instructions
in 20 minutes.
Be at the northeast corner of Taylor and Vine.
Yeah, all right.
- Yes, sir.
- Put me on to Palmer.
I'd like to speak to him. Personally.
Son of a bitch.