Tony Almeida has just informed us
that they were unable to confiscate
this Cordilla virus in Mexico.
This man Amador, where is he now?
Latest working theory is that Amador has this
virus and is headed back here to Los Angeles.
I let you live. Tell me what you know.
When Amador does business on the West
Coast, he washes his deal through Alvers.
- How does Amador contact this Alvers?
- I don't know. I've never met him.
- Hello?
- Marcus, it's me. I'll be there in an hour.
- You got the virus?
- Yes.
- Just be ready.
- I will be.
- I've gotta go see Julia Milliken.
- No.
Don't go anywhere near her or Alan tonight.
- You think I'm scared of you?
- Julia. My pills!
- No, don't.
- What are you doing?
- Don't.
- Sherry.
This is your way out.
- We killed him.
- No.
There's one thing you have to be really clear
about when the authorities question you.
I was never here.
- I got her.
- Agent Bauer.
I'm Jason Carasone from Division.
These men'll escort the prisoner to CTU.
- She doesn't leave my sight.
- You can accompany her in the lead van.
This is Carasone.
Yeah, he's right here. Agent Edmunds.
It's a Chloe O'Brian from your office.
- Jack, I'll take another car.
- OK.
- Yeah, Chloe.
- Chase, they found out.
- Who found out what?
- Angela. They all know she's your daughter.
What? How?
The baby-sitter flaked.
She had an emergency and brought her here.
- You brought Angela in to CTU?
- Your sister's out of town.
There is no one else.
You have no idea what I've been through.
OK. Chloe, thank you for covering.
I appreciate it, but where is Angela now?
She's downstairs with Marcy
until you get back.
Did Kim find out?
- Chloe, did Kim find out?
- Yes. Yes, Kim found out.
- How'd she react?
- Gosh, Chase, I think she's kinda pissed.
I'm coming back to CTU.
I'll take care of everything.
Fine.
Here's the situation. We believe Michael
Amador is in possession of the Cordilla virus.
We believe he is headed to Los Angeles
or is here already.
We estimate he has enough of the pathogen
to take out a major metropolitan area.
Our only lead is Nina Myers, who's
being brought back to CTU right now.
She thinks Amador is meeting with a man
in Los Angeles by the name of Marcus Alvers.
Adam's done a workup on him.
We have some background, but nothing
places him definitively in Los Angeles today.
That's it? What about Interpol?
What do they have on Alvers?
Our data tracking's a little behind,
so we weren't able to access that report.
Why are we behind?
We didn't update the European contact logs
while I was down.
- Michelle, you were the ranking agent.
- I didn't think Europe was a priority.
- Obviously it was.
- There was a lot going on at the time.
All right. Let's get back to work.
Let's try to ease up on the mistakes, as there
are millions of lives depending on us.
Michelle.
Come.
I just got off with CTU.
- What's the status on the virus?
- It's not good.
The limited intelligence they have
supports their suspicion.
- It's on its way to Los Angeles?
- David, it may already be here.
We should prepare in case
they target other cities.
Our people in the security envelope
have been alerted. It's being handled.
Why don't you try and go get some rest?
I'm on this.
Mr President,
Mrs Palmer's here to see you.
Send her in, please.
Start waking people up. Set up
a conference call with the cabinet members -
Homeland Security, FBI,
National Health Services.
- We're gonna need everyone on this one.
- Yes, sir.
Wayne.
Sherry, I asked you here to help me,
not make things worse.
I did not want you going
to Alan Milliken's house.
Relax, David. I didn't go there.
- You didn't go?
- No.
When we spoke on the phone, you told me it
was crucial that you speak to Julia in person.
Yes. And I changed my mind.
I spoke to her over the phone.
- About what?
- About Kelly's disappearance.
I asked her if she would check
Alan's cellphone for any recently made calls.
- And?
- She wouldn't do it.
You don't take no for an answer, Sherry.
What aren't you telling me?
Nothing, David. I swear.
What have you been up to
if you weren't at Milliken's?
- Making calls.
- You could have made them from here.
Yes, but I didn't.
I parked on the side of the road.
I started making calls
because I didn't wanna wait.
I told you, we have a small window
of opportunity here.
I wanted to exploit the fact
that Milliken may not have had time
to cover his tracks
when he had someone grab Kelly.
All right.
- I have other things to attend to.
- OK.
- Is there anything else?
- That's it.
Hello, Nina. Take her to Interrogation 819.
Yes, sir.
- What's the security configuration?
- Don't worry. We're handling Nina.
- Ryan, you know what she's capable of.
- That's none of your concern.
- I'm sending you to Medical.
- I'm fine.
- I don't think you are.
- What's this about?
We found evidence
you've been injecting heroin.
Tell me I'm off here, Jack. Tell me I'm wrong.
- I didn't think so.
- Ryan, I haven't missed a step. I'm fine.
I have to cover my ass.
I need to get you checked out.
You're wasting time.
- Kim.
- Yeah.
I thought you'd wanna know your dad's back.
- What about Chase?
- He's a few minutes behind him.
Thank you.
- Kim.
- Dad.
Oh, God. Hi.
- She's here.
- I know, sweetheart. I know.
Look, I have to debrief Chappelle.
I'll see you in a minute, OK?
Dad, I know about your drug problem.
Why didn't you come to me with this?
Come here.
I'm sorry, baby. I'm sorry.
I was embarrassed.
And it wasn't your problem, and it still isn't.
I didn't want you to worry.
Well, is it over?
No, not exactly.
I think I'm gonna have to go
into a programme, get some help.
- I'm so sorry.
- It's OK.
Look, Chappelle wants me to go
into the clinic and get checked out.
We'll talk about this later, OK? Don't worry.
- I love you.
- I love you, too.
Jack.
I'm glad you're back.
It's been difficult without you.
Thanks, Chloe.
- Chase.
- Yeah?
I need to talk to you about the baby.
Why don't you take a few minutes
and then meet me in my office?
Mr Milliken?
Oh, my God.
Mrs Milliken!
Come quickly!
Quickly!
Hey. How's the hand?
It's fine. How'd Chappelle find out?
I don't know. It doesn't really matter.
What's going on?
Almeida'll interrogate Nina.
I'll follow it from a feed.
Good. Make sure Tony puts
double security on the doors.
Get back to me as soon as
she gives you anything.
- Agent Bauer, keep pressure here.
- Sure. Thank you.
Jack, you're about to find something out
about me that's not gonna make you happy.
- What are you talking about?
- Excuse me. Do you mind?
I've got a daughter.
- A daughter?
- Her mother dropped her off and she split.
- It's a long story.
- Does Kim know about this?
Yeah.
From you?
I haven't had the chance
to talk to her myself yet.
You square this with her, Chase.
You understand me? You just make it right.
And get back to me
as soon as Nina gives you anything.
I will.
- Are we up yet?
- Yep. Video's piped in. Voice analysis.
- Vitals. Transcription. All set.
- Nick, do you copy?
- I read you.
- We're ready to go.
Recording to hard drive now.
- So Tony's doing this?
- Yeah.
Is that gonna be weird for you?
- What do you mean?
- Didn't he and Nina go out?
Yeah.
- We set?
- Yeah.
All right. I want you to do
a high res on her eyes.
She's tired. We might be able to pick up a tell.
OK.
- So are we all right?
- Yeah, we're fine.
All right. Let's do this.
I got the high res on monitor two.
Tony.
Didn't know I was gonna see you today.
You know what we want.
We need to find Michael Amador
before he unloads the virus.
I already told Jack everything I know.
I want you to tell me.
First Jack, now you.
What does that remind me of?
You told Jack that Amador
might try to contact a Marcus Alvers?
So, where do we look for Alvers?
It's a nice ring. Who's the lucky girl?
Hope you did a background check cos you
don't wanna make the same mistake twice.
You're going back to prison. There's
a good chance you'll be executed as a traitor.
You know if you cooperate you may be able
to save your own life, but you're stalling.
Which means you know something
and think there's a play you can make,
only now's not the right time.
Very incisive.
I hope your wife appreciates that about you.
Why don't you tell me about Alvers?
All I know is that he works only with Amador.
I don't know him personally.
All we've been able to dig up on him
are a few random medical records
under one of his known aliases.
He had an MRI on one of his knees.
There's a prescription for antibiotics.
Treated for HIV.
Her pulse is spiking.
Someone hasn't been using protection.
She's probably had sex with him.
See, Nina, my colleagues in the next room
are telling me that something
in those medical records concerns you.
I'm guessing it's not the knee.
Marcus.
Michael.
- How was your trip?
- Interesting.
I still don't understand
why you risked so much in Mexico,
why you didn't come here directly.
240 million dollars made it worth the risk.
What about Nina?
If she wasn't killed by the bomb,
I'm sure her buyers took care of her once
they found out she didn't deliver the virus.
Either way, she's out of the picture.
I hope so. She can point to both of us.
We'll be long gone
before anyone starts looking.
Kim.
- I know we haven't talked since I got back.
- No, we haven't.
I know what you must be thinking.
Give me a chance to explain.
I don't know what to think.
Look, I'm happy that you're OK,
but this thing...
You have a baby, Chase.
We've been together more than three months
and you kept this secret.
- Who's the mother? Where does she fit in?
- That's what I wanna talk about.
- I didn't know until a month ago.
- How could you not know?
Angela's mother and I
went out last year. It's over.
And when it ended,
she never told me she was pregnant.
She calls a month ago and tells me
she has a baby and that I'm the father,
and that she's in trouble
and she can't handle it.
I was afraid to let people find out.
I was afraid it was gonna mess us up.
- But you told Chloe.
- Chloe and my sister have been helping me.
She's a good friend.
Excuse me. Chase, you wanted me
to let you know when Angela woke up.
- Thank you.
- Sure.
Kim, I'm just as confused as you are.
But all I know is that I love you,
and I'm falling in love with Angela, too,
and I need to make this work.
Go on.
Hey.
- What's happening with Nina?
- They're getting something.
The connection between
Alvers and Nina might be deep.
You better hope she's not spinning your
wheels cos she can manipulate our protocol.
- Tony knows what he's doing.
- Fine.
I need to get together with Chloe.
I need everything she's got on Amador.
- Not yet.
- Ryan, you're wasting my time.
I humored you with the physical.
We both know there'll be trace amounts
of opiates, but enough is enough.
Rae Plachecki from the inspector general's
office is here to talk to you.
- This is not the time.
- Actually, it is.
You'll talk to her, then we'll evaluate whether
you can go back to work or not. Come on.
Rae Plachecki, this is Jack Bauer.
You know the drill. I'm gonna ask you
some questions, but I'm on your side.
We wanna establish that this heroin addiction
was a necessary part of your cover.
It was necessary to maintain my cover.
Are we done now?
Sit down, Jack.
This is Rae Plachecki. The time is 2.31am.
Interrogation of Jack Bauer,
director of field ops, CTU.
Ryan Chappelle is present.
Jack, tell us how you established
your cover with Ramón Salazar.
I first came in contact with the Salazars
approximately two years ago.
They were an up-and-coming
narcotic cartel in Mexico.
So when did you meet Amador?
Did you know him
when you were working at CTU?
Tell me something, Nina. What kind of a deal
do you think you're gonna cut?
You've betrayed everybody you know,
including me.
You murdered Jack's wife.
You helped terrorists smuggle
a nuclear bomb into this country.
You're helping to unleash a deadly virus
into the general population.
Help me understand this.
What do you want?
What is it you get
out of being a mass murderer?
Your neck is bleeding.
- Dalton, what have you got?
- So far the only reactions are subliminal.
If she won't talk we need
to be plugged into her vitals.
We can take her to seven,
do a passive-response test.
Seven's not secure enough. She stays here.
- Where's Richards?
- He's waiting.
Let's bring him in.
Send Darren in.
Nina, I don't think you've met Darren
Richards. He joined us after you left.
Hello, Darren.
Don't take it personally. He doesn't talk much.
Something's
not connecting up for me, Jack.
You weren't in with the Salazars
until early February,
but the first time you started using
was late December.
That's six weeks of shooting up for the
benefit of no one. Am I missing something?
I was trying to pass as a junkie.
I wanted to be prepared.
- What do you mean, prepared?
- The Salazars lived in the drug world.
If I couldn't handle the narcotics,
they'd have known I was a cop and killed me.
- I needed to be able to handle it.
- That makes sense.
But in January, when you were injecting,
you didn't have a meeting on the books.
- It could have been a year for all you knew.
- What are you saying?
I am trying to establish evidence
that you did drugs as part of your cover.
If I submit this, it's not gonna hold up.
What do you want me to say?!
I did drugs to get in with these people
and I got in with them!
No matter how difficult it's been,
I don't use any more.
Look, I'll write it up that way
and maybe it'll fly,
but I think you'll have a problem because
you never told anyone, not even your partner.
That's suspicious.
Rae, you know my history.
I've had a very difficult time
since my wife passed away.
If I told anyone I was using drugs to develop
a case, they would have misinterpreted it.
I couldn't afford that risk.
Yeah, well, that's what they're gonna do now.
Rae, let's put down that Jack started
using heroin in late January,
after the first meeting with Salazar
was established.
I appreciate what you're trying to do,
but that's not what happened.
Just trying to save us all some paperwork.
- I'm OK with that.
- I'm not.
I started using in December.
I've got nothing to hide.
This office demands results
and that's what I provide - results.
- Fine.
- Can I get back to work?
Not quite yet, Jack.
He'll be here in an hour.
Just as long as we have enough time to leave
the country before they let this virus out.
Please be seated.
Five hours ago I went public with a statement
that there was a domestic terror threat,
but it had passed.
And now it appears that that was premature.
Ladies and gentlemen, do we or do we not
have a threat of this virus being released?
Sir, I'm afraid we can't answer that question
with any kind of certainty.
What can you tell me?
What few leads we have indicate that Michael
Amador has the virus and is in Los Angeles.
For what purpose we can't say.
Then we have to prepare for defensive action
here in Los Angeles,
and, for that matter, in all our major cities.
Mr President, you know our position
here at Homeland Security.
We think being forthright and making such
preparations in the open is the correct course.
We have to assess
the downside of that course.
I have no problem with that, as long as
we realize we are working against a clock.
I want all departments present to work up
an open versus covert containment strategy
and report back to me in 30 minutes.
In the meantime, I want
Health Services to issue guidelines,
but only to be distributed internally.
That is all. I'll be in my office.
David.
- Give us a second, please, Aaron.
- Of course, sir.
Secret Service just received a phone call from
the West Los Angeles Police Department.
- Alan Milliken is dead.
- What?
He was found 15 minutes ago in his home.
All signs point to a heart attack.
- It isn't possible.
- Well, apparently, it is.
You told me Sherry was on her way
over there about an hour ago.
She changed her mind, made some phone
calls from her car, came straight back here.
David, is that what she told you?
Yeah.
- And where is she now?
- Resting.
- Aaron, take me to Sherry.
- Yes, sir. She's right this way.
- Hasn't your shift ended?
- I stayed on.
I sensed it's a difficult day
and I wanted to be here for you.
- I appreciate that.
- Right in there, sir.
- Sherry.
- David.
- What's wrong?
- Alan Milliken is dead.
- What? How?
- Why don't you tell me?
What do you mean?
I told you I didn't go there.
I know what you told me. You sat in your car,
made some calls and came here.
That's the truth.
Then you won't mind the police checking
your cellphone and the car you used tonight.
You know, you asked me
to take care of a problem, and I did.
If you want the police to check phone logs,
then have them check yours first.
Remember, you called me tonight.
I am here because of you, David.
What happened, Sherry?
I went over to the house,
just to speak to Julia.
Alan interrupted us,
there was an argument and...
...he had a heart attack.
There's going to be an investigation.
You're gonna have to tell the truth about this.
The truth isn't gonna save either one of us.
All they're going to hear
is that I was there on your behalf
to prevent Alan from meddling
with your presidency
and that he died from natural causes.
How do you think that's gonna play out in
The New York Times for the next six months?
What did you do to Alan?
Honestly, David?
Nothing. Absolutely nothing.
Kim, I transferred that feed.
Do you want me to pull it up for you?
Yeah.
She won't give him anything.
We're gonna have to find Alvers.
What can I do?
I followed up on his Asian connections,
but there's something for you to look at.
- It's a long shot.
- What is it?
A list of cities Alvers has been in the last
three years, each time for a couple of days.
Cross it with the other suspects.
Let me know what you come up with.
I don't know why we have to go
through this again. I already answered that.
- What is it, Edmunds?
- Just wanted to give you an update on Nina.
- Rae, could you pause that?
- Did she give us anything new on Alvers?
No. Other than the probability she knew him
personally, she's not cooperating.
What are we doing?
Richards is working on her now.
- I think that's a mistake.
- Why?
I don't think anybody should be in there
that hasn't worked with her.
- She'll manipulate him.
- All Richards does is inflict pain.
There's no way for her to manipulate him.
Right.
How much more of this
do you wanna endure, Nina?
I think this is about it.
- She hit an artery!
- Call Medical!
She's bleeding! We gotta take her there now.
- Tell security we need an escort!
- We need Medical.
-  Uncuff her.
-  Now!
So what did Sherry have to say?
- That Alan had a heart attack.
- And you believe her?
I'd be a fool to believe
anything Sherry says to save herself.
But murder... I can't imagine she'd do that.
We can't allow ourselves
to be caught off guard.
Now, we have to assume the worst.
Then we'd also have to assume
that Julia was somehow involved.
What?
Whoa, whoa. Listen.
David, I'm sorry, but Julia's
not the same kind of person that Sherry is.
When we find out all the facts,
we'll proceed from there.
I have to go over
the morning brief with Jerry.
All right.
- Hello?
-  Julia, it's me.
Wayne?
I just heard about Alan, and I...
Are you alone?
The police are here. I was just going
to speak with one of the officers.
All right, tell me what happened.
Sherry was here when it happened,
but she told me not to tell the police.
I need for you to tell me
exactly what happened.
We were talking with Alan. He got excited.
Then he started to gasp for air.
- He gets angina.
- So you called 911, right?
- No, no. I tried to give him his medication.
- What do you mean, you tried?
Sherry stopped me.
I went to help Alan and she grabbed my arm.
I just stood there. I couldn't move. I...
- I killed him, Wayne.
- Shh. Listen, be careful here.
- I killed him.
- Call Alan's lawyer.
And do not say anything, anything, to anyone
until he gets there. You understand me?
Wayne, could you come down here
and help me?
No, and please don't call me.
I will help you, but for right now
I have to keep my distance. I'm sorry.
Come on, let's go!
One, two, three.
The carotid's been lacerated.
Start a twilight drip.
- Clamp.
- Line, please.
- Keep steady pressure.
- Got it in?
- Yeah.
-  3-0 silks.
-  3-0 standing by.
-  More gauze.
-  Gauze.
-  Got it open.
-  Clamp it.
Here you go, Doctor.
Keep the pressure on.
Let's get some more gauze in here.
She's under.
I want you two stationed right here. Do not
leave unless you hear directly from me.
Those are all the questions I'm obliged to ask.
If you've got anything to add,
now's the time.
That's my statement, as it is.
My God! Tony!
Nina tried to commit suicide.
She jammed her neck into Richard's needle.
- Where is she now?
- In the clinic being operated on.
- Who's with her?
- She'd sedated...
Tony, who's with her?!
Dammit!
Which way'd she go?
Lock down the building!
This is Ryan Chappelle. Nina Myers
is loose in the building. Lock it down - now!
Nina.
Drop the gun. Put your hands on your head.
Now!
Kim, what the hell are you doing?
- You don't wanna be any part of this.
- Shut up.
Just turn around and walk away.
If you leave now, you won't get hurt.
Kim.
Don't do it, Nina. I swear to God I'll shoot you.
- You won't kill me.
- Nina, dammit.
Kim, back up. Back up.
Kim, go back into CTU.
Tell them we've got Nina.
- Dad, we need...
- Kim, go now.
Please, baby. Just go.
You don't have any more
useful information, do you, Nina?
I do.
No, you don't.