What we're doing here is very simple.
We're going to release a certain substance
so it flows into your pipelines.
Take the canisters
to the main distribution tank, quickly.
Is Wayne Palmer dead yet?
- No.
- Explain.
We rolled his car,
but he survived and got away.
- It was sloppy. We'll make it right.
- You better. You know what's at stake.
Get down!
It's the truth. Audrey Raines was my contact
at the Department of Defense.
- You met with her face to face?
- Yes.
- Dammit, Audrey! Tell me the truth!
- I am telling you the truth!
You already lied. Tell me what you know, or
I promise this will become very unpleasant.
Bill, we have a connection.
Henderson made calls to Collette.
That voids her agreement.
You have three seconds to tell me
where the target is, or I will kill you.
Where is the target?!
A natural gas distribution centre.
Once the Sentox hits the main tank and goes
right into the pipes, it's impossible to stop.
From there, it goes to people's homes.
The Sentox is in the system.
- I need C4 and a timer. Get these people out.
- What are you doing?
To deliver the Sentox,
it had to mix with natural gas.
If we can ignite that gas before it leaves
the plant, the Sentox will be incinerated.
Bierko!
- That's it. The main tanks are going. Get out!
Jack, are you clear?
Jack, respond.
Curtis. Curtis, this is Audrey.
Any sign of Jack?
Nothing.
I've got men searching the main tank area.
Rescue units have arrived.
They're assessing the situation.
Chloe, what are we getting
from the air monitors?
- Come on, Jack.
- Chloe.
Trace readings of the nerve agent,
below danger levels.
It looks like the Sentox was incinerated.
Jack's plan worked.
I'm going to brief the White House.
Apprise me of any developments. Miles.
Curtis,
have we searched the area for Jack?
It's under way.
He hasn't gone out the north exit.
CTU, Jack's OK.
Get a medical team over here now.
Jack! Are you OK?
Give me a hand.
I got him.
Bierko!
- I need him conscious.
- Yes, sir.
- The nerve gas, did it leave the plant?
- There's no trace. It worked.
- Good.
- He's in shock. We need to transport him.
- I want him taken back to CTU Medical.
- Yes, sir.
Curtis, organise an escort team.
You get him back to CTU alive.
You got it.
On my count. Three, two, one.
Team A, meet me by the staging area.
We need an escort to CTU.
- Buchanan.
- Bill, it's Jack. Is your line still secure?
- Yes.
- What's your status on Henderson?
- He's still an active protocol.
- You need to make him a priority.
Bill, listen to me. I know Henderson.
He couldn't have planned this.
He's a soldier and a patriot.
However misguided,
he believes what he's doing is right.
He was willing to let his wife die
in order to protect someone very powerful.
- Who?
- I don't know.
Bill, I'm scared.
I think this is bigger than anything
we could ever have imagined.
Karen, you're not hearing me.
They managed to prevent an attack.
It doesn't negate the fact CTU's performance
has been one misstep after another.
I'm not disputing that,
Mr. Vice President.
Then why hesitate to carry out your mandate?
Have Homeland absorb CTU.
CTU is still actively looking
for Christopher Henderson.
A shake-up right now could hamper that.
I won't hold up this takeover
because of a procedural mop-up.
- Henderson will be caught. Understood?
- Clearly.
Whatever hoops you have to jump through,
just get it done.
- Yes, sir.
- Keep me informed.
- I guess we should get started.
- Buchanan is not gonna take this lying down.
Despite what the vice president said,
CTU saved a lot of lives.
If Buchanan mounts a challenge, it will be
seen in that light. This could be reversed.
If we were to find someone who would go
on record citing Buchanan's mismanagement,
how he superseded Lynn McGill's authority,
how he allowed CTU to be compromised,
it'd go a long way
to mitigating his successes.
- It'd give us the protection we need.
- Buchanan's people are extremely loyal.
I'm not thinking about a member of CTU.
I'm thinking of Audrey Raines. She was here
all morning. She saw what went on.
And her loyalty is split
between CTU and DOD.
We could take advantage of that.
Let me draft a statement and present it to her.
We're being rolled up, Audrey.
Homeland's taking over.
That's impossible.
Karen told me herself.
No, they can't do that.
Not after what you've accomplished today.
I'd like to think we've earned a reprieve,
but I doubt it.
CTU is in the middle of an investigation.
Henderson is still at large.
I know, it doesn't make any sense.
Karen's taking orders from the vice president.
He wants this to happen.
- Why?
- I've been asking myself the same question.
- We lost him.
- How did you lose him?
Palmer knocked Cobb out
and took his weapon.
We tried to pursue,
but someone came to Palmer's aid.
- Who?
- That's unclear.
They got away.
All right. We're going to our fall-back.
Scrub the scene and get over here.
Yes, sir.
You're all right, Mr. Palmer.
- Just take it slow.
- Aaron.
We're at the presidential retreat.
Can you try to sit up?
- I think we need to get you looked at, sir.
- There isn't enough time for that. I'm all right.
Then maybe you can explain to me
what's going on.
Why were those men trying to kill you?
Because David had a source
inside the White House.
Someone was trying
to prevent me from seeing her.
Who's this source?
Mrs. Logan's assistant.
- Evelyn Martin?
- Yeah.
She and David were trading emails. I need
to find out the content of those messages.
I think David was killed
because of information Evelyn gave him.
I drafted a letter to the families
of the victims of the Sunrise Hills Mall.
- It's here for your review.
- Thank you.
Your schedule's there.
You have a 9am with the press office
and the president
wants you in on his briefing.
Evelyn, are you all right?
I'm fine. I'm just tired.
It's been a long day.
I'm surprised any of us got through it.
Oh, do you have your credentials with you?
There's still a curfew in place.
I have them with me.
Good. Try to get some rest.
- Good night.
Evelyn.
Hi.
- I really need to talk to you.
- I'm sorry, Mr. Palmer. I need to go home.
Ma'am, please.
This won't take but a second.
You were sending emails to my brother.
- Why?
- I don't know what you're talking about.
I traced the IP account right to your address,
so, yes, you do know what I'm talking about.
I need to know what you told David.
- I didn't tell him anything.
- Evelyn.
I have the record of your correspondence.
David deleted the content of the messages,
but I know, Evelyn.
I know you were in contact with him,
so please don't lie to me again.
Tell me what I need to know.
Someone killed David. They killed him.
And then just tried to kill me.
Now, I think they knew
I was coming here to see you,
so I think that means we're both in danger.
- Please, I have to go now.
- Give me what I need! Talk to me!
I can't!
They kidnapped my little girl.
They kidnapped my baby.
They said they would give Amy back to me
if I gave them the evidence.
What evidence?
I have proof about who's behind
everything that's happened today.
They're gonna kill my baby.
They're gonna kill...
Listen to me. Listen.
Even if you turn over this evidence,
they're not just gonna give you back your
daughter. That's not what these people do.
Now, you've gotta trust me, Evelyn.
Please, talk to me.
Ma'am, if I may.
Mr. Palmer's right. You know too much.
They'll kill you both.
I'll give you the evidence that I have
if you get me back my daughter.
I got Henderson's work records
for the past ten years. There's a lot.
I'll start data mining, see if there's anything
we can use to track him down.
That's Chloe O'Brian.
That's Jim Hill from Homeland.
I'm Jim Hill, Homeland Security.
Could you show me your station?
- Chloe O'Brian?
- Yeah?
I'm taking over your station.
I need your access codes.
- Who are you? What's going on here?
May I have your attention, please?
These men and women
are from Homeland Security.
I've just authorised
a unitwide backslash protocol.
CTU is being absorbed
by the Department of Homeland Security.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I realise this is sudden,
and this has been a very difficult day,
but let's cooperate
to make this transition as smooth as possible.
There is still work to be done.
Vladimir Bierko is en route to CTU,
and Christopher Henderson
remains an open protocol.
Thank you.
Ms Raines, would you mind joining me
in the situation room?
- Why?
- We need to speak in private.
Fine.
- This is Bauer.
- Jack, it's Wayne Palmer.
Are you all right?
I just heard about the explosion.
I'm fine, but I wish the people responsible for
your brother's assassination were in custody.
- Yeah, well, maybe I can help you with that.
- How?
I'm at President Logan's retreat.
I'm with Evelyn Martin, Mrs. Logan's assistant.
- What does she have to do with this?
- She has proof other people were involved.
- Who?
- She won't tell me.
Why not?
Her daughter's been kidnapped.
They'll kill her
unless Evelyn hands over the evidence.
- This has to be Henderson.
- They'll call with a place to meet.
I wanna be on that call when it comes.
CTU will provide operational support.
We're gonna need a place to meet.
I passed an old barn about a mile west
of the retreat, off service road 19.
Service road 19. I'll be there in 20 minutes.
See you then.
Jack's gonna meet us. We should go.
Listen, they may be watching you,
so I don't think we should leave together.
- What do you want to do?
- We'll separate.
- Get to your car. We'll meet in the parking lot.
- OK.
See you soon.
"The acting director's failure
to enhance security, in the light of the threat,
effectively invited the subsequent attack
that resulted in loss of personnel"?
You can't possibly expect me to sign this.
It's a complete distortion, designed
to place blame on Bill Buchanan and CTU.
But you agree that today's attacks represent
a serious failure that needs to be addressed?
Thanks to CTU, hundreds of thousands
of people are alive who would be dead.
But if CTU had been operating effectively,
those people would never have been at risk.
I couldn't more strongly disagree
with this statement.
Well, I'm disappointed with your decision,
but I appreciate your loyalty.
Of course.
Oh, just to confirm,
as on-site liaison for DOD,
you participated
in today's decision-making process.
- What's your point?
- Serious mistakes were made here today
that resulted in the loss of American lives.
It would be a shame to see the taint of CTU's
mismanagement spread to your agency.
And your career.
By signing this,
you isolate the fallout for today's mistakes
to Bill Buchanan and CTU -
where it belongs.
I'm proud of what we did here today.
The people of CTU are heroes,
especially Bill Buchanan.
This takeover is completely unwarranted,
and I won't help you justify it.
- Hello.
- It's Jack.
- Jack, where are you?
- I'm on my way to see Wayne Palmer.
Wayne Palmer?
Wayne told me
the aide to the first lady has evidence
that proves who's behind
David Palmer's assassination.
She won't give it to Wayne because her
daughter's been kidnapped to keep her quiet.
- They want to trade the evidence for the girl.
- Oh, my God, Jack.
I'm gonna need you to retask a satellite
to those coordinates.
- That could be difficult.
- Why?
CTU is being rolled up. Karen is replacing
everyone with people from Homeland.
- What? That doesn't make sense.
- I know.
Even if she has a reason to,
we're tracking down Henderson.
We'll never bring her team up to speed.
I know that she's taking orders
from Vice President Gardner himself.
- Maybe you should talk to Karen directly.
- No.
She's the one in control.
When I was interrogating Henderson,
he was protecting someone very powerful.
He'd have let his wife die
rather than give him up.
And now Vice President Gardner
is shutting down CTU
when we're actually in a position
to bring Henderson in.
Do you really think Gardner's involved?
We can't afford
to take the chance that he's not.
- All right, what do you want me to do?
- Get Chloe to retask the satellite.
Chloe has been let go,
along with the rest of her department.
I need the satellite.
Figure out a way to get Chloe back on.
All right, all right. I'll call you back.
I could approach senior CTU staff.
- That's a waste of time.
They're worried about their jobs.
We could promise them some security.
Excuse me.
I've reconsidered my position.
I'll sign your statement.
May I ask why the sudden change of heart?
I don't agree with everything in the statement,
but I see the need to shield DOD
of any possible controversy
that could reflect back on my father.
Miles.
Thank you.
- I want one thing in return.
- What's that?
- That Chloe be kept on and assigned to me.
- Why Chloe?
I'm gonna need considerable server access
to compile my report for DOD.
- Chloe can help me finish it in half the time.
- Other people can do that job.
I have a working relationship with Chloe.
She's an asset that you cannot afford to lose.
Do we have a deal?
Yes.
Good.
Evelyn Martin will leave
the presidential retreat in a couple of minutes.
- It's time to get going.
- What about the girl?
I'll take care of her.
- Wayne Palmer.
- I'm at my car. No one's around.
- I'm on my way.
- OK.
I'm extremely uncomfortable
sending the two of you off without protection.
We've been over this. If you leave the
compound again, we risk raising suspicion.
I know it, sir, but I don't like it.
Wayne.
Well, this is a surprise.
We didn't know you were coming.
Are you here to see the president?
No.
Mr. Palmer came here to give me a memento
from his brother. It's a service medal.
Sorry, I just knew you and the president
were gonna be dealing with this crisis today
and I just... I didn't want you people
to feel obliged to see me.
It would never ever be any obligation on
our part, especially under the circumstances.
I just want you to know how sorry I am.
Your brother was one of the greatest men
to ever occupy the office.
His loss, to all of us,
can't be expressed in words.
Thank you.
I know the president would also like
to express his condolences to you personally.
That means a lot, sir,
but unfortunately I have a plane to catch.
I'm...
flying David's body back to Washington, so...
Oh, I understand.
Safe trip.
- Thank you, sir.
- I'll walk you out, sir.
Excuse me.
Mr. Buchanan.
Ms O'Brian, we're not done here.
- How can they get away with this?
- This is not over. Just follow instructions.
- Everyone's getting fired.
- I'll do everything I can to get that rescinded.
Once what we accomplished today
is made public,
I am confident we'll be back at our posts.
The best thing you can do is stay focused and
follow your orders. Do you understand me?
- Yes, sir.
- It's gonna be all right.
O'Brian, don't transfer your station to Valerie.
You got a pass.
- I did?
- Yeah. So get back to work.
I don't understand. Why am I staying?
Because Ms Raines requested
that you keep your position.
What does Audrey Raines
have to do with this?
Ms Raines signed a statement documenting
the numerous missteps made today by CTU...
and by you in particular.
So, for the moment, she gets what she wants,
and she wants O'Brian.
Audrey would never sign anything like that.
I did sign it, Bill.
Why?
Because it's the truth.
You realise this effectively kills
any chance we have of rescinding that order?
Yes, I know.
I'm sorry.
O'Brian.
I got a call from a man about an hour ago
who told me that he had my daughter,
and if I ever wanted to see her alive,
I'd have to follow his instructions.
- Did he give you proof he had her?
- I talked to her. She sounded so scared.
Did you tell anybody else about this?
I couldn't.
He said that if I did, he would know.
We have a deal. I'll do everything I can
to get your daughter back, but...
No, I told you before. I can't tell you anything
until I have Amy back.
You called David with this information.
Why him?
I knew him.
He and the first lady were friends.
He was truly a wonderful man.
Yes.
Yes, he was.
I still can't accept talking about him
in the past tense. It just...
I just can't believe he's gone.
I told him this information
because I trusted him.
I never thought for a moment
that it would endanger him.
I have your brother's blood on my hands
and I will never forgive myself.
Evelyn...
you did nothing wrong.
It's them.
Bauer.
- Jack, the call's coming through.
- Patch me in.
Are you ready for this?
- Hello.
- What took you so long to answer, Evelyn?
I was passing through security. I just left.
- Are you alone?
- Yes.
- Why was Wayne Palmer at the retreat?
- Wayne Palmer?
Please don't waste my time. He was there
for a reason. It wasn't to drop off his résumé.
- I think he was there to speak with you.
- I didn't even know he was there.
- I don't believe you.
- I didn't see him.
If you're lying to me,
it is your daughter who will suffer.
I'm telling you the truth.
Please, you have to believe me.
Did you bring what we discussed?
Yes.
Please, let me talk to Amy.
Very well.
All right, sweetheart.
This is your mommy. Say hello.
- Mommy?
- It's me, honey. Are you OK?
Uh-huh. Are you coming to get me now?
Mommy's gonna be there real soon.
I want you to keep being brave, OK?
- You promise me?
- I promise.
I love you, my baby.
- I love you too.
- OK, that's enough, sweetheart. Very good.
Now take down this address.
4615 Tarpin Street.
- Got it?
- Yes. I've got it.
- Hello.
- Audrey, it's Jack. I just got off the call.
It was Henderson.
Have you got Chloe back online?
- Audrey?
- Sorry, Jack. Yes, Chloe's still here.
- I'll give you the address for the satellite.
- All right. Go ahead.
4615 Tarpin.
All right. Give me a few minutes.
- Chloe, come with me.
- Don't talk to me.
- It's for Jack.
- Jack?
Chloe, Jack needs your help.
Please.
Fine.
- What's going on?
- I had to keep Karen from replacing you.
That's why I signed. I didn't have a choice.
- I don't understand.
- You're the only one Jack and I trust here.
Jack needs one of the satellites retasked.
- Why?
- Here's the address. We need a full sweep.
- I'm gonna need an explanation.
- I will give you one, but we need to hurry.
Something's wrong.
Wayne.
Jack.
- Are you all right?
- Yeah. It's good to see you.
Good to see you too.
Evelyn, my name is Jack Bauer.
I promise you
we're gonna get your daughter back.
But right now I need to know what you know.
I already told them I wouldn't give up
any information until I have my daughter.
Fine.
Excuse me for one second.
- Audrey Raines.
- Let me speak to Chloe.
OK, Jack. Hold on.
- You're on speaker.
- Jack, Audrey told me.
- I can't believe the vice president's involved.
- I know. Where are we with the satellite?
It's coming up now.
I'm sending the image to your PDA.
There are men all over the place.
- How many?
- I'm counting ten.
OK, I want you to keep the satellite on target
and download real-time images to my PDA.
- OK.
Jack.
I'll go with Evelyn to make the exchange.
Find somewhere safe
and stay there until this is over.
- I'm going with you.
- I can't allow that. This will be dangerous.
- I was a marine, Jack.
- I know that, Wayne.
And you never saw combat.
There is a big difference between training
to kill someone and actually having to do it.
I can't put you in harm's way, out of respect
to your brother. Your family needs you now.
These are the people
who killed my brother, Jack.
They shot a bullet right through his neck,
and then he died in my arms.
Put yourself in my position.
Could you just walk away?
No.
Neither can I.
I'm coming with you, Jack.
Thank you for your support,
Mr. Prime Minister.
Give my regards to your lovely wife.
We'll talk soon.
- It'll take me a day to return these calls.
- That's wonderful, Mr. President.
World leaders, prominent Americans - they're
all lining up to offer their congratulations.
Sir, were you aware
that Wayne Palmer was on the premises?
- He was?
- Yes, I just spoke with him a half-hour ago.
He just left. You didn't speak with him?
No.
What was he doing here?
He said he had a memento from President
Palmer to give to Aaron Pierce - a medal.
That explains it.
David and Aaron were very close.
I'm just surprised
he didn't want to speak with you.
It's no secret that his brother and I had
our share of disagreements over the years.
It's possible Wayne harbours
ill feelings towards me.
That must be the reason.
- Are you clear on the plan?
- I don't think I can do this.
Do you want to see your little girl again?
These men didn't hesitate to kill Palmer and
won't hesitate to kill you and your daughter.
Right now I am your last chance.
We have to stick to the plan.
Do you understand me?
- Once you have your daughter in your arms...
- I know what to do.
We are going to get her back.
Let's go.
Call out, "Testing, one, two, three. "
- Testing, one, two, three.
- Chloe, did you get that?
You're coming through.
I'm refreshing your screen.
OK, we're at the southeast corner entrance.
There's a tunnel through that door that leads
to a conveyor belt to the middle of the plant.
Be careful. There's a hostile at the exit.
Copy that.
Draw your weapon.
Let's go.
Bravo, check,
have you got a visual on the mark?
Negative, sir. All units holding.
Copy.
This way.
Let's go.
There's too many of them.
We're running out of time.
I need you to take out a guard so I can
climb this structure and take out the sniper.
It's about 100 yards north of here
on the other side. Can you do that?
- Yeah. I can do it.
- Wait!
One of them's moving.
Go.
- Mr. Palmer, can you hear me?
- Copy.
I'm south of the lower belt, moving west.
Continue to the end. Your target's north.
Jack, it's all clear.
This is Bravo.
I think I hear a car.
Vehicle headed north.
Single occupant, female. Over.
Bravo, what have you got?
I repeat, Bravo, what have you got?
Bravo, come in.
Woman is alone in the car.
Say again. I didn't get that.
I repeat, woman is alone in the car.
Copy.
We've taken out four men.
Evelyn is in position.
- Wayne, I want you to wait for my signal.
- Copy.
We need Henderson alive.
Do not shoot to kill.
- Yes.
- Open all the doors and the trunk of the car.
Very good, Evelyn. Now go to the front
of the car and drop the keys on the ground.
I have the evidence with me.
I want my daughter.
Bravo, hold your position. I'm coming out.
I have a visual on Henderson and the girl.
OK, Evelyn. Give me the evidence.
I'll give you the evidence
once you give me Amy.
Come on. Let her go.
OK, honey. Go see Mommy.
- Mommy!
- She's moving.
Give me the evidence, Evelyn.
Get down. Get down.
Bravo, check, come in.
Bravo. Come in, Bravo.
Wayne, I didn't get him.
If you've got a shot, take it.
Henderson escaped in Evelyn's car.
Do you have him on satellite?
We saw, but he's leaving the grid. We're
scanning the plant, not the neighbourhood.
Well, then reprogram it. We can't lose him.
- Is she all right?
- Evelyn's been hit.
The bullet passed through.
It hasn't hit an artery.
It's not serious, but it needs to be dressed.
You got your daughter,
now tell me what I need to know.
Who is behind this? Is it the vice president?
- Evelyn, is it the vice president?
- He has nothing to do with this.
You promised me
you would control this.
I didn't count on Jack Bauer showing up, sir.
He outmanoeuvred me.
Sir, Bauer and Palmer won't be around long
enough to tell anybody else what they know.
I'm putting together another team.
I will handle this, sir, I promise you.
I will not let you down.
See that you don't.